<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Urban Legends: Final Cut</title>
    <desc>Amy, a film student, makes her thesis film on urban legends. However, she realises something is deeply wrong when members of her cast and crew begin to mysteriously die during filming.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p26263_v_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>04:35AM</start>
    <finish>06:20AM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Redbelt</title>
    <desc>A ju-jitsu instructor, Mike Terry, who tries to make ends meet, refuses to compete in the ring. He is forced to return to the ring in order to raise money after his debts mount.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p172798_v_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>06:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Sniper 2</title>
    <desc>A Marine sniper is forced to team up with a convict on death-row to take out a rogue general as he is committing various inhumane acts on a certain ethnic group.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p30968_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:50AM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Daredevil</title>
    <desc>A blind man, whose other senses are extraordinary, works as an attorney during the day and fights crime at night.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p31328_v_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Absolutely Anything</title>
    <desc>A group of eccentric aliens gives an ordinary human being named Neil the limitless power to do anything he wants. Unbeknownst to Neil, this is an experiment to see if Earth deserves to be destroyed.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p12027577_v_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Grown Ups</title>
    <desc>Five childhood friends take their families for a weekend trip to a lake house in their hometown, where they reunite to attend the funeral of their former high school basketball coach.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7937506_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>The One</title>
    <desc>Gabriel Yulaw travels to parallel universes and starts killing alternate versions of himself in order to absorb their energy and become a godlike being.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28653_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Jeepers Creepers 2</title>
    <desc>A bus carrying a high school basketball team suffers a flat tyre following the kidnapping of Billy Taggar. Trouble ensues when those on board encounter the Creeper, a demonic winged creature.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p32291_v_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:20PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Man of the Year</title>
    <desc>Tom Dobbs, a news anchor, contests the presidential elections. When he manages to win, he is shocked. However, unknown to him, he owes his win to a technical glitch.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p162724_v_h10_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>06:20PM</start>
    <finish>08:15PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>The Green Hornet</title>
    <desc>After his father's death, Britt inherits the largest media company in Los Angeles. He teams up with Kato to fight crime but ends up becoming the target of a gangster, Benjamin Chudnofsky.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p3546312_v_h10_am.jpg</image>
    <start>08:15PM</start>
    <finish>10:05PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Stomp the Yard</title>
    <desc>After his brother is killed, a dancer moves away to study at a university. However, two rival dance fraternities on the campus recognise his talent and want him for themselves.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p162827_v_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:05PM</start>
    <finish>11:50PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Stomp the Yard: Homecoming</title>
    <desc>Chance Harris, a young man, tries to find a solution to balance his life, school, work and relationship in order to participate for a national step competition.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8224227_v_h10_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>11:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:15AM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Center Stage: Turn It Up</title>
    <desc>After getting rejected by a renowned dance academy, Kate, an exceptional dancer, works at a club and falls in love with a talented person.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p189264_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:15AM</start>
    <finish>02:40AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>The Craft: Legacy</title>
    <desc>Four teenage witches decide to make a coven and practise their witchcraft. But soon they realise that they are in over their heads when a classmate ends up dying.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18911576_v_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>02:40AM</start>
    <finish>04:05AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Boa vs. Python</title>
    <desc>A genetically altered, gigantic python escapes its confines and the FBI has to stop it. However, they pit a bio-engineered boa constrictor against it to end its terror.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p34312_v_h10_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>04:05AM</start>
    <finish>05:45AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Runner Runner</title>
    <desc>Richie, a Princeton graduate, loses his tuition in online poker and seeks out Ivan, a wealthy gambling tycoon, only to find himself entangled in a dangerous web of crime.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9872855_v_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>05:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Red Water</title>
    <desc>Aboard a rig, a group of workers are attacked by ruthless pirates. However, they must join forces when a freshwater bull shark targets them.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p32506_v_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:05AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>The Other Guys</title>
    <desc>When two disgraced police officers are given a task to probe a case involving an evil magnate, they must put aside their differences to become like the top detectives they idolise.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8045197_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:45AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>The Amazing Spider-Man</title>
    <desc>After a genetically altered spider bites him, Peter Parker develops superhuman abilities and confronts a humanoid reptilian creature.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8548776_v_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:45AM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Underworld: Awakening</title>
    <desc>Selene, a vampire warrior, finds out that the humans have decided to eradicate her clan and leads a battle, along with another vampire and a young girl, against them.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8761312_v_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Life</title>
    <desc>As astronauts discover the first evidence of extra-terrestrial life on Mars, they begin realising that the life form is extremely intelligent and hostile.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p13458606_v_h8_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Ghostbusters</title>
    <desc>Four women paranormal enthusiasts set out to capture ghosts when they realise that someone is attempting to cause an apocalypse by summoning evil entities in the city of New York.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11471579_v_h8_af.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:20PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>The Bone Collector</title>
    <desc>A vicious serial killer terrorizes the city and brutally kills people. Lincoln, an exceptional detective, joins forces with his partner to solve this baffling case.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p23612_v_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>06:20PM</start>
    <finish>08:20PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>The Producers</title>
    <desc>A ruined producer schemes with his neurotic accountant to create the world's worst movie and pocket the surplus, offering them a chance to get rich quickly.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p90713_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:20PM</start>
    <finish>10:25PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Jawbreaker</title>
    <desc>Three popular high school girls, Courtney, Marcie and Julie, find themselves in serious trouble after Liz suffocates and dies from a jawbreaker.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p22609_v_h10_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>10:25PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Sniper: Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Brandon Beckett and his men are attacked by a sniper while on a mission to rescue a farmer. Following the incident, he seeks the help of his father's protege to avenge the death of his squad.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8583971_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:55AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Vanguard</title>
    <desc>Qin, an accountant living in the UK, is targeted by the leader of a terrorist organisation. His only hope for survival is Vanguard, an elite security company.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18965213_v_h10_aj.jpg</image>
    <start>12:55AM</start>
    <finish>02:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Chef vs Fridge</title>
    <desc>Thinking outside the box is not going to cut it. These chefs must think inside the mystery refrigerator to prove their culinary skills and creativity.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p26206096_b_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30AM</start>
    <finish>03:05AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>China Salesman</title>
    <desc>A young Chinese engineer, Yan Jian, competes against a French spy in a competition that awards the right to control communications technology in Africa to the winner.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15151872_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:05AM</start>
    <finish>05:10AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>The Sound of Silence</title>
    <desc>A house tuner, Peter Lucian, calibrates the ambient noises of a house to alleviate the resident's mood. But he is soon baffled by chronically exhausted Ellen, whose problem he cannot seem to solve.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p16835600_v_h8_ai.jpg</image>
    <start>05:10AM</start>
    <finish>06:55AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>When a Stranger Calls</title>
    <desc>During a babysitting job, Jill, a young woman, is terrorised by a psychopathic killer's ominous calls. Years later, he returns to menace her once again.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p5165_v_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>06:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Talladega Nights: The Ballad of Ricky Bobby</title>
    <desc>Ricky, a NASCAR racing sensation, is the number one racer in the world. After Jean beats him in a race and becomes the top racer, Ricky tries to regain his dominance.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p159752_v_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Ultraviolet</title>
    <desc>A female rebel is infected with a virus that provides her with superhuman abilities. Thereafter, she tries to safeguard a boy in a futuristic world, who carries the virus's antigen.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p159164_v_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>21</title>
    <desc>Micky, a maths professor, enlists five gifted students to use their abilities to win millions at blackjack in Las Vegas. He exploits their talents for personal gain in the glamorous casino city.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p173597_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>The Equalizer</title>
    <desc>Robert McCall gives up violence and wishes to lead a quiet life. However, brutal events force him to take up the fight for justice once again.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10549100_v_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Premium Rush</title>
    <desc>Wilee is a bicycle messenger who rides a single-gear bike with no brakes. His routine delivery turns into a dangerous chase when his last package of the day is pursued by corrupt police officers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8786097_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>When a Stranger Calls</title>
    <desc>During a babysitting job, Jill, a young woman, is terrorised by a psychopathic killer's ominous calls. Years later, he returns to menace her once again.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p5165_v_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>06:05PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Flix IN</name>
    <title>Movie</title>
    <desc>Bringing the best in television.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p809747_b_h8_af.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
