<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>DIVE INTO KOREAN</title>
    <desc>?Dive into Korean? is an introductory educational documentary series designed for learners beginning their journey with the Korean language. The program explores the historical and cultural essence of Hangeul, the Korean alphabet, and the spirit behind its creation by King Sejong the Great. Through engaging storytelling and real-life experiences, the series helps viewers understand the beauty, science, and philosophy embedded in the Korean language.  Episode 1: Hangeul ? A Script Anyone Can Learn Easily Discover how Hangeul was designed as an easy and logical writing system for all people, embodying King Sejong?s vision of communication and equality.  Episode 2: Hangeul ? A Script That Illustrates the Sounds of Speech Explore the scientific principles behind Hangeul?s creation ? how its characters visually represent the shape and movement of the human speech organs.  Episode 3: The More You Know the Culture, the Closer You Get to Korean Understand how culture and language intertwine, and how learning about Korean traditions and expressions brings learners closer to authentic communication.  Episode 4: Korean Language Connecting the World Witness how Korean has grown into a global language of culture, creativity, and connection ? a bridge linking people across nations.\&quot;Sponsored by King Sejong Institute Foundation\&quot;.</desc>
    <image>https://epg.best/assets/program-icons?program=eyJpdiI6IkNKRWszcVgySFk4MFhlZmNOTE5yYWc9PSIsInZhbHVlIjoiQWFsM3h0OFdBR2tOWFpHcldVekZTQ1BReUZxeFlDeEFNa2V5SnRscURzdjhNczYrT1RnYzJnY3JISjlFM2o5anJOUmg3enp6dWxRYWZSMG5pc3hOaTc3UUtwMytrRk9EVGh4RzJld2xzd1RtRWJPSG05YndteTh2SUFsUG03UFd1UG94TVJSSjZSUkVjZGZiYXAyTG1qaXdsZlV6bktNZjdNSjZrVkI1SGk1OVJHQWtKYzZubis1dVwvOXMzQlNiSyIsIm1hYyI6IjQwOGIwMjdiYmRjMjc3NjQ1YjBmNDVhNzg4ZjExOGI3ZTE3NGVkNDM5NDIwMTA3NGZkOThjYjM1MjI2ZDNiNDAifQ%3D%3D&amp;signature=151daaf8b0b47167b42c0d3d4cd5f4cce63b726337003d4077c6d2b4d7447957</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 November 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
