<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>NEWS GENERATION [R]</title>
    <desc>NEWs Generation is Arirang TV?s daily news program covering latest trends and current affairs affecting people in their twenties and thirties. It opens discussions with millennial and Gen Z panelists and experts who would like to share their insight and firsthand experience on various topics of interest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202308/2080785597756080772.png</image>
    <start>06:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>THE GLOBALISTS</title>
    <desc>?Where Does Korea Need to Go?? We reflect on the lives and experiences of global opinion leaders who have made their mark on the world to understand what Korea?s future vision should be and where the country needs to be headed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202504/2970861493769208592.png</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>KOREA TRAVELOGUE 5(20?)</title>
    <desc>A trip to find the hidden secrets of Korea. A live on-the-scene documentary that captures stories of Korea.? VOD service is currently not available due to copyright issues.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202210/1652771094655926447.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>EXPLORING KOREAN LITERATURE A</title>
    <desc>2021 Exploring Korean Literature There is a growing interest in Korean literature among readers from around the world and so we bring Korean classics to Korean modern literature to viewers in this special series under three themes. What They?ve Read Well-known TV personalities read three translated works of Korean literature that have recently received attention. Kim Soom's novel \&quot;One Left\&quot;, brings the comfort women issue to the forefront of the literary world, and her book is recited and discussed by Darcy Paquet, a translator and essayist for the film \&quot;Parasite,\&quot; and translator and essayist Colin Marshall, Italian architect Simone Carena, and fashion designer Shin Ji-hye. The novel was published in the U.S. in September 2020 and a second book print was released this year. Cho Nam-Joo's novel \&quot;Kim Jiyoung, Born 1982\&quot; has been translated into 25 languages and is recited by TV personality Daniel Hicks (UK), Carlos Gorito (Brazil), YouTuber Sarah Mack (USA) and singer Punita (India) who share their thoughts about the book. Howon, a member of the boy band, W24, recites passages from Kim Young-ha's novel \&quot;Diary of a Murderer\&quot; and gives commentary. Living to Tell a Story This documentary features Korean writers whose works are not only popular in Korea but also overseas. In episode 1, poet Kim Yi-deum, the Winner of the National Translation Award and the Lucien Stryk Award for her collection of poems, \&quot;Hysteria,\&quot; as well as Korean novelists Kim Cho-Yup and Kim Yeon-su appear to talk about the creative process and how they carry out research before writing a novel. In Episode 2, novelist Yun Ko-Eun, the winner of the Crime Fiction in Translation Dagger award for her book, \&quot;The Disaster Tourist\&quot;, and novelist Ha Seong-nan and poet Jin Eun-young explain what they were trying to convey to readers through their works. In Episode 3, novelist Hwang Sok-young, whose works are mostly inspired by his own experience of living in modern Korean society, tells the story of his life and literary journey. A Word Depicted in Stories The cultural characteristics in Korean literature that encompasses Korean classics to modern novels are highlighted on this show. Six episodes with different themes ranging from female poets in classical literature, makeup culture, wine and arts, tea ceremony, pets, and a literary discussion forum will begin airing on November 5th. --&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/old/A_UpFile/TvPg_Info_Img/T210812162657_SCH.jpg</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>WITH SCIENCE, WE LIVE</title>
    <desc>Humanity has learned from the past, transcended the present, and dreamed of the future.\&quot;With Science, We Live\&quot;explores the frontiers of science alongside some of the world?s leading thinkers, offering insights into what lies ahead and uncovering new possibilities.In an era of rapid change, where are we headed?As we navigate between the vast universe and the smallness of human existence, we reconsider the direction we must take.Now, in this very moment, we imagine the future shaped by our choices?and move forward toward it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202507/3092792820386235212.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>1DAY 1K-CULTURE: K-STORY</title>
    <desc>The emergence of the word ?K-Brand? indicates the level of worldwide interest in Korean culture today. [1Day 1K-culture] is a daily series of cultural programs designed to bring viewers closer to the everyday cultures of Korea.  K-Trend What's popular in Korea K-People Like and follow, Koreans of interest K-Story What Koreans are viewing now K-Stage Must-see performances.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202504/2969259464642790160.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>DISCOVERING KOREA: VIEW</title>
    <desc>?Discovering Korea? is a travel information program that delivers specific tourism information about Korean destinations including food, attractions and scenery etc. Throughout this program, it promotes Korean culture and conducts global tourism marketing promotion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202407/2598649329237361406.png</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>THE DAILY REPORT [L] (30?)</title>
    <desc>The Daily Report airs from Monday to Friday at 2 p.m. KST and offers the afternoon edition of Arirang News.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202209/1623490255543861281.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>PRESS PERSPECTIVE [L]</title>
    <desc>Daily 17:30-18:00((KST) Press Perspective.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202410/2696972320861324034.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>I'M LIVE</title>
    <desc>?I'm Live is a live concert program featuring Korea's top musicians? Musicians and fans interact with one another in close proximity, becoming one in the name of music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202504/2971229173537833744.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>K-STAGE PAN(30?)</title>
    <desc>To establish itself as an unprecedented gugak music concert program by Gugak broadcasting, where the charms of Korean music, played in various styles through the ages, can be truly felt.? VOD service is currently not available due to copyright issues.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202302/1838988630819865095.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>THE GLOBALISTS</title>
    <desc>?Where Does Korea Need to Go?? We reflect on the lives and experiences of global opinion leaders who have made their mark on the world to understand what Korea?s future vision should be and where the country needs to be headed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202504/2970861493769208592.png</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>BRAVO K-SCIENTIST</title>
    <desc>There are people who, unafraid of failure, take on challenges for new discoveries and embark on expeditions into the unknown without hesitation. They are the K-Scientists leading Korea?s world of science.  The most outstanding scientists in Korea. What were the joys of science they discovered after repeated failures, and what were the joys of life they realized through such experiences? Join us on a journey into their everyday lives.? VOD service is currently not available due to copyright issues.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202310/2192622589640180384.png</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>NEWSCENTER [L] (30?)</title>
    <desc>Watch the Latest Stories Here: Arirang's Primetime News Center (Weekdays 8 PM KST).</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202506/3060932114795987770.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>WITHIN THE FRAME [L]</title>
    <desc>Ranging from politics, economy, foreign policy and culture, \&quot;Within the Frame\&quot; is a daily in-depth analysis show, delving deeper into different topics every day.With a panel of experts, \&quot;Within the Frame\&quot; will delve deeper into the headlines of the week, providing for premium news analysis in an easy, well-trimmed manner. Tune into \&quot;Within the Frame.\&quot;.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202410/2736035322507821826.png</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>THE KULTURE WAVE [R]</title>
    <desc>Riding on the Korean Wave! A culture news program that explores K-culture from all aspects with a variety of panelists and guests. Stay up to date on K-entertainment, K-trends, K-people, K-everything with \&quot;the Kulture Wave\&quot;!The Kulture Wave?Daily 14:00-14:30(KST). Kwon Soa.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202410/2696964145273635586.png</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>1DAY 1K-CULTURE: K-STORY</title>
    <desc>The emergence of the word ?K-Brand? indicates the level of worldwide interest in Korean culture today. [1Day 1K-culture] is a daily series of cultural programs designed to bring viewers closer to the everyday cultures of Korea.  K-Trend What's popular in Korea K-People Like and follow, Koreans of interest K-Story What Koreans are viewing now K-Stage Must-see performances.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202504/2969259464642790160.jpg</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>ARIRANG SPECIAL(A-15' ??A)</title>
    <desc>Arirang Special features a variety of unique and special programs produced by Arirang TV. These exciting programs will open your eyes to a new part of the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202410/2728785761695433474.png</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>WITH SCIENCE, WE LIVE</title>
    <desc>Humanity has learned from the past, transcended the present, and dreamed of the future.\&quot;With Science, We Live\&quot;explores the frontiers of science alongside some of the world?s leading thinkers, offering insights into what lies ahead and uncovering new possibilities.In an era of rapid change, where are we headed?As we navigate between the vast universe and the smallness of human existence, we reconsider the direction we must take.Now, in this very moment, we imagine the future shaped by our choices?and move forward toward it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202507/3092792820386235212.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>HOME TO TABLE</title>
    <desc>In the rush of everyday life, we often lose sight of the precious moments shared with family. But memories we thought forgotten come back to life, right at the dinner table. In this heartwarming journey, young people learn time-honored Korean home recipes passed down with love from their parents. Discover the rich flavors of family, seasoned by time spent together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202504/2991435715537011480.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>PRESS PERSPECTIVE [R]</title>
    <desc>Daily 17:30-18:00((KST) Press Perspective.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202410/2696972320861324034.png</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
