<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>BRAVO K-SCIENTIST</title>
    <desc>There are people who, unafraid of failure, take on challenges for new discoveries and embark on expeditions into the unknown without hesitation. They are the K-Scientists leading Korea?s world of science.  The most outstanding scientists in Korea. What were the joys of science they discovered after repeated failures, and what were the joys of life they realized through such experiences? Join us on a journey into their everyday lives.? VOD service is currently not available due to copyright issues.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202310/2192622589640180384.png</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>NEWSCENTER [L] (30?)</title>
    <desc>Watch the Latest Stories Here: Arirang's Primetime News Center (Weekdays 8 PM KST).</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202506/3060932114795987770.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>WITHIN THE FRAME [L]</title>
    <desc>Ranging from politics, economy, foreign policy and culture, \&quot;Within the Frame\&quot; is a daily in-depth analysis show, delving deeper into different topics every day.With a panel of experts, \&quot;Within the Frame\&quot; will delve deeper into the headlines of the week, providing for premium news analysis in an easy, well-trimmed manner. Tune into \&quot;Within the Frame.\&quot;.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202410/2736035322507821826.png</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>THE KULTURE WAVE [R]</title>
    <desc>Riding on the Korean Wave! A culture news program that explores K-culture from all aspects with a variety of panelists and guests. Stay up to date on K-entertainment, K-trends, K-people, K-everything with \&quot;the Kulture Wave\&quot;!The Kulture Wave?Daily 14:00-14:30(KST). Kwon Soa.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202410/2696964145273635586.png</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>1DAY 1K-CULTURE: K-STORY</title>
    <desc>The emergence of the word ?K-Brand? indicates the level of worldwide interest in Korean culture today. [1Day 1K-culture] is a daily series of cultural programs designed to bring viewers closer to the everyday cultures of Korea.  K-Trend What's popular in Korea K-People Like and follow, Koreans of interest K-Story What Koreans are viewing now K-Stage Must-see performances.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202504/2969259464642790160.jpg</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>ARIRANG SPECIAL(A-15' ??A)</title>
    <desc>Arirang Special features a variety of unique and special programs produced by Arirang TV. These exciting programs will open your eyes to a new part of the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202410/2728785761695433474.png</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>WITH SCIENCE, WE LIVE</title>
    <desc>Humanity has learned from the past, transcended the present, and dreamed of the future.\&quot;With Science, We Live\&quot;explores the frontiers of science alongside some of the world?s leading thinkers, offering insights into what lies ahead and uncovering new possibilities.In an era of rapid change, where are we headed?As we navigate between the vast universe and the smallness of human existence, we reconsider the direction we must take.Now, in this very moment, we imagine the future shaped by our choices?and move forward toward it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202507/3092792820386235212.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>HOME TO TABLE</title>
    <desc>In the rush of everyday life, we often lose sight of the precious moments shared with family. But memories we thought forgotten come back to life, right at the dinner table. In this heartwarming journey, young people learn time-honored Korean home recipes passed down with love from their parents. Discover the rich flavors of family, seasoned by time spent together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202504/2991435715537011480.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <id>ArirangWorld.kr</id>
    <title>PRESS PERSPECTIVE [R]</title>
    <desc>Daily 17:30-18:00((KST) Press Perspective.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202410/2696972320861324034.png</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
