<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Beeba Boys</title>
    <desc>To assume authority over Vancouver's illegal ammunition and drug trade, a gang leader goes up against an affluent crime lord.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p12208284_v_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Sniper: Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Brandon Beckett and his men are attacked by a sniper while on a mission to rescue a farmer. Following the incident, he seeks the help of his father's protege to avenge the death of his squad.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8583971_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Stomp the Yard: Homecoming</title>
    <desc>Chance Harris, a young man, tries to find a solution to balance his life, school, work and relationship in order to participate for a national step competition.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8224227_v_h10_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Vincent N Roxxy</title>
    <desc>An unlikely romance develops between Vincent, a loner, and Roxxy, a rebel, while they are on the run to save their lives. However, their violent past seems to catch up with them wherever they go.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p13963103_v_h10_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>30 Days of Night: Dark Days</title>
    <desc>Stella Olemaun moves to Los Angeles to create awareness about vampires, but soon becomes the target of the local blood-thirsty demons. She decides to face them and avenge her husband's death.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8298187_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Monster House</title>
    <desc>Three teenagers discover that their neighbour's house is actually a monster that hates children. They then decide to destroy the heart of the house and kill it.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p159533_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:25PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Brian Banks</title>
    <desc>Brian Banks, a former American football player, was falsely accused and arrested for raping his classmate. Things change when a criminal defense lawyer and his team uncovers the truth.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p16362286_v_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>08:25PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Underworld: Rise of the Lycans</title>
    <desc>Lucian, a werewolf slave, convinces his Lycan compatriots to rebel against their vampire masters, who are led by Viktor, a powerful vampire elder. This leads to a full-fledged war between the two.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p187411_v_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:15PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Chef vs Fridge</title>
    <desc>Popular celebrities and professional chefs compete in a unique challenge, crafting delicious dishes using only random ingredients from their fridge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20453532_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:15AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Dance With Me</title>
    <desc>Terence Lewis delivers a captivating performance, mesmerising Shakti and Mukti Mohan. Furthermore, they witness impressive dance routines featuring innovative costumes and props.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p19074508_b_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:15AM</start>
    <finish>01:15AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
