<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>The Last Stand of Ellen Cole</title>
    <desc>A ruthless land developer targets an elderly widow's Montana ranch, expecting easy intimidation. He soon discovers her resilience means he's bitten off more than he can chew.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p30074788_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:05PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Please Stand By</title>
    <desc>Wendy, a young woman with autism, runs away from her caregiver and embarks on a journey of a lifetime in order to submit her manuscript to a screenwriting competition.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14793145_v_h10_bf.jpg</image>
    <start>06:05PM</start>
    <finish>07:35PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Donnie Brasco</title>
    <desc>While investigating a New York Mafia family from within, an FBI agent faces a moral quandary as he grows close to the organisation's feared hitman.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p19088_v_h10_af.jpg</image>
    <start>07:35PM</start>
    <finish>09:25PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>The Replacement Killers</title>
    <desc>John Lee, a hitman, is hired to kill a cop's son. He is unable to accomplish his mission and decides to flee. However, his boss hires replacements to finish the task and kill John Lee.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20495_v_h11_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:25PM</start>
    <finish>10:50PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Resident Evil</title>
    <desc>Two associates of an elite commando team fight an army of zombies controlled by an evil desktop computer in a genetic research facility.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29625_v_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:50PM</start>
    <finish>12:20AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>America's Sweethearts</title>
    <desc>When Kiki helps facilitate a final public appearance between her famous boss and her estranged husband, she experiences an unexpected spark of attraction and falls for him.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28040_v_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>12:20AM</start>
    <finish>02:05AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Underworld: Evolution</title>
    <desc>Vampire warrior Selene and the half-werewolf Michael search for hints to understand the history of their races and the intense conflicts between them.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p159383_v_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>02:05AM</start>
    <finish>03:35AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>S.W.A.T.</title>
    <desc>When a drug lord offers a huge reward to anyone who can get him out of prison, the SWAT team in Los Angeles, USA is tasked with preventing the escape.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p30520_v_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>03:35AM</start>
    <finish>05:25AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>The Walk</title>
    <desc>Philippe Petit, a French street performer, dreams of performing daring stunts. He attempts to walk between the Twin Towers of the World Trade Center in New York on a tightrope.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11819840_v_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>05:25AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Jerry Maguire</title>
    <desc>Sports agent Jerry Maguire tries to get back on his feet after being fired from his job. However, the only client he has is Rod Tidwell, a disgruntled football player who wants a better contract.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18815_v_h8_ai.jpg</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>30 Days of Night: Dark Days</title>
    <desc>Stella Olemaun moves to Los Angeles to create awareness about vampires, but soon becomes the target of the local blood-thirsty demons. She decides to face them and avenge her husband's death.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8298187_v_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>The Book of Eli</title>
    <desc>Eli, a vagabond who wanders 30 years across the regions within North America, has to face several challenges to safeguard a book that contains the secrets to protect mankind.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p189972_v_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Vacancy 2: The First Cut</title>
    <desc>After checking into a motel, a young couple and their friend are horrified to discover they are trapped in their room, watched by hotel employees who delight in torturing guests.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p195940_v_h8_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Absolutely Anything</title>
    <desc>A group of eccentric aliens gives an ordinary human being named Neil the limitless power to do anything he wants. Unbeknownst to Neil, this is an experiment to see if Earth deserves to be destroyed.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p12027577_v_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Flashbacks of a Fool</title>
    <desc>A self-absorbed Hollywood star returns home after his best friend's tragic death. his loss forces him to confront his past and deeply reconsider his life's direction.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p180423_v_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Runner Runner</title>
    <desc>Richie, a Princeton graduate, loses his tuition in online poker and seeks out Ivan, a wealthy gambling tycoon, only to find himself entangled in a dangerous web of crime.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9872855_v_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>War of the Arrows</title>
    <desc>Orphaned siblings are raised by their father's close friend. When one is abducted before her wedding, the other courageously stands against the formidable Mongols.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8879189_v_h10_af.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>And Prive IN</name>
    <title>Movie</title>
    <desc>Movie to be announced.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p12971380_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
