<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Parent Wars</title>
    <desc>In Illinois, one man calls his mother for help after he flees the scene of a car crash; in Colorado, a father saves his son from a car crash inside a donut shop; in Minneapolis, a 10-year-old drives a car through a park full of kids.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p30005252_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Casey attempts to keep a rein on Rene's spending habits; Darrell and Brandon use their intuition to soar above their competitors; Ivy tries to secretly learn Jarrod and Brandi's purchasing strategy.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The auction action moves to downtown Los Angeles, where Darrell and Brandon seek additional merchandise for their 24/7 store; Ivy locates a locker filled with tools; Mary takes on the heavy hitters.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders seek hot deals in Palm Desert, Calif.; Rene is challenged by local buyers; Mary goes over her limit; Jarrod and Brandi turn to unreliable help.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Jarrod and Brandi bring their children to an auction; Rene and Casey embrace the concept of teamwork; Ivy hopes to stock up on goods; &quot;Gambler&quot; Darrell puts his nickname to the test.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Dan and Laura face tough competition in the neighborhood of North Hollywood; Dave's locker may be a hit; Mary eyes two units that, if purchased together, would make a perfect fit.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The bidders travel to San Jacinto, Calif.; Darrell makes a musical purchase; Brandi and Jarrod must team up with Barry in order to turn a profit; Nabila attempts to expand her territory.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Jarrod has difficulty finding his groove in Riverside, Calif.; an item stumps Dave; Ivy tries a new strategy; Mary discovers the romantic side of purchasing lockers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Darrell hopes to humiliate Ivy in his own backyard; Jarrod and Brandi are surrounded by pigs; Rene purchases a &quot;crappy&quot; locker.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Dan and Laura face a life-or-death crisis as the buyers assemble in Hemet, Calif.; Brandi tries to keep Jarrod focused on business; Mary finds an out-of-this-world item.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Rene and Casey take on rival couple Jarrod and Brandi; Darrell wins an intriguing locker after dodging a bullet; Ivy encounters a furry friend.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
