<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Ivy brings his son to Moreno Valley, where good things always happen, and leaves with yo-yo's of an unexpected kind; Rene and Casey discover that their shoes are more &quot;air&quot; and less &quot;Jordan.&quot;.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers look for deals in City of Industry, Calif.; Dave makes a profit; Barry visits the &quot;King of Kitsch.&quot;.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The Gambler returns to form in Huntington Beach, Calif.; Rene gets on everyone's bad side; Mary finds her likeness lucrative; Ivy faces cloudy prospects.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Kenny bids on a massive locker; Rene and Casey attempt to go small; Shana and Edwina's mystery box is mislabeled.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The Vegas Ladies show up in &quot;Bourgie Brea,&quot; and find the place fascinating; Mary decides to deal with her storage stress by introducing a bit of yoga into her routine; Ivy and Dave go head to head on a giant pair of sister lockers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_ao.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Customer Wars</title>
    <desc>In Allen, Texas, a parking lot dispute turns into a bizarre tirade of passive-aggressive insults; at a luxury hotel in West Palm Beach, Florida, an unruly guest clashes with staff and police.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p22962383_b_h8_an.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Customer Wars</title>
    <desc>At a restaurant in Washington, a customer who's upset over a pick-up order begins directing her anger at the staff, prompting a nearby diner to intervene; in New York City, a ride-share driver is attacked by one of his passengers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p22962383_b_h8_an.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Customer Wars</title>
    <desc>In Toronto, confusion over handicap accessibility on a streetcar causes tempers to flare; in Charlotte, N.C., an amateur fashion show devolves into an all out brawl; a plane is forced to make an emergency landing in Albuquerque, N.M.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p22962383_b_h8_an.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Customer Wars</title>
    <desc>On a bus in Los Angeles, Calif., tensions rise over a woman's refusal to give up her seat to accommodate a wheel-chaired passenger; in West Palm Beach, Fla., a woman fails to comply with police.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p22962383_b_h8_an.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Customer Wars</title>
    <desc>In Florida, a dress shop employee suspected of taking money from the cash drawer is confronted by police; in a Charlotte fast food restaurant, employees attempt to remove two argumentative customers from the premises.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p22962383_b_h8_an.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Customer Wars</title>
    <desc>In Orem, Utah, tempers flare when a neighbor lashes out at a construction crew for playing music while they work; in Hollywood, Fla., a shoplifting suspect flees from police, leading to a dramatic on-foot chase.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p22962383_b_h8_an.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A man attempting to elude arrest leads officers on a high-speed chase; a medical emergency causes chaos on the highway in Hilliard, Ohio; deputies search for a missing child in the swamp.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>Shoplifter fires at police during pursuit; Florida deputies and K-9 look for drugs during traffic stop; police rescue children from roof.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A trooper saves a motorist's life; a Marine unit rescues three brothers from their capsized boat; an officer is shot in the line of duty.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A San Antonio suspect with a baby flees from the police; a pregnant woman is held hostage at gunpoint; deputies search for fugitives in a cow pasture.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A trooper's cruiser is totaled on the freeway; a country music singer gets mouthy during a DUI arrest; a helicopter chase leads to a shootout in Florida.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A suspect attempts to flee during a high-speed pursuit in Georgia; police rescue an elderly couple from their burning home; an officer is rescued from a brutal assault.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A man attacks an officer with a pipe; a group of thieves is caught mid-theft; a deputy rushes to save a trapped man from a multicar highway pileup.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>Officers attempt to convince an armed man to drop his knife; animals escape during a DUI stop; a high-speed chase in Missoula, Mont., ends in a crash.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
