<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Ivy makes use of a dastardly tactic when the buyers compete in Indio, Calif.; Mary moves out of her comfort zone; Darrell refuses to let Brandon's sour disposition distract him from winning lockers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_db.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Brandi is fired up about expanding her brand in San Bernardino; Rene is positive that everyone is out to get him; Dusty tackles a locker dustier than him.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p24695827_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Rene gets lukewarm results bobbing for profits in Stanton; Dusty finds a hoard of quality equipment, inking himself a decent payday; looking for treasure, Brandi ends up with the green in an unexpected manner.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p24695827_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The new bidder returns; Barry is intrigued by a locker with a hole in the wall; Jarrod pulls a sneaky trick.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_db.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A woman who killed her husband is disowned by her children in court; a teacher who slept with her teenage students apologizes to the victims' families; a courtroom melee breaks out between an accused murderer and the victim's family.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A daring courthouse escape; an angry defendant flips a podium, a chipmunk interrupts a Zoom hearing.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A former mayor opens fire on a SWAT team; a grieving mother berates her child's killer; a convicted murderer has a surprise for the court.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A desperate man attacks a courthouse with guns and smoke grenades with deadly consequences; a man declares he is not the father of a young woman's baby; an angry judge hits an unruly defendant with a shocking sentence.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A man accused of driving with a suspended license gets caught lying to the judge; the grieving partner of a drunk driving victim gets tasered outside the courthouse; a man testifies that his son wasn't assaulting him, and more.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A man who is accused of indecency with a child's doll faces his accuser in court; an arsonist who killed nine people hears it from the judge; a multi-murder suspect misbehaves in the courtroom.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A retired NFL star comes face to face with the man who invaded his home; a Kentucky courtroom goes wild; four bailiffs struggle to contain a furious defendant.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>Tempers flare at the trial of the deadliest biker brawl in U.S. history; the father of a murder victim comes face to face with his daughter's killer; it's a matter of life or death when a defendant goes for a deputy's gun in a packed courtroom.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>The First 48</title>
    <desc>The target of a drive-by shooting in Tulsa, Okla., walks away from the attack, while his girlfriend is not so fortunate; police uncover a long-simmering feud as they hunt for the killer.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185469_b_h8_an.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>The First 48</title>
    <desc>A Miami detective suspects a drifter was responsible for the stabbing death of an elderly man; a woman is murdered during a robbery in her illegal game room.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185469_b_h8_an.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>The First 48</title>
    <desc>When a young man from Tulsa., Okla., is found shot dead in his van, homicide detectives retrace his final hours and get caught up in a web of lies.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185469_b_h8_an.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
