<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Joni Table Talk</title>
    <desc>Joni and guests tackle a wide range of relevant issues, controversial subjects and hard-hitting news topics with candor and wit.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p26403145_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars Texas</title>
    <desc>The buyers return to Dallas; Jenny seeks industrial material for a custom job; Mary ignores the law to land a dream locker; Ricky and Bubba discover cash in the wind.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8666432_b_h8_bj.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars Texas</title>
    <desc>A deceased tycoon's unit goes up for sale; antique kitchen gear; soaring highs and crushing lows greet the bidders.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8666432_b_h8_bj.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The women outnumber the men in Rosamond, as Dusty and his girlfriend discover a stockpile of vintage TV memorabilia; Brandi enlists the help of both Danielle and Lisa to dig for gold.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p24695827_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>In Huntington Beach, Calif., Darrell's insider information amplifies his investment considerably; Mary's find cooks up some oversized accoutrements; Kenny takes advantage of others' missteps to grab a unit.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_db.jpg</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers head to Palm Springs, Calif., in search of higher-end goods; Kenny tries to amp up the profit on an otherwise unimpressive unit; Rene sees quick potential where others don't; Brandi and Bozek try to keep their gains from squirming away.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p24695827_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Brandi allows Jarrod to spend freely in El Monte, Calif., but Mary winds up landing the priciest locker of the day; Rene achieves good results on a low budget.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_db.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Brandi surprises Jarrod with a thick bankroll in hopes of getting the best unit of the day; Mary brings in some extra help for the huge lockers; Darrell and Brandon win an auction that contains something that unexpectedly lands them in a courtroom.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_db.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Ivy takes on a supervisory role in Stanton, and it leads him to a bit of Slavic success; Brandi tries to help Danielle outfit her new apartment; Lisa gambles on a painting.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p24695827_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Barry hires two psychics to &quot;see&quot; inside storage lockers; Jarrod and Brandi hope to save their store by taking a gamble on a unit.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_db.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Darrell and Brandon seek a large quantity of items for their store as the buyers invade the community of Rancho Dominguez; Mary gets mean; Jarrod and Brandi recruit a new teammate.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_db.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>The buyers trek to Murietta, Calif.; Jeff Jarred resurfaces but that doesn't sit well with the Dotsons; Barry Weiss figures a couple things out; Jarrod and Brandi gamble on a unit and the results are electric.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_db.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>Darrell and Brandon score big when when the buyers return to Moreno Valley, Calif.; Mary Padian looks for romance and attractive units.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8354064_b_h8_db.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>High-speed chase in Seattle; shootout with a murder suspect; an officer is shot during a traffic stop.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A man attacks an officer with a pipe; a group of thieves is caught mid-theft; a deputy rushes to save a trapped man from a multicar highway pileup.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>Officers attempt to convince an armed man to drop his knife; animals escape during a DUI stop; a high-speed chase in Missoula, Mont., ends in a crash.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A trooper saves a motorist's life; a Marine unit rescues three brothers from their capsized boat; an officer is shot in the line of duty.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A man attempting to elude arrest leads officers on a high-speed chase; a medical emergency causes chaos on the highway in Hilliard, Ohio; deputies search for a missing child in the swamp.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A battle over a gun in Lakemoor, Ill.; a U.S. marshal is dragged by a fleeing vehicle; officers respond to an apartment fire and discover a trapped family.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>The security team is on high alert during scorching temperatures in Cleveland and fans tailgating in the heat hours before kickoff; from medical emergencies to a vaping ejection that escalates, the teams face challenges at every turn.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476906_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>Protecting this stadium are highly trained men and women from law enforcement, private security teams and medics. In this episode, tensions are at an all-time high between these rivaling fans when a fight quickly erupts requiring multiple personnel to break it up. The medical team responds to different calls of fans who have passed out while the security team must handle a curious accusation of a younger fan assaulting an older gentleman. Fortunately, the video tape does not lie.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476906_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>Highly trained law enforcement officers, private security teams and medics protect this stadium; a winter storm descends on the stadium, covering it in snow, which intensifies the night.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476906_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>The security team handles a range of incidents, from ejecting fans for vaping and breaking up a large scuffle in the stands, to investigating the disappearance of a young man whose worried parents and girlfriend report him missing.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476906_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
