<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>In Boston, a couple accuses their neighbors of feeding their dog chicken bones; a Florida man cleaning his rental home makes a shocking discovery under the bed.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>Two California neighbors jockey for a prime spot at the annual Christmas parade, leading to plenty of holiday jeer; in Ontario, a man is stopped from entering an apartment building claiming his grandmother needs her medication.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>After a California woman removes a fence along her property line, her relationship with the neighbors turns sour; a neighbor in Santa Monica woken up by a loud gathering and unleashes her fury on the party throwers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29015735_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>South Carolina roommates are subjected to a string of bizarre insults by a neighbor outside their home; neighbors turn ugly in Oklahoma City when an apparent handshake agreement to not park in front of each other's houses is ignored.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29015735_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>A woman in rural Iowa angrily scolds her neighbor about the smoke from burning yard waste; a man in Buffalo backs into a neighbor's van in the driveway and the commotion causes a stir in the community.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p30061641_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>A video gamer is so spooked by would-be burglars that he opens fire through the door of his Dallas apartment building; a neighbor driving a golf cart subdues a stranger smashing up property in Illinois.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
