<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Who Has Access to Your Personal Data?</title>
    <desc>Even if YOU do everything right to protect yourself, company and institutional data breaches are out of your control. Nearly 1 out of 4 US consumers have been a victim of identity theft. Find out how LifeLock can help protect your identity.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28553630_st_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:02AM</start>
    <finish>10:31AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>NECTAR TRI-PILLOW -Cooler, Comfy, Better Sleep! Buy One Get One FREE!</title>
    <desc>Discover the Nectar Tri-Comfort Cooling Pillow for the ultimate sleep experience! Adjustable to three firmness levels to provide customized support and cooling all night long. Order NOW to get a second pillow FREE, plus a 30-night home trial!</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p30176714_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:31AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Ready for a safer shower? Enjoy a one-day bath remodel with Jacuzzi.</title>
    <desc>Trusted brand Jacuzzi Bath Remodel and interior designer Christina Hall share their secrets on how you can easily and affordably transform your bathroom into a gorgeous custom, safe, stylish space in 1 day! Call for a FREE quote &amp; installation.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p30074472_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>The Potter's Touch</title>
    <desc>Bishop T.D. Jakes offers practical and spiritual solutions to life's toughest questions including taboos and hidden issues.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p509747_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Zombie House Flipping</title>
    <desc>Derek takes Chauncy to see a house in the North Dallas neighborhood; even though this smaller home has foundation issues, Derek feels its too much of a deal to pass on.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p25896869_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Zombie House Flipping</title>
    <desc>Chauncey and Derek take on a partner in their latest zombie renovation; as the three investors pool their money and resources in hopes of flipping this house on budget and on time, this 60-year-old home has other plans.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p23571149_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Zombie House Flipping</title>
    <desc>The zombie team takes on a promising flip in a small community, but local permit procedures and regulations soon shut down its work; the group tries to finish before its growing schedule leaves it paying thousands more in loan interest.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p12426507_b_h8_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Zombie House Flipping</title>
    <desc>The zombie is so rotten, the only salvageable parts are the home's exterior walls and the roof, which means a huge renovation budget that can just keep going up.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p25896869_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Zombie House Flipping</title>
    <desc>The team wants to tear down a tiny house, but Duke convinces them to save the house and its vintage bathrooms.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p12426507_b_h8_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Zombie House Flipping</title>
    <desc>When the team finds a low-priced zombie in a good neighborhood, it turns out too good to be true; at first, the team only see old termite damage and no live bugs, but the more they look, the more damage they find.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p12426507_b_h8_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty: The Revival</title>
    <desc>In this new series eight years after &quot;Duck Dynasty,&quot; the world has changed on Willie Robertson; his kids are grown, he's a grandpa, and the Duck Commander warehouse has become the hub for multiple family businesses.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29999999_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>Willie takes temporary ownership of a Thoroughbred, which he and the guys enter into a race at a local track; Kay recruits Phil, Martin and Godwin to help her select a new birdbath for her yard.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11158778_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>Jase enters an outhouse race, where the Robertsons face an unexpected rival; Willie enlists the ladies to be taste testers as he tries to create the world's best bologna sandwich for his Duck Diner.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11158778_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>Jase and Phil's disagreement over whether humans in a duck blind can be spotted from the air leads Jep to purchase a drone; Si visits the chiropractor for a spinal adjustment.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p12423838_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>Sadie's homework gets interrupted when Willie and Jase argue whether the latter can outrun a truck; Si steps in to help when Kay's compulsive hoarding becomes an issue.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11158778_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>Jase and the guys turn a pontoon into a floating duck blind, then put their invention to the test; Kay takes bad pooch Bobo to doggie obedience class.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11158778_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>The Robertson family helps ready Jessica and Jep's new home in Willie and Jase's neighborhood; the guys seek the perfect housewarming gift for Jep.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11158778_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>After Uncle Si has a brush with death, he decides to create a bucket list; Kay tries to prove that she graduated from high school.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9084386_b_h8_al.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>Willie decides it's time for his son to have his own vehicle; Jase, Martin and Godwin have a fishing mishap that leaves Phil's boat at the bottom of the swamp.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9084386_b_h8_al.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>NASCAR driver Clint Bowyer visits the warehouse, leading to a drag race showdown between Willie and Clint; Phil and Si attempt to fix Miss Kay's barbecue.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9084386_b_h8_al.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>Expert trapper Phil is called in when the warehouse guys lose their pet lizard; Willie and Si ride along with members of the West Monroe Police Department.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9084386_b_h8_al.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>A husband-and-wife deer hunt leads to a battle of wills in the woods; Si helps Miss Kay search through piles of her belongings to find the original blueprints for Phil's first duck call.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9084386_b_h8_al.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Duck Dynasty</title>
    <desc>Si uses his metal detector to help Jase locate his lost wedding ring, but soon becomes distracted by what he believes is buried treasure from his past.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9084386_b_h8_al.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
