<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>Highly trained law enforcement officers, private security teams and medics protect this stadium; a winter storm descends on the stadium, covering it in snow, which intensifies the night.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476906_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>The security team stays on high alert over a potential influencer interference, intercedes in a heated dispute between two men, handles an intense incident with a highly intoxicated female, and escorts an unruly fan off the premises.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476911_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>Protecting the stadium are highly trained men and women from law enforcement, private security teams and medics. In this episode, the security team escorts defiant smokers from the stadium while on high alert to ensure that the Kelce and Mahomes families go unbothered in their suites. The team also reviews CCTV footage of two incidents to see whether or not a woman flashed some patrons in one of the stadium's clubs and to determine who actually threw the first punch in a dispute.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476911_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>Protecting the stadium are highly trained men and women from law enforcement, private security teams, and medics; the security team breaks up several brawls over unruly behavior and seat disputes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476906_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
