<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>Two brothers find themselves in a heated showdown with a group of Alabama golfers during an afternoon on the back nine.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>In Sacramento, a neighbor mistakenly believes two women exchanging hair products in the park are actually selling drugs; a belligerent woman smashes her neighbor's window in Virginia; neighbors in Canada clash about a lawn care specialist.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>Neighbors in Dayton, Ohio quarrel after construction nails apparently litter a yard where children play; in Olympia, Wash., a couple is awoken by the sound of a neighbor playing basketball against their garage door.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>A pool party causes parking issues with the neighbors and throws the street into chaos; random dogs in a yard cause issues; a woman is proud of her seasonal house decorations until one opinionated neighbor calls it graffiti.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>When a man installs a surveillance system at his East Coast beach house, the neighbor is so angry he drops his pants in protest; in Illinois, a man is awakened in the middle of the night by his elderly neighbor.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>A lakefront beach in Illinois becomes a battleground when two neighbors yell over who is allowed to be there; a California woman sprays disinfectant at her neighbor.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29015735_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>Crossed words between neighbors turn serious with an exchange of gunfire; a woman hiking in mountains is harangued by a neighbor who thinks she is trespassing on his property; a party-loving couple clashes with their neighbors over noise.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>In Boston, a couple accuses their neighbors of feeding their dog chicken bones; a Florida man cleaning his rental home makes a shocking discovery under the bed.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>Two California neighbors jockey for a prime spot at the annual Christmas parade, leading to plenty of holiday jeer; in Ontario, a man is stopped from entering an apartment building claiming his grandmother needs her medication.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>After a California woman removes a fence along her property line, her relationship with the neighbors turns sour; a neighbor in Santa Monica woken up by a loud gathering and unleashes her fury on the party throwers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29015735_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>South Carolina roommates are subjected to a string of bizarre insults by a neighbor outside their home; neighbors turn ugly in Oklahoma City when an apparent handshake agreement to not park in front of each other's houses is ignored.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29015735_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>A woman in rural Iowa angrily scolds her neighbor about the smoke from burning yard waste; a man in Buffalo backs into a neighbor's van in the driveway and the commotion causes a stir in the community.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p30061641_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Neighborhood Wars</title>
    <desc>A video gamer is so spooked by would-be burglars that he opens fire through the door of his Dallas apartment building; a neighbor driving a golf cart subdues a stranger smashing up property in Illinois.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p20365497_b_h8_at.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
