<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>High-speed chase in Seattle; shootout with a murder suspect; an officer is shot during a traffic stop.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A man attacks an officer with a pipe; a group of thieves is caught mid-theft; a deputy rushes to save a trapped man from a multicar highway pileup.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>Officers attempt to convince an armed man to drop his knife; animals escape during a DUI stop; a high-speed chase in Missoula, Mont., ends in a crash.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A trooper saves a motorist's life; a Marine unit rescues three brothers from their capsized boat; an officer is shot in the line of duty.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A man attempting to elude arrest leads officers on a high-speed chase; a medical emergency causes chaos on the highway in Hilliard, Ohio; deputies search for a missing child in the swamp.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Live PD Presents: PD Cam</title>
    <desc>A battle over a gun in Lakemoor, Ill.; a U.S. marshal is dragged by a fleeing vehicle; officers respond to an apartment fire and discover a trapped family.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15702048_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>The security team is on high alert during scorching temperatures in Cleveland and fans tailgating in the heat hours before kickoff; from medical emergencies to a vaping ejection that escalates, the teams face challenges at every turn.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476906_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>Protecting this stadium are highly trained men and women from law enforcement, private security teams and medics. In this episode, tensions are at an all-time high between these rivaling fans when a fight quickly erupts requiring multiple personnel to break it up. The medical team responds to different calls of fans who have passed out while the security team must handle a curious accusation of a younger fan assaulting an older gentleman. Fortunately, the video tape does not lie.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476906_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>Highly trained law enforcement officers, private security teams and medics protect this stadium; a winter storm descends on the stadium, covering it in snow, which intensifies the night.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476906_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <title>Stadium Lockup</title>
    <desc>The security team handles a range of incidents, from ejecting fans for vaping and breaking up a large scuffle in the stands, to investigating the disappearance of a young man whose worried parents and girlfriend report him missing.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29476906_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
