<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Serial Catfish</title>
    <desc>Joe was sceptical when Miss Teen USA, Kari, sent him a friend request. Now, after months of communication, Joe thinks it might be the real deal, and he might have found love with her. (S1, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b033e47d-8699-4baa-8b15-19e9c0e9f980/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Serial Catfish</title>
    <desc>Alyssa's friend Mary urged her to sign up for a dating website and that's where Alyssa met Tyler. As Nev and Max help, they begin to wonder who's behind the Tyler profile. Could it be Mary? (S7, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f22e23d4-3314-44fd-8d0e-8c8e48de29d6/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Serial Catfish</title>
    <desc>Sydney and Ayissha were in an online romance for years before Sydney revealed she is not who she says. But Ayissha still loves her and seeks Nev and Max's help. (S4, ep25).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/0828ba72-318c-4061-b12b-af6dee84598e/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Serial Catfish</title>
    <desc>When Traves asks for help with his online girlfriend Candy, it looks like classic catfishing. But when the guys dig deeper, they realise they may have caught a bigger catfish than expected. (S7, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/9503133d-fcfb-47a3-8ae3-147234d895e2/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Serial Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and Max embark on their biggest case as they track down the infamous Shelly Chartier to uncover truths about the celeb catfishing of Paris Roxanne and NBA star Chris Andersen. (S6, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/422e9a22-df7f-440b-bc90-531e9ac9e95a/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Serial Catfish</title>
    <desc>Eric fell hard for Lianna but despite living nearby, she was a no-show! Nev and Kamie help Eric get answers but they uncover a rabbit hole that runs deeper than they could have imagined! (S8, ep25).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/8d7f0b64-a5f3-47c0-bf70-64d7bb17a43e/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom UK</title>
    <desc>Charlie struggles to accept Shannon's pregnancy, while Megan can't step away from Dylan. Ste stays over at Amber's and Chloe and Jordan make a tearful breakthrough. (S5, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ec814bdc-5b90-42fe-b15d-6ed3f7d304d6/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Mackenzie surprises her family when she reveals she's pregnant with twins. Ashley moves into a new home to escape memories of her past. Ryan proposes to Amanda with Bentley's help. (S2, ep28).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/58732160-84b1-4070-8575-071db57a9dde/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Dorion is about to give up everything for online love Jeszica, including his relationship with girlfriend Raffinee. But first he wants to know, is Jeszica really the girl in the pictures? (S2, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/8a4fe9e4-cfff-4998-bcc4-a7bc6cab7e4a/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Snatched And Sold For Sex</title>
    <desc>Hard-hitting documentary. This film reveals the shocking stories of four women who were sexually exploited by men.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b476dfa9-56af-4f6b-847c-8ebbdcb1db12/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
