<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Infiniti is a 19-year-old dancer who is certain that her online romance is the real deal. But when Nev and Max dive deep, they find Infiniti's bae is far shadier than they ever imagined. (S7, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e330b891-de34-443c-aa8b-3d144e791397/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Ciatta has a bright family future planned with Juan. But before Nev and Kamie give their blessings on Ciatta's move to LA , they uncover details that put her life plans into question. (S8, ep94).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/6446812c-33f4-4698-aa3e-32d9ab87299b/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Justin Combs joins Nev to help CJ find Shana, a woman who CJ's been having a steamy relationship with for eight years but has never met! (S7, ep37).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5d7b42ee-f5e0-479b-a051-bedb63af3859/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>A Tinder match ignited a fire for Jordan that caused Angel to end a real relationship to pursue him. Nev and his wife Laura uncover dark truths that could lose Angel everyone she loves. (S7, ep13).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/71df9246-bc70-4cb3-ad1e-fcbf8b9496fe/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Ryan thought he'd found his quarantine bae. But when Kamie and Nev start to dig, it's not long before they uncover that Micah may be more interested in Ryan's wallet than his heart. (S8, ep18).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f8a8654f-6921-4a87-a18b-427b6148b821/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Keontae was hooked when he met Tyler on Instagram but Tyler won't meet in person. As Nev and Kamie dig deeper, they find that Tyler's sexual identity may not be the only secret he's hiding! (S8, ep64).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ee977642-a412-47de-89f2-7fe5396f8104/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom UK</title>
    <desc>Series finale. Sassi and Darren come to blows on a weekend away. Amber and Ste are hoping they get answers from Brooklyn's ADHD assessment and Mia and Manley have an overdue heart to heart. (S8, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/4fe694cd-0b55-4bb4-b552-d2a7a49543fd/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Help! I'm In A Secret...</title>
    <desc>Relationship! Rick met girlfriend Shanelle on social media. Their first date lasted until the sun came up! But three years later, Rick still hasn't met Shanelle's family or friends. (S1, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/eed2a8c3-cd51-4796-8a62-7975812a458d/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Queerpiphany</title>
    <desc>Musician Cat Burns reveals her Queerpiphany, queer dating series Are You The One: Come One, Come All. (S4, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f110ae4c-4e7a-41f8-9daf-776a7db79b65/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Queerpiphany</title>
    <desc>Content creator GK Barry reveals how watching Absolutely Fabulous after a disastrous relationship with a man led to her realising that she was, in fact, a lesbian. (S4, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/77d71bd3-fee8-4552-ba3e-a436ea14d48f/16-9</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Hitman</title>
    <desc>A gun-for-hire known only as Agent 47 is ensnared in a political conspiracy, which finds him pursued by both Interpol and the Russian military as he treks across Russia and Eastern Europe.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/05c19d61-fd29-4b2b-8c36-6aafc1891dda/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Annie Lennox</title>
    <desc>On the 3rd of July 1992, Annie Lennox recorded a genre-spanning Unplugged show at the Montreux Jazz Festival, including covers of songs by Eurythmics, The Beatles, and Ike &amp; Tina Turner.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/225a577a-e669-4911-9655-93fc9d64c6c5/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Mariah Carey</title>
    <desc>The legendary MTV show that lets you enjoy the best of music in an acoustic version. In this episode: Mariah Carey's 1992 Unplugged, including her hit cover of \&quot;I'll Be There\&quot; by The Jackson Five.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7ceec825-c94c-4faa-963f-52b6db73517d/16-9</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Gonzo With Jack Saunders</title>
    <desc>Legendary alternative music show Gonzo is back on MTV! Host Jack Saunders brings all the latest hot new alternative tunes, news and views! (S4, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2ebdf4d4-95bc-40e2-80fc-6351e6ceabef/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>In the season premiere, tattooing is a team sport as artists from nine of America's best Shops arrive to battle it out for a massive $200K and the first ever title of Master Shop. (S9, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/258c4ce4-e3d1-4308-9e16-037c09521090/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:45AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Celebrity Ex On The Beach</title>
    <desc>After an emotional double elimination Jarred is left frustrated and upset. Tamara fears history could repeat itself with Jessika Powers and Callum makes his move. (S3, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/4825dd9c-9958-3ac9-a630-b5f2ff9f1b61/16-9</image>
    <start>02:45AM</start>
    <finish>03:35AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>Jimmy O. Yang takes MTV around his vibrant Los Angeles digs. MTV's Catfish, Nev Schulman, gives the expos? on his family friendly abode. Hannah Brown, charms us with her Santa Monica crib. (S19, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5eb5780a-1592-442d-82d2-5b0e386ffa31/16-9</image>
    <start>03:35AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image//16-9</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>We live the ranch life with actor and environmentalist Adrian Grenier at his Austin crib; then, gold medalist Nastia Liukin invites MTV to tour her stunning mansion in Dallas, Texas. (S19, ep19).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/25ab3c35-46af-3aae-8531-7ed7b37cbbb1/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:25AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>Actor Jonathan Bennett shows off his retro, Palm Springs oasis. Actor and comedian Nicole Sullivan takes us around her family's LA home. Then, R&amp;B artist DaniLeigh shows us her Miami crib. (S19, ep20).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/9daa506e-f780-3fb2-802b-f2d8cc48deed/16-9</image>
    <start>06:25AM</start>
    <finish>06:50AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Ashley is staying at her mum's house after a fight with Bar turned physical and she had to get the police involved. Lexi has to let Kyler know that her parents do not want him at the house. (S1, ep22).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/efb3d3d0-ca7b-47e4-ab17-ffa0b5598429/16-9</image>
    <start>06:50AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Teen Mom returns for another dramatic and emotional series as we follow the unpredictable lives of the four original teenagers. Expect trouble with the police, and battles in court. (S2, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ce0d5088-6c0d-4493-b7dc-056cde538547/16-9</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Tonight's rehearsal starts with a big bang when DCC Technical Director Kitty Carter makes a surprise visit to Valley Ranch. (S6, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/777043dd-7cc9-4a7d-983a-a34bce02e307/16-9</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>The Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders are two weeks away from the first game and Kelli McGonagill Finglass and Judy Trammel are hard pressed to make final cuts and announce the squad. (S6, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/821b1486-1123-4113-86fa-7fac58638a74/16-9</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>It has all come down to the final night of training camp. Kelli decides to throw the girls a curveball by taking them out on the Cowboys' practice field to watch them perform. (S6, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/9af6be5f-ba7d-4e84-995c-a9b7a26a7c6d/16-9</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>In this extended season premiere of Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders: Making the Team, 600 hopeful candidates arrive at Cowboys Stadium for the Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders preliminary auditions. (S7, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/0212f2fb-db2c-419b-8816-42b89d43ad43/16-9</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Confessionals</title>
    <desc>Ramon met Paola on Facebook and established an exclusive online relationship. But after many failed attempts to video chat, is she really who he thinks she is? (S2, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e0a7f681-a2d0-420e-a32d-8752838b5394/16-9</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Confessionals</title>
    <desc>Jeni fell hard for Elijah. Now he's sending different pictures of what he looks like! Jeni's confused about who she's in love with. Nev and Kamie help untangle Elijah's web of lies! (S9, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/dbd28bfe-01ec-4465-b689-6f1d2d11d3fe/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Confessionals</title>
    <desc>When Sandra learns that her granddaughter, Yasmine, sent money to an online boyfriend, she asks Nev and Max for help. And they soon discover there's much more that Yasmine has been hiding. (S6, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e5fad607-f997-41d9-a322-949a27c2b11b/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Confessionals</title>
    <desc>Angel met Sharon and quickly formed a deep emotional connection over their shared trauma. Kamie and Nev help Angel expose whether Sharon and her life are really fact or fiction! (S8, ep72).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/6b646651-dd37-41e4-93e3-ab44b4a51398/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Confessionals</title>
    <desc>Percy Rustomji joins Nev in helping Genesis find Jerison, a man she met 12 years ago. While Genesis is hopeful for a new beginning, Nev and Percy suspect she may be headed for heartbreak! (S8, ep93).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3647e1cd-5343-47dd-93ba-721db38e8d14/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Confessionals</title>
    <desc>Nev and Max discover that Dejay and Malik are being played by the same guy. Sparks fly as they discover just how explosive a love triangle can be. (S5, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/d3daab2d-6ee1-4988-8c1e-ae2ced28ee9f/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Confessionals</title>
    <desc>Michael convinced Romeo to move to Atlanta to pursue their dream of being together. Now Romeo's in Atlanta but Michael still won't meet up! Nev and Kamie help track Michael down! (S8, ep53).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/9574aaa8-e696-4816-911c-c8401e4a296d/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Confessionals</title>
    <desc>Jeremy struggled to find other gay men to date until Alex. But when Alex dropped a bombshell that he wasn't the man who Jeremy thought he was dating, Nev and Arlissa dig deep for the truth! (S9, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/01a82c57-0a7d-4c24-a21f-56187bffa77c/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom UK</title>
    <desc>Angels left holding the baby while her boyfriend is down the pub. Whitney is 37 weeks pregnant! Chloe feels broken, Isha feels lonely, and Ellie is just angry! (S1, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a55b2045-96f6-3f6c-b037-d0b5a55acd8a/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Tatu Baby, Jason Clay Dunn, and Julia face Human Canvases that walked out on them during the competition. This time around, can the Artists and Canvases see eye-to-eye to get redemption? (S1, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e1ae2312-1ed7-45a5-ac50-6d64eff6fc36/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Rival Artists design head-to-head to please unhappy Canvases, but only one will receive a shot at redemption. Josh Hibbard and Kyle Dunbar, and brothers Robbie and Jayvo return. (S1, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3ea4216a-6cd1-40db-8f4b-946b15c1a15c/16-9</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>RSVP are off to New York's biggest Italian festival San Gennaro to help find Vinny love. Ang wants to be a pop star. Nicole gets more information about her birth mum. (S8, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/d0013ad0-156c-40a1-8b12-38723fa40e1b/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>With only eight Artists left, an unexpected Team shuffle transforms the Competition. Transforming tattoos are judged blind as the battle continues for $250,000 and the title of Ink Master. (S15, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/41755f05-9000-3f25-b9ab-d440f3d3e8bb/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Beavis And Butt-Head</title>
    <desc>Wall Of Youth: Beavis and Butt-Head contribute in their own special way to a student art display at the mall. (S4, E01).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/93e5f225-1dbc-3bc0-9e20-c4de6f41b4ee/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:15AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Beavis And Butt-Head</title>
    <desc>Cow Tipping: After watching a milk commercial, Beavis and Butt-head attempt cow tipping, but instead Beavis ends up getting squashed by a cow and nearly killed by a crazy farmer. (S4, E02).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/81a7939c-9365-4afa-bda8-4c7c2417d66e/16-9</image>
    <start>01:15AM</start>
    <finish>01:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Jackass</title>
    <desc>Spend a unique Thanksgiving with the Knoxville family as everyone gathers around to watch Johnny's nephew fart. (S2, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a0f82a99-56c5-4cdf-90e6-46253ee7cafb/16-9</image>
    <start>01:30AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Model Dallas has had his sights set on sexy Safari ever since she slid into his dms - but despite flirty promises, she won't meet. Nev and co-host Tallulah Willis begin a hunt for Safari. (S7, ep25).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/126c0a3b-3a7e-435d-b71d-6e8019a5ce6b/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:45AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and co-host Slick Woods help 19-year-old Aubri find her Snapchat love, Brian. Brian says he lives at Aubri's college but has shady excuses not to meet. Nev and Slick hit the campus. (S7, ep26).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/eaa5ecf3-cc87-488e-9b04-118f114edec0/16-9</image>
    <start>02:45AM</start>
    <finish>03:35AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>Stas wows MTV with her stylish Hollywood crib. Then, Mario Lopez and his family, takes us around their California mansion. Lastly, Pauly Shore is back to show off his Las Vegas crib. (S19, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/0947ef00-a7a5-4132-9ee7-65ec2046298a/16-9</image>
    <start>03:35AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image//16-9</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>Drag queen legend Alyssa Edwards shows off her fab abode in Texas. MTV stops by comedian Atsuko Okatsuka's L.A. house. Voice actor E.G. Daily debuts her stunning home in Los Angeles. (S19, ep21).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e0ff0a13-9572-3906-b4d0-b8af860bd822/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:20AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Ashley is unsure how to move forward after Bar's apology. Jade is frustrated when Sean's attempt to start rehab doesn't go as planned. Lexi's family plans a camping trip. (S1, ep23).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5cda798e-598f-45b3-a55b-c78c1662c83c/16-9</image>
    <start>06:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Catelynn gets caught in a lie and faces losing her boyfriend Tyler. Amber's boyfriend Gary tells her he might leave her for another girl, and Maci tries to move into a shared house. (S2, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b46d545b-9ba5-43dc-91c4-faf8d54dfe7a/16-9</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Fresh Out</title>
    <desc>Becca Dudley returns with another episode of MTV Fresh Out; featuring the freshest videos, interviews and live performances. She's joined in the studio by KSI and rock star Damiano David. (S2, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/93ef5566-ce5e-4410-85ff-a176a807bac0/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Training Camp opens and many of the new candidates have had to uproot their lives and move to Dallas with no guarantee of making it through Training Camp. (S7, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/80b26146-4bbf-4da2-9d94-3fa589497cd1/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>It is just the second week of rehearsals and Kelli and Judy are quick to run the Training Camp Candidates through the signature moves. (S7, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a7dad07a-29cd-46f4-9efd-63a56da56756/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>The rookie candidates are brought in for their DCC makeover. Under the scrutiny of Kelli Finglass, new hairstyles and make up applications give the girls the DCC look. (S7, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/60e30875-a7ea-4b27-82b2-3ea5fb143428/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Kelli is out sick so Kitty Carter fills in and runs the first rehearsal of the week. Kitty has a no holds barred approach as she calls out several girls who have messy routines. (S7, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ee5d26d4-95d0-49c2-b00f-dc2f91fdef1a/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>A year after meeting \&quot;T-lights\&quot; on Instagram, \&quot;Instaceleb\&quot; Antoinette is ready to meet him, but he always brushes off the idea. Is he really the online celebrity he claims to be? (S3, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3fc479d0-e13b-41a6-be4c-70ac7098e155/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>In the first ever virtual Catfish episode, Nev and Kamie won't let quarantine stop them from helping love struck Jason find the dirt on his Insta-model Keith. (S8, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/4ae215c4-ee8d-4c86-a755-f69e4a09e3e6/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>John is ready to leave Detroit but one thing holds him back: Kelsey. The two have never spoken outside of online chats but John is sure she's the one. Can he include Kelsey in his plans? (S3, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/697f4888-7afa-4f5c-b22a-1f8942c8d037/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and Kamie receive an anonymous email from a whistleblower reporting a catfishing! But when our hosts arrive to help the named victim, they uncover a deeper conspiracy of deception. (S8, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/aabec852-451e-47c7-9a00-3a2c59486b30/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Jaylin is prepared to sacrifice a lifelong friendship and promising videogame career to be with a woman he's never even spoken to on the phone. (S5, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/44e76d56-9364-4de8-8210-41e1ec767092/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Aaliyah has been able to share her life struggles with Alicia. However, despite living only 70 blocks away, Alicia refuses to meet her as she hasn't come out to her friends and family yet. (S2, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7e6c5079-2e35-4a28-bee3-557d88af3f87/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>David is the only love Andria has ever known. Love letters and voice messages make Andria stay. But having never met after 10 years, she needs to know what he is hiding that keeps him away. (S4, ep24).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/09192f58-ae62-4841-b30a-e359c578a4a0/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and co-host Kamie Crawford help Mathan find Leah, a girl he's been talking to for a decade yet can never meet! But Leah has shocking secrets beyond their wildest imaginations. (S7, ep29).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/870b915a-6e4b-441f-b76c-dda205c95059/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ghosted</title>
    <desc>Rachel and Travis learn about Resee's complicated history with his friend Brendan, who vanished online after moving to a different town. (S1, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/bbe9270b-eef8-4425-a67c-6745240f6b25/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Hitman</title>
    <desc>An assassin teams up with a woman to help her find her father and uncover the mysteries of her ancestry.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a79b6075-93cd-45e7-91fc-276935078bde/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Caught In The Act</title>
    <desc>After three years, Sasha and Citi are planning their future and considering having a baby together. Recently Citi told Sasha to get back on birth control. (S3, ep19).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5e751eb5-792a-4a14-b377-888655b19315/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Plastic Surgery Knifemares</title>
    <desc>A firsthand account of so-called 'Botox Parties'. Martin, a lorry driver, faced financial ruin after eye bag surgery went wrong. (S1, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/65470a88-b609-4000-879f-50f8ac46ed7e/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Co-host popstar, Elle King joins Nev to help Nique find her Tumblr love, Alice. Digging deep leads to more questions than answers as Nev and Elle have concerns about who Alice could be. (S7, ep27).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/68c9b034-8a00-4b41-bfc5-b1e8de6934b5/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:50AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and NFL star Rashad Jennings help Deven find his mysterious online love James. James won't videochat yet he invites Deven to fly across the country to meet him! Deven needs answers. (S7, ep28).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a7f44f70-7ae9-4d57-a6ab-af3dae3446d9/16-9</image>
    <start>02:50AM</start>
    <finish>03:35AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>Chris Kirkpatrick shows us his cozy home in Nashville. Betsey Johnson gives us a look inside her colourfully curated Malibu trailer. Then MTV reunites with Jaime King at her home in LA. (S19, ep13).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/969acd68-5b02-4dd5-bf6e-1e80db685611/16-9</image>
    <start>03:35AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image//16-9</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>Actor Mena Suvari shows us her easy-breezy California bungalow. We cosplay with actor Anjali Bhimani at her LA crib. Fitness trainer Shaun T gives MTV a look inside his Arizona estate. (S19, ep22).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/9628ce63-70d6-3a4f-be43-23e4a3533d9d/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Ashley moves back in with her mum. Jade is relieved when Sean starts the drug treatment program. Lexi gets a peek at what her life might have been like when she visits a friend at college. (S1, ep24).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f8aa8410-e2cc-4c3b-9354-48dff3db04e2/16-9</image>
    <start>06:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Maci goes clubbing with friends for Valentine's Day. A crying baby and unrealistic expectations ruin Amber and Gary's romantic night. Farrah shares a big secret about her baby's dad. (S2, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/dc21e00d-ec42-46bc-9dfd-de9f51479026/16-9</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Amber and Gary's vacation shows there's no such thing as spring break once you have a baby. Maci butts heads with Ryan over his new girlfriend. Tyler is still angry with Catelynn. (S2, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2831007f-4caa-44eb-b082-3cb5c5330f05/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Over 600 excited and anxious Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders hopefuls arrive at Texas Stadium for the preliminary auditions. (S3, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/73bce623-a6ae-3a65-9c94-8d80cfc07306/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>In the finals audition, the competition really heats up. Now, surviving candidates must go head-to-head against experienced veteran cheerleaders for a coveted spot in the DCC Training Camp. (S3, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/57c6e048-c308-4855-af7b-b8074b2e8b09/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Training Camp begins! The newly elected training camp candidates are excited, even star struck, as they meet the veterans for the first time at Valley Ranch. (S3, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/bfa79e83-ba59-42b2-a753-7de38eeb773a/16-9</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and Max receive emails from opposite sides of the same online romance, each concerned that the other may be a catfish! What happens next leaves Nev and Max stunned! (S6, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/892f38b1-a926-4ab4-818b-8904e32ea49e/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Chitara took a big leap and came out to her family when she met Priscilla online, but Priscilla ended their relationship unexpectedly. Now Chitara is determined to find out what happened. (S4, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e96159cd-a87c-4a27-b26a-6229caafe66e/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev helps a lovestruck Navajo girl on her vision quest to find the Zuni man she loves, a man who not only admitted to being a drug smuggler but also claimed to have died. (S7, ep36).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/06fe6708-60a7-4dd8-b55f-97b8fb377a3f/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Brendan loves McKenna, but failed attempts to connect have left him wondering if McKenna is for real. Nev teams with social media sensation Karrueche Tran to help Brendan uncover the truth. (S5, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/0166b48e-6e87-406d-895d-b233917dbf91/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Alfred's thirsty to find Adonis, the man of his dreams. But as they dig for answers, word that Nev and Kamie are in town leads to the most explosive confrontation in Catfish history! (S8, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/79a3e217-126d-4ece-9409-f8494db86e3a/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Tracie Thoms had a connection with a fan named \&quot;Sammie\&quot; after hearing about the passing of Sammie's friend. Sammie suddenly disappeared and now Tracie is left wondering who Sammie really is? (S3, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e79b9b29-33e8-4102-86c4-de29a995c2cf/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Gabby was heartbroken when she discovered her online love Kendrick was killed! When Gabby's cousin suspects she's been mourning a fictional character, she calls in Nev and Kamie to help. (S8, ep56).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/60fcb818-33eb-44d2-a3b2-18e567a894bd/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>John has fallen for beauty Megan. But despite living an hour away, Megan keeps making excuses. John's best friend thinks she's lying, but could Megan actually be the love of his life? (S8, ep70).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/42fe4a19-0696-4145-a85e-02e09e95149c/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom UK</title>
    <desc>The Mums are back. Mia is in a rollercoaster new relationship while Sassi deals with heartbreak and loneliness. Amber struggles with a Threenager, while Chloe spies her dream home. (S9, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/bf3eec63-1516-451b-9b9b-4e3527d05ff9/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom UK</title>
    <desc>In London, Amber stays with the oldest mother of quads in the UK whilst Sassi searches for inner peace with a home schooling family from Dorsett. (S1, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/78e0b56a-d9a9-371f-8e37-7b08ce3800e5/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ex On The Beach</title>
    <desc>Becci is tired of being the fat sister while Kieran is sick of feeling like the runt of the litter. Can they transform their bodies in time to bare all in an Ex on the Beach reveal? (S1, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f0b62d24-ee58-3d9d-85e1-e2c571108547/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Skin A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Top dermatologists help members of the public with a range of skin conditions. (S3, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b80c828f-0523-42c3-8b4c-7c432fb1e033/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Rival Artists design head-to-head to please unhappy Canvases, but only one will receive a shot at redemption. Josh Hibbard and Kyle Dunbar, and brothers Robbie and Jayvo return. (S1, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/88d57533-64c5-48cb-bf0b-49da6b48f539/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
