<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Model Dallas has had his sights set on sexy Safari ever since she slid into his dms - but despite flirty promises, she won't meet. Nev and co-host Tallulah Willis begin a hunt for Safari. (S7, ep25).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/91c0e830-3b07-4524-9017-de7e0b77a261/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Tyreme met the beautiful Tomorrow online over 9 months ago. Tyreme is ready to uproot his life to be with her. Will Nev and Max be able help Tyreme finally meet his Tomorrow? (S5, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a7797379-56b8-46b6-9c6c-33dc0449c5c3/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom UK</title>
    <desc>A desperate Chloe tries sleep therapy, Amber feels broken by a bust car and smashed TV, and Ste tries to help. Mia's at loggerheads with Manley and Sassi is fuming with Darren and her mum. (S10, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/61af33b6-baa1-4450-aa49-557bfd01b9e9/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom UK</title>
    <desc>Angel's on a mission to find Matt and Whitney goes into labour. Isha's going out out but is feeling insecure about her body. Chloe lets Liz take EH out for the first time. (S1, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b179bb19-00aa-3e3d-8f39-fd2455ff5a7b/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and Kamie receive an anonymous email from a whistleblower reporting a catfishing! But when our hosts arrive to help the named victim, they uncover a deeper conspiracy of deception. (S8, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/af7174ef-37a0-445c-85d3-0746e936f761/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Caught In The Act</title>
    <desc>From a sporty family, Jasmine has always dreamed of taking her track talents all the way. But when she falls for her trainer, she wonders whether he's crossing the line with other clients. (S3, ep22).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/4ee7d0c1-7866-4c45-a275-327f8ea6b34f/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
