<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image//16-9</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>MTV spends the day with Nicole Scherzinger at her radiant Los Angeles crib, then Nashville lovebirds Jessie James Decker and Eric Decker give a tour of their Tennessee country ch?teau. (S19, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/da58bc79-fc13-4b07-b8cb-63d934e0a565/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:25AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Brianna and Danae need a place to stay, while Ashley also grapples with her living situation. Jade's parents are starting to wear out their welcome. (S1, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/09744b65-e237-47f7-9716-360ffdf0ff75/16-9</image>
    <start>06:25AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom 2</title>
    <desc>Jade's frustrations force her to break up with Sean. Kailyn tries to co-parent through the stress of virtual learning. Chelsea gets busier as COVID-19 numbers spike in South Dakota. (S10, ep16).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/6c4faee5-2a4e-4984-adb9-1ea6e42e92fc/16-9</image>
    <start>07:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom 2</title>
    <desc>Leah steps in when tensions between the twins boil over. Kailyn is forced to navigate the fallout of strong statements she made about Javi. (S10, ep17).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/86616760-c09f-4aa0-8747-e2bee26c302b/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom 2</title>
    <desc>Chelsea makes a difficult decision about her future. Leah withdraws Gracie from cheer in order to keep Ali safe. Jade deals with Sean's messes after he breaks her window. (S10, ep18).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/c72ed3f0-00f0-3f33-b088-5b323e501ba1/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom 2</title>
    <desc>Newest mum, Ashley, takes an anniversary trip with her boyfriend, Bar. Leah receives life altering news about her health. Kail says goodbye to her old house and bittersweet memories. (S10, ep22).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/6ddc6244-da7f-494f-8642-9622c8120bb9/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Joseph's been sending Sabrina money but his sister doesn't buy her lies and calls in Nev for some truth. What they discover is so shocking that they wonder if the lies will ever end. (S8, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/0c8b3bb1-a0a4-45f4-891b-45aa1e1ac178/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and Slick Woods investigate the mystery of Oceanna and her enigmatic, online stalker, Nelly. (S7, ep31).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f421d94b-be6b-467b-a956-d07a29a52949/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Shi is convinced Mira also lives in Philadelphia, but she's dodgy about meeting. When Nev and Kamie discover she might live just five blocks away, they hit the streets of Philly. (S8, ep83).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/bfa4fe7f-718f-3253-9cdd-2848771535d1/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Mandy is in love with a guy that gives her everything but the truth! Mandy's son has had enough and calls in Nev and Max. But following the clues only takes them deeper down the rabbit hole. (S7, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/c28a4c91-d8f6-432b-a10c-9bdd738b0c56/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>When Blaire's Instagram lover Markie broke her heart, she moved on. But now Markie is back and wants to meet. Blaire needs Nev and Max's help to make it happen and reveal Markie's secret. (S4, ep14).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/4dbf589a-75da-4915-8ec6-a5ee1558f2cc/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Max is back to help Zahra find a man she only knows by \&quot;T.\&quot; Zahra met T on a unique website, but their connection became romantic. Nev and Max re-join forces to take on this unique case! (S9, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/766b9801-72cf-3d04-b64b-53a2bc80e81c/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>After Jonathon's online love disappears, he enlists Nev and Max to help track him down. But when the guys discover a former catfish is involved, they begin to suspect Jonathon himself. (S6, ep13).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7ea02224-4c4a-417a-9476-2a835644e923/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Erika fell in love with Jermaine as he supported her through the toughest time in her life, but after 3 years of dating he's remained cagey about meeting. (S8, ep80).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/38e40a80-d8ec-39a2-9e3d-2d2c56c609e4/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Fresh Out</title>
    <desc>Fresh Out delivers the most important music and pop culture news of the week and beyond with artist interviews, in-studio performances, album drops and tour announcements. (S2, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/93ef5566-ce5e-4410-85ff-a176a807bac0/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Help! I'm In A Secret...</title>
    <desc>Relationship! Vivi met boyfriend Diontre on assignment. When the job ended, they were long distance. Diontre wants to live together, but Vivi hasn't met his circle and wants to know why. (S1, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/74c8d275-ca82-491f-92f2-2efba161639b/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Skin A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Thirty-seven-year-old Richard comes to the clinic with a large lipoma on the back of his neck, but when Dr Natalia goes in to remove it, she's astounded by what she finds. (S2, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/dc0f30fd-1f26-4fef-99c1-306d889c5477/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Resident Evil</title>
    <desc>Alice returns to The Hive in Raccoon City for a final showdown with the evil Umbrella Corp, who are preparing a devastating strike against the only remaining survivours of the apocalypse.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3f10900a-e67c-4495-a5de-edb68f6e8c00/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:10AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Lenny Kravitz</title>
    <desc>Brace yourself as we relive Lenny Kravitz's iconic MTV Unplugged! This episode of Unplugged was taped in New York City in April of 1994.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/51995d40-231d-4731-b112-e6a84305d807/16-9</image>
    <start>12:10AM</start>
    <finish>01:10AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>True Life Crime</title>
    <desc>True Life Crime investigates the case of Kenneka Jenkins who vanished from a party at a hotel in Chicago, after going live on Facebook. 24 hours later her body was found inside a freezer. (S1, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/35e9099a-45dc-402b-abb6-0ba17cc76d44/16-9</image>
    <start>01:10AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>The artists must tattoo former smokers who have been scarred for life, and the six remaining artists on Team Nunez battle for a spot in the team's top five. (S8, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2fc02e09-c9ff-3f3a-a4ca-1b6d1e68adae/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:45AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Celebrity Ex On The Beach</title>
    <desc>Anya fancies Kori, but is Kori over Sofie? A new celeb tickles someone's fancy, the OG's of the villa have a tough decision to make and a Gay Pride party reveals a surprise pot of gold. (S2, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5a3252ba-14d9-48a6-b355-f93b62b570a2/16-9</image>
    <start>02:45AM</start>
    <finish>03:35AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>Travis Mills invites us into his trendy bachelor pad, then we get some family time with Marsai Martin, ending with Christian Siriano's glamourous glass house. (S18, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/747373df-134a-4bc4-92a6-d2dbc60b9a09/16-9</image>
    <start>03:35AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image//16-9</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>Power couple Don Benjamin and Liane V take us on a tour of their California crib. Rapper Bleu shows off his Georgia estate. Then, we visit singer and legend Charo's Spanish Colonial Casa. (S19, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5eb5780a-1592-442d-82d2-5b0e386ffa31/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:25AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Brianna and Danae move in with Danae's mum. Jade's family plans a dinner. Kayla helps Stephan when he needs a place to stay. Ashley tries to mend her relationship with her mum. (S1, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/486bd831-eae4-4063-8dc4-c0e8923e2f14/16-9</image>
    <start>06:25AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Just Tattoo Of Us</title>
    <desc>Mum and daughter besties Clare and Chloe put motherly love to the test. Girlfriends Shai and Abbie put their future on the line. And Geordie Shore's Beau dishes up some brotherly banter. (S5, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/30fa472e-cce2-41be-8824-747efce4ed17/16-9</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Just Tattoo Of Us</title>
    <desc>Love fills the air as Geordie Shore's Thalia and mum Vanessa get inked. All's not well for Liam and Amber. Will jokers Hollie and Chelsea see the funny side of their tattoos? (S5, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/80ebba31-d033-401b-b1d0-4dee6e69b000/16-9</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Just Tattoo Of Us</title>
    <desc>Tattoo virgin Kieran trusts his best friend Dan. Jess and Paige reveal some hard truths. Squabbling siblings Tanya and Gemma try to mend their relationship, with tattoos. (S5, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5fee3560-a58a-4af0-bdb4-f09c9ec539a1/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>In just the second week of rehearsals, the first cuts of a training camp loom. A few select veterans in training camp are sent to film a segment for Good Morning America. (S5, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/c689feb5-00b6-4216-90f8-2ac72f1f6271/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Week four of training camp begins with the rookie candidates getting their DCC \&quot;Makeovers.\&quot; (S5, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3ca6e750-5510-46ca-9ca4-1c1746cb11e5/16-9</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>The end of training camp is approaching and DCC Cameo Photos are on the schedule. The Candidates and Veterans are readied for their close-ups dressed in their fitted DCC uniform. (S5, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/adcaeb44-ebab-4dad-9ac9-8bd4df42a095/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>The Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders 2010 squad must be announced in the next two days. It's no secret it is crunch time and the pressure is relentless for the Training Camp Candidates. (S5, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7e27535b-4843-47cf-a7f7-1bf70a59f726/16-9</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>A day of celebration and joy is dampened by the fact that the director and choreographer of the Dallas Cowboy Cheerleaders have yet to officially announce the 2010 squad. (S5, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/49512fc8-50c6-415e-ab53-e16f33d8cf84/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Cowboys Stadium in Arlington, Texas is once again the venue for the Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders auditions. Five hundred candidates with dreams of making the DCC team arrive before sunrise. (S6, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b0a0ce78-7e87-316b-a801-b2112ab028ce/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Mohammed connected online with Ashley. He's developed strong feelings, but she keeps avoiding meeting up. Mohammed calls in the Catfish crew, but Nev and Kamie have upsetting news! (S8, ep97).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e38195cc-7850-352c-8e07-f4999d7b5d18/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Gabby was heartbroken when she discovered her online love Kendrick was killed! When Gabby's cousin suspects she's been mourning a fictional character, she calls in Nev and Kamie to help. (S8, ep56).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/60fcb818-33eb-44d2-a3b2-18e567a894bd/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Cristian fell hard for livestreamer Chantel, but on her live, she never shows her face! With Chantel evading Cristian, Nev and Kamie come up with a clever plan to get them to meet. (S9, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e8a248cb-d97b-3a76-bb47-d3779dd0bd39/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Solana wants to take her relationship with her boyfriend to the next level but she can't stop thinking about her online love Elijah. But Solana has to know if the online persona is real. (S3, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2540ca68-8a47-4ee1-bfc0-8ac12cee49a5/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Single father Felipe is ready to settle down with Jasmine. However, the two have been talking online for eight months and have never met. Max returns and joins Nev to investigate. (S4, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/50004449-646e-48eb-a8cb-accfa6ac20e5/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>In the first ever virtual Catfish episode, Nev and Kamie won't let quarantine stop them from helping love struck Jason find the dirt on his Insta-model Keith. (S8, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2aa50460-d540-487a-8963-8526630121a2/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Tyreme met the beautiful Tomorrow online over 9 months ago. Tyreme is ready to uproot his life to be with her. Will Nev and Max be able help Tyreme finally meet his Tomorrow? (S5, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/394d3507-eda4-431e-b529-3e79e899748c/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev helps a lovestruck Navajo girl on her vision quest to find the Zuni man she loves, a man who not only admitted to being a drug smuggler but also claimed to have died. (S7, ep36).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5bdc573d-6d54-3a97-af75-bc00b6cdf36f/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ghosted</title>
    <desc>Rachel and Travis help an aspiring New York stand-up track down the professed love of his life, but she may have had a good reason for ghosting him after six months. (S1, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/c1aaa4cc-0db3-489b-8a22-24fb56970b4a/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dating Naked UK</title>
    <desc>Ten singles fed up with the world of dating take their pursuit of love to a brave new level. Stripping off completely, they dive into a daring new dating experience in tropical paradise. (S1, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/6813c096-5069-3192-a1fa-d67845267415/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dating Naked UK</title>
    <desc>The first Naked Newbie wastes no time threatening connections. While some relationships grow, others' heads begin to turn, creating tensions before one dater is dumped for good. (S1, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ecec17b5-6cbc-3afa-bb44-214793f54c08/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dating Naked UK</title>
    <desc>After the first dumping, daters are still seeking connections. With some relationships severed, the way is paved for new ones to grow. A game of Dare or Bare leaves one dater with regrets. (S1, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5679f129-6923-380c-959c-db63add421dd/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dating Naked UK</title>
    <desc>Sparks fly as jealousy and competition build. And while one couple takes their connection to the next level, cast is doubt on another. Before a dramatic twist at the dumping ground. (S1, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/1fd2aa77-90d6-3464-93c6-9678756f57c3/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dating Naked UK</title>
    <desc>After the shock of the dumping ground, two daters struggle to adjust. A fancy dress party delivers a special naked treat and too much tongue action pushes one pair to breaking point. (S1, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/30e537bb-59e3-3a2f-9aa9-f5a053056e1d/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:45AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and co-host Jane Carrey help aspiring sugarbaby Mike choose between his LA life of leisure and his affection for the mysterious Joey, a broke mechanic he fell in love with on Grindr. (S7, ep19).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/c2f045dd-1daf-40f9-883a-fe8f03a1a809/16-9</image>
    <start>02:45AM</start>
    <finish>03:35AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>Keep your shoes on while we check out Scott Disick's Calabasas mansion, then travel to the Valley with Chanel West Coast, and then we travel across the pond to Stefflon Don's Essex Manor. (S18, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/6e67bc81-f384-4656-8bc4-0f8f480afd76/16-9</image>
    <start>03:35AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image//16-9</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>MTV Cribs US</title>
    <desc>Adrienne Bailon and husband Israel Houghton show off their Beverly Hills bungalow, a.k.a. Villa Houghton, and we touch down at NFL legend Michael Strahan's epic New Jersey hideaway. (S19, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a9833952-7ec3-44f7-b76c-69460a3521cd/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:25AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Lexi takes steps to move on from Kyler. Kayla is caught between her mum and Stephan. Ashley and Bar move into a new place. Jade questions if she and Sean are meant to be. (S1, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/0551ee6b-9d96-49af-9dbd-4c4031980b28/16-9</image>
    <start>06:25AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Just Tattoo Of Us</title>
    <desc>Lateysha Grace joins Charlotte to wrap up the series. Irish twins Simone and Olivia brew up some trouble. Will brothers-in-law Brandon and Ryan start a family feud? (S5, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e09de284-9432-4edf-bbad-d7410a62ebba/16-9</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Fresh Out</title>
    <desc>Fresh Out delivers the most important music and pop culture news of the week and beyond with artist interviews, in-studio performances, album drops and tour announcements. (S2, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/93ef5566-ce5e-4410-85ff-a176a807bac0/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Tensions run high for the 69 new girls as the 18 returning DCC veterans join the competition for a coveted invitation to training camp. (S6, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/014203c4-b225-4af9-bd62-16625ab5301f/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>The stress for the newly selected training camp candidates is evident as they struggle to re-arrange their schedules and secure new living arrangements in Dallas. (S6, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f8f9cac4-1dce-4472-b46a-2be3abbc723c/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>It's two weeks into training camp, and Kelli and Judy are fixing to make their first cuts. This week the girls are expected to master the world famous DCC kick line and jump split. (S6, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/33a3677c-23da-47f3-96f5-3d5677450751/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>It's week three and the rookie candidates are brought in for their DCC \&quot;Makeovers.\&quot; They're given a new look with a hair and make-up revamp and are transformed in the DCC mold. (S6, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/31609dee-da13-408b-be43-27268465386e/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Kim's been pouring her heart out to Matt for over 10 years. Now, Kim's facing a life-changing decision - should she marry her current boyfriend or find out if Matt is her soul mate? (S1, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7233e17c-1657-4851-90db-fd9e9a357272/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Aaliyah is saving herself for model Jaquan, a guy she's dating exclusively but has never met. As Nev and Kamie dig into his story, they become alarmed that Aaliyah's getting played! (S8, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ec2e6f74-b7cb-41cf-aec1-bd369ab2ed58/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Lauren met Derek online years ago. Derek is caring, supporting Lauren after she had a baby with a former boyfriend. Lauren thinks Derek could be the one, so why has he avoided meeting her? (S2, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/39768121-8f53-4c9b-a19d-b24b516706c5/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and co-host Tallulah Willis help Chelsea, a young woman who's fallen for a reality TV star. But digging for the truth only reveals Chelsea has her own secrets. Will she lose everything? (S7, ep22).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7b9c72cd-8b96-439b-9b01-3cac8f78283d/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Southern sweetheart Kelsie is madly in love with her online Romeo, Brandon. But after years of endless excuses about meeting up, Kelsie recruits Nev and Max to find who Brandon really is. (S6, ep14).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/02409050-383f-4126-8169-654d07fff5db/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Whitney met Brenell on an LGBT website four years ago and is head-over-heels in love. Brenell refuses to video chat with her, and Whitney is desperate to know why. Nev and Max investigate. (S4, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/bfbd8ea1-7dac-4b23-8e63-1fa9824b2be0/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Dylan's fallen for a beautiful model with an elusive secret. With all the standard red flags, Nev and Max assume it's an open and shut case, but the truth is stranger than fiction. (S7, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2da180bc-69cf-45e5-8c0a-fa3120c40917/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>When Zak met Garret online he fell hard, but curious disappearances have Zak worried about who he really fell in love with. Will Nev and Max find Garret before he vanishes for good? (S7, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/69f83f9d-ecdc-43d7-a235-2395bf653600/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Jade helps Briana's surgery recovery and is shocked by a potential pregnancy. Ali discusses the challenges of having a disability. Ashley gets support from a domestic violence advocate. (S2, ep31).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/bed4a1ec-3cdb-4d3f-b448-c3e4c44ff56d/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dating Naked UK</title>
    <desc>A naked newbie shakes up the villa dynamic, as he catches the attention of several female daters. Leylah seizes the opportunity for a steamy cabana date with the boy of her choice. (S1, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/80b7f338-d13d-3b97-ae78-733854b629fb/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
