<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Revenge</title>
    <desc>Brooklyn needs answers about her elusive online ex Jason so she can move on. But Nev and Kamie dig up drama in Brooklyn's dating past that may connect Jason to someone she already knows! (S8, ep20).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/48eecb1b-d622-4f8e-9a4f-b501e8f94a59/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Revenge</title>
    <desc>Jasmine has been texting with Mike for two years and thinks he could be the perfect step-father for her son. Although they live only 15 minutes apart, the pair have yet to meet up in person. (S1, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/76f427be-2cb5-458a-94dd-164dc664f40d/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Revenge</title>
    <desc>Justin Combs and Nev set out to help Cherie uncover Avion's identity, a mysterious stranger who contacted the 26-year-old sales rep after he bought a gadget from her. (S7, ep39).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5f835f9b-7036-4a1e-b42d-7b8d4cc9a3b7/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Revenge</title>
    <desc>Danny is intent on building a life with his online love, despite her violent past. But when he enlists Nev and Max to help him meet her, they discover she may have ties to a former Catfish! (S6, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a9724017-e37c-4f8e-bf3c-a216965bb7f8/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Revenge</title>
    <desc>After being Catfished by her best friend, Larissa turned to online pal Anthony for support. Feelings between them grew, but after some suspicious moves, Larissa is worried he is also lying. (S5, ep14).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/cd55ec64-957f-4567-9431-fe4cdf67dd7b/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Revenge</title>
    <desc>After Jonathon's online love disappears, he enlists Nev and Max to help track him down. But when the guys discover a former catfish is involved, they begin to suspect Jonathon himself. (S6, ep13).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/0c36e0f4-36b7-45cc-8a3d-5b7ede55c07a/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Revenge</title>
    <desc>Jasmine writes to Nev and Max asking for help for a \&quot;friend\&quot;. But they're perplexed when Jasmine drops a bombshell revelation: they've helped her friend before! (S6, ep19).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/19a31765-390c-4cb0-bac1-b7bc1a4b088b/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish Revenge</title>
    <desc>Paris enlists Nev and Max to help her figure out who has been catfishing her for the past four years. But as the guys investigate, they make a shocking discovery. (S5, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/dd4b3b58-be99-4d0c-9aa6-0c6300d147ba/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Amber's daughter, Leah, sends a message. Mackenzie learns her twins' gender. Ashley fights for custody of Holly. A surprise pregnancy shocks one of the mums. (S2, ep32).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/523ecb84-f335-4569-9d1b-442b91890079/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Unhappy Canvases return for a chance at a new tattoo and, unknown to them, their original artist awaits for a shot at redemption. In this episode, Tim Lees and ES face hostile canvases. (S1, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b055225f-4ad3-46a3-b0f6-38955fca29d8/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Mystical Mike and Don are back for redemption, but egos collide when they must tag team with a fan favourite. (S1, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/69270e3f-1701-41fc-8fda-ac04f205a9dc/16-9</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
