<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>After years of hot drama, Gemini is desperate to find Myranda. But the script flips with the first intervention ever for an infamous repeat catfish! (S8, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/52116277-2493-4619-a829-b9e69993ac13/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Luis has fallen for a single mum, and now he's ready to take their online relationship to the next level. But first Nev and Max must help him make sure that she is who she says she is! (S5, ep19).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/cb741ce6-8910-4f74-986f-7d689d7c0d22/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Ciatta has a bright family future planned with Juan. But before Nev and Kamie give their blessings on Ciatta's move to LA , they uncover details that put her life plans into question. (S8, ep94).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/8756b015-c775-4124-a6a7-0254293dbd19/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Iris is stunningly beautiful and a nerd too! Omar thought he had found the perfect girl, but when Nev and Kamie arrive to help Omar, they've got concerns. Is Iris as perfect as she seems? (S9, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3282d20c-6ac6-446f-b354-63c190c1ca34/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Kitty comes to a rehearsal and stirs thing up. The new candidates bond, then are judged as they perform at a mock appearance. Travis Wall comes to town. (S13, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e1c26a30-e8f0-4bba-a35c-9ea9b3d5da05/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Candidates hit the football field for the first time as Judy teaches them the DCC entrance. If a candidate can't pick it up quickly, she will be cut! (S13, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/632532ff-750a-4b8b-a16b-1d2ad9d3a6a0/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom 2</title>
    <desc>Jo confronts Kailyn about dating Jordan, Leah continues planning for her wedding, Jenelle and Kieffer hatch a plan to run off and things between Chelsea and Adam go downhill. (S1, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/25e77167-1b1f-49dd-b9e8-2f4c8cc5c78c/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Laguna Beach</title>
    <desc>It's spring break in Cabo and anything can happen, especially when LC, Stephen and Kristin are staying at the same hotel. And how will LC react when Kristin and Stephen fall out? (S1, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a5d998ba-45a3-36d1-91e9-def9d3fce8bc/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Laguna Beach</title>
    <desc>The clique hit San Diego for a Blink 182 concert, where the atmosphere is still tense after the scandalous events of spring break. (S1, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/05c72b71-b301-3478-9b3a-fccda19895bc/16-9</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Rich Kids Go Skint</title>
    <desc>Eighteen-year-old Rendall is used to getting everything she wants. Now, the home-schooled social media influencer mucks in helping car mechanic Tony and his family. (S4, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/69f8ae4a-f21f-4321-9a65-ee51c1e9b6fc/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Help! I'm In A Secret...</title>
    <desc>Relationship! Gary and Giselle have been together for two years and have a six-month-old baby girl. Gary wants to marry Giselle, but she's started hiding Gary and he needs to know why. (S2, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7ef07b12-a182-31e1-a66c-8dad177cd98e/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>Pauly and Nikki play matchmaker for Vinny. Snooki and Sammi arrive in Jamaica. Things go sideways when Angelina confronts Lauren. (S8, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7e251e16-d87f-4276-bab2-f48dd4832624/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Challenge</title>
    <desc>TJ throws a huge spanner in the players' plans, making the game even more difficult. Two challengers get hot and heavy. The elimination sees the first head banger of the season. (S41, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/df0dc4a2-9107-4217-bd45-80050261e4a7/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Love &amp; Hip Hop Atlanta</title>
    <desc>Karlie tries to figure out life after lock up. Mendeecees finally gives his side of the Frost's story. Sierra's Mum turns a happy announcement about her growing family into a growing pain. (S13, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/bc49e9da-b81f-4a9f-961b-daac1b1a3c15/16-9</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>Anthony Michaels returns to avenge his season ten team by beating bold and brash strategist Josh Payne. Ash Mann confronts former teammate Alexis Kovacs to settle the score with honour. (S1, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/23d99db3-4561-4630-b5cc-b3e88bc4136f/16-9</image>
    <start>01:30AM</start>
    <finish>02:25AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>It's predator vs prey when two epic Ink Master feuds come to a head. Angel Rose fights back against her Season 11 thorn Jimmy Snaz. Season 10's Sparks returns to burn rival Jason Elliott. (S1, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e3229c2e-a6e0-40d0-824f-877360707eb1/16-9</image>
    <start>02:25AM</start>
    <finish>03:10AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Caught In The Act</title>
    <desc>Ruby and Johnny found a common interest in photography but Ruby feels like Johnny isn't as focused on her as he should be. (S2, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3d8b7062-6c71-3035-b3a7-d65e41b909f7/16-9</image>
    <start>03:10AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image//16-9</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Hills</title>
    <desc>Lauren and Lo plan to buy a house and are looking into the real estate market. Meanwhile, Audrina reconsiders her situation as a single woman and Heidi tries to talk to Lauren again! (S3, ep25).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/dbd267cd-1bc2-4063-b27f-4c5267ccc31b/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:25AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>After a shotgun wedding, Brooke and Cody are forced to sacrifice car racing for parenthood. Now they're trying to balance high school life and moving in to their own place. (S2, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b1fe9f19-7f2c-43c6-92f5-d9e6c4691702/16-9</image>
    <start>06:25AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Catelynn and Tyler test Vaeda for an Individualized Education Program. Khesanio's mum meets Mackenzie's kids. Jade finds a private school for Kloie while Briana seeks help through Al-anon. (S2, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7141961d-e7ff-3c72-b969-35aaa3f1708c/16-9</image>
    <start>07:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>After months of intimate texts with Titus, a man she met online, Candice has decided to tell to her husband. But before she does, she asks Nev to help her find out who Titus really is! (S5, ep16).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5430624a-b53d-41f9-9153-b1f84b293dd6/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>After a number of near-death experiences, Lawrence survived through it all with the assurance of Cierra's online love. But with Cierra blowing Lawrence off, Nev and Max must find the truth. (S7, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f902dc4b-90d7-4654-9d63-056206d68025/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Solana wants to take her relationship with her boyfriend to the next level but she can't stop thinking about her online love Elijah. But Solana has to know if the online persona is real. (S3, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/8a9f722c-350e-4eb8-a673-0d775ac23d35/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Dorion is about to give up everything for online love Jeszica, including his relationship with girlfriend Raffinee. But first he wants to know, is Jeszica really the girl in the pictures? (S2, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ef6e856e-8572-413e-ad64-c64dd3fca275/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Vince's online-ex, Alyssa, is stalking him. This caused real life girlfriend, Liz, to break up with him. Nev and Max help Vince confront Alyssa so he can try to salvage a future with Liz. (S5, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/1d9bfce0-2bcc-4346-8cc8-18cf5e3430e1/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>When Kristina met Faith in a chatroom, she didn't intend to fall in love and betray her real-life fianc?. Now Nev and co-host Tallulah Willis navigate a treacherous love triangle. (S7, ep30).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/dcfbb562-fed2-47d6-b00a-837a14bf93a8/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nick struggled to meet other gay men until he met England! But this perfect match turns sour when a weird \&quot;business\&quot; trip has Nick thinking England's work might be more than meets the eye. (S8, ep62).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b3ee2b7b-a2c4-467a-a67e-7ada140b336b/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Victoria calls on Catfish to help her meet the fine man that she's been chatting with for eight years! But what Nev and Kamie uncover chills Victoria to the bone. (S8, ep61).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/6f03f9f5-98d0-4a2f-8e69-67091f2355d5/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Candidates take their publicity photo. Being photogenic is a must. You either take a good photo or not. Kelli puts the ladies through media training. (S13, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/6bb0fd34-4bee-408e-bd0c-8a4f9a94123c/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Michael Jackson dancer, Marcea Lane comes to town to shake things up. The candidates learn how to rejuvenate. The swim suit calendar covers are revealed at a special event. (S13, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a8b49216-7182-4828-ba0e-99ddf046ba32/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom 2</title>
    <desc>Things between Leah and Corey turn ugly, Chelsea decides to celebrate her break-up, Jenelle's plans start to crumble and Kailyn settles into life at her mum's house. (S1, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/8e38d923-537e-48b4-8049-6553830425b7/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Laguna Beach</title>
    <desc>It's prom time, and all the girls get invited in the most romantic of ways. But Kristen has a secret admirer. will she be tempted away from Stephen by this new guy's advances? (S1, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/c6fcf4e1-df34-3229-b8cc-16ebde8ec7ad/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Laguna Beach</title>
    <desc>The Laguna kids are going camping at Catalina, but it's not all fun and games when the park ranger tells them that, due to a drought, bears may come into the camp looking for water! (S1, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/17febefa-d601-30c8-ae92-1d2c06b61606/16-9</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish UK</title>
    <desc>Leanne is desperate to find out if online love Jamie is her Mr Right. After cancelling on her numerous times, Leanne wants Oobah and Nella to investigate and finally bring them face to face. (S2, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5e5ab179-5bdb-4f3b-b688-b6480404248e/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Skin A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Top dermatologists help members of the public with a range of skin conditions. (S3, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2ed4ba76-deda-48d7-be6a-57c00080f04b/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Lindsay Lohan's Beach Club</title>
    <desc>Disappointed in the performance of the team's first work day, Lindsay calls a meeting to question the group's intentions, leading Aristotle to voice concerns about Brent's offensive antics. (S1, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/df2101cb-0670-435e-834a-692d48eeecf2/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Shakira</title>
    <desc>Latin pop superstar Shakira's acclaimed Unplugged performance &amp; subsequent 2000 live album earned her first Grammy Award.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/04ee0d12-b6d1-4ede-9870-d6aaf813571f/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Behind the Music</title>
    <desc>Christina Aguilera shares her journey from Mouseketeer to trailblazing pop diva. She overcame abuse and mental health struggles and found happiness in music and family. (S1, ep26).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/0637c9dc-1915-432c-849a-a4f504d10e0a/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>It's a battle of egos as season twelve's Cam Pohl and Pon put their versatility to the test. And it's style vs style as season eleven's Tim Stafford clashes with Kyle Mackenzie. (S1, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/8764f24d-c756-4210-ba1b-2260b45aee7b/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>Egos collide when season nine's Dane Smith calls out Ink Master veteran Christian Buckingham to prove that talent knows no age. Jeremy Brown battles coach Steve Tefft for respect. (S1, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/9c892054-ae1c-475b-8b5b-dd009ecc5ae3/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:45AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Caught In The Act</title>
    <desc>Before moving forward with intensive fertility treatments, suspicious lover Star wants to make sure her much younger boyfriend Ricky is committed to her and their future child. (S2, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b8c27a77-297a-3f23-b1df-f81cbbafb08d/16-9</image>
    <start>02:45AM</start>
    <finish>03:35AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Hills</title>
    <desc>Tension arises when Stephanie Pratt and Lauren find themselves in the same class at fashion school. Meanwhile, Whitney tries to impress her new boss in New York. (S3, ep21).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/931d6f43-a0cb-4e9d-ade5-66ffc239d6ff/16-9</image>
    <start>03:35AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image//16-9</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Hills</title>
    <desc>The girls go out to find a new home. When they do finally find one, the guest list for the housewarming party may be subject to more than one argument. (S3, ep26).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/668d61d6-efa0-4c02-8fed-8977a35d5f7e/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:25AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Hills</title>
    <desc>While Lo and Lauren enjoy living at the house, Audrina feels more and more left out. Meanwhile, Stephanie thinks it time to get rid of Spencer and Heidi. (S3, ep27).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/34e2c2b5-2425-4bca-93e8-726c2271fd1b/16-9</image>
    <start>06:25AM</start>
    <finish>06:45AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Friendzone</title>
    <desc>Franklin likes everything about his friend Erica but she doesn't know that he's had a crush on her for five years. Now he's ready to open his heart to her. (S1, ep20).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/77953f27-8b05-43b9-b4a6-d6c58bbd160b/16-9</image>
    <start>06:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>The youngest of five, Felicia's the only one in her family with a shot at graduating. But when it gets tough with her boyfriend and she leaves home, will she be forced to drop out? (S2, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5ff596a2-6209-4269-8b16-fada24404396/16-9</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom OG</title>
    <desc>Amber celebrates Easter but is disappointed when another scandal comes out about Matt. Catelynn and Tyler find their dream home while Farrah makes an effort to get to know her mum's fiance. (S6, ep26).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/bf70d0a4-b9a3-49d4-9220-4d58c77c5e21/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:55AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom OG</title>
    <desc>While on vacation in Key West, Farrah and her mum's fiance argue over their lack of respect for each other. Catelynn and Tyler's offer on their dream home is accepted. Maci confronts Ryan. (S6, ep27).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ec534f32-45b8-44d7-b9ea-baf1f4389731/16-9</image>
    <start>08:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom OG</title>
    <desc>Amber loses her cool with Ryan's wife. Maci wants Ryan to complete rehab. Catelynn worries about Tyler's dad since he's off parole. Farrah celebrates her birthday in New York. (S7, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/38e192aa-8c34-4fab-bb0a-81c32ca4616a/16-9</image>
    <start>10:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>The new candidates get an eye-opening taste of what it means to be a DCC; girls struggle to learn the dances; Melissa Rycroft meets the new girls for the first time. (S11, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/533ff081-6ed0-469c-befe-b616b69bbbb1/16-9</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>With the first cut looming, the girls must push their dance skills to the limit. Stress increases on makeover day as the girls try to get the DCC look. (S11, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e5805686-9e53-4ee4-9f2e-75fa2aa249a8/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Trina is a dancer who always had trouble meeting trustworthy guys, until she met Scorpio, a fellow dancer, online. Will Trina finally get to rendezvous with the only man she's ever loved? (S1, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2afe6a38-863d-439d-b8ae-11e582bc84f9/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Kim's been pouring her heart out to Matt for over 10 years. Now, Kim's facing a life-changing decision - should she marry her current boyfriend or find out if Matt is her soul mate? (S1, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2c9dded9-d259-40ba-8225-0868657f41ac/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Jasmine has been texting with Mike for two years and thinks he could be the perfect step-father for her son. Although they live only 15 minutes apart, the pair have yet to meet up in person. (S1, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3a45536e-adc8-4777-8ab4-4d8e2b875ae3/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Jarrod never thought he'd find love until he fell for Abby on Facebook. Jarrod thinks Abby could be \&quot;the one\&quot;, but she's refusing to see him. What is Abby hiding? (S1, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/efeae119-1882-4256-b178-d30a419567b2/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>In this episode we meet Kya and Alyx, who fell in love quickly after meeting online. Are they being honest with each other? Hosts Nev Schulman and Max Joseph investigate. (S1, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e58b6407-36ec-4e77-b3f9-ebae721db6ee/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Joe was sceptical when Miss Teen USA, Kari, sent him a friend request. Now, after months of communication, Joe thinks it might be the real deal, and he might have found love with her. (S1, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/aed8de83-cbab-4d3d-8c56-e33111c491e1/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>After a year and a half of chatting with her online, Tyler thinks he may have a future with Amanda. But are Tyler's friends correct because they suspect that something isn't right? (S1, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/c7aaed5e-2e17-4215-8ced-8ebd160e1245/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Mike and Felicia met online and soon hit it off. After agreeing to meet, Felicia stood Mike up, offering only thin excuses. Can Mike trust Felicia - or will he end up disappointed? (S1, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f4c86067-a399-4f1f-9f52-3b90b667338f/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>In a Redemption first, Runner-Up Master Canvases defend their tattoos against the Artists who defeated them. Cleen Rock One, Anthony Michaels, Jime Litwalk and Joey Hamilton return. (S3, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/90a7049d-52c0-4e1b-a064-abcba02ee0b3/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Season 5 Artist Julia Carlson is back for another shot at Redemption with not one, not two, but three unhappy Canvases. (S3, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5be6b66e-7dd6-4d7b-b0a2-8e4ec116754d/16-9</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
