<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and co-host Tallulah Willis help Chelsea, a young woman who's fallen for a reality TV star. But digging for the truth only reveals Chelsea has her own secrets. Will she lose everything? (S7, ep22).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7b9c72cd-8b96-439b-9b01-3cac8f78283d/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Southern sweetheart Kelsie is madly in love with her online Romeo, Brandon. But after years of endless excuses about meeting up, Kelsie recruits Nev and Max to find who Brandon really is. (S6, ep14).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/02409050-383f-4126-8169-654d07fff5db/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Whitney met Brenell on an LGBT website four years ago and is head-over-heels in love. Brenell refuses to video chat with her, and Whitney is desperate to know why. Nev and Max investigate. (S4, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/bfbd8ea1-7dac-4b23-8e63-1fa9824b2be0/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Dylan's fallen for a beautiful model with an elusive secret. With all the standard red flags, Nev and Max assume it's an open and shut case, but the truth is stranger than fiction. (S7, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2da180bc-69cf-45e5-8c0a-fa3120c40917/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>When Zak met Garret online he fell hard, but curious disappearances have Zak worried about who he really fell in love with. Will Nev and Max find Garret before he vanishes for good? (S7, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/69f83f9d-ecdc-43d7-a235-2395bf653600/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Jade helps Briana's surgery recovery and is shocked by a potential pregnancy. Ali discusses the challenges of having a disability. Ashley gets support from a domestic violence advocate. (S2, ep31).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/bed4a1ec-3cdb-4d3f-b448-c3e4c44ff56d/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dating Naked UK</title>
    <desc>A naked newbie shakes up the villa dynamic, as he catches the attention of several female daters. Leylah seizes the opportunity for a steamy cabana date with the boy of her choice. (S1, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/80b7f338-d13d-3b97-ae78-733854b629fb/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
