<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfishing Long Distance</title>
    <desc>Apryl fell for artist Daryl after years of him courting her by drawing portraits of Apryl. Suspecting the art of deception, Nev and Kamie fear this case is going from sketches to sketchy! (S8, ep37).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7d177625-3079-4d69-abe3-869ac8e39b63/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfishing Long Distance</title>
    <desc>After being Catfished by her best friend, Larissa turned to online pal Anthony for support. Feelings between them grew, but after some suspicious moves, Larissa is worried he is also lying. (S5, ep14).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3fd42e18-0b6d-4f2f-bca7-1bed388cf08a/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfishing Long Distance</title>
    <desc>Alexis and Jaymes have been there for each other for 5 years. When Nev and Kamie uncover Jaymes may have a guy on the side, it leaves Alexis wondering who she's really fallen in love with! (S8, ep43).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/1fc12290-b795-3c15-b8df-69d0c6e84810/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfishing Long Distance</title>
    <desc>Dianela fled her home in Venezuela to start a new life with Jos?, a man she's been in a relationship with but has never met! Nev and Kamie tackle this mystery to get Dianela answers. (S8, ep19).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b2a7a10a-7c36-4c8e-925c-77df51053747/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfishing Long Distance</title>
    <desc>Zark's been dating Roger for two years, but on videochat, Roger will only show the bottom half of his face. A shocking discovery leads Nev and Kamie to question Roger's intentions. (S8, ep45).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/751312ce-7e25-4f27-9a50-dda4372865fb/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom UK</title>
    <desc>Sassi launches 'Sassi's Salon'. Chloe decides she wants to be a midwife but Jordan has doubts. Megan finds out a secret about Dylan. Shannon lets her insecurities get the better of her. (S6, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ca825584-e942-427b-878c-0ab4a6b2e602/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Rich Kids Go Skint</title>
    <desc>Rich kids share homes with families living on the breadline. (S3, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/baf3908b-9c35-4f4b-a645-b78355758e4c/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Maci, Cate, Tyler, Leah, and Gary reunite in NYC with their teens to celebrate 16 years of Teen Mom. Cate finds her place without Carly. Back home, Amber works through trauma with her mum. (S2, ep29).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b4b7f7b9-4bdc-42e0-8c32-f49461969181/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dating Naked UK</title>
    <desc>Two familiar faces return and are hell bent on reclaiming their connections. The daters engage in a steamy reverse strip tease, an intimate game that brings new desires to the surface. (S1, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3731b296-26dc-3971-be64-95776fcd5163/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
