<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo and Rocsi Diaz roll strikes in 'people bowling', fire off 'board bullets' and work up their appetite for 'living snacks'. (S39, ep33).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/497f81ba-e139-420f-b2c9-315d1672f182/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ridiculousness</title>
    <desc>Rob, Steelo, and Karrueche Tran watch some bros get diagnosed with 'dude doctors', get caught off guard by some 'unexpected interruptions', and check out people who are 'pool partied out'. (S39, ep32).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/341cba20-35bb-42e6-9dc4-f596981bdca8/16-9</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>The Artists must compose an incredible work of art that's completely invisible in the Flash Challenge. One Artist gets caught in the splash zone and is sent packing. (S11, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7ff2101c-941e-4e27-b58f-25801bf4d169/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>The tools are hot but the Competition is on fire as the Artists battle for control in the Flash Challenge. The battle heats up for $100K and the title of Ink Master. (S11, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/27e2eb51-9493-4d0e-b44e-dad1afc290a2/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:45AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Love At First Lie</title>
    <desc>The couples discuss their sex lives during a chat which leads to speculation about who's real or fake, especially when one couple reveal they're non-monogamous. (S1, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/883030b7-27c5-4062-9928-7ba40974ab42/16-9</image>
    <start>02:45AM</start>
    <finish>03:35AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Hills</title>
    <desc>Audrina's back from a weekend away with Justin and she just can't stop smiling. After all the drama, it seems they've decided to officially become a couple. (S3, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/72de73c3-bf62-413b-a2ab-14559b3bf007/16-9</image>
    <start>03:35AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image//16-9</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Hills</title>
    <desc>Jen Bunney texts Lauren saying she wants to talk, but Lauren hasn't heard from Jen since the fallout when Jen and Heidi conspired against her. What could Jen possibly have to say? (S3, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b9041529-862e-486f-a526-e7455e9fb2cb/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:25AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>Maci is the classic overachiever and cheerleader. Now that's all set to change as she's pregnant and planning to graduate early and move in with her boyfriend, Ryan. (S1, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e5d5c04d-d8f5-44ff-8170-42f9360306b3/16-9</image>
    <start>06:25AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Ashley is left alone to care for Holly when Bar learns he must serve 2 years of probation in California. Catelynn supports Tyler as he works on overcoming his childhood sexual abuse trauma. (S1, ep27).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/8b39b2c5-de28-346a-b784-cfeaff706e3f/16-9</image>
    <start>07:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Jade visits her mum in rehab and worries about her commitment to staying sober. Ryder has a difficult time with Cory away competing on The Challenge. (S1, ep28).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ea365f77-72d6-37d3-9da3-31c990724f24/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Hundreds of beautiful and talented women start the hardest audition process in professional sports, trying out for a coveted spot on the most famous NFL cheerleading squad in the world. (S12, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b0a0ce78-7e87-316b-a801-b2112ab028ce/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>The 119 remaining women have one hour to learn a power pom routine and the famous kickline. The stress of mastering the choreography in such a short time leads to numerous mistakes. (S12, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/7b838d8d-1b37-404c-aba4-fc0a45157f1b/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Vince's online-ex, Alyssa, is stalking him. This caused real life girlfriend, Liz, to break up with him. Nev and Max help Vince confront Alyssa so he can try to salvage a future with Liz. (S5, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/4097173c-0db6-486c-b194-23d90d860d54/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>An online love story between Shay and Ceejay turned dark after Ceejay insisted Shay have a baby with her, tracking her every move! Nev and Tallulah Willis help Shay get answers. (S8, ep76).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b6999dc4-45a0-4f66-848e-f54d8eea3bfe/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Angel met Sharon and quickly formed a deep emotional connection over their shared trauma. Kamie and Nev help Angel expose whether Sharon and her life are really fact or fiction! (S8, ep72).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/71174ad1-7960-41b8-8f5d-6632b534459c/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Lucille led a simple life until she was asked to work for music producer Kidd Cole. Companies were never paid and one day Kidd couldn't be found. Will she get the answers she needs? (S3, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/8265c3c2-7378-4913-aa6a-3ed955b95397/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Brittany finds love online with Bryon, a marine who may get deployed again to Iraq, she seeks Nev and Max's help before she runs out of time to discover if the perfect military man is real. (S4, ep28).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/040a3aeb-1e7d-4c2c-a9c0-c38886c7363a/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Alfred's thirsty to find Adonis, the man of his dreams. But as they dig for answers, word that Nev and Kamie are in town leads to the most explosive confrontation in Catfish history! (S8, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a4f0ffef-82c9-47cc-b0f8-6a7c6d012891/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Anthony is a war veteran who wears his heart on his sleeve. Over a year ago, he bonded online with a caring man named Marq. Today, they're head over heels in love - but what is Marq hiding? (S2, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2eab4922-4df0-460e-b540-b79e41a645f9/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>After a three-year online relationship, Tiana moved across the country to be with love-of-her-life James, and reveal her secret. Now in the same state, James seems more elusive than ever. (S4, ep18).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/71913797-408a-41d7-b4e7-400108e66a62/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Celebs On The Ranch</title>
    <desc>Fun reality series as ten UK celebrities try their hands on an Arizona cattle ranch. The girls are pitched against the boys in a Line-Dance Off. Eyal and Jenny feed the chickens. (S1, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f19177d6-924d-4660-b4d2-c3f0aead3357/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Rich Kids Go Skint</title>
    <desc>Tiana is astonished that Candace and her two kids live in a two-bed flat. But as she cooks dinner for only ?6, her wealthy father hopes she comes back a changed character. (S4, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f118dab8-6693-497e-a027-480993f4861d/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Help! I'm In A Secret...</title>
    <desc>Relationship! Ben and Matt met their first day of college and became instantly inseparable. But lately, Matt's been completely avoiding Ben. Why is Matt hiding Ben from his life? (S2, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/8775b953-b7ed-3a22-8764-8a59473f7d15/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Jersey Shore Family Vacation</title>
    <desc>Vinny runs the New York City marathon. Jenni has her directorial debut. The roomies prepare for their first international family vacation in years. (S8, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f5a86016-f1d5-4390-8ce2-4a95b25698c7/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Challenge</title>
    <desc>The Challenge kicks off with a bang as 16 seasoned vets and 16 New Threats race up a mountain. Rivalries flare, strategies form, and sparks fly as the game begins. (S41, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/355fa845-c25b-4ba8-b6c3-c5e060b5b505/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Love &amp; Hip Hop Atlanta</title>
    <desc>The wellness retreat takes a turn for the worse when Spice and Bambi's ailing friendship leaves the whole group in diss-stress. Salma shows us how she's taking over the ALT music scene. (S13, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/fa90510e-123c-4f82-b77d-9ad548715c11/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>With only six Artists remaining, the power to control the game is everything. The battle is more intense than ever before when the Artists must collaborate to create powerful tattoos. (S11, ep13).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/bc7904f8-2d68-46f9-9ffc-59c7ae6e05b4/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>There's nowhere to hide when the Artists are tested in precision portraiture. One Artist misses the mark and is sent packing. The battle continues for $100K and the title of Ink Master. (S11, ep14).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a88f41dd-da0b-45aa-a122-4193b1c66137/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:45AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Love At First Lie</title>
    <desc>It's the countdown to the final but should the couples keep trying to vote off the liars or should they rely on strategy and tactics, in order to stand a chance of winning the cash prize? (S1, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/85bd5109-7b82-489b-a568-e6ed17a81686/16-9</image>
    <start>02:45AM</start>
    <finish>03:35AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Hills</title>
    <desc>Lauren and Jason have been spending a lot of time together lately, but while at lunch, Jason lets it slip that not only does he have a girlfriend, but they're moving in together! (S3, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e99d3413-11d1-460d-9b43-74f7c277af60/16-9</image>
    <start>03:35AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image//16-9</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Hills</title>
    <desc>After kissing Brody in Vegas, Lauren wonders what their status is. Testing it out at dinner, she tells Brody that she hasn't been on a date in weeks. Will he be next on the menu? (S3, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3f4a2764-84f6-48e1-8cf8-d149bf15359d/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:25AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>Meet Farrah, a popular high-school cheerleader. As if being pregnant isn't difficult enough, she is facing difficulties with the father of the baby, her friends and her mother. (S1, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/fe8d8224-a171-4779-9f36-48e5d33b2421/16-9</image>
    <start>06:25AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Catelynn supports Tyler in the next step of his healing journey. With Ryan in jail, Maci follows through on her promise to change and attends her first Al-anon meeting. (S1, ep29).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b1dcbf12-1bdb-3480-ae8e-954a85681ad6/16-9</image>
    <start>07:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom</title>
    <desc>Catelynn and Tyler find out they can see Carly. Leah attends a pole fitness class. Cheyenne tries hypnotherapy to cope with anxiety. Jade's mother tries to leave rehab early. (S1, ep30).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ca29f28c-20d9-3446-ad1a-b7e0cf3b4995/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>The veterans finally enter the audition process. All 83 women are judged head to head during a panel interview, a solo dance performance and on their appearance on the football field. (S12, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ba98393b-f072-41f5-82ed-a637580c202b/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>The very first training camp begins at the new 1 billion dollar Cowboys' facility. The Star; Kelli lays down the law and makes it clear that eight women will be sent home this summer. (S12, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a53e89a2-695f-481c-839a-8bd5ed389332/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and co-host Kamie Crawford help Mathan find Leah, a girl he's been talking to for a decade yet can never meet! But Leah has shocking secrets beyond their wildest imaginations. (S7, ep29).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/4a813904-ffc9-4aee-9f4a-d1e691b62835/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Single father Felipe is ready to settle down with Jasmine. However, the two have been talking online for eight months and have never met. Max returns and joins Nev to investigate. (S4, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/d7f61f5b-88a7-42e2-b247-526f987fb6d1/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and NFL star Rashad Jennings help Deven find his mysterious online love James. James won't videochat yet he invites Deven to fly across the country to meet him! Deven needs answers. (S7, ep28).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/dd427e23-6fd8-4594-a03a-e8d436bb7291/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>John is ready to leave Detroit but one thing holds him back: Kelsey. The two have never spoken outside of online chats but John is sure she's the one. Can he include Kelsey in his plans? (S3, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/dff408be-fe5a-4278-903d-24f7e95db966/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>For the last six years, Red's been talking to Jalissa and her group of celebrity besties. Hot on the trail to meet Jalissa in LA, Nev and Kamie help Red uncover a truth. (S8, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/de176af4-d2e5-41c6-be8c-9a923f704157/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>A Tinder match ignited a fire for Jordan that caused Angel to end a real relationship to pursue him. Nev and his wife Laura uncover dark truths that could lose Angel everyone she loves. (S7, ep13).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/99618c4b-4a4d-4757-88c3-b0d8357e2ff9/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>When Blaire's Instagram lover Markie broke her heart, she moved on. But now Markie is back and wants to meet. Blaire needs Nev and Max's help to make it happen and reveal Markie's secret. (S4, ep14).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/26d864bc-c21d-4df1-aa7c-7b6fe36ef53d/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Dylan receives an anonymous text warning him that his online love, Ally, is not who she says she is. After the mystery texter is revealed, Nev and Max uncover a huge web of deceit! (S6, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/c85fd523-302d-4fe9-9a75-d7f9679f54ee/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Celebs On The Ranch</title>
    <desc>Fun reality series as ten UK celebrities try their hands on an Arizona cattle ranch. The celebs face a Trailer Reversing Challenge, and we learn which of them can't drive. (S1, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/d7279a3d-0e72-42a9-87aa-20f747990d9f/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish UK</title>
    <desc>Jerry needs help meeting his first love Karla. Karla claims to have already met Jerry but refuses to talk to him on the phone. Can Oobah and Nella find out if Karla is who she says she is? (S2, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ec1e8527-b7eb-4d58-99b8-6a84a366d608/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Skin A&amp;E</title>
    <desc>Top dermatologists help members of the public with a range of skin conditions. (S3, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/9ea115bf-f7c2-411f-a5ad-3945c94e920e/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Oasis</title>
    <desc>Legendary British rock band Oasis performed a number of their best hits unplugged, incl. \&quot;Wonderwall\&quot; and \&quot;Don't Look Back In Anger\&quot;, at London's Royal Festival Hall in August 1996.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ccc4ef1b-6d6b-4355-8771-fbe959f93bed/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Nirvana</title>
    <desc>On the 18th November 1993, Nirvana recorded their now legendary MTV Unplugged performance. Relive the special gig now, including seminal classics like 'Come As You Are' and 'All Apologies.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f1a15221-7e67-4dba-9551-97f8d4b26f63/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Beavis And Butt-Head</title>
    <desc>Rabies Scare: Beavis is bitten by a dog and ends up having to go to hospital for rabies injections. (S4, E04).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ad997507-2058-34ac-9faf-1d6329552308/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:15AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Beavis And Butt-Head</title>
    <desc>They're Coming to Take Me Away, Huh Huh (aka Psychiatrist): Beavis and Butt-Head are forced to see the school psychiatrist after goofing off in class. (S4, E05).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/c58ba0f6-a6fb-369a-a828-076055efb443/16-9</image>
    <start>12:15AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Jackass</title>
    <desc>Johnny Knoxville gets pelted with paintballs in the behind-the-scenes footage of his magazine cover shoot, and Bam Margera leaps off a bridge with a large umbrella. (S2, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/77a7ad86-674a-4d03-b533-f530f642a1d1/16-9</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>Four Artists remain but only three will earn a spot in the finale. Cleen and Christian are one step closer to settling the score in the ultimate Grudge Match. (S11, ep15).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/9fa955a9-767e-4c22-811a-3f032cae4eda/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master</title>
    <desc>Christian and Cleen Rock One return to settle the Grudge Match once and for all. The battle concludes as the top three Artists reveal their 35-hour Master Canvas tattoos. (S11, ep16).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/02f27671-b54d-47e1-aed4-a4075eb312c7/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:45AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Love At First Lie</title>
    <desc>There's only a small number of couples left and they've never been so exposed. But can the fakers keep up their lies? (S1, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3a8ab9a1-e791-4c36-b7b0-749ed11f80b7/16-9</image>
    <start>02:45AM</start>
    <finish>03:35AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Hills</title>
    <desc>After the drama at Jason's engagement party, Lauren needs to leave The Hills for a while. What better way to escape than to head to Vegas to surprise Brody on his 24th birthday? (S3, ep9).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/6660c711-a173-4173-8156-755c73b27feb/16-9</image>
    <start>03:35AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teleshopping</title>
    <desc>Teleshopping.</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image//16-9</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>The Hills</title>
    <desc>After weeks of hard work, Whitney thinks she's finally found the perfect place for Teen Vogue to host the Young Hollywood party. But will the old church impress her boss? (S3, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/22e6d926-00c0-457a-9d5d-c5109c0feb2c/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:25AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>16 &amp; Pregnant</title>
    <desc>In this episode, we follow Amber, who's expecting a baby with her boyfriend Gary. They decide to move in together but it's not always easy for these teen parents. (S1, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5898b9b7-5d59-4023-93f7-a58184191727/16-9</image>
    <start>06:25AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom OG</title>
    <desc>Amber and Gary get ready for Leah's first day of school, while Catelynn continues to struggle with her anxiety. Ryan takes Bentley for the weekend, though Maci isn't convinced he's changed. (S6, ep10).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/c0929dfb-3624-4687-8ec3-b47e9ebbc214/16-9</image>
    <start>07:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom OG</title>
    <desc>Amber and Matt attempt to put a stop to the tabloid rumours surrounding them, but are sidetracked by a visit from Matt's son. Tyler and Catelynn celebrate Butch's first year out of prison. (S6, ep11).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/fd43f41b-4f45-4625-9b74-a0fe8f993e8d/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom OG</title>
    <desc>In an attempt to keep Matt's son sober, Amber and Matt invite him to move in. Catelynn and Tyler attempt to celebrate their first year of marriage, but are worried about Carly. (S6, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/ff3cf0ad-ebb2-453f-adce-fde95f68de83/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Teen Mom OG</title>
    <desc>Farrah and her mother uncover old family wounds and get into a huge fight. Matt is offered the opportunity to write a book about his life, and Maci and Taylor head to Las Vegas. (S6, ep13).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/36f4ab68-8a1a-4ad7-bf3f-c9915dc7b6a7/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>As Training Camp starts Kelli lays down the law. Girls start to crack as the reality of how hard it is to become a DCC sets in. Melissa Rycroft offers advice on how to make it through. (S10, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/6eceaf78-6ff9-4f9e-bf89-4552442c7ca8/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>Kelli and Judy must cut 10 girls to get to the magic number of 36 for the squad. Uniform fittings gives Kelli a better idea of who has the whole package. (S10, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/81758791-a37e-4010-af68-8b6d169c6ec0/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>For shy Devan, meeting Rylan was love at first click. Devan wants to believe that Rylan is marriage material but her suspicious behaviour is leaving him with doubts. (S4, ep27).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b824baf3-e417-4013-a5ed-bd7d4f24a0ae/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Kimiko Glenn joins Nev in helping Matthew find his elusive Instagram love, Chance. But as they search for answers, they run into unsurpassable roadblocks that make them question everything. (S7, ep35).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3f96191c-2c07-468c-adfb-73071aca08cc/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Daisy met Marcus on Instagram and he instantly stole her heart. But Marcus won't speak to Daisy on the phone, let alone meet her in person, so Nev and Tyler try to arrange a face to face. (S4, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/9a0c5745-babd-4bda-ac8f-2c4484f19507/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Model Dallas has had his sights set on sexy Safari ever since she slid into his dms - but despite flirty promises, she won't meet. Nev and co-host Tallulah Willis begin a hunt for Safari. (S7, ep25).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/6bc652a9-d48c-455e-a829-416ee5ec86ea/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Max and co-host iO Tillett Wright help Mecca connect with a boy she's loved for years. But soon it's discovered that Mecca's digital beau may be using her pictures to catfish others! (S6, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/37f62ba6-4ab0-4bf5-a3fe-632dee6b7b34/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Nev and Nick Young, aka Swaggy P, help Sheila figure out if she's being romanced by Love and Hip Hop's Rich Dollaz. Is it a fan girl crush or is Sheila really talking to the reality star? (S7, ep21).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/93c80ed0-4b8b-454d-972f-b9705a632e94/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>After 20 years, Motherwolff, a witch, is now ready for her true love David. Will their lifelong romance prove to be as magical as she dreams, or will she learn the hard way. (S8, ep74).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5f48b40f-83f0-441b-b3fe-271c131cc489/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>After splitting from her husband of 20 years, Angela reinvented herself and is excited by her new love interest Justin. He's been dodgy about meeting, but she's ready for something real. (S8, ep77).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/b2370ce6-69af-4faf-aec3-836b9cceb649/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Kito is faced with not one, but three unhappy Canvases - including one of Ink Master's most infamous Canvases of all time. Can Kito keep his cool or will he lose his shot at redemption? (S2, ep1).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/0dacb7ec-21a6-442e-b5ab-d4f1b6b784d8/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>James Vaughn returns to redeem one of the most infamous pin-up mistakes; Kyle Dunbar and Sebastian Murphy try to keep their cool when faced with unhappy canvases. (S2, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/9fdb9ebe-b497-4111-aa28-04f2a8cd0e4b/16-9</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>James Vaughn returns to redeem one of the most infamous mistakes in Ink Master history. Faced with unhappy Canvases, can hotheads Kyle Dunbar and Sebastian Murphy keep their cool? (S2, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/a9eae4e6-5876-428c-b90c-fe636fa5eaec/16-9</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Unhappy Canvases bring back-up to face their Artists Ashley B. and Ally Lee in the Ink Master shop. Can Ashley and Ally keep their cool under pressure? (S2, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5cd87d62-f667-4d5f-8172-e0ba6f4cdf67/16-9</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Sarah Miller returns to the Ink Master shop to call out Steve Tefft. Miami Burgess returns to call out Big Ceeze for the tattoo that sent him home. (S2, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/d95c525b-76b8-487e-a6f4-29dbc4f41923/16-9</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
