<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Dallas Cowboys Cheerleaders</title>
    <desc>With the first cut looming, the girls must push their dance skills to the limit. Stress increases on makeover day as the girls try to get the DCC look. (S11, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e5805686-9e53-4ee4-9f2e-75fa2aa249a8/16-9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Trina is a dancer who always had trouble meeting trustworthy guys, until she met Scorpio, a fellow dancer, online. Will Trina finally get to rendezvous with the only man she's ever loved? (S1, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2afe6a38-863d-439d-b8ae-11e582bc84f9/16-9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Kim's been pouring her heart out to Matt for over 10 years. Now, Kim's facing a life-changing decision - should she marry her current boyfriend or find out if Matt is her soul mate? (S1, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/2c9dded9-d259-40ba-8225-0868657f41ac/16-9</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Jasmine has been texting with Mike for two years and thinks he could be the perfect step-father for her son. Although they live only 15 minutes apart, the pair have yet to meet up in person. (S1, ep4).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/3a45536e-adc8-4777-8ab4-4d8e2b875ae3/16-9</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Jarrod never thought he'd find love until he fell for Abby on Facebook. Jarrod thinks Abby could be \&quot;the one\&quot;, but she's refusing to see him. What is Abby hiding? (S1, ep5).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/efeae119-1882-4256-b178-d30a419567b2/16-9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>In this episode we meet Kya and Alyx, who fell in love quickly after meeting online. Are they being honest with each other? Hosts Nev Schulman and Max Joseph investigate. (S1, ep6).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/e58b6407-36ec-4e77-b3f9-ebae721db6ee/16-9</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Joe was sceptical when Miss Teen USA, Kari, sent him a friend request. Now, after months of communication, Joe thinks it might be the real deal, and he might have found love with her. (S1, ep7).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/aed8de83-cbab-4d3d-8c56-e33111c491e1/16-9</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>After a year and a half of chatting with her online, Tyler thinks he may have a future with Amanda. But are Tyler's friends correct because they suspect that something isn't right? (S1, ep8).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/c7aaed5e-2e17-4215-8ced-8ebd160e1245/16-9</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Catfish</title>
    <desc>Mike and Felicia met online and soon hit it off. After agreeing to meet, Felicia stood Mike up, offering only thin excuses. Can Mike trust Felicia - or will he end up disappointed? (S1, ep12).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/f4c86067-a399-4f1f-9f52-3b90b667338f/16-9</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>In a Redemption first, Runner-Up Master Canvases defend their tattoos against the Artists who defeated them. Cleen Rock One, Anthony Michaels, Jime Litwalk and Joey Hamilton return. (S3, ep2).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/90a7049d-52c0-4e1b-a064-abcba02ee0b3/16-9</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>MTV UK</name>
    <title>Ink Master Redemption</title>
    <desc>Season 5 Artist Julia Carlson is back for another shot at Redemption with not one, not two, but three unhappy Canvases. (S3, ep3).</desc>
    <image>https://images.metadata.sky.com/pd-image/5be6b66e-7dd6-4d7b-b0a2-8e4ec116754d/16-9</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
