<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Classica DE</name>
    <id>Classica.de</id>
    <title>Mosa?que Project</title>
    <desc>Dieses besondere Konzertevent zahlt der Diversit?t und Vielf?ltigkeit Kanadas aus der Perspektive seiner Einwohner Tribut. Das patriotische &quot;Mosaique Project&quot; des Ensemble Canada beinhaltet eigens in Auftrag gegebene Klavierquartette aus der Feder von 14 verschiedenen Komponisten, jeweils inspiriert durch eine andere Region Kanadas. Das Ensemble, bestehend aus Elissa Lee (Violine) Sharon Wei (Bratsche), Rachel Mercer (Cello) und Angela Park (Klavier) ist derzeit auf dem Weg an die Spitze der kanadischen Klavierquartette. Ensemble Made In Canada consist of Elissa Lee (violin) Sharon Wei (viola), Rachel Mercer (cello) and Angela Park (piano) and is rapidly gaining recognition as Canada's premier piano quartet Awarded the 2006 CBC Galaxie Stars Award from the Banff Centre for the Arts, EMIC was featured in 2008 Chatelaine Magazine's 80th anniversary issue as &quot;Women to Watch&quot; and an ensemble that is leading the next generation of classical musicians. The members of the group have been forging outstanding individual careers and bring together a wealth of experience having already appeared at prestigious festivals such as Marlboro, Ravinia, Orford, Verbier, Prussia Cove, Pablo Casals and Evian. EMIC has performed for Winnipeg Virtuosi, Montreal Pro Musica, SUNY New Paltz, Stratford Music Festival, Ottawa Chamberfest, Parry Sound Festival of the Sound, Jeffery Chamber Music Series, Lindsay Concert Productions, Almonte in Concert, Women's Musical Club of Toronto, Kawartha Concerts, including multiple work cycles for the Kitchener-Waterloo Chamber Music Soceity. EMIC has provided master classes, chamber music coachings, and lectures at universities across Canada and in the United States and have also participated in outreach programs for public schools in Ontario. The group is grateful for support from FACTOR, the Canada Council for the Arts and the Ontario Arts Council. EMIC has been Ensemble-in-Residence at Western University since 2014.</desc>
    <image>https://img.tvspielfilm.de/ec/2c/4a/6177d1ba8189652ccb4a2cec.jpeg?im=Crop,rect=(0,0,4000,2246),gravity=Center;Resize,width=780</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:08AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
