<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <title>I'M LIVE</title>
    <desc>?I'm Live is a live concert program featuring Korea's top musicians? Musicians and fans interact with one another in close proximity, becoming one in the name of music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202504/2971229173537833744.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <title>PERFORMARTS RELOAD:NTOK</title>
    <desc>PerformArts Reload(Biweekly)?PerformArts Reload Season 4? takes you to the world of sage cultural arts! We are delighted to help you open your eyes to the new dynamics of K-cultures&amp;arts, offering a variety of artsy stages in gugak, classical music, musicals, opera and traditional dance. ? #CulturalArts_Now #KCulturesnArts_WAVE --&gt;.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/old/A_UpFile/TvPg_Info_Img/T200909105101_SCH.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <title>SIMPLY K-POP GATEWAY TO KOREA</title>
    <desc>2025 Overseas TV Viewer Survey???K-pop fans around the world get up close and personal with this unique music program!Watch Kpop stars as they perform on-stage and interact with the audience throughout the show.No more, no less - Only the essentials on \&quot;SIMPLY K-POP Gateway To Korea\&quot;!Join our Simply K-Pop: Gateway To Korea audience,? either in person at the STUDIO or online from the comfort of your home!</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202503/2944944718309491469.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <title>SPOTLIGHT - ROOKIES</title>
    <desc>K-Pop is at its height. From BTS to BLACKPINK, idol groups have been evolving to become global pop stars. With idols having great influence in national economy and diplomatic culture, they are going beyond artists, and growing to become a bigger brand! Right here, we have those who have completed their long training period to become a global K-Pop group, the next BTS.  They will perform their debut stage on Arirang TV?s , the music program known to be the gateway of rookie idol groups! Taking you back to three hours before the live broadcast, witness the exciting yet nerve-racking moments from the waiting room, the rookies? youthful charms towards the global fans, and exclusive behind-the-scenes from the rehearsal! Who will become the next rookie idol group to take over the K-Pop market?  Find out on .</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202407/2576900210676466429.png</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <title>ARIRANG LAND</title>
    <desc>Arirang Broadcasting Foundation is opening our doors to you, making its many spaces accessible. Let us know what kind of day you envision to spend at Arirang, and the desired date and time. Arirang Broadcasting Foundation will transform into a dreamland ? Arirang Land ? for those seeking out the space.  \&quot;Arirang Land\&quot; presents a reality observation program, which will capture the unique stories of those who visit Arirang to utilize its diverse spaces.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202504/2975172662940140304.jpg</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <title>WITH SCIENCE, WE LIVE SPECIAL</title>
    <desc>Humanity has learned from the past, transcended the present, and dreamed of the future.\&quot;With Science, We Live\&quot;explores the frontiers of science alongside some of the world?s leading thinkers, offering insights into what lies ahead and uncovering new possibilities.In an era of rapid change, where are we headed?As we navigate between the vast universe and the smallness of human existence, we reconsider the direction we must take.Now, in this very moment, we imagine the future shaped by our choices?and move forward toward it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202507/3092792820386235212.jpg</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <title>SMARTBIZ ACCELERATORS(30?)</title>
    <desc>Along with the strengthened manufacturing capabilities of various countries all around the world, \&quot;Smart Factory\&quot; has garnered a lot of attention in the global market.  And the government has unveiled and promoted a roadmap \&quot;Manufacturing Innovation 3.0,\&quot; as part of an effort to enhance the competitiveness of the domestic manufacturing sector. Moreover, a domestic major company Samsung Electronics has provided a smart factory solution in order to boost mutual growth with small and medium-sized businesses. SmartBiz Accelerators introduces a variety of domestic small and medium-sized companies that have achieved continuous growth based on the smart factory project provided by Samsung Electronics as well as gives information on the technological competitiveness and the outlook for the companies in the global market.  #SmartBizAccelerators #ArirangTV #smartfactory #smartfactoryproject #competitiveness_of_manufacturing #strengthening_competitiveness_of_SMEs #expanding_into_overseas_markets #growth_into_globalbusiness   For more information: smartbizacc@arirang.com&lt;!--[data-hwpjson]{ \&quot;documentPr\&quot;: { \&quot;di\&quot;: \&quot;\&quot;, \&quot;dp\&quot;: { \&quot;dn\&quot;: \&quot;test.hwp\&quot;, \&quot;ta\&quot;: 1, \&quot;d1\&quot;: 5, \&quot;d2\&quot;: 1, \&quot;dv\&quot;: 0, \&quot;dr\&quot;: 1, \&quot;do\&quot;: 1, \&quot;vj\&quot;: \&quot;1.1\&quot;, \&quot;an\&quot;: \&quot;Hancom Office Hangul\&quot;, \&quot;av\&quot;: \&quot;10, 0, 0, 13015\&quot;, \&quot;ao\&quot;: \&quot;WIN\&quot;, \&quot;ab\&quot;: \&quot;32\&quot;, \&quot;ar\&quot;: \&quot;LE\&quot;, \&quot;as\&quot;: \&quot;Windows_8\&quot; }&quot;text&quot;:&quot;.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202503/2953409952149930765.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Arirang World KR</name>
    <title>REGIONAL TASTES: GANGWON</title>
    <desc>An archive video produced to record the local foods in the regions of Gangwon-do  Province. Stories about the recipe, history, and characteristics of each regional dish. ? VOD service is currently not available due to copyright issues.</desc>
    <image>https://img.arirang.com/v1/AUTH_d52449c16d3b4bbca17d4fffd9fc44af/public/images/202504/2965429408145343248.png</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
