<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CW Boston US</name>
    <title>Two and a Half Men</title>
    <desc>After their split, Alan wants to gain custody of his and Kandi's dog.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184925_b_h10_ap.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CW Boston US</name>
    <title>Two and a Half Men</title>
    <desc>Alan offends Charlie by choosing harebrained cousins as Jake's guardians in the event of his death.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7895741_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CW Boston US</name>
    <title>Last Man Standing</title>
    <desc>When Mike and Vanessa invite Jen's father to her graduation, Jen struggles with accepting his &quot;plus one&quot; - his girlfriend Fiona; the Outdoor Man crew debates over which word was said in a viral audio recording that's been tearing the internet apart.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8679132_b_h8_ax.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CW Boston US</name>
    <title>Last Man Standing</title>
    <desc>A car restoration article throws Mike, Chuck, and Ed into the spotlight, while leaving Joe feeling unappreciated; Ryan overreacts after taking Kyle's psych test.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8679132_b_h8_ax.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CW Boston US</name>
    <title>In Depth With Graham Bensinger</title>
    <desc>Before the age of 30, journalist and Emmy-winner Graham Bensinger worked not only for major networks like NBC and ESPN, but he also began his own syndicated interview program that airs weekly across the country. Bensinger chats with some of sports' biggest names, including pro football players Terrell Owens and Tony Romo, professional basketball player Kobe Bryant, boxing champion George Foreman and broadcaster Joe Buck. The half-hour show features sports stars discussing their lives and careers, including some controversial topics they would probably like to forget.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28126535_b_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CW Boston US</name>
    <title>The Verdict With Judge Hatchett</title>
    <desc>A woman sues her stepmother over a baby grand piano; a cosmetologist seeks compensation after a photoshoot.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p13115779_b_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CW Boston US</name>
    <title>Justice for All With Judge Cristina P?rez</title>
    <desc>An influencer blames a photographer for a lost brand deal because &quot;before&quot; photos were posted online; a man and his mom's ex-boyfriend argue over plane tickets.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9341095_b_h8_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CW Boston US</name>
    <title>Forensic Files</title>
    <desc>A coroner finds telltale clues on the badly burned body of a murder victim, sending police in pursuit of a couple of killers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p439881_b_h8_bc.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CW Boston US</name>
    <title>Lauren Lake's Paternity Court</title>
    <desc>A single mother wants to prove to a married man that he is the father of her infant.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10063603_b_h10_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
