<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When the BAU team travels to Denver to investigate several murders, Prentiss is forced to evaluate her relationship with Special Agent Andrew Mendoza.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Rita Deveraux tells Pride that Douglas Hamilton is about to make a deal to get out of prison; Pride and the team re-investigate the Clearwater case in hopes of spoiling his plans.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>After a deadly armed robbery and high-speed chase is linked to an undercover ATF operation, Percy reconnects with her former ATF partner.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>03:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Sebastian's high school friend asks for help when her business partner is killed at a gaming convention; FBI Special Agent Raymond Isler believes Adrian is the hacker that the Cyber Crimes division has been tracking for years.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>A petty officer's murder leads the team to a night club where Pride's mother used to perform; Lasalle must return home to Alabama after receiving an unexpected call from his family.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>A former kidnapping victim is linked to a series of murders that includes the daughter of an NYPD detective; Kristen begins to doubt her ability as an agent after a training exercise leaves her shaken.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:52AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a businessman with a history of harassment claims against him is killed, the team suspects the killer may be one of his many accusers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:52AM</start>
    <finish>06:44AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>A bank holdup leads the team to a safe deposit box, the contents of which have the potential to destroy national security; Kristen is eager to get back into field work while other team members still have their concerns.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>06:44AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The son of a retired FBI agent is kidnapped, and the team must investigate if it's an act of revenge; Isobel must make a hard call when information from the past comes to light.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:26AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When an attorney is found dead near the body of a private escort, the team must piece together what connected the two seemingly random victims; Jubal's connection with one of the victims makes finding the killer much more personal.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>08:26AM</start>
    <finish>09:18AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a truck filled with armor-piercing rifles is hijacked, the team works to discover who stole it, and what they have planned for the stolen weapons; a friend from OA's past returns to help with the case, but OA isn't sure he can trust him.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>09:18AM</start>
    <finish>10:09AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After the police ignore a desperate father's plea for help, he abducts a billionaire's daughter and holds her hostage in a safe room until his own missing child is returned to him; Jubal puts his hostage negotiation skills to the test.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>10:09AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>At the last minute, Dr. Carter asks Abby to be his date for his grandfather's (George Plimpton) charity event.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Greene is angered when a review board questions his competency; Dr. Carter tries to save a boy whose parents neglected to immunize him against measles.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>A train wreck has the doctors facing one of the bloodiest traumas of their careers; Dr. Kovac recalls the painful loss of his family.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Weaver fears her relationship may be exposed when a suicidal woman claims Dr. Legaspi (Elizabeth Mitchell) sexually harassed her.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Benton witnesses a shooting in the ER; Carter and Abby treat children who became sick on their school bus from toxic fumes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Drs. Greene and Corday encounter problems while trying to make it to their nuptials; Dr. Weaver takes an out-of-town trip after not being invited to the wedding.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Prentiss and J.J. are faced with important decisions to make about their futures as the BAU travels to Texas to investigate a series of murdered businessmen.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Rossi develops some new theories about Everett Lynch, aka The Chameleon; the team sets out on an epic hunt to capture Lynch.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>While hallucinating after he gets a brain injury, Dr. Reid is visited by ghosts from his past; the BAU makes a shocking discovery about Lynch that affects Rossi personally; the team comes together to celebrate Rossi's retirement.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU interviews candidates to take the opening left by Kate's departure; the team tracks a serial killer who leaves behind evidence that indicates a person intent on revenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team must find the person responsible for a sarin gas attack on a Los Angeles bus before a larger incident occurs.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team suspects a jilted unknown subject is responsible when brides are murdered on the eve of their nuptials.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When a robbery-homicide leaves three restaurant employees dead, a cold case that occurred in the same town six years earlier could yield a lead.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A notorious street artist becomes a suspect when corpses are used in macabre graffiti art in Detroit; Dr. Lewis tries to balance work and her relationship with her fiance.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>A petty officer is murdered while in town to help a refugee family; Wade works on the special election campaign for Mayor Zahra Taylor that takes place during Mardi Gras.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>FBI Special Agent Raymond Isler asks Pride for help with an off-the-books opioids theft investigation he is personally invested in; Percy works under cover as a getaway driver, with Isler as the muscle for a job tied to the case.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>03:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>A congressional aide disappears after a hit man saves her from two men posing as NCIS agents; LaSalle struggles with life-altering decisions regarding his brother's future.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the murder of a Navy captain who was searching for a priceless 200-year-old fleur-de-lis during the annual Louisiana Pirate Festival.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When the team is called to the scene of a murder, it quickly suspects political motivation; Maggie contemplates a decision that could affect her entire career.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:52AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>Jess LaCroix and his team come to help OA find a fugitive LaCroix arrested years ago after a bus with 26 students goes missing and he's the main suspect.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:52AM</start>
    <finish>06:44AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a drug deal gone bad after the body of a college student is found; Detective Hailey Upton temporarily joins the team and finds her investigative methods clash with the Bureau's more buttoned-up environment.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>06:44AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team welcomes a new member, Special Agent Tiffany Wallace, as they search for killers who orchestrated a mass shooting at a media company; OA's personal connection with the case threatens to cloud his judgement.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:26AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team races to stop an active serial killer after three women are found weighted down at the bottom of a lake; Jubal looks into an old closed case after there are multiple similarities to the recent victims.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>08:26AM</start>
    <finish>09:18AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When the leader of a drug cartel and one of the world's most wanted men is apprehended by the team, the entire FBI headquarters is put at risk when his henchmen unveil a plot to free him; Isobel must make a difficult decision.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>09:18AM</start>
    <finish>10:09AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>A shooting at a quincea?era leaves two dead, but the team believes they may not have been the intended targets; Maggie is conflicted as the team decides the best plan of action for using a witness to take down their suspect.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>10:09AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Carter accompanies Abby on a road trip to retrieve her mother; Dr. Corday prepares for childbirth with Dr. Greene at her side.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Abby fears her suicidal mother may be released from the mental hospital after she appears coherent before the judge; Dr. Benton injures his hand.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Abby is encouraged when her unstable mother gives her enlightening advice in a rare moment of clarity; Dr. Weaver ignores Dr. Carter's interest in the chief resident position.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Gunshot victims flood the ER when a distraught father goes on a shooting spree in a foster-care facility.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Greene ministers to a young woman (Jessica Townsend) who was injured during a confrontational television talk show.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891888_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Carter deals with heavy-metal roadies following a concert accident; chief resident Chen panics when she is overwhelmed with patients.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891888_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A murder in a Florida community of sex offenders results in a large number of possible suspects; a career opportunity could take Lewis away from the BAU.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Rossi's daughter, a journalist, investigates the disappearance of a college student; JJ comes back from maternity leave.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>An unknown subject in Phoenix abducts people and deprives them of sleep; Garcia and Hotch deal with a threat from hit men.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU works with the NSA when two undercover DEA agents are murdered and another goes missing; Hotch hopes the team's work with the NSA will bring them closer to finding a ring of hit men.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The members of the BAU team track an unknown subject who appears to be fascinated with medical experimentation.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Reid plays a central role in the BAU's elaborate plan to take down a ring of hit men known as the Dirty Dozen.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When corpses are discovered in public places in Boston, a ride-sharing service may lead the team to the killer.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU looks for a suspect and a motive when victims are found in truck stop restrooms in the South.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Pride, Sebastian and Tammy travel to South America after Pride is personally requested by a former colleague to assist with a classified operation that has been compromised.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Percy and Lasalle go under cover at a high-stakes poker game after the organizer targets players with access to a naval research laboratory; Laurel Pride visits her dad during spring break to discuss options after her upcoming graduation.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>03:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Pride and his bar patrons are held hostage by a group of volatile thieves.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Gregorio calls on her former behavioral science professor when the team's latest case matches one she studied during FBI training.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team searches for a young girl who was kidnapped from a cabin during a family vacation; Maggie questions her relationship with Nestor when she learns he hasn't been completely honest with her.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team must infiltrate a drug trafficking gang after the robbery of a chemical plant leaves two customs agents dead; Nestor offers his help on the case, giving Maggie new insight into his character.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team hunts a killer who is fatally shooting seemingly unrelated targets; new agent Tiffany Wallace experiences tension between her work as an FBI agent and the responsibility she feels to her community as a Black woman.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a bomb leaves three people dead, the team presses a reluctant informant to gather information from his close friends who are under suspicion; OA and his girlfriend clash over where the informant's rights lie.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When a reporter is kidnapped and held without a ransom demand, the team must dig into her past relationships in order to pin down her assailant's motive; Isobel's relationship comes under fire when the case makes a connection to her boyfriend.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team must track down two assailants who wear animal masks while committing armed robberies; Tiffany and Scola butt heads on whether or not to accept the local NYPD's offer to help in the investigation.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Detectives Lupo and Bernard investigate when an aspiring musician is found dead; a bag of cash leads to multiple suspects.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>While searching for the murderer of the adoptive mother of 10 disabled children, detectives uncover a reality-show offer and an affair.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a doctor is murdered, the detectives investigate an abortion protester; Van Buren receives more bad news; Connie faces a moral dilemma.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The revelation of a murder victim's true identity leads detectives to a suspicious web site with threatening posts.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a wealthy young woman is found dead in her apartment, a few signs lead detectives to believe the killer was not after her wealth; a security video exposes two potential suspects, leading the detectives to a drug cartel.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A suspicious nasal spray is found at the site of a deadly car crash; after the medical examiner realizes the spray could easily disorient its user, the detectives become suspicious of the victim's boss.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a key witness in a murder trial is found dead in her hotel, detectives get involved in a spiraling case that unravels into an intricate conspiracy.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Detectives Lupo and Bernard think a violent armed robbery might be a scare tactic for a shakedown.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a campaign volunteer is murdered, Detectives Lupo and Bernard end up dealing with more than just dirty politics.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a journalist is found dead in an abandoned apartment, the investigation uncovers a relationship between the victim and a daytime talk-show host, who admits to a series of workplace affairs and a blackmail threat.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a family is found murdered at home, a runaway teenager becomes a suspect.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The investigation of a 16-year-old student whose body was burned causes Lupo and Bernard to question the young person he mentored, the last person to see him alive; the investigation draws attention to a vicious high-school rivalry.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A woman's body is found stashed on a food service cart in a hotel; Detectives Bernard and Lupo discover evidence that leads them to a medical school research project.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>After a man is found guilty of a hate crime, Emily Ryan (Amy Madigan) and The Innocence Collective try to prove his innocence.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
