<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU is called to investigate a series of homicides in which cryptic messages are found inside the mouths of the victims.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU is called when the New Orleans Police Department discovers a mass grave inside a vandalized above-ground crypt in a local cemetery.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The FBI's assistant director of national security joins the BAU as it investigates the quadruple homicide of a group of roommates in St. Louis.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU meets in secret to investigate a subject who appears to be kidnapping and photographing young women.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU is called to Oklahoma to investigate a murderous clown who is terrorizing a town.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU travels to Chicago to investigate a case where red roses are left on victims; Rossi gets an unexpected visit from his ex-wife.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU takes charge of a hostage situation at a law firm where Matt Simmons' wife works.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU is called upon when bioterrorism is suspected in a series of mysterious deaths; Garcia visits her stepbrother to take care of a difficult family issue.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>After a member of the United States Navy Band is murdered in her home, Pride looks after the victim's nephew, who is the only witness to the crime.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The NCIS team investigates when a Marine corporal who is an amateur race car driver is in a fatal crash on the track.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>03:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Pride needs to protect a family friend engaged to the prime suspect in an ongoing NCIS and FBI cartel case.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Sebastian goes under cover; Patton practices his old gambling skills; Pride and the team embark on a perilous plan to trap Garcia.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>Maggie and OA must find a couple that is responsible for a spree of violent armed robberies that led to the death of an off-duty police officer.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:52AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After an investigative journalist is murdered, the team uncovers information linking the suspect to past cases; the victim's death strikes a chord with Maggie, leaving her desperate for answers in regard to a traumatic event in her personal life.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:52AM</start>
    <finish>06:44AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>A serial bomber appears to be targeting Wall Street's elite; Maggie and OA search for a suspect who seems set on revenge; Dana deals with Spencer Briggs, a cocky profiler brought in to consult on the case.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>06:44AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The daughter of a wealthy family is kidnapped in an attempt to gain notorious internet fame; Maggie and OA discover the kidnapper's plans go far beyond abduction.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:26AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>Maggie and Dana struggle to find justice for victims murdered by a serial killer; the mayor limits the investigation to cut costs.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>08:26AM</start>
    <finish>09:18AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>OA and Maggie team up with members of the FBI's Fugitives Department to track down a person wanted for murder who is also on America's Top 10 Most Wanted list.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>09:18AM</start>
    <finish>10:09AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team must take down a dangerous drug ring after an American diplomat is killed while being used as a pawn; Jubal and OA try to help friends from their past fight off their inner demons.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>10:09AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Benton's current love interest, Dr. Finch, asks him to overrule Corday for surgery on a young boy; Abby advises an exhausted pregnant woman to have an abortion.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891886_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>A family feud threatens a girl's chance for getting a bone-marrow transplant; Greene admits his father, who has pneumonia.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891886_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Greene shares final memories with his father; Hathaway receives flowers from a secret admirer; a 6-year-old car-accident victim says her father sexually abuses her.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891886_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Weaver goes on the warpath after she discovers several problems in the ER; Dr. Greene re-evaluates his priorities in the wake of his father's death.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891886_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Kovac and Benton clash over prioritizing care for a victim of a school shooting vs. a more seriously wounded gunman.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891886_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Carter struggles with his drug dependency; a custodial strike leaves the ER cluttered with garbage; a riot at a high-school football game leaves several wounded.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU is called to Taos, N.M., when someone targets victims' temporal lobes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team questions the credibility of a former FBI agent's bizarre account.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When Reid and Garcia are abducted by a mass murderer, it's up to the rest of the team to find them; the BAU looks to their past to solve why the two heroes have been targeted.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team tracks a serial killer when remains of numerous victims are found in the walls of an elderly couple's home; the hunt becomes urgent after the BAU learns the killer's specific ritual of when to strike; Rossi reconnects with his ex-wife.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Packages with gruesome contents are delivered to six people in the Washington, D.C.. area; Simmons and Kristy struggle to connect with their son, David, who is suspended from school for aggressive behavior.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Soon after the BAU steps in to help local law enforcement isolate a suspect for a murder, a second person who is related to the first victim is killed under similar circumstances; Prentiss is concerned about Garcia's behavior.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates a spooky local ghost story of the &quot;Tall Man&quot; and the clues it provides when two people go missing in the woods; a third person mysteriously surfaces the following day with limited details as to what happened to her friends.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates four murders along the eastern seaboard; the crimes become personal for Alvez when the team discovers there are ties to his time spent in pursuit of a notorious hit man; Alvez and his girlfriend decide to move in together.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>After Pride travels to a deep-sea oil rig for a murder investigation, the team uncovers a gas leak that's on the verge of causing a catastrophic explosion; Sebastian starts his NCIS special agent training.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>After thousands of classified government files are stolen, the NCIS team searches for an underground group of hackers who were co-founded by Elvis Bertrand, Pride's old contact.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>03:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>NCIS agents McGee and Torres head to New Orleans to partner with Pride and his team in the search for the missing homeland security theoretical terror playbook.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Painful memories come flooding back when a gruesome copycat murder leads to the reopening of a case for Wade.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When a controversial senior leader from Egypt comes to New York for a heart transplant, OA struggles to balance his personal opinion with his professional duty when he is assigned to the security detail.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a decorated FBI agent is murdered, the team investigates and learns that the man led a double life; Maggie struggles with what information she should reveal to the agent's widow, who is also her personal friend.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>A woman who has information about the death of Maggie's husband is abducted, leading OA and the team to uncover a criminal operation larger than anyone imagined; Dana puts her career in jeopardy when she allows Maggie to work on the case.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a bomb detonates at a restaurant in Queens, the case becomes personal for OA, who grew up eating there; OA goes under cover to prevent another incident.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After the son of a prominent blogger is kidnapped, the team must sweep through her two million followers to find the culprit; Kristen continues to adjust to life as a field agent with her new partner Stuart Scola.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a female presidential candidate, Valerie Caldwell, is targeted with a car bomb, OA and Maggie must find them before they strike again; the case leads them to wonder if she is being targeted for her political aspirations or something else.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Detectives find no shortage of possible suspects when a psychiatrist who treats disturbed teens is found shot to death in his office.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The police break up a dog-fighting ring and discover a woman's finger inside one of the dead animals; detectives plot to trick an ambitious reporter.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When an art dealer is found stoned to death, detectives suspect that her killing may be linked to some of the art in her gallery, but a deeper look into her personal life reveals another motive.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a notorious hustler is found dead, Cyrus Lupo discovers that his partner, Ed Green, is the shooter; internal affairs takes over the case, forcing Green to reveal his troubled past.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Detectives Cyrus Lupo and Kevin Benard have reason to believe a cult is involved when a novelist is found dead in her car; Assistant District Attorney Michael Cutter has trouble prosecuting when several jury members fear for their own safety.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a legal aid striker is killed outside the courthouse, the sand in his wounds leads detectives to investigate a greensman; due to the strike and shortage of defense attorneys, Rubirosa and Cutter must face each other in court.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The murder of an automobile mechanic leads detectives to uncover a fraudulent online relationship, a bizarre case of blackmail and money laundering.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The murder of a jeweler leads detectives to an illegal prostitution ring; Jack McCoy's job is threatened.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The beating death of a stockbroker causes a battle of epic proportions between the victim's family and the faction responsible for his death.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A mentally challenged man is reunited with his mother, who gave him away after his brother was killed.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A young woman (guest star Jena Malone) escapes from a polygamous cult.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A crane collapse kills a man, and it may not have been an accident; a rift forms between Jack McCoy and Michael Cutter.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A revered sheriff becomes a possible conspirator in a case involving a murdered tourist.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Detectives Lupo and Bernard investigate when the writer of a best-selling memoir is found dead in a community of male prostitutes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Pride's longtime friend, state and military attorney Rita Devereaux, asks NCIS to investigate the disappearance of a JAG lawyer who specializes in classified cases and volunteers at a private military academy.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:02AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>A highly skilled special operations Marine assaults six men in a bar, sending the NCIS team on a city-wide manhunt.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>02:02AM</start>
    <finish>03:03AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Tammy is reunited with her ex-husband, Ethan McKinley - who embezzled millions in Katrina relief funds - after he's tied to the murder of a crime boss' son.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>03:03AM</start>
    <finish>04:05AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>A deadly accident at a naval base exposes a unit of Seabees to a super virus and leaves the rest of the base and the city of New Orleans at risk for an outbreak; Wade is infected with the virus and given hours to live.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>04:05AM</start>
    <finish>05:05AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>After Torres and Bishop are victims of a hit-and-run, Torres fights for his life in the Intensive Care Unit.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>05:05AM</start>
    <finish>06:05AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>The lead suspect in a murder investigation is a woman that Gibbs' friend met on a dating site; Sloane has a secret admirer on Valentine's Day.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>06:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team tries to piece together how a retired Navy officer obtained a rare and valuable coin.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>A Navy officer is murdered the same way his parents were murdered a decade ago; the team stumbles across a storage container filled with dollhouses that display re-creations of murder scenes; the team members agree to clean out their living spaces.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>09:03AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>The body of a well-regarded Navy technician is found floating in a lake, which isn't far from where a popular community event takes place; Sloane's daughter makes an unexpected request.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>09:03AM</start>
    <finish>10:02AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>When Kasie and Jimmy are held hostage in a diner after a jewelry store robbery goes awry, they attempt to keep the other customers safe from the thieves.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>10:02AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>A young couple cope with their baby being premature; Greene and Corday struggle with their relationship.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Benton pays the price for challenging Dr. Romano; a recovering Dr. Carter performs restricted duties his first day back on the job.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Frustrated Benton searches for a new position at a different hospital; Abby finds herself attracted to Dr. Kovac.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Greene accompanies a heart patient in an emergency helicopter; Benton tries to manage a short-staffed emergency room.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Abby's unpredictable mother (Sally Field) visits; Benton discovers that a gunshot victim is a close relative.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891887_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <desc>Wrongfully accused of murdering his wife, Richard Kimble escapes from the law in an attempt to find her killer and clear his name. Pursuing him is a team of U.S. marshals led by Deputy Samuel Gerard, a determined detective who will not rest until Richard is captured. As Richard leads the team through a series of intricate chases, he discovers the secrets behind his wife's death and struggles to expose the killer before it is too late.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14930_v_h8_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>A Time to Kill</title>
    <desc>Carl Lee Hailey (Samuel L. Jackson) is a heartbroken black father who avenges his daughter's brutal rape by shooting the bigoted men responsible for the crime as they are on their way to trial. He turns to Jake Brigance (Matthew McConaughey), an untested lawyer, to defend him. Brigance struggles to believe that he can get Hailey acquitted in this small, segregated Southern town, given Hailey's race and the deliberate nature of his crimes, but Carl has unshakable faith in him.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18232_v_h8_bo.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>The Fugitive</title>
    <desc>Wrongfully accused of murdering his wife, Richard Kimble escapes from the law in an attempt to find her killer and clear his name. Pursuing him is a team of U.S. marshals led by Deputy Samuel Gerard, a determined detective who will not rest until Richard is captured. As Richard leads the team through a series of intricate chases, he discovers the secrets behind his wife's death and struggles to expose the killer before it is too late.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14930_v_h8_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Lasalle must investigate his former partner in the Vice unit after the NCIS team finds a link between an international drug ring and the New Orleans Police Department; Rita looks into a connection between the mayor and illegal activity in Clearwater.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:02AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Pride listens in on a wiretap of Mayor Hamilton; the NCIS team investigates when Navy weapons get stolen in a train heist; featuring musical performances by Sheryl Crow.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>02:02AM</start>
    <finish>03:03AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The murder of a Navy chaplain leads Pride to uncover a possible connection between Mayor Hamilton and illegal activity taking place in the city of Clearwater; Percy continues to face repercussions of her choices on a previous case.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>03:03AM</start>
    <finish>04:05AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>When Pride is spotted tracking one of Mayor Hamilton's accomplices on a crowded street, the suspect opens fire, putting innocent lives at risk before disappearing.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>04:05AM</start>
    <finish>05:05AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Unable to trust anyone in New Orleans, the NCIS team calls in FBI Assistant Director Isler to help expose and stop Mayor Hamilton's sinister scheme.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>05:05AM</start>
    <finish>06:05AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>While Pride remains on probation after his rogue takedown of the corrupt Mayor Hamilton, his team is closely monitored by a strict supervisor; the team must secretly investigate after the FBI takes the lead on a case involving stolen nuclear waste.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>An erratic whistleblower who calls Pride her mentor kidnaps him to help her locate a serial killer targeting young women in the Gulf of Mexico.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team tries to verify the identity of Joe Smith, who claims he served on the U.S.S. Arizona during the attack on Pearl Harbor and wants to be buried there upon his death.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>09:03AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>Gibbs and Fornell attempt to track down the leader of a drug ring who supplied drugs to Fornell's daughter; the team deals with the case of a missing cadaver from the NCIS autopsy room.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>09:03AM</start>
    <finish>10:01AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>To Be Announced</title>
    <desc>Programming to be announced.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p514472_b_h8_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>10:01AM</start>
    <finish>10:02AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>Flashbacks reveal the murder case that first introduced young Gibbs to NCIS and to Ducky.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>10:02AM</start>
    <finish>10:57AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>To Be Announced</title>
    <desc>Programming to be announced.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p514472_b_h8_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>10:57AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>The discovery of two dead bodies in a forest leads the NCIS team into the wild world of modern-day treasure hunting; Gibbs and Fornell get deeper into their search for the opioid kingpin.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>McGee and his wife Delilah's Bahamian vacation turns into a high-stakes mission; Gibbs fears the worst when his search for Fornell leads to blood.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>Following a tip about smuggled weapons, Bishop and Torres engage in a shootout in a former sheriff's residence that's now a historical site, only to find themselves locked in abandoned jail cells there.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>NCIS investigates the murder of a Navy officer who was killed while driving home a recently released inmate; Gibbs helps Palmer deal with a personal trauma.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>When Sloane's name is discovered in Afghanistan at the site of an abandoned bus with a dead driver, Gibbs accompanies her on a trip to find a group of girls who were kidnapped from the bus; a hacker emails compromising information to the Taliban.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>NCIS dives into the competitive world of food trucks after finding a man frozen to death in the back of one.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team uncovers a secret dogfighting ring, which leads to an unexpected move by one of the team members.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>Gibbs and Fornell's crusade to find the head of the drug ring responsible for Fornell's daughter Emily's overdose comes to a climax; Gibbs and Vance finally let the team in on a case that has dangerous implications.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>Vance assigns McGee, Torres and Bishop to COVID compliance duty at a foreign affairs summit, where they discover a link to another NCIS team's murder case.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU races to capture the vigilantes behind a series of attacks taking place every 27 minutes in the nation's capital; Prentiss and Unit Chief Andrew Mendoza lead the effort to identify the vigilantes and what's motivating them.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates a double homicide and kidnapping in New Hampshire; Rossi's plans to elevate his relationship with Krystall don't go as planned.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A professor from Lewis' past tips off the BAU to an alarming number of overdose deaths of patients who just completed rehab.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Prentiss faces her past when the BAU is sent to investigate the murders of prominent businessmen, all of whom are missing their hearts; Prentiss plans a romantic first date with Mendoza, but the evening is cut short by an urgent call from Rossi.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team heads to Portland, Ore., to investigate a chilling abduction that may be linked to a local couple who were killed in their home a week earlier.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
