<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a young girl is kidnapped from her daycare, the team must help her parents navigate a debt owed to the deadly gang in their neighborhood; Maggie struggles to focus on the case when her sister returns from rehab.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>A widow is shocked that her new &quot;boyfriend&quot; is the manipulative leader of a terrorist group planning an attack; Scola is reminded of his brother's death on 9/11; Tiffany worries about his emotional choices during the investigation.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After Rina is critically wounded while heading to work with Jubal; the team makes the chilling discovery that a vengeful Vargas orchestrated the shooting from behind bars and continues to target the rest of their team and their loved ones.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a key witness in a murder trial is found dead in her hotel, detectives get involved in a spiraling case that unravels into an intricate conspiracy.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Detectives Lupo and Bernard think a violent armed robbery might be a scare tactic for a shakedown.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a campaign volunteer is murdered, Detectives Lupo and Bernard end up dealing with more than just dirty politics.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a journalist is found dead in an abandoned apartment, the investigation uncovers a relationship between the victim and a daytime talk-show host, who admits to a series of workplace affairs and a blackmail threat.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a family is found murdered at home, a runaway teenager becomes a suspect.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The investigation of a 16-year-old student whose body was burned causes Lupo and Bernard to question the young person he mentored, the last person to see him alive; the investigation draws attention to a vicious high-school rivalry.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A woman's body is found stashed on a food service cart in a hotel; Detectives Bernard and Lupo discover evidence that leads them to a medical school research project.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>After a man is found guilty of a hate crime, Emily Ryan (Amy Madigan) and The Innocence Collective try to prove his innocence.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Detectives Lupo and Bernard tackle a complex case when four police officers are shot.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When Dr. Oscar Silva, an environmental scientist, is poisoned during a conference, Lupo and Bernard suspect competitors from Silva's field of study.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When the body of a model is found burning in an alley, Detectives Lupo and Bernard search for her killer.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a young heiress dies of an apparent drug overdose, Lupo and Bernard begin to suspect her cousin, whose inheritance increased after her death.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A man's double life comes to light after he is stabbed to death.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a reality TV crew finds a dead man's body locked in a dog cage, detectives suspect the victim's wife.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Mission: Impossible Rogue Nation</title>
    <desc>With the IMF now disbanded and Ethan Hunt (Tom Cruise) out in the cold, a new threat - called the Syndicate - soon emerges. The Syndicate is a network of highly skilled operatives who are dedicated to establishing a new world order via an escalating series of terrorist attacks. Faced with what may be the most impossible mission yet, Ethan gathers his team and joins forces with Ilsa Faust (Rebecca Ferguson), a disavowed British agent who may or may not be a member of this deadly rogue nation.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10989210_v_h8_be.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Mission: Impossible - Ghost Protocol</title>
    <desc>Blamed for a terrorist attack on the Kremlin, Ethan Hunt (Tom Cruise) and the entire IMF agency are disavowed by the U.S. government, while the president initiates the Ghost Protocol. Forced to go &quot;off the grid&quot; - left without resources or backup - Hunt must somehow clear the agency's name and prevent another attack. Complicating matters even more, Ethan must undertake the impossible mission with a group of fellow IMF fugitives whose actual motives are suspect.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8493689_v_h8_br.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Mission: Impossible Rogue Nation</title>
    <desc>With the IMF now disbanded and Ethan Hunt (Tom Cruise) out in the cold, a new threat - called the Syndicate - soon emerges. The Syndicate is a network of highly skilled operatives who are dedicated to establishing a new world order via an escalating series of terrorist attacks. Faced with what may be the most impossible mission yet, Ethan gathers his team and joins forces with Ilsa Faust (Rebecca Ferguson), a disavowed British agent who may or may not be a member of this deadly rogue nation.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10989210_v_h8_be.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>An 85-year-old patient (Red Buttons) accuses Dr. Carter of killing his wife more than 10 years earlier; Dr. Pratt helps a victim of domestic violence and winds up making a date with the social worker assigned to her case.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891891_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Newly appointed chief resident Morris clashes with Pratt as they deal with casualties from a fire at an apartment building; Lewis takes out on Carter her frustrations about not getting tenure, and Weaver's attempts to calm Lewis make things worse.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891891_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Pratt rages at Neela for performing a complicated procedure on an infant; Carter reunites with Kem (Thandie Newton) when he rushes to Paris after learning that her mother has been hospitalized.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891891_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Disaster casualties flood the ER, which is short-handed because most of the staff is at Dr. Carter's going-away party; Dr. Pratt works up the courage to confront his father, Charlie (Danny Glover).</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891891_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>When Sam's diabetic son runs away without his insulin, she suspects the boy has gone to find his father in Colorado and reports him missing.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891892_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>An infant's life hangs in the balance when a surrogate mother makes a dramatic decision after being injured in a car crash; Pratt is forced to deal with his feelings about the past after he encounters his estranged father (Danny Glover).</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891892_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>A Time to Kill</title>
    <desc>Carl Lee Hailey (Samuel L. Jackson) is a heartbroken black father who avenges his daughter's brutal rape by shooting the bigoted men responsible for the crime as they are on their way to trial. He turns to Jake Brigance (Matthew McConaughey), an untested lawyer, to defend him. Brigance struggles to believe that he can get Hailey acquitted in this small, segregated Southern town, given Hailey's race and the deliberate nature of his crimes, but Carl has unshakable faith in him.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18232_v_h8_bo.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>The Pelican Brief</title>
    <desc>Taut thriller about a young law student whose legal brief about the assassination of two Supreme Court justices causes her to be targeted by killers. She realizes just how accurate her accusations have been when her lover and mentor is murdered. Forced to go on the run in New Orleans, she is aided by a journalist who helps her unravel a conspiracy involving senior government figures.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15247_v_h8_bc.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>A Time to Kill</title>
    <desc>Carl Lee Hailey (Samuel L. Jackson) is a heartbroken black father who avenges his daughter's brutal rape by shooting the bigoted men responsible for the crime as they are on their way to trial. He turns to Jake Brigance (Matthew McConaughey), an untested lawyer, to defend him. Brigance struggles to believe that he can get Hailey acquitted in this small, segregated Southern town, given Hailey's race and the deliberate nature of his crimes, but Carl has unshakable faith in him.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18232_v_h8_bo.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
