<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>A multiple-car accident floods the emergency room with patients; a patient (Malgoscha Gebel) believed to be mentally impaired surprises the doctors.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891881_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates a spooky local ghost story of the &quot;Tall Man&quot; and the clues it provides when two people go missing in the woods; a third person mysteriously surfaces the following day with limited details as to what happened to her friends.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates four murders along the eastern seaboard; the crimes become personal for Alvez when the team discovers there are ties to his time spent in pursuit of a notorious hit man; Alvez and his girlfriend decide to move in together.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU races to capture the vigilantes behind a series of attacks taking place every 27 minutes in the nation's capital; Prentiss and Unit Chief Andrew Mendoza lead the effort to identify the vigilantes and what's motivating them.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates a double homicide and kidnapping in New Hampshire; Rossi's plans to elevate his relationship with Krystall don't go as planned.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A professor from Lewis' past tips off the BAU to an alarming number of overdose deaths of patients who just completed rehab.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Prentiss faces her past when the BAU is sent to investigate the murders of prominent businessmen, all of whom are missing their hearts; Prentiss plans a romantic first date with Mendoza, but the evening is cut short by an urgent call from Rossi.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team heads to Portland, Ore., to investigate a chilling abduction that may be linked to a local couple who were killed in their home a week earlier.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team flies to Iowa to investigate the disappearance of three 10-year-old children who appear to have been abducted from their homes, with surveillance video from a park as their only lead to finding the children's whereabouts.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
