<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>A loving husband and father of two is kidnapped after accidentally getting involved in illegal dealings far beyond what he imagined; Jubal must make a difficult decision regarding his family and their future.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:52AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a Wall Street investor is murdered, the team is led to an insider-trading ring that uses unconventional methods to gain information; OA struggles to maintain confidence in his budding relationship with Mona.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:52AM</start>
    <finish>06:44AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When a board member of a soon-to-be-public medical tech company is murdered, the team tries to find out who had the most to gain from his death; OA is conflicted when pressure to help a family member is at odds with his commitment to tell the truth.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>06:44AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>A car crash results in the death of a photographer; Maggie sympathizes with his widow when she notices similarities with her own husband's death.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:26AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After an altercation with a student, teacher Patrick Miller goes missing, leading the team to investigate everyone who might have had a grudge against him; a key witness in the case steps up to help.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>08:26AM</start>
    <finish>09:18AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>A former kidnapping victim is linked to a series of murders that includes the daughter of an NYPD detective; Kristen begins to doubt her ability as an agent after a training exercise leaves her shaken.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>09:18AM</start>
    <finish>10:09AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a businessman with a history of harassment claims against him is killed, the team suspects the killer may be one of his many accusers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>10:09AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Carter's inquisitive girlfriend (Thandie Newton) makes an impact as she observes hospital operations; Gallant is almost shot during a domestic dispute; Weaver dedicates a center to the memory of Dr. Romano.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891890_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Sam treats an abused, pregnant teenager; Carter shows Makemba (Thandie Newton) the wonders of wintertime; emergency-room mayhem shocks a risk-assessment expert (Richard Kline); Dr. Pratt and Abby restrain a man who has tuberculosis.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891890_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Claustrophobic Neela accompanies a poisoned newborn into a hyperbaric chamber; Lewis and Abby treat a man covered in blood; a boy tests positive for leukemia; Chen returns from China with her sick father in tow.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891890_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>A psychotic patient threatens the hospital with a stolen Army tank; Dr. Kovac's French friend visits; an E.R. staffer has a heart attack; 13-year-olds have chlamydia.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891890_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Carter's protege takes his advice too far and treats a brain-injury patient; Dr. Gallant falsifies a medical report; Chuck defends Dr. Lewis from a pervert; Dr. Chen searches for a caretaker for her combative father.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891890_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Weaver tries to save Sandy after she is severely injured fighting a fire; Dr. Lewis is confined to bed rest; tensions between Dr. Gallant and Neela mount; Dr. Corday gets a pleasant surprise.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891890_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team heads to Portland, Ore., to investigate a chilling abduction that may be linked to a local couple who were killed in their home a week earlier.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team flies to Iowa to investigate the disappearance of three 10-year-old children who appear to have been abducted from their homes, with surveillance video from a park as their only lead to finding the children's whereabouts.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Rossi questions his actions in the aftermath of a struggle with a serial killer who appears to have outsmarted the BAU.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates a string of murders taking place in supposedly haunted houses in Lewiston, Maine.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Rossi prepares to marry Krystall; the team investigates a series of fatal shootings following car accidents.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team investigates an unsub with striking similarities to Rossi's latest obsession, &quot;The Chameleon.&quot;.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team searches for Everett Lynch and his daughter; Spencer has a meaningful visit with his mother.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team investigates a series of seemingly random fatal explosions throughout Kentucky and Tennessee.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The staged suicide of a petty officer turns out to be murder; the team secretly works on an online dating profile for Pride.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>A Mardi Gras celebration at Pride's bar is cut short when he and Mayor Douglas Hamilton (Steven Weber) are abducted by unknown assailants.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>03:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Evidence suggests that the man responsible for saving a lieutenant's life is a soldier who was captured in Afghanistan.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Special Agent Pride and the team uncover a domestic drug ring - led by Sonja's childhood friend, Marion Watkins (Samaire Armstrong), that is producing cocaine.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>A bank holdup leads the team to a safe deposit box, the contents of which have the potential to destroy national security; Kristen is eager to get back into field work while other team members still have their concerns.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The son of a retired FBI agent is kidnapped, and the team must investigate if it's an act of revenge; Isobel must make a hard call when information from the past comes to light.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When an attorney is found dead near the body of a private escort, the team must piece together what connected the two seemingly random victims; Jubal's connection with one of the victims makes finding the killer much more personal.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a truck filled with armor-piercing rifles is hijacked, the team works to discover who stole it, and what they have planned for the stolen weapons; a friend from OA's past returns to help with the case, but OA isn't sure he can trust him.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After the police ignore a desperate father's plea for help, he abducts a billionaire's daughter and holds her hostage in a safe room until his own missing child is returned to him; Jubal puts his hostage negotiation skills to the test.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When the team is called to the scene of a murder, it quickly suspects political motivation; Maggie contemplates a decision that could affect her entire career.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The murder of an automobile mechanic leads detectives to uncover a fraudulent online relationship, a bizarre case of blackmail and money laundering.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The murder of a jeweler leads detectives to an illegal prostitution ring; Jack McCoy's job is threatened.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The beating death of a stockbroker causes a battle of epic proportions between the victim's family and the faction responsible for his death.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A mentally challenged man is reunited with his mother, who gave him away after his brother was killed.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A young woman (guest star Jena Malone) escapes from a polygamous cult.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A crane collapse kills a man, and it may not have been an accident; a rift forms between Jack McCoy and Michael Cutter.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A revered sheriff becomes a possible conspirator in a case involving a murdered tourist.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Detectives Lupo and Bernard investigate when the writer of a best-selling memoir is found dead in a community of male prostitutes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Cutter is determined to expose misconduct when he realizes an old friend working in the system is obstructing justice in the murder of an environmentalist.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>While investigating the murder of two divorce lawyers, detectives Lupo and Bernard uncover a child slave-trade ring.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The murder of the plaintiff in a high-profile lawsuit against a major airline leads detectives to a defense attorney (Dallas Roberts) who is willing to do whatever it takes to ensure his big payday.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When the son and housekeeper of a pair of prominent biologists are murdered, detectives suspect the couple's work on a controversial pharmaceutical study may have made them targets for the killer.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The owner of a trucking company, Vic Russell, is found dead after a business meeting; detectives uncover information that leads them to believe that Russell had ties to the Russian mob.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>An NYPD officer kills a troubled fellow officer who took hostages at gunpoint; detectives Lupo and Bernard find valuable stolen documents and a dead body at the man's apartment.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
