<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>After the body of a Marine lieutenant is found hidden under an 18-wheeler, the team tracks the vehicle's previous locations to pinpoint the crime scene and suspect; Sloane encourages the team to sit down and talk about Ziva's recent reappearance.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS</title>
    <desc>The team links a bizarre crime scene at Arlington National Cemetery to a string of attacks on homeless veterans; Vance orders McGee, Bishop and Torres to complete hours of evidence garage cleanup for withholding information.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p184930_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU takes charge of a hostage situation at a law firm where Matt Simmons' wife works.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU is called upon when bioterrorism is suspected in a series of mysterious deaths; Garcia visits her stepbrother to take care of a difficult family issue.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU is called to Taos, N.M., when someone targets victims' temporal lobes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team questions the credibility of a former FBI agent's bizarre account.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When Reid and Garcia are abducted by a mass murderer, it's up to the rest of the team to find them; the BAU looks to their past to solve why the two heroes have been targeted.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team tracks a serial killer when remains of numerous victims are found in the walls of an elderly couple's home; the hunt becomes urgent after the BAU learns the killer's specific ritual of when to strike; Rossi reconnects with his ex-wife.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Packages with gruesome contents are delivered to six people in the Washington, D.C.. area; Simmons and Kristy struggle to connect with their son, David, who is suspended from school for aggressive behavior.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>03:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Soon after the BAU steps in to help local law enforcement isolate a suspect for a murder, a second person who is related to the first victim is killed under similar circumstances; Prentiss is concerned about Garcia's behavior.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The team joins forces with several federal agencies to stop a sniper who has been targeting crowded events in the city; FBI Special Agent Tammy Gregario begins investigating Pride's team.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Pride faces more repercussions from the FBI after he helps a former Navy Intelligence Analyst who is the primary suspect in a multiple homicide case.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>After the discovery of a petty officer's body inside a sports arena, evidence leads Pride and the NCIS team to a kidnapping case of another petty officer, last seen in Mexico.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The NCIS must come to the rescue of one of its own when Sebastian is kidnapped while dining in a restaurant with his mother; Sebastian relies on his gaming skills in a prison break.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The NCIS and the FBI investigate a private plane crash in the bayou that killed three sailors; Sonja and Lasalle interview candidates for a job opening on the team.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>A Navy SEAL candidate is murdered weeks before his graduation; Wade seeks Pride's help when her adopted son announces his plan to join the Navy.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>A sailor is murdered during a rowdy motorcycle rally in the city; Lasalle seeks personal advice from Gregorio.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The police break up a dog-fighting ring and discover a woman's finger inside one of the dead animals; detectives plot to trick an ambitious reporter.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When an art dealer is found stoned to death, detectives suspect that her killing may be linked to some of the art in her gallery, but a deeper look into her personal life reveals another motive.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a notorious hustler is found dead, Cyrus Lupo discovers that his partner, Ed Green, is the shooter; internal affairs takes over the case, forcing Green to reveal his troubled past.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Detectives Cyrus Lupo and Kevin Benard have reason to believe a cult is involved when a novelist is found dead in her car; Assistant District Attorney Michael Cutter has trouble prosecuting when several jury members fear for their own safety.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a legal aid striker is killed outside the courthouse, the sand in his wounds leads detectives to investigate a greensman; due to the strike and shortage of defense attorneys, Rubirosa and Cutter must face each other in court.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The murder of an automobile mechanic leads detectives to uncover a fraudulent online relationship, a bizarre case of blackmail and money laundering.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The murder of a jeweler leads detectives to an illegal prostitution ring; Jack McCoy's job is threatened.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The beating death of a stockbroker causes a battle of epic proportions between the victim's family and the faction responsible for his death.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A mentally challenged man is reunited with his mother, who gave him away after his brother was killed.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A young woman (guest star Jena Malone) escapes from a polygamous cult.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A crane collapse kills a man, and it may not have been an accident; a rift forms between Jack McCoy and Michael Cutter.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A revered sheriff becomes a possible conspirator in a case involving a murdered tourist.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Detectives Lupo and Bernard investigate when the writer of a best-selling memoir is found dead in a community of male prostitutes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Cutter is determined to expose misconduct when he realizes an old friend working in the system is obstructing justice in the murder of an environmentalist.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>While investigating the murder of two divorce lawyers, detectives Lupo and Bernard uncover a child slave-trade ring.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The murder of the plaintiff in a high-profile lawsuit against a major airline leads detectives to a defense attorney (Dallas Roberts) who is willing to do whatever it takes to ensure his big payday.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>03:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When the son and housekeeper of a pair of prominent biologists are murdered, detectives suspect the couple's work on a controversial pharmaceutical study may have made them targets for the killer.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The owner of a trucking company, Vic Russell, is found dead after a business meeting; detectives uncover information that leads them to believe that Russell had ties to the Russian mob.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team investigates an extremist gun group after an anti-gun lobbyist building is bombed; SAC Bashar dangles a possible promotion for OA.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team realize they have a cross-country serial killer on their hands; the case has ties to Isobel's father, Robert, and his hotel, leading to revelations about their fractured relationship.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After an immigration agent is fatally shot at a hockey game, the team attempts to find the shooter, who they believe may also be targeting Congressman Curtis Grange, who was at the same game.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When a young couple is found murdered in a New York City park after returning from a vacation, the team searches for a suspect linked to the drug trade; Scola turns over a new leaf when it comes to his relationships.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>OA is forced to confront one of his biggest fears when the team discovers that deadly sarin gas may have been sold to terrorists.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When a morning show host is murdered inside her home, the team tracks the killer; things become awkward for Scola when agent Nina Chase becomes part of the team during Maggie's recovery.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>A patient (Alan Rosenberg) will not last the night without a heart transplant; Ross admonishes a woman for not buying her daughter asthma medicine.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891881_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>A pizza-delivery man crashes through the hospital's doors; a deadbeat sister (Kathleen Wilhoite) wants to stay with Lewis.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891881_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Nurse Hathaway tells Dr. Ross of her future domestic plans; Dr. Benton realizes something important about his fellowship rival; Dr. Lewis has a surprise birthday party.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891881_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Ross tries to maintain order at the emergency room on Greene's day off; a rape victim is afraid to cooperate with police.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891881_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>An injured teen confesses to Hathaway that he was responsible for two deaths in a car accident but denies it when police arrive.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891881_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>A multiple-car accident floods the emergency room with patients; a patient (Malgoscha Gebel) believed to be mentally impaired surprises the doctors.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891881_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates a spooky local ghost story of the &quot;Tall Man&quot; and the clues it provides when two people go missing in the woods; a third person mysteriously surfaces the following day with limited details as to what happened to her friends.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates four murders along the eastern seaboard; the crimes become personal for Alvez when the team discovers there are ties to his time spent in pursuit of a notorious hit man; Alvez and his girlfriend decide to move in together.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU races to capture the vigilantes behind a series of attacks taking place every 27 minutes in the nation's capital; Prentiss and Unit Chief Andrew Mendoza lead the effort to identify the vigilantes and what's motivating them.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates a double homicide and kidnapping in New Hampshire; Rossi's plans to elevate his relationship with Krystall don't go as planned.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A professor from Lewis' past tips off the BAU to an alarming number of overdose deaths of patients who just completed rehab.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Prentiss faces her past when the BAU is sent to investigate the murders of prominent businessmen, all of whom are missing their hearts; Prentiss plans a romantic first date with Mendoza, but the evening is cut short by an urgent call from Rossi.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team heads to Portland, Ore., to investigate a chilling abduction that may be linked to a local couple who were killed in their home a week earlier.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU team flies to Iowa to investigate the disappearance of three 10-year-old children who appear to have been abducted from their homes, with surveillance video from a park as their only lead to finding the children's whereabouts.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
