<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>A professor from Lewis' past tips off the BAU to an alarming number of overdose deaths of patients who just completed rehab.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The team investigates the death of a Naval microbiologist whose hobby as a &quot;myth buster&quot; resulted in his death at the hands of a legendary bayou creature; Agent Khoury conducts an investigation into previous actions of Deputy Director Van Cleef.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10779088_b_h8_bd.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>As New Orleans grapples with the effects of COVID-19, Pride sends Tammy and Carter to investigate a suspicious death aboard an offshore humanitarian ship; Wade is overwhelmed by the high volume in the morgue due to COVID-19.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18964140_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Tammy and Carter continue to investigate a suspicious death aboard a COVID-infected humanitarian ship; Pride and the team discover what may be the key to finding the killer; Wade helps a grieving woman.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18964140_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Pride and the team take on a group of dirty cops when they discover that a murder victim was also a key witness in multiple excessive force cases; Tammy faces the reality of being in a new relationship.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18964140_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The team continue to investigate the murder of an officer who was about to blow the whistle on police misconduct; Pride must get creative in order to finally get rid of the dirty cops; the mayor asks Pride to join her new task force.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18964140_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>The team investigates a suspicious death and the missing key piece of evidence is a top secret, high-tech battery; Pride and the team realize there could be deadly consequences if it falls into the wrong hands.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18964140_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>When a torpedo hits a fishing trawler at sea, the entire Gulf Coast is in jeopardy as Pride and NCIS race to find the submarine before it can strike again.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p18964140_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When New York's most infamous baseball fan is stabbed to death in a bar, detectives suspect the killer is probably a sports aficionado.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A female Japanese tourist is shot to death, prompting an investigation that leads the police to the victim's husband.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The detectives believe a bride, motivated by greed, killed her groom after the wedding, until they find the murder weapon in her daughter's room.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>When a deliveryman is gunned down on his route, Briscoe and Green discover that he was active on a Web site for arranged liaisons and that his wife had just bought a gun.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Terms of the Geneva Convention come into play when the sister of a former inmate at Abu Ghraib prison is suspected of murdering a female Guardsman in the second Gulf War.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The ex-wife of a firefighter who married a rich Sept. 11 widow is suspected of murder.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The death of a prison gang member leads Fontana and Green to suspect the victim's former associates until they learn the deceased also had a running battle with a hard-nosed corrections officer.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>Detectives investigate the deaths of two college students and find both were participating in a pharmaceutical company's secret testing program for an antidepressant that has resulted in many suicides.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>An illegal firearms sting backfires when two officers are slain, and Green poses as a gun buyer to try to capture the killers, who were able to identify the officers via a Web site identifying undercover cops.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>McCoy must determine whether charges should be filed in civil court or in criminal court when a novelist's death seems to have been caused by careless liposuction, but Branch finds a recurring pattern of negligence by the doctor.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>McCoy takes the issue of gay marriage before the state's Supreme Court when he is unable to compel a man to testify against a crooked developer because the two say they are married.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>The detectives proceed with skeptical caution when a radio personality, known to stage fake muggings for publicity, claims to have been shot and almost killed.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>A philandering jeweler with ties to the Russian mob is one of four people shot to death on a sidewalk, and Fontana and Green learn the victim was cooperating with federal authorities until his murder.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order</title>
    <desc>After a bloody massacre of heroin dealers, Fontana and Green pinpoint a drug-dealing Afghan warlord as their primary suspect, and McCoy and Southerlyn prosecute despite pressure from the State Department.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p183983_b_h8_bm.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
