<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Pattrn</title>
    <desc>Elevating the conversation about climate, extreme weather, sustainability and green living.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21886602_b_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Rocky Mountain Wreckers</title>
    <desc>After a tractor pulling double trailers rolls over during a freak snowstorm, Mountain Recovery faces massive damage and an impossible deadline; heavy winds assault I-80 in Wyoming, closing the highway and pushing Jim and Brendan to their limits.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29136492_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Rocky Mountain Wreckers</title>
    <desc>When freezing fog ices over I-80, Brendan gets his first test on a rollover recovery; heavy snow causes chaos for Big Jon and Kory as they battle a difficult jackknife; a moving van blasts off the highway in a snowstorm, pushing the Stauffer's team to perform a long pull up a steep incline.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29136492_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Rocky Mountain Wreckers</title>
    <desc>Charlie rescues a family trapped in a live lane of traffic; the Stauffer's Utah crew battles to upright a rollover pinned between moving traffic and open water; a sinkhole swallows a 200,000-pound excavator.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29136492_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Rocky Mountain Wreckers</title>
    <desc>Two separate crashes in Utah spur the Stauffer's crew to perform a pair of dramatic recoveries; Bad Grandpa goes for a plunge when the Mountain Recovery team attempts a daring job on a raging river.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29136492_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Rocky Mountain Wreckers</title>
    <desc>Intense winds and icy roads send a semi to the edge of a sheer drop; heavy snowfall forces Charlie out of his comfort zone and into a much bigger truck than normal; Bad Grandpa schools the boss in the art of recovery.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29136492_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Rocky Mountain Wreckers</title>
    <desc>Charlie struggles with a surprise storm on Vail Pass; Brendan faces pressure after a promotion; Cory's rigging and patience are tested by a heavy manure load.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p29136492_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
