<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Weekend Recharge</title>
    <desc>Though it has &quot;weekend&quot; in the title, this show discusses the week ahead in addition to offering suggestions for what to do on Saturday and Sunday. Weather Channel meteorologists go beyond the elements outside and into the realm of lifestyle tips. Each host has a recurring segment on &quot;Weekend Recharge,&quot; which include helping parents get a fresh start to each day and explaining how the weather is expected to impact the weekend's scheduled sports action.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11601105_b_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Weekend Recharge</title>
    <desc>Though it has &quot;weekend&quot; in the title, this show discusses the week ahead in addition to offering suggestions for what to do on Saturday and Sunday. Weather Channel meteorologists go beyond the elements outside and into the realm of lifestyle tips. Each host has a recurring segment on &quot;Weekend Recharge,&quot; which include helping parents get a fresh start to each day and explaining how the weather is expected to impact the weekend's scheduled sports action.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11601105_b_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Pattrn</title>
    <desc>Elevating the conversation about climate, extreme weather, sustainability and green living.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21886602_b_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Timber Titans</title>
    <desc>As a crew races to prep logs for a new heavy lift helicopter, a substitute pilot is tested on postage-stamp sized helipads; another logging crew moves their 40-year-old yarder onto a new block, but a series of mechanical issues set them back.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p26505693_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Timber Titans</title>
    <desc>A logging crew has only days to finish before the spring thaw destroys the road; another team is rushing to find enough salvage wood to keep their heavy-lift helicopter busy and affordable.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p26505693_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Timber Titans</title>
    <desc>Summer is in full effect, and that means moving into the final phase of loading four million dollars worth of timber onto a giant floating barge; the clock is ticking for loggers as they continue to deal with their loader and a wildfire.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p26505693_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Highway Thru Hell</title>
    <desc>James Luke and Black Sheep rush to clear a tractor trailer on its side loaded with heavy doors. An 18-wheeler filled with firewood tests Cam and Colin.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9388134_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Highway Thru Hell</title>
    <desc>A polar vortex brings extreme cold and brutal working conditions to truck drivers and heavy wrecker operators on The Coq; Colin fights to recover a frozen rig; Cam finds himself in a dilemma with one of Jamie's classic wreckers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9388134_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Weather Channel US</name>
    <title>Highway Thru Hell</title>
    <desc>A terrifying crash involving one of their own shocks Team Reliable; Dylan and Merv pair up to lift a heavy load of steel pilings off a highway; Cam races to rescue a fellow tow operator stuck on a blind corner.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9388134_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
