<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>At the world-famous Iowa State Fair, sampling some award-winning new food items; there's a new take on chicken and waffles and a massive meat meal all wrapped up to eat on the midway; the Pork-Tato; the Hash Brown Handful.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Noah Cappe celebrates Memorial Day weekend and uncovers some tasty treasures at the pirate-themed Contraband Days festival.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>A traditional Indian fry bread stuffed with some non-traditional ingredients; trying the Great Pacific Pita and the Deep Fried Chili Dog; eating the Marionberry Volcano; visiting the El Dorado County Fair in Placerville, Calif.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's tasty travels bring him to Manchester, New Hampshire for an epic portion of barbecue that's served on a shovel at KC's Rib Shack; the deluxe cheeseburger mac; a ghost pepper-infused inferno burger challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's tries a falafel sandwich before he tackles the Monte Cristo Reeto with turkey, ham, bacon and Swiss cheese wrapped in a tortilla; the Bay Area's biggest bowls of ramen in the Masumo Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb heads to Ocean City, Maryland to dive into a massive jumbo lump crab cake sandwich, make some of the area's iconic salt water taffy candies and fight to stay afloat in the Titanic Sundae Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey fries up a Latin staple, tackles a Stone Age feast, and makes a four-pound deli platter in the Chompie's Day at the Deli Challenge; indulgent brunch food; a corn bread and potato hash topped with a turkey leg.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey treks to Mystic, Conn. for a bonkers burger; crazy coastal feast and food with a ridiculously massive sundae in Mel's Downtown Creamery's Big Kahuna Challenge; 30-day dry-aged burgers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's challengers include a 3-pound almond butter and jelly sandwich known as the Elvis Challenge, a four-meat pizza with a tater tot topper and a brisket sandwich piled high with burnt ends and spicy pickle slaw.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb rides the wave to Virginia Beach, Va., for a street corn fritter-topped burger, a decadent croissant-muffin hybrid and a dozen-egg duel with the Corned Beef Omelet Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21343487_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's tasty trek takes him to Santa Barbara, California, where he first meets up with a tri-tip steak sandwich with homemade barbecue sauce and apple horseradish; steamed local crab; eight cheeseburger sliders with a portion of tot-chos.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>From lobster roll sandwiches and fresh East Coast oysters to Italian sandwiches and whoopie pies, Andrew Zimmern explores the seaside city of Portland, Maine, loaded with classic New England fare.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew Zimmern visits Prague, a pilsner-lover's paradise in the Czech Republic; the city's cuisine is full of hearty comfort classics like pork knuckle marinated in lager, mushroom soup, sweet plum pastries, and a lot of dumplings.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>25 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>From sweet and savory BBQ pork and enormously artful mountains of lobster to herbaceous Jamaican flatbreads and sinfully gooey butter tarts, Andrew showcases the diverse eats of Toronto, Canada.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>26 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <id>CookingChannel.us</id>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew Zimmern samples some of the best cuisine St. John's, Newfoundland, has to offer; from succulent blue mussels steamed in local beer and creamy cod au gratin to hearty moose stew and savory rabbit pie.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>26 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
