<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>Haylie Duff visits one of his most treasured New Orleans spots, serving crunchy po' boys and spicy barbecue shrimp; in Kansas City, Mo., Michael meets a team that smokes some of the best burnt ends around.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>A triple meat-stacked sandwich with smoked pork belly, bologna and chicken liver pate; deep-fried soft-shell crab patty; jumbo, spicy, fried chicken wings zing with a Szechuan peppercorn sauce in Seattle.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>A traditional Rhode Island hot wiener in a crepe topped with chili; a steak patty topped with Chinese char siu slaw and nestled inside a soft steamed bao bun; cold-smoked baby back ribs on a bed of flaming hay; an 18-ounce bacon steak.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>At the Meriden Daffodil Festival in Connecticut, Noah Cappe samples Italian American family recipes turned carnival fair; he takes in the seafood scene at the Washington State Spring Fair and some rocky road-ified fries at the Four States Fair.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>At the Kansas State Fair; chicken wings get a fair-friendly treatment at the Oklahoma State Fair.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Noah starts the day at the Shasta District Fair in Anderson, Calif. by devouring Southern-style Biscuits 'n' Gravy Breakfast and a Cowboy Funnel Cake; he visits the National Balloon Classic in Iowa for an Iowa-only pizza.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>The fairground wasn't made for forks and knives, so Noah Cappe is checking out the fork-free favorites and the hand-held carnival treats that keep people coming back.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's edible expedition takes him to Portland, Maine, for a lobster-topped cheeseburger and a potato-donut-cannoli mashup; the Taco Gigante Challenge: a footlong hard taco packed with ground beef, chicken and carnitas.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey treks to Mystic, Conn. for a bonkers burger; crazy coastal feast and food with a ridiculously massive sundae in Mel's Downtown Creamery's Big Kahuna Challenge; 30-day dry-aged burgers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>A sandwich mashup of fried chicken and pulled pork; a porchetta sandwich from a roaming rotisserie food truck; a 49-ounce porterhouse steak and sizable side in the Gold Rush-inspired 49er Club Steak Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's tries a falafel sandwich before he tackles the Monte Cristo Reeto with turkey, ham, bacon and Swiss cheese wrapped in a tortilla; the Bay Area's biggest bowls of ramen in the Masumo Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb cracks into crab legs fit for a king at Slippery Salmon Bar and Grill in Anchorage; reindeer meatloaf at Denali BrewPub; the mountainous, double-decker Seward's Folly caribou burger challenge at West Rib Pub and Grill.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's tasty travels bring him to Manchester, New Hampshire for an epic portion of barbecue that's served on a shovel at KC's Rib Shack; the deluxe cheeseburger mac; a ghost pepper-infused inferno burger challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>A sopapilla stuffed with carne asada; game-changing ice cream flavored with the local delicacy, green chiles; Casey Webb ends up in a challenge with three hubcap-sized pancakes weighing in at four pounds total.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb starts with a decadent brioche doughnut that's topped with brunch all-stars and then heads for the sea to dig oysters for a fresh feast; Finally, he faces three 24-ounce milkshakes at a creamery that has been dishing treats since 1928.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew Zimmern digs into the not-to-be-missed unique and exotic foods that define Chesapeake Bay.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew Zimmern digs into the not-to-be-missed unique and exotic foods that define a location, exploring where they came from, how they are prepared, and the right way to eat them.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew highlights Tuscan specialties like small-batch extra virgin olive oil, spicy fish stew served over crusty bread, chickpea pancakes and whole fish simmered quickly in spicy tomato sauce.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew looks at the inventive and time-honored eats of Genoa, Italy, home to big-league favorites like peasant-created seafood salad, pesto with pasta, and crispy, decadent flatbread.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
