<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Unique Eats</title>
    <desc>A pie that's filled with macaroni and cheese; nachos with a Japanese twist; doughnuts filled with jelly and fois gras; a chocolate cupcake with bacon.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8115030_b_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Unique Eats</title>
    <desc>Romantic eateries in New York City.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8115030_b_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Unique Eats</title>
    <desc>Restaurants that showcase unique and pioneering dishes that turn first time customers into long-time fans.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p8115030_b_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>The Best Thing I Ever Ate</title>
    <desc>Velselka's borscht in the East Village; smoked herring on the Upper West Side; hand pulled noodles in Chinatown; Cuban grilled corn at Cafe Habana in SoHo; Motorino's special round slice of pizza.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p297115_b_h8_am.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>The Best Thing I Ever Ate</title>
    <desc>Enjoying delicious food in Philadelphia; featuring pasta at Vetri; mashed potatoes at Parc; crepes at Creperie Beau Monde; Mexican tiramisu at Lolita; Philly cheesesteak at Tony Luke's; the Junkyard Special at Sarcone's Deli.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p297115_b_h8_am.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>The Best Thing I Ever Ate</title>
    <desc>San Diego may be the land of sun, surf and fun, but it's also home to some of the best dining spots around; a bacon burger at Hodad's; chilaquiles at Mexican hotspot Talavera; peanut butter spread at Spread; chocolate cake at Extraordinary Desserts.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p297115_b_h8_am.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>The Best Thing I Ever Ate</title>
    <desc>Dream-worthy oysters at Hog Island; the pork bun at Yank Sing; the souffle at Cafe Jacqueline; the strudel at Schmidt's; the pain au chocolat at Tartine.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p297115_b_h8_am.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>The Best Thing I Ever Ate</title>
    <desc>Heading to New Orleans for some seriously delicious, world-renownd food; Po' Boys at Johnny's; Drago's amazing oysters; Muffaletta at Domilises; gumbo at Dooky Chase's; pastries at Cafe Beignet.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p297115_b_h8_am.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>The Best Thing I Ever Ate</title>
    <desc>Divulging the secrets of Vegas cuisine; the double ribeye at SW Steakhouse; the langoustine at L'Atelier Joel Robechon; drunken noodles from Wazuzu; the Gambler's Special surf and turf at Mr. Lucky's 24/7.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p297115_b_h8_am.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods America</title>
    <desc>Andrew finds that Toronto is a melting pot of edgy eats; Horse heart salami; seal flipper pie; pig's ear.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9054212_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods America</title>
    <desc>Andrew Zimmern finds out that in Virginia, people aren't afraid to shake up tradition when it comes to food.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9054212_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew Zimmern shares a tour of the Iowa State Fair; fresh, locally grown sweet corn, baked sausage cavatelli and Dutch letter pastries; sandwiches like fried pork tenderloin, loose ground beef and the Italian Gizmo.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew reveals what makes the food scene in Krakow, Poland, delicious; the city's edible symbols take the form of pierogies, hearty stuffed cabbage rolls and whole-roasted pork knuckle.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew dives into the adventurous city of Zagreb in Croatia; the city's cuisine has a meat-focused menu and celebrates iconic dishes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew explores the charismatic city of Cork, Ireland, where fertile land and an expansive coastline make it a food lovers' haven; locals line up for traditional favorites and artisanal delicacies like Irish stew and drisheen.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew digs in to Puglia, a coastal region in the heel of Italy's boot; Puglia's simple but stunning dishes include orecchiette pasta, grilled octopus and stuffed pasticiotti pastries.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew Zimmern explores the cuisine of Sitka, Alaska, where the preparation of iconic Alaskan staples like king salmon, venison and rockfish has evolved with finesse.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's tries a falafel sandwich before he tackles the Monte Cristo Reeto with turkey, ham, bacon and Swiss cheese wrapped in a tortilla; the Bay Area's biggest bowls of ramen in the Masumo Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey treks to Mystic, Conn. for a bonkers burger; crazy coastal feast and food with a ridiculously massive sundae in Mel's Downtown Creamery's Big Kahuna Challenge; 30-day dry-aged burgers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey's eating adventure takes him to Fargo, N.D., for a hearty European take on a cheesy classic, a breakfast-dessert mash up, and the Boiler Room's Hot Dish Challenge; giant pretzels and over a dozen sausages.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb follows his nose to Long Island for an Italian chicken parmesan-pizza hybrid, a twist on a Jewish meat-and-potato tradition, and a 10-scoop battle against the Kitchen Sink Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21343487_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb makes his way to Richmond for a lesson on New Zealand-style savory pies, an elevated Jewish deli experience and a towering Ladder Burger Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21343487_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb ventures to Roswell, N.M., for a UFO-inspired Thanksgiving sandwich, a true taste of traditional Mexican food, and a barbecue battle with the 4-pound 10-98 Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21343487_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's appetizing adventure brings him to Detroit for the famous Detroit-style, Sicilian square pan pizza; a bourbon-peach cinnamon roll; M Wings Challenge: six massive jerk chicken wings tossed in fiery Scotch bonnet and ghost pepper sauce.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's tasty trek across America brings him to Boulder, Colo., for a bourbon burger blast, a gooey campfire classic and an insanely hot pizza loaded with three layers of ghost pepper.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21343487_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
