<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>The Best Thing I Ever Ate</title>
    <desc>Velselka's borscht in the East Village; smoked herring on the Upper West Side; hand pulled noodles in Chinatown; Cuban grilled corn at Cafe Habana in SoHo; Motorino's special round slice of pizza.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p297115_b_h8_am.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>The Best Thing I Ever Ate</title>
    <desc>Enjoying delicious food in Philadelphia; featuring pasta at Vetri; mashed potatoes at Parc; crepes at Creperie Beau Monde; Mexican tiramisu at Lolita; Philly cheesesteak at Tony Luke's; the Junkyard Special at Sarcone's Deli.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p297115_b_h8_am.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>The Best Thing I Ever Ate</title>
    <desc>San Diego may be the land of sun, surf and fun, but it's also home to some of the best dining spots around; a bacon burger at Hodad's; chilaquiles at Mexican hotspot Talavera; peanut butter spread at Spread; chocolate cake at Extraordinary Desserts.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p297115_b_h8_am.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods America</title>
    <desc>Andrew finds out if it is food that keeps Detroit's motor running. Andrew visits Motown and gets revved up about tasting some of the city's food, including iconic soul food and lamb brain sandwiches, in the heart of Arab America.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9054212_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods America</title>
    <desc>Andrew visits northern California where people are reinventing the way they look at food. Grilled dove hearts; barf flavored jelly beans; monkey face eel.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9054212_b_h8_ag.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew explores the classic tastes of Tel Aviv; rich in Middle-Eastern tradition, the Israeli city's food is a modern reflection of an ancient culture, featuring crispy falafel, savory schnitzel, world-renowned hummus and sweet malabi.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew explores the iconic eats of Lisbon, Portugal, where seafood reigns supreme, including sardines and shellfish feasts; late-night snacks are piled with pork, soups overflow with sausage and dessert is a religious experience, too.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Insanely juicy steak; perfect New York pizza; Jewish pastries; decadent cheesecake; Russia's take on ravioli.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Soul food classics like fried catfish and hush puppies, BBQ chicken, crunchy fried green tomatoes and refreshingly cool pie.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Legendary sun-dried beef; deep-fried chimichangas; bacon-wrapped hot dogs; shaved ice treats called raspados.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Blazing hot chicken to cool, sweet pie; savory pork chops and biscuits smothered in gravy; juicy BBQ.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>A triple-layer burger; Cuban-inspired ice cream flavored with cream cheese; guava and cookies; Casey Webb is joined by two teammates to go up against a monster 30-inch pizza challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's first stop is San Antonio's oldest restaurant, a German deli for the Wienerschnitzel, the Puffy Taco; the 3-pound Cinnamon Roll Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's challengers include a 3-pound almond butter and jelly sandwich known as the Elvis Challenge, a four-meat pizza with a tater tot topper and a brisket sandwich piled high with burnt ends and spicy pickle slaw.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb chows down on a historic Reuben sandwich, a soul food feast featuring fried chicken from a 100-year-old recipe and a monstrous pile of pork with all the breakfast fixings weighing more than 3 pounds.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb gets into the tailgate tradition with a green and gold burger piled high with bratwurst, cheese curds and jalapenos; a local fish fry with flaky Great Lakes whitefish; 12 crispy egg rolls.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's quest for the best brings him to the beaches of Delaware for an ice cream custard that has locals lining up and a brewery that blends two beloved bar foods; he takes on a daunting surf-and-turf challenge that's never been done before.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21343487_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's massive meals include a bacon-wrapped hot dog with a crazy combination of toppings and a foot long chicken burrito blanketed in ghost pepper sauce; a slow-roasted pork shank served with potato salad and sauerkraut.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb heads to Ocean City, Maryland to dive into a massive jumbo lump crab cake sandwich, make some of the area's iconic salt water taffy candies and fight to stay afloat in the Titanic Sundae Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
