<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Cake Hunters</title>
    <desc>Horror film fanatic Monica craves a wedding cake as spooky as a scary movie, but her fiance, Jesse, wants a cake that represents their home state of Maryland; three scary-talented bakers take a stab at creating a Maryland Wedding Cake of Horrors.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14892013_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Cake Hunters</title>
    <desc>Shivana and Spencer, want a wedding cake that tells their modern American love story while honoring their Indian and Middle Eastern backgrounds; bakers attempt to bridge the divide between old and new to create a 21st-century Taj Mahal cake.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14892073_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Cake Hunters</title>
    <desc>Kendelle wants a mature cake that celebrates music, theater and the arts, but her mom, Bambi, wants sugar, spice and everything nice for her baby girl; bakers are tasked with designing a birthday cake that unites and delights the whole family.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14892013_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Cake Hunters</title>
    <desc>Courtnei pictures a luxurious, towering cake featuring icicles, jewels and a custom monogram, while her groom, G, prefers technical gizmos and an edible snow globe; cake designers must turn this couple's brewing winter storm into a winter wonderland.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14892013_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Minutes away from desert trails, mountains and limitless outdoor adventures, Andrew highlights the delicious and iconic foods of Salt Lake City; classic dishes include a pastrami burger, steak tips with mole and Utah scones.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew explores Harlem, a neighborhood with a diverse cross-section of cultures; Andrew highlights its colorful restaurants offering soul food, Caribbean classics and the national dish of Senegal.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew Zimmern shares a tour of the Iowa State Fair; fresh, locally grown sweet corn, baked sausage cavatelli and Dutch letter pastries; sandwiches like fried pork tenderloin, loose ground beef and the Italian Gizmo.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew Zimmern explores the international flavors of the Bronx, N.Y.; Italian-influenced bites; dry-aged pork sausage; spicy Jamaican meat pastries.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>Michael Symon eats a spicy burger that ignites a four-alarm fire; chorizo-pineapple burger; cheesy grits with a pile of blood orange, and IPA, braised pork; a classic Reuben sandwich gets a smoky upgrade; spicy venison bologna.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17700313_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>A Sloppy Jai with lamb hash and 30 Indian spices; towers of Japanese-American fusion with katsu-style deep-fried burger patties; pastrami-spiced burnt ends pork belly and spicy, jalapeno-glazed lamb pops fresh out of the smoker.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>A slammin' sandwich with three different cuts of pork smothered in triple-cheese sauce; a flaming hot burger stuffed with spicy jalapeno Jack cheese and covered in Buffalo sauce; a brewery's drunken chicken pot pie.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>Josh Charles meets up with Michael at his favorite place for crab cakes in town; after a round of bocce ball, Michael introduces Josh to some of Baltimore's best new spots for juicy, inventive burgers and craft brews.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Noah Cappe's tummy wins big at the Clark County Fair and Rodeo in Nevada with the chili cheese cake and the penne alla cone; he keeps cozy with a hot cocoa pretzel at Winter Fest OC and visits Tallahassee, Fla., for a shortcake stuffed candy apple.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p25093810_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Noah Cappe visits the Nederland Heritage Festival for food and an egg-stravaganza; the Dogwood Festival for an Oh Boy! po'boy sandwich and cocoa bananas.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Arabian Nights-themed Riverside County Fair and National Date Festival in Indio, Calif.; Churro Dog; Clay County Agricultural Fair; Cubano Dog; Hawaiian Typhoon.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Manatee County Fair in Palmetto, Fla.; the Pizza Supremo Burger and the Ulti-Melt Burger; Sandia Loca; Kentucky classics at Hillbilly Days in Pikeville, Ky.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>The most stacked, loaded, saucy and succulent sandwiches around, from whiskey-and-foie gras decadence to a macaroni and cheese bun.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>All across America, folks cook up red, white and blue meals, from classics to contemporary updates, that pay tribute to tradition and tempt the taste buds.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>From seriously saucy barbecue sandwiches to nachos on a pizza and the perfect burger for &quot;Dirty Dancing,&quot; these restaurants serve up some of the best dishes in America's heartland.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>From bacon-wrapped meatloaf and a double-decker pizza burger to boozy French toast and smothered biscuit sandwiches, restaurants across the country offer up a warm, comforting hug of flavor.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>It's Chicago deep dish vs. Detroit pan and New York vs. St. Louis thin crust as pizzerias across the country roll out the dough for the pizza playoffs.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
