<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>In Minneapolis, Casey dines on the Juicy Lucy, a burger with a cheesy secret, a Ferris wheel full of sliders and bacon and a massive, three-foot long bahn mi, a beefy Vietnamese sandwich.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's latest detour brings him to St. Paul, Minn., for an indoor food truck park, a timeless diner and a colossal crepe piled high with Thai ice cream.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>The iconic foods of Hanoi, Vietnam, including sweet-and-sour snail soup, breakfast crepes filled with ground pork and sweet-potato fritters topped with shrimp.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Andrew Zimmern explores the cuisine of Brussels, Belgium, a city often overshadowed by its European neighbors; from Belgian waffles to steamed mussels and fries.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Bursting with beauty and culinary icons of near mythical proportion, the Greek island of Santorini is home to tomato fritters, lamb fricassee and natural delicacies like grilled octopus.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>From saffron-tinted risotto and warming minestrone to impossibly fluffy, fruity panettone, Andrew Zimmern shows how Milan's rich and refined dishes earned a place in the international culinary cannon.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
