<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey treks to Mystic, Conn. for a bonkers burger; crazy coastal feast and food with a ridiculously massive sundae in Mel's Downtown Creamery's Big Kahuna Challenge; 30-day dry-aged burgers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey's eating adventure takes him to Fargo, N.D., for a hearty European take on a cheesy classic, a breakfast-dessert mash up, and the Boiler Room's Hot Dish Challenge; giant pretzels and over a dozen sausages.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb follows his nose to Long Island for an Italian chicken parmesan-pizza hybrid, a twist on a Jewish meat-and-potato tradition, and a 10-scoop battle against the Kitchen Sink Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21343487_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb makes his way to Richmond for a lesson on New Zealand-style savory pies, an elevated Jewish deli experience and a towering Ladder Burger Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21343487_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb ventures to Roswell, N.M., for a UFO-inspired Thanksgiving sandwich, a true taste of traditional Mexican food, and a barbecue battle with the 4-pound 10-98 Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21343487_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's appetizing adventure brings him to Detroit for the famous Detroit-style, Sicilian square pan pizza; a bourbon-peach cinnamon roll; M Wings Challenge: six massive jerk chicken wings tossed in fiery Scotch bonnet and ghost pepper sauce.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's tasty trek across America brings him to Boulder, Colo., for a bourbon burger blast, a gooey campfire classic and an insanely hot pizza loaded with three layers of ghost pepper.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21343487_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
