<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods With Andrew Zimmern</title>
    <desc>Andrew tastes pig appendix and raw turtle testicle; hunting feral hogs and brewing ancestral pot likker.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p12858957_b_h10_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods With Andrew Zimmern</title>
    <desc>Andrew Zimmern takes a voyage of self-discovery across the Mojave Desert; from Palm Springs pickleball with oxtail stew and alien-inspired rejuvenation and jerky to a Sin City meal with Carrot Top, this journey explores the joy of escape.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14219827_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods With Andrew Zimmern</title>
    <desc>Andrew follows in the footsteps of Lewis and Clark while experiencing the bountiful cuisine of the Pacific Northwest; sampling Pacific lampreys, forages for edible barnacles and harvests for sea salt on this culinary adventure.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p13603302_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man Fire Food</title>
    <desc>Roger meets a pit master with a PhD who cooks Carolina-style whole hog barbecue in Louisiana; Dr. Howard Conyers is an engineer for NASA by day, but a pit master at night, on weekends, and every moment in between.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9389343_b_h8_aq.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man Fire Food</title>
    <desc>Roger visits chefs who use unusual tools over live fires; Erik Niel cooks rabbits rotisserie-style with bamboo poles; Chef Tim Byres of Smoke cooks flank steak and whole chickens on swords.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9389343_b_h8_aq.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man Fire Food</title>
    <desc>Smoked chicken bathed in white sauce at Big Bob Gibson B-B-Q in Decatur; &quot;The Big Red&quot; pulled pork sandwich at The Brick Pit in Mobile.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11844688_b_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man Fire Food</title>
    <desc>Roger cooks up two whole hogs in two different ways; Roger visits MOPHO restaurant for a Southeast Asian spit-roasted pig that is a twist on a classic tradition; Chef Miles McMath hinges two steel troughs together to make a quick-cooking oven.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p9389343_b_h8_aq.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man's Greatest Food</title>
    <desc>The tastiest chicken, beef, alligator, lobster and more; together, they'll prepare the flame, season the food and reveal all the secrets for the best grilled foods in the country.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14527546_b_h8_ai.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man's Greatest Food</title>
    <desc>Roger Mooking searches for the 12 best island eats from lobster, conch and shellfish to low-country boils and key lime pies; he joins chefs in their kitchens to learn everything about putting the country's freshest island treats together.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14527546_b_h8_ai.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man's Greatest Food</title>
    <desc>From traditional Philly cheesesteaks and ribs to juicy steaks and entire steers; learning everything there is to know about each cut of beef; some of the best beef-centric recipes in the country and all of their steer-crazy secrets.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14527546_b_h8_ai.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man's Greatest Food</title>
    <desc>The 12 best super-sized dishes; Roger Mooking hangs out with chefs to learn all their secrets for creating ultimate omelets, steaks, sandwiches, seafood platters and more decadent, XXL-sized dishes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14527546_b_h8_ai.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey's eating odyssey has taken him all over the country and back again, and now it's time to honor the best of the best by inducting the top five pork dishes into the &quot;Man v. Food&quot; Hall of Fame.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey counts down the five fish feasts that will be inducted into the Man v. Food Hall of Fame.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb heads to Charlotte, N.C., for three takes on Southern specialties; there's a cheesy chicken classic, care of Korea, a time-honored institution's signature sandwich and the biggest walking taco in all the Carolinas.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb starts with a 2-pound barbecue behemoth packed with every meat, sauce and side on the menu; gourmet doughnuts; a duel with the spiciest sauce in town in the Six-Alarm Fire Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
