<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man's Greatest Food</title>
    <desc>From traditional Philly cheesesteaks and ribs to juicy steaks and entire steers; learning everything there is to know about each cut of beef; some of the best beef-centric recipes in the country and all of their steer-crazy secrets.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14527546_b_h8_ai.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man's Greatest Food</title>
    <desc>The 12 best super-sized dishes; Roger Mooking hangs out with chefs to learn all their secrets for creating ultimate omelets, steaks, sandwiches, seafood platters and more decadent, XXL-sized dishes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14527546_b_h8_ai.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey's eating odyssey has taken him all over the country and back again, and now it's time to honor the best of the best by inducting the top five pork dishes into the &quot;Man v. Food&quot; Hall of Fame.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey counts down the five fish feasts that will be inducted into the Man v. Food Hall of Fame.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb heads to Charlotte, N.C., for three takes on Southern specialties; there's a cheesy chicken classic, care of Korea, a time-honored institution's signature sandwich and the biggest walking taco in all the Carolinas.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb starts with a 2-pound barbecue behemoth packed with every meat, sauce and side on the menu; gourmet doughnuts; a duel with the spiciest sauce in town in the Six-Alarm Fire Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
