<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Noah explores the huge variety of options carnival cooks have come up with to honor America's much loved sandwich; from classic beef burgers to exotic meats to buns made from pretzels and even donuts.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>A pho burrito is the perfect mashup, and barbecue mac and cheese nachos double the yum, proving there are infinite ways to use your noodle.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>Top picks featuring a New Jersey drive-in slinging sky-high burgers, a New Orleans doughnut shop turning diner dinner classics into quick-bite hand-helds, and a Southern California spot serving decadent seafood fries.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>A doughnut burger brings both sweet and savory to California; a restaurant in Arizona offers a Bloody Mary with more options than a new car; cookie pancakes in New Jersey.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>Former MLB baseball players Iv??n &quot;Pudge&quot; Rodr??guez and Kevin Millar highlight unforgettable eats, from brisket nachos to an award-winning rack of ribs.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>Diners featuring massive meat loaves, garlic fries, candied bacon, and chocolate waffle lava cake; former MLB baseball players Eric Byrnes and Jeremy Affeldt highlight food from San Francisco's AT&amp;T Park, including the Crazy Crab Sandwich.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
