<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb chows down on a historic Reuben sandwich, a soul food feast featuring fried chicken from a 100-year-old recipe and a monstrous pile of pork with all the breakfast fixings weighing more than 3 pounds.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb gets into the tailgate tradition with a green and gold burger piled high with bratwurst, cheese curds and jalapenos; a local fish fry with flaky Great Lakes whitefish; 12 crispy egg rolls.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's quest for the best brings him to the beaches of Delaware for an ice cream custard that has locals lining up and a brewery that blends two beloved bar foods; he takes on a daunting surf-and-turf challenge that's never been done before.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p21343487_b_h8_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb's massive meals include a bacon-wrapped hot dog with a crazy combination of toppings and a foot long chicken burrito blanketed in ghost pepper sauce; a slow-roasted pork shank served with potato salad and sauerkraut.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Man v. Food</title>
    <desc>Casey Webb heads to Ocean City, Maryland to dive into a massive jumbo lump crab cake sandwich, make some of the area's iconic salt water taffy candies and fight to stay afloat in the Titanic Sundae Challenge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p192792_b_h10_cn.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
