<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Korean tacos and the LA street dog in Los Angeles, California, with a stardom cuisine and edible icons.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Dungeness Crab Louie and sourdough bread on the West Coast in San Francisco; some of the best eating on the West Coast.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>Smoking a whole hog and making chorizo from scratch for a saucy barbecue brunch burrito with two different fire-roasted salsas; Caribbean roasted pork sandwich; the breakfast burger of champions with hash browns, bacon and a fried egg.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>A burger loaded to the max with beef, ham, bacon and sausage; Korean-style smoked pork sandwich with miso-barbecue sauce makes Atlanta the frontier of barbecue fusion; a spicy, fried Cornish hen in Houston.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>Chef Michael Symon sinks his teeth into a burger in Memphis, Tenn.; pizza gets a brunch makeover in Atlanta with creamy scrambled eggs and crispy pancetta; Thai-style fried chicken; Caribbean jerk smoked ribs.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>In Lockhart, Texas, one family remains at the forefront of America's greatest barbecue after four generations; in Brooklyn, N.Y., a lobster meat and pork belly BLT; in Louisville, Ky., a juicy venison burger ignited by unique sauces and seasonings.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Noah visits the Norfolk County Fair in Ontario, Canada and enjoys the Thanksgiving bowl and butter bacon poutine; the Columbia County Fair in S.C. serves gator nuggets with swamp sauce, the hog on a log and angel and devil dogs.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Tri tip beef sandwich in Portland; chicken wing ice cream at a fair.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Noah visits the annual Rio Rancho Pork &amp; Brew festival in New Mexico, where he samples a trio of meaty meals before devouring adorable Baby Cakes; Noah visits the Ionia Free Fair in Michigan, where he enjoys The Tator Grenade and Churro S'mores.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Noah explores the huge variety of options carnival cooks have come up with to honor America's much loved sandwich; from classic beef burgers to exotic meats to buns made from pretzels and even donuts.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>A pho burrito is the perfect mashup, and barbecue mac and cheese nachos double the yum, proving there are infinite ways to use your noodle.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>Top picks featuring a New Jersey drive-in slinging sky-high burgers, a New Orleans doughnut shop turning diner dinner classics into quick-bite hand-helds, and a Southern California spot serving decadent seafood fries.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>A doughnut burger brings both sweet and savory to California; a restaurant in Arizona offers a Bloody Mary with more options than a new car; cookie pancakes in New Jersey.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>Former MLB baseball players Iv??n &quot;Pudge&quot; Rodr??guez and Kevin Millar highlight unforgettable eats, from brisket nachos to an award-winning rack of ribs.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>Diners featuring massive meat loaves, garlic fries, candied bacon, and chocolate waffle lava cake; former MLB baseball players Eric Byrnes and Jeremy Affeldt highlight food from San Francisco's AT&amp;T Park, including the Crazy Crab Sandwich.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
