<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Tasty traditions of some of the best street food like barbacoa, chicharrone and huarache in Mexico City.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</title>
    <desc>Bitterballen and haring in the Netherlands for the best eating in Amsterdam.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11177369_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>A slammin' sandwich with three different cuts of pork smothered in triple-cheese sauce; a flaming hot burger stuffed with spicy jalapeno Jack cheese and covered in Buffalo sauce; a brewery's drunken chicken pot pie.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>A burger that originated as an off-menu secret and accidentally became the talk of the town; a beer hall serves a mammoth, pretzel-breaded, deep-fried pork shank; baby back ribs get a spicy, fruity makeover with a homemade guava-habanero glaze.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>Smoked turkey and sweet potato fried pie; a burger is stacked over a foot tall with three beef patties, mozzarella sticks, jalapeno poppers, onion rings, bacon, ham, eggs; chile-rubbed duck breast.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Burgers, Brew &amp; 'Que</title>
    <desc>In Baton Rouge, La., chef Jay Ducote, introduces a French and Cajun-inspired burger; in St. Louis, toasted ravioli stuffed with burnt ends; in Austin, Texas, a gigantic peach-glazed pork chop and peanut butter mousse pie.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11831234_b_h8_ak.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Riverside County Fair and National Date Festival; fire fingers kartwheel and the sonoran fire dog; palm date shake; Pensacola Interstate Fair for some Flori-Bama fun; crabby tots and the love me tender pizza; queen of funnel cakes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>From a giant BBQ stuffed baked potato at the Houston Livestock show, to a Forth Worth Tex Mex Burrito almost as big as the state itself, Noah discovers that everything is bigger, and yummier, in Texas.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>At the Ostrich Festival in Chandler, Ariz., sampling the Tacocolada; trying Amanda's green bean fries; Noah's first ever visit to the Colorado State Fair for a breakfast burger like no other and a rattlesnake corndog that's got a real bite.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Carnival Eats</title>
    <desc>Noah Cappe heads to the Arkansas State Fair for the Arkansas Slamwich, the Stuffed Thanksgiving Taco and more; a savory funnel cake called the Chick 'N' Cake, deep-fried rice pudding and other delights.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p10883921_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>Decadent dishes smothered in the richest sauces, from gravy-covered biscuits and skyscraping burgers to Caribbean curries and perfect pancakes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>Restaurants prove that good food is even greater when it comes in a tasty package, featuring ice cream and cereal stuffed burritos in Los Angeles and a deep-dish pizza wrapped in a whole other pizza in Chicago.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>From a lobster and filet mignon taco donut to a classic Japanese noodle dish done as juicy burger, chefs serve up some of the country's most mouthwatering mashups.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>A 15-pound bloody mary, a palatial pizza made of chicken Parmesan and more.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Cooking Channel US</name>
    <title>Food Paradise</title>
    <desc>Next-level backyard cookout classics include a loaded picnic dog, truffle beer can chicken, a whole lobster Cajun seafood boil, superstacked barbecue sandwiches, burgers, wings and more.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p236187_b_h8_ar.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
