<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings accidentally set off a mechanism in a tower.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e9cf14341b241a06302d7e7d3dc087a</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over the last jar of Yummy chocolate spread in the cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38276f1f8a2f9d717e4402bd81ba81b0</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom tries to prove Sledkin caused an explosion that injured a dragon in the Hidden World.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5893c8953f72743dceaa0c044872c377</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>D?Angelo struggles to keep a cool head and find a cure for the victims of an attack.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p727d57c1ee4b53ba2c81f655e4600c30</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>Ken is back, and it seems like everything is back to normal. However, when a famous photographer arrives to take pre-debut photos, the trainees realise they still have issues to work out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p25bb505ccc302d4d5e28e4c83cb31d06</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>With a thunderstorm raging outside and rehearsal time running out, Henry struggles to pick up the choreo for a nationals routine. Trying to help Henry, Summer finds their relationship tested. After the lights go out in the studio, Kingston, Ozzy, and Lily discover that someone shut the power off on purpose and everyone at the studio becomes a suspect. Heath and Izzy bond over their survivalist ways, much to Ozzy?s dismay.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa06c7fb87734892d28a257aad6cd1fc5</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>The Vipers are not getting along, so Aoife blags them onto a team-building weekend. The only thing is that it?s at school, military style and with the boys - what could go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p15dc335e196d0bebf4629f17a317b53c</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Alien zombies, space monks, a demon clown, an evil knight and a world record attempt -it's just another day at Cranmede Academy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a4f6570cbeeb3d53adb000b54c1d578</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:40PM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Diamond when the guest on a live TV show can?t stop pumping! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes, pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p124aa384cfc9de9b57a6c0777805b147</image>
    <start>06:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>05 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Can Shaun rescue gluttonous goat Mowermouth before being harvested along with the maize.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdc76309ac0cb46f053b3a317a8e60795</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When all the other danger agents become supersmart due to a batch of genetically enhanced celery, Danger Mouse might need to find a new job.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd3564fbdb5d3af356c096d2505f6a6f2</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis needs to pull off a magnificent stunt to save the skate park from closure, so Gran gives him the skateboard of the legendary Kendo 360 to help. When the special board goes missing at the worst possible moment, Dennis needs to dig deep and realise that it's the skater and not the board that's important.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54738b714536b205261da7b9c907d809</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The CEO buys Jocko?s old amusement arcade and vows to tear it down. However, Boy loves the arcade and challenges her to an epic video game battle with the fate of the arcade at stake.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p841fc93c4ca27297d05e07073f8d029f</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2f9886b7bcc2633283b4deeef6faf959</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings take possession of a magic sceptre that has the ability to shrink objects.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p777d66872fcd3672633acf25cf19f79b</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy swipes the peanut reserves of the elephant playing with the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54036a52fcc54e05e7dec7e09578175a</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56daa2b3ab5c528d73d6bf96351ed71c</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>It?s been ages since their last quest, and the heroes are losing their edge, so Mr Friendlyface invents a strange and terrible monster that he says is stomping through the forest causing havoc, and sends the heroes on a fake quest to get rid of it. Friendlyface soon comes to regret his trickery when, with the heroes out of the way, the goblins decide to take over the forest for their jam jamboree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd73f5a342e51bd6aa4e1226b5b388fb</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to Zambia for the first time, where he hears hippo communication on a whole new level, spots a high-diving croc and meets some incredible sniffer dogs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3986f49991a9204dc06d5907226e9e8c</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 7-9 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about what humans are doing to the planet, as well as deforestation and plastic pollution.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82b6116374a43a5de5ff9bc8065361a9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>Meet the zoo?s powerful animals as Sonika the Asiatic lioness gets a grip in a tug-of-war and Tyler takes on Marion the sulcata tortoise in a contest of strength.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d5c59a0ad274d349b9f50da51aaabe9</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Year 8 get their hands dirty in the school allotment, while Year 7?s green team focus on recycling.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p495d7d05db968f57df7bcf329657566e</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Art Ninja</title>
    <desc>Whilst looking after Gav's cat and Sarah's guinea pig, Ricky gets bitten and suddenly he can hear the pets talking! Not only that, they're gossiping about him. He also has to contend with the Grand Master making a kazoo and artist Joan Miro inspiring him to craft a 3D name sculpture, before heading to the Yorkshire Sculpture Park to make animal art really worth talking about.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0f6d021633bba6dd8752fbac9b9e74a</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Get ready for incredible experiments and mind-bending puzzles to impress your friends. Owain and Tilly are here to explore epic science tricks to try at home and showcase brand new technology innovations from around the world! In this episode, discover a cool coin-catching trick, find out how to make movie magic using the power of perspective, and learn a quick fix for filling that empty ice cream tub.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51d2024e820f4610e85bc3cf5be9a856</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Could you build a slide to the other side of the world? You would need to start in space, use the slippiest slide ever and make sure you have enough supplies before you go down it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c93e4b0e1fc4adb5f1d0842be1d0abe</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories presents our guide to Ancient Civilisations, featuring new sketches about Alexander the Great's first kiss, Emperor Nero's greatest hits, and how double parking in ancient times could result in being impaled, rather than fined. Also, Swill Gumbitz takes a look at Greek statues, the musical instrument that could make you poo yourself, and the evolution of bottom-wiping.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb061542a1366b2ec92cb4d193a65984</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Duncan from Glasgow is passionate about protecting orangutans and wants to raise awareness of their plight within his local community. He wants a den where he can hang out, learn more about his favourite primates and how to help them, and share his passion with friends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf7a107877c2eb098db94fe5f6e374e6a</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>After Moxy?s drums go missing, Andy concludes it was their rival band, Sandy and the Same Socks! Getting paranoid, a chase ensues as Andy accuses them of stealing everything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb25b473cf84269836f676090139fbcec</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>The Go Jetters travel to Algeria in north Africa to check out the ancient Timgad Ruins. Built by the Romans nearly 2,000 years ago, the city was built as a grid, with all the roads running in straight lines from north to south or from east to west. Meanwhile, Grandmaster Glitch's computer game controller has broken, so he is looking for a new one. When he sees the map of the Timgad Ruins on the ship's big screen, he realises that the grid layout makes it look just like a computer game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p213e7889d0e75493f644dcdba401341b</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Cosima and Big Lizard find some fascinatingly slippery fruit, but bringing it safely back to the ship is more challenging than they imagined.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f770807e1c9b4adae5c07afc1c11262</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. Whether it's a perilous voyage to the bottom of the sea or the piratey pursuit of a giant squid, the Octonauts leap into action. When a giant wave hurls creatures from the Amazon river up into the trees, the Octonauts must get them down safely without disturbing the poison dart frogs who live there.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3e12710ed136182630cc11e7be43c741</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The world is in jeopardy and the only thing that can save it is a 1,000ft Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7dcc9c255cb548ada924dfbdc51cc0cf</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>Miss Berrington, Evie's new school teacher, and teaching assistant Mr O'Donnell have come to meet Evie at home before term starts, and Waffle is under strict instructions to be on his best behaviour. But Waffle is teething, and won't stop chewing everything in sight.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p36588dda5dcc56e67db828b9ab3c85b0</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Evil Pea has trapped Supertato and replaced him with an evil robot lookalike called Robotato. She has programmed it to do mean things in order to destroy Supertato's reputation so that she can take over the supermarket. Luckily, Carrot senses something's amiss and eventually figures out what's happened. She frees Supertato just in time for him to stop Robotato from carrying out Pea's meanest command yet: splatting everyone with a giant cream pie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7196de0e9b3b637207465499c7d26c68</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Professor von Screwtop gets mistaken for the new kid in school and joins Class 3C for the day. Rubi is so embarrassed at her dad?s antics that she resorts to pranking to get him into trouble and out of the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p060c373a4ae75d174dc60fc03089f42e</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>JJ applies for an elite sporting school. However, not realising it's miles away from Beanotown, he needs to do badly in the sporting assessment to get out of it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p25f8c727ad716ff6332cb203cd3afeab</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom draws the short cheese straw and, rather than join her friends on a picnic, she has to take a magic wand to the recycling centre. Faced with a long queue and a rumbly tummy, Blossom decides that life is too short for recycling - with disastrous consequences. The heroes must skip their picnic and go on a quest to save the forest from the magical mess Blossom has gotten them into.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38db6a019d90d683a5c507a27c6477df</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Yin and Yang are missing one brick to finish the Great Wall of China. With the minister quickly approaching to see the completed wall, Yang orders a brick from the Ninjas.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3d4e0f4f517467e77515c8efbc52ce0b</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Drama series. A new girl called Sasha stops off on her way to a secure home and causes chaos. Can the Dumping Ground handle her bad behaviour.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf47c848d3d6b975d9ed9348f65817f1b</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Eldon runs a chaotic group rehearsal, and Izzy learns an important leadership lesson. Meanwhile, Pete and Heath do everything in their power to look like dance captain material.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf7b1387b4b8af7734efce9f15eca26bf</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A look at how World War II played out on the home front, featuring Churchill's secret loo, the heroic 'ATA Girls' and German spies being caught out by their delicious sausages.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34479d246837eb45065d27a320a85e07</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis can?t get Grizzly?s new animal training method to work on a wilful Gnasher. However, when they realise that Gnasher can use the method to get humans to obey him instead, they exploit this new power to the max.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p965cb1910091f1f086e689ad9c5309e4</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis is mega-excited to trial a pair of hi-tech Smarty Pants - underpants with all the capabilities of a smartphone. However, whenever he and the gang test the pants, Walter is always one step ahead of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa879352069255fc7bf2e01b1a28abf51</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron steals DM's confidence and gives it to his shy daughter, Delilah Von Greenback, creating a dangerous criminal mastermind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5df627a084f7c486593e10df1725c85c</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When Pam D?Terre and her giant rabbit sidekick confiscate all the potatoes in the world, the Ninjas must go on a rescue mission to get them back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5b0ff086652d29157b3522733883604</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a strange card game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd8280ea25f4c5c8ac45b8837320db09d</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Suddenly feeling too old to be collecting toys, Boy gives up his bobbleheads and decides to do the things that grown-ups do instead. The others desperately try to turn Boy back into his slightly more interesting self by taking him to meet the owner of the world's biggest collection of bobble heads, where Boy must choose between what he thinks is cool and what he loves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p53eae7f2ec93d84dbfefaf2b4a97f238</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Blossom accidentally uses a witch?s broom to make sticks for toasting marshmallows, the owner of the broom casts a spell of squeaky voices on all the heroes. The spell will be lifted once the heroes have returned with new broomstick branches. A simple enough quest, think the heroes, until they realise that a witch?s broom can only be made from the branches of the Really Spooky Tree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe37511be85e501039449287ddef18d2b</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Agents compete against rival Odd Squad agents to solve an odd problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e0f6430aadd878214936f5dfa5c7be5</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Otis and Olympia investigate why people in town are stuck in slow motion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcea725021fcaffbb3d36283dd3eda6a0</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Courtney challenges Owen and Jude to be the next social media star, with little success.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6ccccb2b9a1b1595dc58abdcbfafd582</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face an elusive villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde8c939cb2856a527ae4925122886276</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>During a match against Rika of the Elite Four, Liko realises what battling is all about.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb554686e74adacd1687add781341b4df</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>When Pickle gets stressed about her birthday party, she unintentionally opens the magical portal to Kleftania, bringing evil Lord Clunkett to Earth and seeking revenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96ec8c1439beecfc1c976f03fff179f6</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. The A-Troupe is split into two teams to test the leadership skills of the girls competing for the role of dance captain. As the competition for the position heats up, Kate warns the dancers to put their differences aside and focus on teamwork.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae268654408cc0cdd7b7a4f3ea9d31d6</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings decide to free a spirit and send it to Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf3e17ba97de1e96e38a2afc361b91a20</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun tries to ensure that Bitzer won?t be defeated in the box cart Grand Prix again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc87d8de89a68ada2f5856aad2fd1c6c1</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Has Danger Mouse finally met his match? An evil version of the hero escapes from a parallel dimension and joins forces with Baron Greenback.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa755ac1daa2a711230c9321971439bf6</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Gran's Harley gets impounded, Dennis thinks she's lost her groove and given up on her thrill-seeking ways. In trying to help her, Dennis accidentally becomes Old Man Dennis, and teams up with Gran to prove you're never too old to be a rebel.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p06462bc6c222a8dd4acf59ba9de0a0b7</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>K-Jam is moving into the neighbourhood and staying with the family for a while. However, Girl gets insecure and thinks that her awesome best friend is trying to take her place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbace25267391c527963e66f359240ab</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3b43642c96048138824aaaf58461b0b6</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a pig who has the ability to find food using his snout.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p196b5bca0acf23ff7985ace82777a786</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings take part in a safari photo competition on an animal reserve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p87591ace945bfdf453a92c3829fd0bc0</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents try to escape from a time loop.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae025c43ad493f0de739ac8970e53148</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to Suriname, a country with more forest than anywhere else on earth. He kayaks upriver in search of some deadly critters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae61be0573c4be4246d27fa124cbcdc0</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 7-9 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about the journey of a river, in this case the Nile, as well as hydropower and dams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82b7581f7039e84791f08f09a1505bbd</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The brothers learn all about different types of cosy animal dens. Bird expert Nadeem helps Cam build a bird box, and Aaron reveals why the Asiatic lion is most endangered.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcc2bea3a0b9396f6a346a5fc0fae598f</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Fashion fun as students are challenged to design and model outfits for a school show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a8b5ed563b79e0b055cb6e86b7ee169</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Art Ninja</title>
    <desc>Ricky starts to receive countless gifts from a mystery superfan whilst coincidentally items begin to disappear from his flat. Gavin is instructed to keep watch, though he's a little distracted. Meanwhile, Ricky makes a shiny selfie in homage to Gustav Klimt, an octopus using a candle and a squirty flower! With his flat half empty, can Ricky finally recover his stuff and uncover his mystery fan.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd06cc3d022cb8d7985eddf08b59cd88c</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Get ready for incredible experiments and mind-bending puzzles to impress your friends. Owain and Tilly are here to explore epic science tricks to try at home and showcase brand new technology innovations from around the world! In this episode, discover why a boomerang always comes back, search for forensic evidence to catch a cake thief, hitch a ride in a car with no driver, and see a ball defy gravity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea0387dd16800881de2d72e86b241d24</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Wouldn't it be cool to be able to walk through walls? From turning into a gas to quantum trickery, we discover why it wouldn't be quite as useful as you'd like.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0e230fa2ad1567230d5610a5e88a4cf3</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Chop, chop, it's the Horrible Histories' Terrible Tudors Special, with everything you need to know about history's most famous family. Featuring a never-before-seen sketch with the murderous Medicis, hilarious outtakes, and a special one-off written by a CBBC competition winner - it's your one-stop Tudor shop.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4990fa93a56a86c7058a3f4015bff7d5</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Zoe from Oxfordshire is mad about science and dreams of becoming a scientist one day. She loves to carry out messy, noisy experiments, but her dad works night shifts, which means she has to be quiet while he sleeps. She desperately wants her own space where she can pursue her passions and make a mess whenever she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1362ca6c17f3b744fcd72eef1ba4224c</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy has double-booked himself and must attend a family party rather than the band?s anniversary celebrations. Moxy plans a daring mission to break him out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12ee72b007386e686b82538b87e65f3e</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>The Go Jetters are visiting the Everglades National Park in Florida, USA. It's an area made up mainly of water with amazing wildlife living there, including alligators! The Go Jetters are working with a local park ranger to put up signs warning people not to eat food near the water as it might attract the alligators. Meanwhile, Grandmaster Glitch is also at the Everglades enjoying a holiday with his Grimbots. He decides to stop and have a picnic by the water, which brings the alligators dangerously close to him and a boat full of tourists. It's down to the Go Jetters and the park ranger to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96ceda2bd6dcf2f9fa0f8b790460efd1</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Big Lizard wants to have a go with Dad's new drone, but first he has to prove that he can go a whole day without breaking something precious. Good luck, Big Lizard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p850b309749660e2b38b39d00c45b2933</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. Whether it's a perilous voyage to the bottom of the sea or the piratey pursuit of a giant squid, the Octonauts leap into action. The Octonauts are exploring Antarctica when Shellington discovers strange microscopic creatures living under the ice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p242d7c633b4f9fd6586900df211d6a72</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When secret information is leaked from HQ, all eyes fall on Colonel K. Is it possible he is a traitor, or is there something suspicious about his moustache.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db875e58f17940935f6776c5bb499c3</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>While Zoe helps Doug with his homework project about Alaska, Simon and Jess take Waffle and Evie to the shops to buy new school shoes. But Waffle's attempts to help end up causing chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ea5a4f370ad0cb1ad9431c914904fb6</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>The Tato Team are playing beach volleyball. But when Evil Pea's parents, Mummy Pea and Daddy Pea, pay her a visit, they are disappointed to learn that she doesn't rule the supermarket. They vow to help their daughter defeat Supertato once and for all. After cornering him with three freezy hoses and freezing his super sidekicks, it looks like Evil Pea might finally be victorious. But when she is distracted, Supertato and the veggies use their beach volleyball to block the attack and the plan backfires... freezing her parents instead.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81357dbe11e26974b460a16c167532f7</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang take on the power of WilburCorp to stop Walter?s new line of collectable toys ruining the Beanotown environment with all its wasteful plastic packaging.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c44a8d584dd7a07558e7563e65f62b0</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Rubi?s dance machine gets accidentally muddled up with Crusty the Robot Pie?s coding. Dennis and Gnasher have to dance on it all day in perfect sync, or Crusty?s entire persona will be wiped forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc196d03c4998053896105cc5f5c04bc8</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>It?s been ages since their last quest, and the heroes are losing their edge, so Mr Friendlyface invents a strange and terrible monster that he says is stomping through the forest causing havoc, and sends the heroes on a fake quest to get rid of it. Friendlyface soon comes to regret his trickery when, with the heroes out of the way, the goblins decide to take over the forest for their jam jamboree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd73f5a342e51bd6aa4e1226b5b388fb</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After the battery dies on her laser shoe, special agent Gloria Hope calls on the Ninjas to help her find a new one and foil criminal mastermind Pam D'Terre.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10d3013b50db1457cc92c2ac34d58fdc</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Drama series. Sasha can stay at the Dumping Ground as long as she obeys the rules. All is fine until her naughty little brother Dexter arrives.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2db44f3427b4b413392bea3cf77b9535</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Ariana comes to a realisation as she fights her way through the Dance Captain Battle Royale, and the international twists are far from over.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc4c1a50126c1fa172d0b05da89038e4e</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A celebration of some of history?s greatest females, including Spartan Queen Gorgo terrorising Historical Love Island, supergroup The Tudor Queens, and the original Wonder Women.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p582ac5e48494296f4adc6415c654b2b8</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>There?s a new tripe hound in Beanotown, and Gnasher falls head over paws in love with her. Bertie is looking after the visiting dog, Ginger, and is determined to keep her away from riff-raff like Gnasher.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c6935906c9fad8f02b717eec4e4caaa</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>An order mix-up leads to a delivery of hyperactive tentacles at Bash Street School. However, no-one wants the job of looking after the pesky things, and attempts to duck out of the tentacle-care duties lead to chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd04f790a2a06b0b64f43ec40406c119c</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron releases a new strain of elephant flu. Can DM and Penfold find the cure before everyone is turned into a snotty elephant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51f8cb9515674180a911e9981fe74ee0</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After some playful gnomes take her phone, a mum and her son ask the Ninjas for help. However, a game of magical tag ensues when the gnomes also take the Ninjas' delivery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e6614daa2f8b7a97e30b3497c60c300</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a tree with chocolate spread sap.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3585c633baec4c2b027d134bc532043b</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse is tested on his experiment to create the perfect family and is sure he will fail! However, his siblings convince him to hire actors to play perfect versions of themselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p74d538ded050c20a33665d7e2f080fec</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest until a heroic one comes along. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Odd Squad and Villains work together to stop a giant robot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ecb8fd587aedc874bc91e06bf8e589a</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents accidentally lose someone in headquarters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pffe16f8607e9b7c534d70c45b0848532</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth and Leshawna try to outdo each other with fake injuries to gain more attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe635ab159f06f65d1cb8af629461d176</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Gold Record.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6bb881e9b26f09372f21fa4936589205</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>A visit to Naranja Academy results in answers, and new questions, about Terapagos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pecf6b702814f4d246f300391aff711a4</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>There?s a brand new slide at school, and Pickle really wants to try it out. However, things get complicated when Pickle's mood magic causes Mia and Mr Ludcomb?s hair to grow uncontrollably.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fdd46f4b3717baf8071605b9e07bf96</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. When Kate asks Emily to hold dance evaluations for placements in the group dance, Emily decides to put Michelle in the back row, which causes waves amongst the dancers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa3145037e37ecb44a9edb7f99a35d148</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find an ultra-modern glowing cabin they can use for their party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1b288d68d121be98f9d5b947e9b4735f</image>
    <start>06:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
