<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Charlie is fast asleep in bed and is about to be late for school once again. With a ticket to an Odd Socks gig in jeopardy, can the band wake him up and get him to school on time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p541c429a086625c643c25ef0a8febe36</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Double-booked for a gig and not wanting to let down their fans, the Odd Socks unveil digital duplicates of themselves. But what happens when they go rogue and take over.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef8672a3f98ba3464dd278d8165164d8</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to meet some of the most endangered animals in southern Africa - wild dogs. He meets the people working to save them and explores why their survival is so important.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa86bff10b00032a9259c03724729dbc1</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve goes in search of ocean acrobats, mischievous coyotes and deadlies in miniature - but he ends up having an encounter with a humpback whale he will never forget.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p456f14218e320dab5b002d13ae8a2f0c</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Gladiator Dynamite is back to make sure things don?t get too explosive when Dr Dan and Dr Raph get into a Body Battle in a planktastic challenge to test their core muscles. On the basketball court, we meet Joel Henry, our Brilliant Bodies slam-dunk champion, to find out how he jumps so much higher than Dr Chris. It?s game on in the lab when Dr Xand becomes Saliva Man and Dr Chris tries everything he knows to overcome his superpowers as the doctors show us what spit is for. In an amazing Bodytricks, six kids surprise themselves by lifting Dr Ronx off a chair using only two fingers! And in the emergency department in Edinburgh, we follow the treatment of Niamh, who has broken her elbow doing a back handspring at gymnastics, and Adhya, who took a whack on the thumb during a hockey match. Ouch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p08db54266af2514592094cbe1c2c13cd</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A look at how World War II played out on the home front, featuring Churchill's secret loo, the heroic 'ATA Girls' and German spies being caught out by their delicious sausages.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34479d246837eb45065d27a320a85e07</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A celebration of some of history?s greatest females, including Spartan Queen Gorgo terrorising Historical Love Island, supergroup The Tudor Queens, and the original Wonder Women.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p582ac5e48494296f4adc6415c654b2b8</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Giant is pranked by Nitro when he appears as a guest of honour at a fake school award ceremony! The other Gladiators have sneaky fun backstage at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe24d7c7ee4f1aef3442ee32cdd611f0c</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When an old enemy returns, Colonel K must come out of retirement to save the world from an outbreak of rudeness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2e371392bd76d59ab61f378473f577e</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The world is in jeopardy and the only thing that can save it is a 1,000ft Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7dcc9c255cb548ada924dfbdc51cc0cf</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When secret information is leaked from HQ, all eyes fall on Colonel K. Is it possible he is a traitor, or is there something suspicious about his moustache.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db875e58f17940935f6776c5bb499c3</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>With Paul on vacation, Pieface falls under the influence of a fiery chilli pepper and unexpectedly turns rogue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6a5852bb24bcb8b318f0993738dc0f68</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Paul the Potato is love-struck by the poster girl potato advertising WilburCorp?s new line of super-posh chips. The gang stage a daring potato rescue in the WilburCorp factory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p509b952fbaf1e149740c52cc753d1901</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Eager to prove her babysitting ability for a permit, Gran?s on the hunt for a baby stand-in. Walter is suspiciously all too willing to offer up Bertie. Can the gang help Gran wrangle the reluctant baby-sitt-ee.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41b8db6365e28a69acc1df3de0b9363a</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle uses her excellent pocket beast card skills when on a quest to rescue the missing Council of Happiness from Grackle the Giant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c52df7e45b3a76f78f6ac5a5d573bb1</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Forest inspectors pay the forest a visit to check its super-happy status. Friendlyface sends the heroes on outlandish quests to guarantee results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf423a5126c7145dec4e840079fa076e4</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes wake up on Snow Day morning, there isn?t a snowflake in sight! The heroes must quest to free the Snow Dragon and save Snow Day for all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70e545bcacb2d124e1fd8b0469e27b2a</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Retrieving data. Wait a few seconds and try to cut or copy again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5182ecf611fd5ff1885769a76c91b757</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy notices that the Lemmings have laid hands on a pirate cannon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf7d718e20f9db9f57661911a80b230c3</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings are determined to train Grizzy, who would rather lounge around.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p626f7acad3ba778ca7f57e803cbcb8c9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom and Jun get trapped inside a giant tree with an anxious colony of woodchipper dragons.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ccbffbb3cb7fb4e4fcc777a9bd89bb9</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Thunder must lead the Hero Dragons in a desperate attempt to save Tom and the riders.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac17ec434a7cf848baf29f54c9108136</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>Ken assigns everyone the task of filming a promo to introduce themselves to the world, but it brings up unexpected connections and jealousies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p496de0671a31835b94228fcc25875a55</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>When Summer makes a choice affecting Henry's spot at Nationals, he questions her decision, leading to a difficult realization about their relationship. Piper cancels plans with Finn and Amy at the last minute, and the pair spend the day getting to know each other, with surprising results. Meanwhile, Cleo clashes with an unruly Jude in rehearsal and makes a discovery about why Jude struggles to learn choreo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p33e4e024a013cc22d36b00c6506a1ad2</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>It?s teachers v students week - can the Vipers help win the cup, become school heroes, and impress Aoife?s new crush, Jamie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0174069b4479aab09bd6e163ba4c3a41</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Lily pretends to be sick, Claire pretends to care, Jin pretends to be healthy, Tam pretends to be helpful, and Mr Malone pretends to be confident to win over Miss Marmaduke.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf6c66339b394250b689c0239460d701</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:40PM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Viper with a fake interview that ends with an unexpected splashdown, but he doesn?t find it funny! The other Gladiators have sneaky behind-the-scenes fun at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d2e22d45141442e761e7181750d3d5d</image>
    <start>06:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>19 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun is in serious trouble when the Farmer discovers he is the cake thief who has sabotaged his baked goods. When another farmer arrives and begins negotiations with the Farmer, Shaun fears the worst. Is this the end of our hero's time on Mossybottom Farm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p962c33f0da6cad7b3c024131565cd96c</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse's uncontrollable laughter annoys a race of clown aliens so much that they invade Earth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p71ad5c62d44a3d366830c3351b73c1ce</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Gnasher gets sent to dog obedience school for gnashing Mrs Creecher's saxophone, one of Professor Screwtop's inventions, the Chatterbox, allows Dennis to understand animal noises, so he can ask Gnasher why he did it - if only all the other animals in Beanotown would stop chatting to him for a minute.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p962f969cb9c962bbff530699c20c9605</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy and Tuck offer to build a clubhouse for Cat and Charlotte, but the two boys have a hard time letting go of their wonderful creation, driving the two girls up the wall.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe57d1a3dab33749509621e5f543584cc</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e680541cfcaa464f1be6f5c2fe0b0c3</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Using a ring that lets their astral bodies travel, the Lemmings decide to haunt Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3d4c3cf119692497d318da30bb58dfed</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find magic books that make their story content appear in real life when opened.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p01c270a57a4691a1423701fd684d5433</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents bring someone with an odd problem back to headquarters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p68cae65ead64454d95150e06cb856e32</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom is terrible at keeping secrets, and Trevor can?t help but point that out. To prove him wrong, Blossom refuses to reveal the secret hiding place for her piece of the Amulet of Protection, even though the heroes need it to stop Balthazar casting a weather spell on the forest. With a rain of crabs heading their way, the heroes must quickly persuade Blossom to reveal her secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96c570335130856ee7aaba63648a0da2</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Wildlife series. Steve tracks the weirdest-looking fish on the planet, comes face-to-face with a giant Pacific octopus and goes kayaking with killer whales.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa4c585dd09f25ace8fc2a2a27ed1e0cd</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 9-11 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about texture in music, soundscapes and layering sound.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p25bcf54d49f7246591725271c1e0d26e</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch! Do Try This at Home</title>
    <desc>There is chaos in the kitchen lab as Baby LiLou joins the doctors to reveal why you need kneecaps. Find out how your knees work with a simple Do Try experiment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe7117fb014f4a363f7c16a138590c46a</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>We look at whether some animals can get gigantic and find out that if you are being chased by a giant snail or a humungous butterfly, then fear not, you must be dreaming.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p50f0b48fe0361e718c0cf303916a6202</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Since being diagnosed with scoliosis and undergoing spinal surgery, Emily hasn?t been able to follow her passion for dance. However, with the help of best friend Lottie and a special visitor, that is all about to change.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p239155d5e1604c3544690ff6df2dfe2e</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The OZT brothers meet the wildlife heroes working to save Britain's woodland animals. Cam rescues red squirrels, Tyler meets bears and wolves, and Aaron reveals the wonders of the tawny owl.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03d88735a6410867c13bc3442aa20875</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>This time, futuristic basketball-playing robots and banana drama. Come and check it out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3511564e352193462c5ad72453bf63d5</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Dara O Briain joins Rattus for a show marking the 1969 moon landings. The first use of rocket power, the Space Race, and poo floating in the Apollo 10 cockpit - it?s all here.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3b16feb8fe52de83be854e94c8528cc0</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Joe and Meryl are joined by the Dengineers Designers to give a masterclass on creating your own dream space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14839d77aefdd1aef3d3508cdaffa9cb</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>It?s time for the interschool sports day! However, Moxy?s hyper-competitiveness starts to overshadow the events on the field, causing the Odd Socks to make a stand.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b91003b8bac40331972a43ba9ad0bd2</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>It's a dark night and Glitch is flying his Grim HQ over the sea around the Isles of Scilly. He's in the middle of reading a bedtime story to his Grimbots when his lamp breaks! He needs a new light, and when he sees the Bishop Rock Lighthouse in the distance he demands that the Grimbots get him the bulb. Meanwhile, Xuli, Foz and Lars are flying the Vroomster nearby. They almost crash into the lighthouse, and Lars realises that the bulb is missing. Glitch and the Grimbots have taken it and turned it on inside Grim HQ. But the new light is so bright that Glitch can't see anything, and Grim HQ goes out of control.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d6e3b9ce6f7811e3bae283acc606134</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When all the vegetables from their garden are stolen, detectives Cosima and Big Lizard investigate all over the neighbourhood - only to return to the scene of the crime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb5b7a681560c098be7b69ba4d703b8b3</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Join Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers for more deep sea adventures. When a population of crawfish is stricken by a mysterious illness, the Octonauts race to find a cure.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf1b19da7fabe704ed84a1609bf06132</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Professor Squawkencluck's mum comes to visit, a gigantic, enraged rubbish monster is not far behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b7ec02901562c8e1059c044cd0f4ea2</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>Waffle is at Mrs Hobbs? house until the Brooklyn-Bells return from holiday. He acts like a cat to please her and helpfully washes up his bowl, but accidentally leaves the taps on.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p90f8605d5c1dce7b7042a81cd1981786</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Whilst Carrot works on Robotato, the rest of the Tato Team go to watch a magician, who is actually Evil Pea in disguise. Evil Pea makes Broccoli, Chilli and Tomato ?disappear? under the stage, and just as Supertato volunteers to be next, Carrot arrives and recognises Evil Pea. Supertato worries about where the rest of their friends are, but Carrot has already come up with her own magical plan to get them back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7efc1256692a899db02dc1a3eb7429fe</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>There?s a new tripe hound in Beanotown, and Gnasher falls head over paws in love with her. Bertie is looking after the visiting dog, Ginger, and is determined to keep her away from riff-raff like Gnasher.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c6935906c9fad8f02b717eec4e4caaa</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>An order mix-up leads to a delivery of hyperactive tentacles at Bash Street School. However, no-one wants the job of looking after the pesky things, and attempts to duck out of the tentacle-care duties lead to chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd04f790a2a06b0b64f43ec40406c119c</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert receives a bottle of Goldenbeard to make his beard longer, stronger and more golden than ever ? and the results are dramatic! Everyone is talking about Herbert Goldenbeard, the great hero and quester, and Herbert is loving the attention. However, when he is kidnapped by the goblins and needs his friends to rescue him, Herbert soon realises that they are much more important than any golden beard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p86555ecedfb25de25cc47ca98336e9a0</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas are delighted to be reunited with their old nanny when she calls on their delivery service. Together they reminisce about the day they discovered their powers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p694693e8839c1b91925731ad9b2cef3a</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Kazima fails her age assessment and so the immigration authorities want to send her back to Somalia. The Dumping Ground must rally to help her any way they can.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdebb980710be21330f314b834b5dfaf8</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Eldon chooses the internationals duet as Kenzie considers a big opportunity. Meanwhile, Olive is conflicted about having her friend back on the team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9033e7687f75dafb24033de8dae7e12e</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketches. The Tudors sing their family history, Bob explains the history of Rome in two minutes, and a mad Victorian gentleman eats King Louis XIV's mummified heart.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6745f6db5ccb2c0b4a64bd4a977f8858</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>With Paul on vacation, Pieface falls under the influence of a fiery chilli pepper and unexpectedly turns rogue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6a5852bb24bcb8b318f0993738dc0f68</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron and Penfold are stranded on a desert island. In the skies above, there is a race to snatch Brunel's All Encompassing Remote Control.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa7b8e966b5c6c306f3a119bdf3118798</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A trainee witch asks the Ninjas to find her a cat so she can pass her magic exam. However, getting the easily frightened kitten to participate proves to be a challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4057a11885fce1ebd8e72996ee149c8e</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy discovers a special lamp that can compact organic elements.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db012894fcac6a72802b96de04dbf13</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>Eggs, sausages, a freezer and toilet roll are among the items getting the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pca10d3e982537144c48ab02c8dd7731c</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>With the rest of the gang sick with colds, Mouse builds his own personal transparent bubble to keep himself healthy. But soon the others get also their bubbles to enjoy their own space, even if they're not sick anymore.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peac044daa2577ce7a3c237afbdaf0f7b</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes aren?t really meant to do quests without Mr Friendlyface?s express permission. But when they come across a cute little squirrel queen, and she begs for their help, they find her impossible to resist. All they have to do is quest to the Tree of Certain Doom and pass his challenges. But the squirrel queen is not who she appears to be, and the heroes have to quickly un-quest their quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc66ead86a1798e4f31033a6bf01a29a</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents try and stop baby Agent Orson from getting kicked off the squad. Curriculum: Using bar graphs, pie charts and Venn diagrams to sort, classify and analyse data.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb7cd8f4c94c7c40d3964df087a8b0d70</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Oona gets zapped into an alternate dimension. Curriculum: Place value, number operations.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf30c5fe866d4f3672488024755c03fed</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>The kids confuse Chef by blaming Hoppy, a stuffed rabbit, for everything they do wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pefd8c699555e272663057fb43d22fdc8</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Hoaxer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67813c59d73568d0e83966c42c041a90</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Joined by Perrin, the Rising Volt Tacklers set out to find Kleavor on Tengu Mountain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d673cc286577b672f953048a7f66c0a</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Big Brain has a chemical catastrophe, Sir Isaac Newton rides a coaster again, with shocking results, Loofah is after a murderer, and Dr Henry VIII on call.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peee6d9a3675c97b17d21716f58b7d6ed</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Michelle secretly choreographs a new routine for regionals. When Michelle begins recruiting some of the A-Troupe to learn her routine, she missteps by inviting one of the E-Girls.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9745432e83df685fcb720139f57f916d</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. Mr and Mrs Strawberry watch the sunset, until gooseberry ruins it. Fishing Finger dives in the kitchen sink and comes face to face with danger, and the manic mopping lemons are clumsily cleaning up. Daring, dainty meringue attempts diving with disastrous results, Dr Rhu-barb is chased by his arch-enemy trying to 'extermi-grate' him, and Fearless Pete Parsnip impresses the judges with his performing dog trick in the Ooglies talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e6dc8214064ab9c5629dc97981988e5</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The flock are delighted when a birdwatcher drops his duck call in their field and Shaun uses it to entertain them. However, swallowing the duck call isn't what he had in mind - and the ducks aren't too happy either.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p45f23d6f4c52f060b9c696aba44222d8</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse and the Baron are forced to team up in order to defeat a cheese-obsessed villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc640fda27059d028e627a20d12c99338</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>New teacher Miss Mistry is taking Class 3C on a trip to Flumes o' Doom theme park. If anyone is a nano-second late, the bus leaves without them. Walter pulls out all the stops to make Dennis late for the bus.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb1a2b6da96c302dbf59dd322ca1e52b3</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Girl and K-Jam find Gherkin crying because nobody likes him, he confesses to them that he wants to change and become nicer. After asking the girls to help teach him how to be nice, the girls reluctantly agree and recruit Girl's siblings to help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p275e250d52bedc89a9aa938a144ef1f6</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5264071caed26d233b5e2114a6a6e65d</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a card that enables them to teleport a magic closet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa08b154dad94ed665954fc65a2a2e098</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Retrieving data. Wait a few seconds and try to cut or copy again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p439992281191416513974240e3164911</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents bring someone with an odd problem back to headquarters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb19926a3095a1d527ec8908a0ccbb945</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Gnome Crystal Mine has ground to a halt, leaving the forest with no crystals, no power supply and melting ice lollies! The heroes are tasked with a quest to find out what has happened and to fix it. It turns out that a slimy beast named Smarg has made the mine her home. But with Hoofius?s fear of gunk getting the better of him, evicting the slippery Smarg is not going to be easy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p858de20cb9333a64f647c54c77975ddd</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall takes to the icy waters of British Columbia in search of the biggest, baddest sea lion in the world. After an unexpected encounter with a killer whale, he heads back to the city on the trail of one smelly contender before trying his hand at becoming a raccoon. Despite immense strength, powerful claws and a fearsome reputation in Canada, there's a surprise in store when Steve tracks down the infamous black bear.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e188a4a0ebcbd7b0cee3f7c7503a9ec</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 9-11 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about improvising, improvisation games, and the role of a conductor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p87c2af2464404a0907bee86054cc17d9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch! Do Try This at Home</title>
    <desc>The doctors make the most of Mr Grumbles?s weekly shower to demonstrate how your hair has a secret skill that enables it to measure moisture in the air.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb11b0de4d9e0d0b235bc3e509ad2fde7</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>We try using a gravity-bending black hole and spinning the earth faster to see if we can make it possible to walk on the ceiling.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe31de16e0f0f23bcf0292ddce0393834</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Twins Lily and Rosie are battling with stage fright as they are asked to perform in the choir at the big school concert. Meanwhile, Crystal discovers a new passion when she joins the school cross-stitch club.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p55dd9ffa2c3c89887a3299125a0435ca</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>It?s literally a packed show as the OZT HQ is crammed full of some of the fastest-swimming marine life and deepest divers surrounding Britain?s shores. Tyler takes the plunge in Plymouth to reveal how a special marine plant is being brought back from the edge of extinction to help fight climate change. Plucking up courage, he then dives deep to swim with sharks and is amazed by what he discovers about this incredible but sometimes misunderstood species. Just off Britain?s north east coast, Cam also slips into his wetsuit to go snorkelling with seal whisperer Ben. Getting up close with some inquisitive seals, he learns of the threats they face from plastic pollution. It?s all eyes on the Scottish skies as the OZT brothers go on a mission to the Isle of Mull to look for the ultimate soaring sea bird, the white-tailed eagle - but who will spot one first, and can Cam get the perfect picture? Back at OZT HQ, Aaron?s animal knowledge gets put to the test with some quickfire questions from the OZT crew, and Cam reaches for the sky with a drone to reveal how the incredible killer whale shots were filmed for Sir David Attenborough?s Wild Isles.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8a685403df3e7de3727825052313c405</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Tune in for vocal gymnastics and limboing on a motorbike - you have to see it to believe it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf734d99d77fd4d77d33df37a9f789b6a</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Dani Dyer becomes Rattus? political advisor as we look at everything from the birth of democracy to Margaret Thatcher having to change her voice so she would be taken more seriously.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe182f6581902cd62ce7c49196c4794d8</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Ten-year-old Florence from Oxfordshire wants a cool hotel den so that she can relax, hang out with friends and be on holiday whenever she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7df7868e7dd6838fd10576d8577005d3</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Mac?s latest invention, an AI assistant named Felicity, makes everyone?s lives easier. However, as the band take advantage, Felicity takes matters into her own hands.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p93230023027bf937bd3ad75002395c13</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>It's farming time at the Go Jet Academy and the Go Jetters are growing corn in a big field. Their crops need watering and so the team are putting up an irrigation system which will water all the crops in the field. Growing corn is a slow process, and Grandmaster Glitch doesn't want to wait for the crops to grow. He shoots them with his size ray to make them bigger! The Go Jetters want the crops to go back to normal, so Glitch sets the size ray to shrink mode to make them small again. But disaster strikes when he accidently hits the Go Jetters and Ubercorn with the size ray and they shrink to the size of ants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae37d6a101303714fa76bb968b57a89f</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Big Lizard isn't happy in his skin! Cosima tries everything to stop him scratching until she realises that's exactly what he needs to do. He's shedding his skin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc6c6abf47d547f20cf001458e36522a7</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Join Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers for more deep sea adventures. The Octonauts wade through a swamp to find a lost flamingo chick before hungry predators do.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ad8af2a61876e267ed99d05e33925de</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Squawkencluck reboots the now 100 per cent reliable Big Head base computer, which immediately locks up everyone in a maximum security prison.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p807580e7b44481f79c8475072cd446ef</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>It's early in the morning after the Brooklyn-Bells have returned from holiday and there's someone banging on their front door. It's Mrs Hobbs and she's furious. Waffle left Mrs Hobbs's kitchen taps running and now her home is flooded and there's water pouring out of her front door! But Jess and Simon will be Mrs Hobbs's 'knights in shining armour' - Sir Jess and Sir Simon Brooklyn-Bells to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde3f1f0567fe3ced1f63d723547b6f36</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Evil Pea takes over the Tato Tower HQ and uses Carrot?s new security system to keep Supertato out. Supertato and Carrot work on a cunning ice cream plan to sneak back in.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd802f786e04d43c2d7da72e46d5dcda2</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>On the first day of a new school year, Dennis and the gang imagine all the things that might be new and unfamiliar at Bash Street School. By the time they reach the front gates, they are all expecting the worst.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3faada4acf7db9d5c697dcdb4bf0045a</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The kids of Beanotown decide that they can run the town far better than the grown-ups. However, they discover it isn?t nearly as easy or fun as they had hoped.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa15e18ace150b21c21fc62dda6a4fddb</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom is terrible at keeping secrets, and Trevor can?t help but point that out. To prove him wrong, Blossom refuses to reveal the secret hiding place for her piece of the Amulet of Protection, even though the heroes need it to stop Balthazar casting a weather spell on the forest. With a rain of crabs heading their way, the heroes must quickly persuade Blossom to reveal her secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96c570335130856ee7aaba63648a0da2</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Two gnomes entrust the Ninjas to find them cloth so that they can make trousers for a giant and his upcoming dance competition. However, finding a giant-sized piece of cloth proves to be more difficult than they thought.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21ff23841c7005414f98171a0b5a05fb</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>We?re joined by Adam Peaty, one of the fastest swimmers on the planet, basketball superstars the Harlem Globetrotters show off their skills, Paralympic medallist Bly Twomey shows Abby how to smash table tennis, and Women?s Euros champion Ella Toone answers your questions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb31f9e69fd79d6e0b2d5c28917a7ed91</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Eldon fights Anthony over which dancer should represent TNS in the Home Field Advantage competition, while Ebby deals with a dilemma.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p107fb8ab84f42a25adcde85f5c06d3fd</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketch show based on the successful books. A priest makes a piano from live pigs, Emperor Caligula declares war on the sea, and there are some disgusting beauty tips from ancient Egypt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc86f99c2b81ea0854db65cb489fb9044</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Paul the Potato is love-struck by the poster girl potato advertising WilburCorp?s new line of super-posh chips. The gang stage a daring potato rescue in the WilburCorp factory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p509b952fbaf1e149740c52cc753d1901</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Colonel K disappears on a free holiday, Danger Mouse pulls rank and assumes the mantle of caretaker colonel. However, the role is much less exciting than he anticipated, as world-saving missions make way for endless paperwork. Meanwhile, K's freebie spa retreat happens to be a diversion tactic in Greenback's latest plot to take over the world, with the baron banking on the Danger Agency falling apart without its figurehead and the world descending into disarray.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paef6868cdecdac98504d06f4fc8a956a</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>While fulfilling customer orders, the Ninjas realise that a spy has been following them to help a copycat Ninja delivery service steal their business.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfa1f6025e5cc54d907f1d54131f3c3d8</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The extraordinary animals from a tablet game come to life after the device explodes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3a27aae2aea7f6befb2d2839f29139f</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The ninja sushi are back, and fearless Pete Parsnip comes face to face with a terrifying snake. Star bar attempts another trip to the moon, the toast soldiers try again to ambush an egg, and Mrs Strawberry takes part in the talent show, with shocking consequences.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3d57600bad43f4c9d41bd1369535c13b</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids' mean neighbour Wanda has started enforcing a dogs-on-leashes law. Boy, Girl, Cheese and Mouse each come up with ideas about how to show that Dog is special and doesn?t need a leash.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf8723c8d7f782d6c8c671fa9819a3ba</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The blossom has gone missing. No, not Blossom the unicorn, the blossom on the trees! The heroes are sent on a quest deep into the heart of the forest, where legend has it you can see a face watching you from the trees. Twinkle doesn?t believe in legends, but when help comes from nowhere as they try and stop the scoundrel that is stealing the blossom, she is forced to reconsider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2f8d2357ef662dfdfa8453de1222ecd1</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia discovers a secret about her partner. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs, data analysis and collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p487861630ae6473048dde909b125dabf</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia discovers a secret about her partner. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs, data analysis and collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e75c16a01b1950e3e8d1fbbdab6f880</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan escapes during a class walk, only to discover he has to babysit Cody and Bridgette.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4af7c94f5b1c9176b563b148209a0332</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Reflekta again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f9e19260bb307be583812c9dbe63579</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko, Roy and Dot finally find Kleavor of the Six Heroes - and it wants to battle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p73e5b5f7499b291235e01e0a835bf146</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Dr Big Brain has an electrical short circuit, Marie Curie is wowed by a rocket man, some of the great women of science are celebrated, and 200 monks get electrocuted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21daa97d981587de14f8ff3ad8bddf40</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Emily begins to suspect Michelle is up to something behind her back. Eldon gets tired of people questioning his relationship with Emily and decides to set the story straight.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p55bd7499bb01535e2d59c77b457e22bb</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The thrill-seeking eggs snowboard down the ironing board, the Stunt Tomato and his glamorous celery stick assistant attempt a death-defying stunt, and the apple dropouts come up with an explosive new way to break free. Mr and Mrs Strawberry stargaze with a little help from the gooseberry, and the mushroom cavemen attempt to wow the judges with their rock-balancing trick in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3b72b6262667300da9c4a44da7aa00be</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>While the Farmer is engrossed in trying to set up his new computer, the flock takes the opportunity to have a game of football. When the ball accidentally lands inside the farmhouse, under the nose of the Farmer, Shaun comes up with an ingenious disguise to retrieve it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p360bf4ef7d4524ad1bbabe763c53bf8a</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. In trying to prove he does not believe in magic, Danger Mouse accidentally unleashes an evil magical queen into the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd4935d86a65a4e2a8c44fe8bd4ffa0d5</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface is secretly doing underpants laundry chores for Walter, hoping to help Dennis save up some cash. He urges the gang to audition for a replacement Pieface to make up for his mysterious absence.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0ced6f09c8a135c0107ac2cf9c4bc6b</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse discovers that Dog is able to make a sad puppy dog that allows him to get whatever he wants. When Mouse asks Dog to use this trick to get the Professor to loan him a special rare rock for his experiment, Dog refuses. To get his own back, Mouse uses a special invention that allows him to impersonate Dog and get the rock. What happens next is absolute mayhem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0fee9a17d06cbe804db1fbd83719f950</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e4dd04c5f0f1bd63ba023d06534a124</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings meet a parrot that can identically reproduce any sound.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p424ba0bba126544e6d4cfa74f499c8a8</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a spherical object that can control Earth's rotation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p921c74484ac5bb64fd88423c0d82ac6a</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. It's villain report card day at Odd Squad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9dae7f88c4e057d5a1eacff1e5e09570</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is acting very strangely indeed. He refuses to stamp any of Admin Bunny?s documents, keeps getting distracted by butterflies, and seems oddly happy! The heroes are extremely suspicious and decide that someone must have swapped him with a doppelganger. Now they must quest to find out where the real Friendlyface is and get him back before the forest descends into total chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde2e0b6ed02cd81a52a1b5ae1f9bd3e8</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve and the crew are thrown deep in the steamy rainforests of Costa Rica. They are on a mission to find the largest cat in South America - the awesome jaguar. But the jungle is teeming with wildlife - from venomous snakes to squealing frogs - so there is plenty to see along the way. Even after dark the forest is alive with deadly creatures, and down by the river Steve has a battle with a giant, reptilian predator.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p20a28fb0855d4abc535967fd969571b5</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Sounds using the voice, body percussion and composing using the body.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c3a3f2e79ea3ff0d2abc4145926c3ca</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch! Do Try This at Home</title>
    <desc>The doctors look at scabs and explain why they shouldn't be scratched - unless it?s a Do Try edible scab.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe713c85f229823dc504af718afe1ac66</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>What would the planet be like if all other humans disappeared, leaving you as the last person on earth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbbcebcd3b420833dfd12f3363dbb0169</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>The girls reconnect with family for a revealing new history project, and Teni throws herself into a self-defence class after homesickness hits. Meanwhile, some of the boarders are treated to a surprise visit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef4903877e12e9ac5e3a70a9df38659e</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The OZT brothers are on an adventure to take a closer look at some of Britain's threatened grassland animals. Aaron and Cam go off-road in a bumpy dash across the wilds of Exmoor to try and gather more than 100 semi-wild ponies off the moor for their annual health check. Cam meets 12-year-old wildlife hero and butterfly champion Rebecca to find out why she is so fascinated with butterflies. Meanwhile, Tyler heads to the Forest of Dean to team up with ?the snake whisperer?, on a mission to track down an adder, one of our most secretive and threatened snakes. In the heart of mid Wales, Aaron meets a wildlife hero who has played a big part in the recent success story of the red kite, and he is blown away when hundreds of red kites fill the sky. Back at OZT HQ, Cam gets his hands on the latest wildlife filming kit to give us the low-down on how the incredible shots of high-jumping hares were filmed in Sir David Attenborough?s Wild Isles series. Aaron is put to the test with some quickfire questions from the OZT crew in Ask Aaron, and the OZT Gallery puts viewers? wonderful wildlife pictures in the frame.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf2d7366ea4dc6415cc9092b7f43464ca</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>From eggs on rollercoasters to chart-topping Christmas crackers - come and see these records for yourself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1201eaccd9ecf318dc137ed16a648354</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A look at how World War II played out on the home front, featuring Churchill's secret loo, the heroic 'ATA Girls' and German spies being caught out by their delicious sausages.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34479d246837eb45065d27a320a85e07</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Doctor Who fan Adam wants a den where he can celebrate his favourite TV show and pursue his passion for drama. His den story takes him on an incredible voyage of discovery that includes a surprise chat with someone very special.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2d44ea3a306166de8ef6b294d94a564</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Hopeful of getting more students to join, Andy leads an open day to show off the school at its best. However, disaster strikes after a mix-up with Andy?s plan for the band.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p173fdf3447ff58f2253a8e2c2fe2ed08</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>The Go Jetters are on the Strait of Gibraltar in southern Spain, working with a team of conservationists who are tracking a group of baby storks as they migrate from Europe to Africa, where it is warmer. The baby birds follow the grown-ups so they know where to go, and then they remember the way for the rest of their lives. The storks are flying high above the sea towards Morocco in northern Africa, but Grandmaster Glitch is also up in the air with his Grimbots working on their flying formation and nearly crashes into the migrating birds! In all the commotion the baby storks start following Glitch and not their grown-ups, meaning they might not make it to Africa.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc847fc7dbb63b55de6effa0bca8c5e2d</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad gets a severe case of Proximan hiccups. Big Lizard and Cosima do their best to help, but their attempt to scare Dad goes wrong when a real 'monster' turns up.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ddd5626eeb3a49f1e8f652d03cfb731</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Preschool animation. Tweak must help her friend Sandy the sea turtle escape a hungry tiger shark.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbbe2b7e7b1f7c94babee74b4c5ed8a58</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's attempts to boost Penfold's confidence backfire when they lead to a ferocious games monster escaping into the real world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p107003566b41bffd5346594c3f9d54eb</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>It's the morning of Evie's first day at school and the Brooklyn-Bells are on schedule. But Waffle isn't happy as he is expecting his usual morning walkies. Doug tells Waffle that Gramps will be walking him today; he'll be coming to the house later. Waffle is insistent, he wants to walk to school with the rest of the family?now! Evie thinks it's a great idea. She's nervous about starting Reception and walking to school with Waffle will make her feel happy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p685c02df7b41f5a3275d1866966ba570</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Evil Pea freezes the Veggies so she can take over the whole supermarket. Chilli?s heat unfreezes Supertato, who then races on lolly-stick skis to thwart Evil Pea and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p90803b456c32fb3c3a97c3e0e46ca13c</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>New teacher Miss Mistry is taking Class 3C on a trip to Flumes o' Doom theme park. If anyone is a nano-second late, the bus leaves without them. Walter pulls out all the stops to make Dennis late for the bus.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb1a2b6da96c302dbf59dd322ca1e52b3</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface is secretly doing underpants laundry chores for Walter, hoping to help Dennis save up some cash. He urges the gang to audition for a replacement Pieface to make up for his mysterious absence.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0ced6f09c8a135c0107ac2cf9c4bc6b</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Gnome Crystal Mine has ground to a halt, leaving the forest with no crystals, no power supply and melting ice lollies! The heroes are tasked with a quest to find out what has happened and to fix it. It turns out that a slimy beast named Smarg has made the mine her home. But with Hoofius?s fear of gunk getting the better of him, evicting the slippery Smarg is not going to be easy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p858de20cb9333a64f647c54c77975ddd</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When Pam D?Terre and her giant rabbit sidekick confiscate all the potatoes in the world, the Ninjas must go on a rescue mission to get them back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5b0ff086652d29157b3522733883604</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Bailey's world is rocked when his mum turns up at Ashdene Ridge. Can he forgive her for abandoning him as a toddler? Meanwhile, Carmen resorts to drastic measures when Ofsted inspectors arrive unexpectedly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8cd73ce95a1382ec638b9f834690293a</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Kenzie and Team France?s Camille have plans that might not be best for A-Troupe. The rest of the team do their best to make sure Anthony doesn?t pick them as alternate.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd38034095deb1362940b009e38960912</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketch show based on the successful books. There is a terrible smell in the Houses of Parliament, Cinderella struggles with the Blitz, and Helen of Troy reveals her complicated love life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ee87dab453d43e0721f82eba82b5a7d</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Eager to prove her babysitting ability for a permit, Gran?s on the hunt for a baby stand-in. Walter is suspiciously all too willing to offer up Bertie. Can the gang help Gran wrangle the reluctant baby-sitt-ee.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41b8db6365e28a69acc1df3de0b9363a</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Envious at Danger Mouse's ever-growing medal collection, Penfold questions whether he will ever be deemed special enough to receive a prize of his own. Seconds later, a knock at the door reveals a holographic Quark, who anoints Penfold as 'the chosen one' in a suspiciously automated message that culminates in an overawed Penfold receiving his very own magic wand. Penfold's joy is short-lived however - as he and DM step outside of HQ to find that the streets of are London teeming with hundreds of wannabe wizards, all brandishing identical wands. After discovering that the wands are mass-produced shavings from Merlin's legendary staff, the pair set out to stop Quark's latest money-making scheme by reuniting the staff with its rightful owner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p323dc2e8e64fccd5de7990c027816ff5</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Desperate for peace and quiet, an alien leader orders an entertainer to take care of his planet's creatures. However, things nearly go wrong when Konpeki brings a giant cake.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5456763dfebacd2f3cd1490329ffc3f2</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>There is only one carrot left in the house, and both Grizzy and the Lemmings need it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe46d875f87e6c30fabb9f97f7b4df6c7</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. Star bar finds a new rocket to fly to the moon, the ninja sushi are attacking, and fearless Pete Parsnip comes face to face with some savage staplers. The cavemen mushrooms hide from the rampaging plant pots, the baby blocks have a little accident and a heavy metal watermelon wows the judges at the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p91d2e8568079cfa37f458949fb8d56cf</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Dog reveals he's colour blind, the kids rally to help him see the world like they do. Mouse makes him some colour-correction glasses, and Dog is blown away by colour. He becomes an artist and neglects the family as he focuses on his painting career. But when the day of his art gallery premiere comes, Dog will have to choose between art and family.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcf67c683814674b034097cf82bfe82d8</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are relieved that the loud, threatening voice they can hear actually belongs to a small slug named Zorgoth, who is armed with a megaphone. However, when Zorgoth uses his Orb of Compression to shrink the heroes down to the size of ants, their relief evaporates. They must now embark on a long and dangerous quest, through their picnic items and beyond, to warn the Council before Zorgoth shrinks the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe50df153eaba594e89a65c54ae953f0c</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf326fb9ddf1e4b8189998894cdaba294</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9219a4ed6990cdd4d9ec30d5d0a40f34</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan breaks out of nursery and finds life outside daycare is not as fun as he imagined.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p01272c0d6e7e30d5711e91554c65e743</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face a revolutionary enemy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11fa9293672de81facd83707f8abc3e6</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Diana returns and tells the Rising Volt Tacklers about the true origin of the Explorers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5df79c6a5eb77b014ab02a079cd6e32f</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Rapping science teacher Matt Green becomes the first human being ever to visit Quark when he joins Pipette on her home planet to help host this special episode about Earth and space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc7de445b1ca12b41b36ae36d7c7a831a</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Emily and Michelle's battle for leadership comes to a head when Kate learns that Michelle has choreographed a different routine for regionals.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ce8e3c16eb5b5746265bbd7b7ac03a4</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The band get a new trumpet player, with disastrous consequences. Also, the apple dropouts hatch an explosive plan to break free, and superhero Slippery Nana comes to the rescue to save a tomato... sort of! Deep in the back of the fridge, Frankfurter's monster is on the rampage, and Dr Rhu-barb surprises the judges with his white rabbit trick in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8c471f9f68f6507f216d1cf5a73b2804</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>22 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun and the flock discover that the Farmer has grand plans for their barn - that don't include them! Drastic action is needed if life on the farm is ever going to be the same again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70db5f914e9e85aaeca4f3e982bba28a</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Jeopardy Mouse wins the Agent of the Month competition, Danger Mouse and Penfold are forced to travel to New York for a lesson and to take on the criminal organisation known as Hydrant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9bea4a009f4a743a746eef2582c505df</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s time for Gnasher?s annual bath, but the stinky hound will do anything to avoid the tub. Dennis and Gnasher go head to head in a town-wide game of cat and mouse ? or rather, tripe hound and wheelie bathtub.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cd3695300ecc962061ac4a3338675c2</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Girl's football skills catch the attention of a little girl named Bella, she declares herself Girl's number one fan. Unfortunately for Girl, having a fan is more work than she thought.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc19aa4531b6ea3203c920752ac9d349b</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc41f4734dc6b281251e898d9be80a655</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings decide to make a giant pinball in the middle of the jungle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd605d914c65dbd94ee73fa30c3a68dc9</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A Super Lemming transforms any plant he touches into a giant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb93a7cdb1c40ea9de04b260762bd7596</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. A villain steals Ms O's voice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdc1671b3b4871bb46a7a120acb8b8e3d</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is particularly tetchy this morning. He is packing for a skiing trip, but a dragon has pinched his golden fleece, and he urgently needs the heroes to quest it back ? how else will he stay warm and cosy on the slopes? However, when the heroes accidentally agree to let his niece Trixie tag along with them, they fear that her clumsiness and lack of hero skills will ruin everything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c3ff87984db3abc93407af293a6fe99</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall and his long-suffering crew return for a series of deadly encounters with animals hoping to earn a place on his hallowed Deadly 60 list. Steve and the team are in the jungles of Costa Rica. On his search for the Deadly 60, Steve gets strangled by a giant boa, is struck dumb by the strike speed of a viper, and plays hide-and-seek with a deadly bushmaster. As if that wasn't enough, he gets hands-on with a poisonous frog - and nearly gets a nip from a blood-sucking vampire.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p166b6813108c28b68afe9c87f22fdf77</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about tempo and dynamics, and how to use them both.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc647ce550448769cc405803a4045c232</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch! Do Try This at Home</title>
    <desc>With the kitchen lab upside down, the doctors reveal the incredible job of the optic nerve and show how to make your own eye-popping game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe810c47dc0898ae51b3ffc5ad170df40</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Is it possible to build a sand castle the size of a real castle? We imagine how it could be done, using a pneumatic drill and a huge, solid gold steamroller.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0bcde15a567c8dce677c4e780ba8ec9</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>While classical music is a part of everyday life at the boarding school, Queen fan Ella wants to turn the volume up by starting the school?s first rock band - but who will join her, and will they face a tough crowd.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/padf8944fb84a113493e13309ebd08d36</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The OZT brothers pack their binoculars to explore the natural world right on our doorstep, meeting some of the surprising urban wild animals that can be found in our towns and cities. Tyler finds himself holding onto a cliff edge in Bristol to find out why the fastest bird on earth, the peregrine falcon, is quickly becoming the top bird in town. Aaron heads to Devon to reveal how the water vole is being brought back from the brink of extinction. He also lends a helping hand at a wildlife rescue centre as they give two hedgehog patients a new home Back at OZT HQ, bird expert Nadeem pits the brothers against each other to find out which of them is the ultimate bird brain. Cam demonstrates how clever camouflage can help capture incredible wildlife shots similar to those from Sir David Attenborough?s Wild Isles. Meanwhile, Aaron is joined at OZT HQ by the brown rat, one of Britain?s most successful and adaptable animals, and reveals rat facts galore - but are they all Fact or Fake.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p44de96fad0fb6e3cabad3862fe32ab00</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Join in with the biggest bangs and the shiftiest socks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa4150cb9d89ac17a2f82c87e7b8bc94e</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A celebration of some of history?s greatest females, including Spartan Queen Gorgo terrorising Historical Love Island, supergroup The Tudor Queens, and the original Wonder Women.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p582ac5e48494296f4adc6415c654b2b8</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Vilonu is a huge CBBC fan and dreams of becoming a TV presenter when she is older. She wants a space where she can write, film and edit her very own TV shows.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf091cca4f9c20d1d9a26f822feec7c8f</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Fearing he and the band have failed to save the school, Andy vows to give up rock forever. With help from the Guardian of Rock, Andy and the band travel back in time to where it all began.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pec571bc696603a79d1f8c8e4d783684a</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>The Go Jetters are on Whistler Mountain in Canada, doing some skiing and checking out the amazing cable car. Kyan and Foz are about to have a go at the Go Jet Ski Challenge when Grandmaster Glitch comes along and wants to show them how it's done - but the sneaky Grandmaster cheats by using his jet pack to power him forward! But Glitch's jet pack is too powerful and propels him right into the cable car that Lars and Xuli are riding in. The Grimbots try to help by messing with the controls of the cable car in the control room, but they end up breaking everything and the cars stop moving. Glitch, Lars and Xuli are left hanging on to the cable car high above the ground and need urgent help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6d0c8cb0a5310d973bd59071bcb3cba2</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When Cosima finally finds a quiet place to read her book, she realises peace and quiet aren't all they're made out to be. Where's Big Lizard when she needs him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf6a031a32b235b0337a9292749747db2</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Join Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers, The Octonauts, for more deep sea adventures. The Octonauts roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. Whether it's a perilous voyage to the bottom of the sea or the piratey pursuit of a giant squid, the Octonauts leap into action and always prove that eight heads are better than one. The Octonauts must help a giant sunfish who can't swim straight, before it hurts other sea creatures and itself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdeeb086b6cf3103b7b03d600ec48fba2</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Brunel, the crazed time-travelling Victorian gentlechimp, is back and determined to change history so that Danger Mouse and Penfold never meet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c7b4ec1cfd4ed38c7cbcb24ef88353f</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>Mrs Hobbs supervises Waffle at the Brooklyn-Bell house. Waffle wants to join Evie at school and tries to escape. Later, the family look at photos and Evie asks about her birth dad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2dcc6e94f838578c9bc6db3c7466ad20</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>It?s a space race as Supertato helps Carrot fly her baguette rocket to become the first Veggie on the cheese moon, but halfway there Evil Pea makes them crash land.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p40e73d37996e68a49b03ddaf0bd6912b</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s time for Gnasher?s annual bath, but the stinky hound will do anything to avoid the tub. Dennis and Gnasher go head to head in a town-wide game of cat and mouse ? or rather, tripe hound and wheelie bathtub.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cd3695300ecc962061ac4a3338675c2</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The after-school art club is under threat of imminent demolition. In trying to save the club, the gang end up on the trail of the mysterious undercover urban artist known only as Pranksy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p361a97fdcd2b35beabb23cae8c4b65d6</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is acting very strangely indeed. He refuses to stamp any of Admin Bunny?s documents, keeps getting distracted by butterflies, and seems oddly happy! The heroes are extremely suspicious and decide that someone must have swapped him with a doppelganger. Now they must quest to find out where the real Friendlyface is and get him back before the forest descends into total chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde2e0b6ed02cd81a52a1b5ae1f9bd3e8</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After some playful gnomes take her phone, a mum and her son ask the Ninjas for help. However, a game of magical tag ensues when the gnomes also take the Ninjas' delivery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e6614daa2f8b7a97e30b3497c60c300</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Bailey has to break some bad news to his mum - but what is she hiding from him? And what has it got to do with the Shakespeare play the young people are staging.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paafa15d78465070399e41a635000d6cb</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>The Horrible History of (sometimes literally) dressing to kill. Henry VIII has beef over whose armour is best and Louis XV dresses as a hedge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c7dbeb45cd739828723ad58e7a98425</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketch show based on the successful books. The Saxons exchange disgusting Christmas presents, and a caveman goes on a TV cookery show. Plus, discover the bizarre causes of World War I.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4f5721be670680f3392a56a9f8757eae</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold accompany Professor Squawkencluck to the Brainiac Symposium - the annual science convention, where King Kong Brunels's latest misfiring invention, the Cow Trainer, reminds his fellow boffins exactly why he is the laughing stock of the scientist community. When King Kong Brunel suggests that the Professor's success is all due to her privileged life as Danger Agency lab technician with scientist parents, an irked Squawk uses Brunel's Cow Trainer to swap bodies with him in order to show that she could be just as successful in his shoes. However, she soon finds that life as King Kong Brunel is as dispiriting as he makes out, as she is laughed out of the symposium when masquerading as her simian adversary. Elsewhere, an opportunistic King Kong Brunel finds himself revelling at playing Squawk, as finds he himself inside her lab having hitched a lift back to HQ with an unwitting Danger Mouse and Penfold. On discovering the truth, Danger Mouse and Penfold have the body- swapper turned on them, as KKB escapes back to the convention with his newly acquired Squawk-shaped credibility, and a new invention so poorly put together that it could end the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10d782c873c5cb440e14211052a06036</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When a scientist borrows the Ninjas? powers and takes her pet bird on a trip around the world, the powerless trio struggle to run their delivery business.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcb61f203895a48a888727a6ff8e9999a</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings decide to free a spirit and send it to Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf3e17ba97de1e96e38a2afc361b91a20</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Transformed into a fairy, a lemming organises a magic show and gets rid of Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p79472921af261a462aeefc900957d5bb</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A toaster, cheese grater, bin and washing machine are among the items getting the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe6cce340940968710e0977e228d06240</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse is bored of always doing the same things the same way, so Girl suggests he starts thinking outside the box and lives his life differently. Boy and Dog don?t agree, but Mouse, Cat and Cheese follow Girl's lead and it's fun! But when things get out of control, Girl turns to Boy and Dog for help getting things back to normal. With so much chaos in the house, maybe it's time everyone lives back inside the box again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd58240466c21a6b26183b09425e4d16c</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes quest to stop Balthazar from turning forest folk into household objects, Herbert realises that he can defeat the wizard?s spell by using the magic tricks he has practiced. Blossom is particularly intrigued by Herbert the Peculiar?s tricks, not to mention his stage name, so when Herbert himself is transformed into a table lamp, it?s Blossom the Very Impressive to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p02b5755668bd5974ec3f672d77162daf</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Agents Opal and Omar uncover the location of a legendary odd artifact.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb1a1fbc6396eb897cd452bcd1881ce6e</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Agents Opal and Omar uncover the location of a legendary odd artifact.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc49600638d5f1f9d3c6ad4fe99da29fa</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan and Leshawna try to take advantage of Izzy's love for the game of Simon Says.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6aaf405756a724290c20cdc97d40c5e9</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir unknowingly face Queen Mayor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ddd267d48b17366fafe68beb1bbb05b</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>At the Crystal Pool, Rystal recalls when she, Lucius and Gibeon reached Laqua.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b30852837d2e00a21bc71408768804d</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A special guide to working scientifically, whether that involves drinking black vomit, measuring people?s farts, or firing arrows into their bum.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p353c0c51ff7efe9e6d78587b0b2209b1</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Emily and Stephanie have trouble adjusting to life in the studio with Michelle as dance captain. Michelle's captaincy is tested when James's mother tells A-Troupe that James has to stop dancing to focus on his studies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e2dc6ac995330493d653e1cfec7b6c9</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. Star bar finds a new rocket to fly to the moon, the ninja sushi are attacking, and fearless Pete Parsnip comes face to face with some savage staplers. The cavemen mushrooms hide from the rampaging plant pots, the baby blocks have a little accident and a heavy metal watermelon wows the judges at the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p91d2e8568079cfa37f458949fb8d56cf</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The flock and the pigs are in the middle of a high-spirited game of rounders. Tensions are high as Shaun steps up to the plate. Will he score the winning run? Will the pigs' foul play prevent victory? Or will the Farmer discover what they are up to.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa3eba37eaa18cc5ad1d17f75fe88056a</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Penfold's addiction to social media helps the Baron turn all of Danger Mouse's secrets against him in a plot to deflate the planet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6f7ce120fee94baea61d80208ee3e590</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The after-school art club is under threat of imminent demolition. In trying to save the club, the gang end up on the trail of the mysterious undercover urban artist known only as Pranksy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p361a97fdcd2b35beabb23cae8c4b65d6</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Mom and Dad's vacation plans get cancelled, they decide to take the whole family on a getaway to wherever they'd like! The kids decide to vote on where to go, but Cheese deceives her family and tricks them into going to a spa instead of the theme park they originally wanted to go to. After realizing how selfish she's been, Cheese decides it's up to her to save what's left of the family vacation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf9ccabf3943a30eb1d2c22f7100fb1be</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9950dceed3316f2dc4b113984af4bc68</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A magic reaction creates doubles of Grizzy and the Lemmings at different ages.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5dabd7d7d3b4339ec6440811448b086</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy discovers a magic blowpipe in a canoe filled with traditional fishing gear.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd4b4d6b5f474b36950397ebefc7ebab4</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents are called in to help when Ohlm and Orchid have problems working together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e8b829eb0abd5c0de0709ad46d99cd3</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert is really proud of the plants he has grown ready for a visit from The Complete Gnome Gardener magazine. However, when a Wind Dragon flies through the forest destroying all his hard work, Herbert turns to desperate measures ? a barrowful of Stinkweasel?s stinkiest compost! Now, the whole forest is at risk of being overwhelmed by the smell, and the heroes must quest to get rid of it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6fbe790ae4282b14265104a8bedddd57</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Panama is home to one of the largest and most impressive birds of prey in the world - the harpy eagle. But to track it down, Steve and the crew have to trek into a remote part of the Darien jungle. Along the way Steve chases a deadly racer snake downriver, and even faces his fears to handle some giant bullet ants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p279360d8f87d66e5da05f1614398370e</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 7-9 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about using musical structures, form and the blues.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb63cfd17186890401769413df2722c73</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch! Do Try This at Home</title>
    <desc>A camera pill shows Dr Chris?s digestive system at work squidging food, and the doctors show how to make your own fake stomach.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p15a57cfa9332c57da941fc276c3c1a5d</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>We find out what would happen if you shrank the earth. You could jump higher and move faster, but you would end up with altitude sickness even at sea level.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8c61af5c9976090668c55895b9e9d3cd</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Flo and Chloe make a new pen pal and invite her to school for a tour and a big surprise. This episode was filmed in 2021 before the death of HM the Queen.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4d8533017f3b15f4317f277e5e113df1</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>Cam, Tyler and Aaron explore the wonders of the wetlands and meet the wildlife heroes working hard to help protect its animal inhabitants. It?s an early start for Tyler as he heads to Devon hoping to bump into a beaver and discover why this furry eco engineer is having a huge impact on the land and its wildlife. Cam is on the outskirts of Manchester to lend a hand restoring a wetland habitat that is helping combat climate change, all thanks to a super-plant called sphagnum moss. On the Isle of Mull, the OZT brothers go head-to-head as they look to spot an otter. They find out how this wetland wonder is making a big comeback - but whose animal tracking skills will win the day? Back at OZT HQ, a mini murmuration of starlings is flying around, and Aaron is ready with some starling statistics, but he has the crowd guessing when it comes to playing Fact or Fake. Cam reveals an incredible scene from Sir David Attenborough?s Wild Isles and gives Tyler a real soaking as he demonstrates how they might film similar shots using a super slo-mo camera. And the brothers find out what has been going wild near you, in the OZT Gallery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6de71fcbc6af07329b3515a8342913e5</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Strap in tight as we see some ludicrously good leaping and fearless free-falling.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7b520f28f68bb72a86219acc64e4b753</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Alex Scott joins Rattus for a sport-themed special. Mary Queen of Scots goes grief-golfing, the H2 Freestylers take on a whole village, and sports-mad Henry VIII sings Get Sweaty.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c51af73f227c5f0d489a2caccb3374f</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:25AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Gregor from Aberdeenshire needs somewhere to practise, store and maintain his bagpipes. A keen player and member of a local pipe band, Gregor one day dreams of becoming a professional. However, his passion requires lots of practice and it?s just too loud for the rest of the family.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb84025645ef5490150e19a92fd2fea52</image>
    <start>11:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>With less an hour to go, the band and students launch into action to put on the best show possible to save the school. Little do they know that some rock star magic might help..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfb528bc9cfddff10c089d5cc48a67fca</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>At the Go Jet Academy, the Go Jetters are about to watch one of nature's most spectacular events - a solar eclipse. They watch in amazement through their pinhole projectors as the moon moves between the Earth and the sun and its shadow throws them into darkness. As the moon moves past the sun, things become light again, but all of a sudden they are thrown into darkness once more. But this time it's not the moon passing in front of the sun, it's a giant moustache! Grandmaster Glitch has made a giant solar panel shaped like a moustache to power his Grimbots. To fix this giant glitch there's only one thing for it - the Go Jetters need to head into space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc241e63e42cb7b89fe6a97f4bf5086a6</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Whilst Dad searches for a faulty wire, Cosima and Big Lizard play tag in the ship and accidentally break Big Lizard's bath bed! Where will he sleep now? And where's that pesky wire.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27b20bb3866865593fa592da4ecbf022</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Join Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers, The Octonauts, for more deep sea adventures. The Octonauts roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. Whether it's a perilous voyage to the bottom of the sea or the piratey pursuit of a giant squid, the Octonauts leap into action and always prove that eight heads are better than one. While exploring a dark and spooky cave, the Octonauts discover the fossil of a powerful, prehistoric fish... but it may be more than just a fossil.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa863db2afa889857eca8006005a6528f</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse and Penfold are sent on a rescue mission to a mysterious island, Danger Mouse's over-competitiveness borders on criminal.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94611482810f95a6584eec90dad349c5</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>Waffle isn?t allowed at school, so he?s being looked after by Connie, the Brooklyn-Bell?s neighbour, at her house. Connie has dressed as a dog and made a huge, doggy maze game from cushions and suitcases for her dog, Jelly, to race through with Waffle. Waffle asks for one more race through the maze at home but Jess explains that the time for noisy play is over and offers him a quiet cuddle instead. After dinner, Evie tells Jess she?s been given her first reading book at school and gets the book out of her school bag to show her Mum. Waffle sits next to Evie and watches her read. When he starts to say words from the book out loud, Evie wonders if he?s reading, but Jess and Simon refuse to believe it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p386d5267968f24dff4f8aa4f03eb7280</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>In the perilous plant aisle, Supertato and Evil Pea team up to find treasure as they have half a map each, but she tricks him and steals the map to find the treasure for herself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paa18a711a529a0126d45530dd61de0c2</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Convinced that Mrs Creecher is secretly a master of Blamjitsu, JJ persuades the gang to help trick her into revealing her blam credentials.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p631f5a239e4e0ec4323d1cb7272bc565</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is particularly tetchy this morning. He is packing for a skiing trip, but a dragon has pinched his golden fleece, and he urgently needs the heroes to quest it back ? how else will he stay warm and cosy on the slopes? However, when the heroes accidentally agree to let his niece Trixie tag along with them, they fear that her clumsiness and lack of hero skills will ruin everything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c3ff87984db3abc93407af293a6fe99</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A brave little girl orders a shield to protect her from a monster and sets off with the Ninjas, her scaredy-cat dad, a goblin, a troll and a dragon to find her missing aunt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p684f43d0b585056e21b15b866ae9630a</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Sparks fly when Tee recruits Jody to help her and Carmen win a street dance competition. But who's more out of their depth, Carmen or Jody.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf305b316b73159aad98d6b7faaae86f7</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A look at how World War II played out on the home front, featuring Churchill's secret loo, the heroic 'ATA Girls' and German spies being caught out by their delicious sausages.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34479d246837eb45065d27a320a85e07</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketch show. A Victorian inspector checks that school is suitably cruel, HHTV News reports live from the Great Plague, and Thumbelina drowns unpleasantly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p71a7989ead2c77a2da5a87e65e68b456</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang can?t wait for their all-day PE training day with Grizzly Griller and are baffled when their idol makes them learn a range of boring non-sports that only Walter excels at.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13014ffef7cef77e45cb02cd6a8721d2</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Having put the Danger Babies through their adorable paces, Professor Squawkencluck leaves it to Danger Mouse to settle them down with a nice soothing story. Unfortunately telling stories to children isn't one of Danger Mouse's strong points, and he ends up scaring his captive audience with a tale that reimagines him as an evil villain. Squawk returns to find Danger Mouse bound and gagged and that the Danger Babies have made off with the Danger Car and are on their way to Arkwirght Asylum to free the 'heroes' from Danger Mouse's topsy-turvy story.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8674b3e1d60465dd8263514a763f9227</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>To win the annual Golden Wand contest, Merlina summons the Ninjas to find her an amazing magic trick to impress the judges. But the final winner takes everyone by surprise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p24416808631b7fb8497c6fb022cb8ebe</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find an ultra-modern glowing cabin they can use for their party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb652f231f7d9980cc9d08668c1128c88</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Girl decides to write her school project about Cat as she is so mysterious and it would nice to know more about her. The gang decides to help, and soon everyone is following Cat from a distance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c294ff4f4dfcf66ec93fa2af4aea959</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Witch, who was trapped in a Merhaven clam shell while pinching a pearl, grants Blossom a single wish to thank her for releasing her and saving her life. Blossom excitedly chooses a mermaid?s tail to improve her swimming. However, when the Merqueen complains that her pearl is missing, and the heroes have to quest to get it back, Blossom soon realises how tricky a mermaid?s tail can become on land.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5de1c5363e6236bc3067ca23bed0355e</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Agents Opal and Omar uncover the location of a legendary odd artifact.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde5af9c73d0f8b081215c96f51015b55</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings use a frog with hypnotising powers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbd74eae5287515b461c9282bcc4d8e8</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>We have an exciting announcement ahead of the new series of Walking with Dinosaurs. Abby discovers dino footprints on the Isle of Skye, and the team come face-to-face with a walking T-rex in the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2e05b41d1ed7298c1d31fa894b13545d</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef tries to trick the kids into making his mother gifts after he forgets Mother's Day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb83be820d725d3dca24249aa7e59fa8</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: Gift of the Night Fury</title>
    <desc>Festive animated short featuring characters from How to Train Your Dragon. Hiccup and his friends are preparing for Snoggletog, the Viking equivalent of Christmas, when all of the dragons suddenly fly away and leave Berk. All, that is, except for Toothless, who cannot fly unaided. Hiccup has a solution for Toothless, but will the dragons return to Berk? Featuring the voices of Jay Baruchel, Gerard Butler and America Ferrera.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1a50b1b524f797da08ef2e7f67ef9476</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A weird and wonderful look at how gravity, magnetism and friction impact everything. With Fred Sirieix.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94fd45c10fe71cfd50c37b15a03b378a</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. Michelle decides to change the line positions, but Emily and Stephanie are not happy about it. Emily confesses a secret to Eldon that brings them a little closer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa22439632e1e3aa19a89d4961d676dbb</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The thrill-seeking eggs take up bungee jumping, the potato racers whizz around, and Mr Strawberry serenades Mrs Strawberry. Fearless Pete Parsnip comes face to face with a terrifying hairy spider, and Slippery Nana comes a cropper impressing the judges in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9af765987c32160992a5512af85bce81</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
