<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Get ready for incredible experiments and mind-bending puzzles to impress your friends with Wow That?s Amazing. Owain and Tilly are here to explore epic science tricks to try at home and showcase brand-new technology innovations from around the world! In this episode, find out how rubber bands can make the perfect bouncy ball, meet Spot, the dancing robot dog, pick up handy tips to make art pop off the page, and try a watery trick that won?t dampen your day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51ca28bc90c6938922f118119f8aca93</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Imagine if we had a thermostat that could turn the world temperature down - could we fix global warming??But be careful, a few degrees too far could cause an ice age.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1930619574c1e72bdd429122903b847a</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>BBC Teach Live Lessons</title>
    <desc>Evie, Rhys and BBC Children in Need?s Pudsey discover mood-boosting ways to support mental well-being. Meanwhile, Evie faces an epic challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p04e0e19565a09ab1bf0ce0b918eb854a</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Avanaya from Leicester wants a relaxing, Indian-themed den so that she can escape her three cricket-loving brothers, and to remind her of the special times she has spent visiting her grandma in India.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d09db047f07d3e21a6570f0ab7e19ca</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Emerald has deceived them, their record label has dropped them, and they?re very firmly in bottom position. How will Andy and the Odd Socks defy all the odds to save Planet Rock.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd0ae7802c961786b992303656e38099b</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>When a storm washes up lots of plastic litter onto the Go Jet Academy beach, the Go Jetters leave Ubercorn, Grandmaster Glitch and the cadets behind and head to the Pacific Ocean to try to solve the problem of the Great Pacific Garbage Patch. This is a massive collection of plastic garbage which has gathered together and floats in the ocean. It causes big problems for animals and sea birds which live in the oceans as they can eat the garbage or get tangled up in it. Sorting this out is going to be the Go Jetters' biggest challenge yet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81901d9a0f7a8270d8db3adece85e13a</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>After a storm passes overhead, many creatures turn up in surprising places and need Cosima and Big Lizard's help. But try as they might, the friends can't find poor Rex.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p204bcfe13418cf82b5db4cba5a5b25d7</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Captain Barnacles and his niece and nephew, Ursa and Orson, must rescue walrus pups who are stranded on a runaway ice floe - before it collides with a huge iceberg.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p818b67530057d7cae7e667faf610d8a9</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>In order to stop a deranged Victorian time-travelling chimp from uninventing the world, Danger Mouse and Penfold must arrive in the past just before the nick of time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb89086a78e1589c68cd9ddbc5eb06285</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>When Jess takes Evie for her first school visit, Waffle goes along too - on the condition that he doesn't sing. He tries his best to behave, but it's hard for a Wonder Dog! On their walk to school, Jess and Evie bump into Connie Lester and her daughter Ruby. Ruby reveals that she will also be starting at Sommersby School too, in the year above Evie. Ruby enjoys stroking Waffle and tells Evie that she loves animals. She has a pet dog of her own, Jelly, a yellow labrador. Waffle introduces himself to Jelly, but decides Jelly is a grumpy dog. Meanwhile, there's a For Sale sign in Mrs Hobbs' front garden. Mrs Hobbs and George are moving house and leaving Maple Close forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa951aec53739ae13af13b7f6403fd910</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Chilli can?t wait to see his hero Jalapeno attempt a treacle-tart jumping record. But Evil Pea adds an extra tart at the end of the jump, and Jalapeno gets stuck. As Supertato tries to rescue him, Evil Pea claims that she will break the record - by cheating. But just as Evil Pea starts her jump, Supertato pulls Jalapeno free with his plunger, and they all get tangled midair. Chilli transforms into Captain Chilli and does the jump himself, saving Supertato and Jalapeno as Evil Pea drops into the tart.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9373c54529abea5dbbf6abe07ecbc5c1</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang find out that JJ has a set of pre-match good luck rituals. In the run-up to an important Blamjitsu event, Walter deviously throws bad luck omens into JJ?s path, threatening her chances of success.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3c30a8458c845f0ca547fee6492f559c</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>While helping Sergeant Slipper prove that he has what it takes to remain Beanotown?s policeman, the gang unknowingly become entangled in Doctor Pfooflepfeffer?s real theft.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc05891fb066c59115954c3de0a3c01f0</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Stinkweasel drops a rain of yukkiness onto the forest, the Fairy Squad, with their excellent flying skills, decide they are the ones for the job. However, Hoofius insists this should be their quest, even if he does hate ick! And when the Fairy Squad get their wings gunked and are unable to fly, the heroes can resume their quest to end Stinkweasel?s reign of stinky nonsense - no flying required.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d85af1ed37a16cec54b2e5a529e9bbc</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>In order to secure the highest star rating for her restaurant, Chef Topsee turns to the Ninjas to find a giant egg for critic Jean-Pierre Point D'orgure.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34ad50ac5670ffe0903db420b45f5e91</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Mo gets the lead in the school play, but his delight is short-lived when his dad falls ill and a devastating secret about his family history is revealed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p78d0f6c2ade4d80736cc48a60c9e08fb</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories presents a collection of some of history's finest songs, as Rattus attempts to put together his own festival (the delightfully named Glastonsmelly). From singing poos to tuneful Warlords, there's something for all musical tastes, and Rattus has somehow also roped Brad from The Vamps in to help him out, although rather than playing live on the main stage, Brad's role seems to be more about unblocking the toilets just behind it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p97fc0c68a8cc6ce158f83c3adf1cf960</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Rattus has launched his own radio station (?BBC Radio Number Two?) and who better to advise him on the songs he should be playing than social media star Holly H? Together, they bring us a collection of some of the best songs of this series, plus new material from some of the famous historical faces we meet along the way. Queen Elizabeth I, Mary I, Mary Queen of Scots and Lady Jane Gray - aka supergroup The Tudor Queens - are here to sing about having 'the power', before Elizabeth I tells us about using an astrologer for advice during her reign. The romantic poets (Wordsworth, Keats, Mary Shelley, Percy Bysshe Shelley and Lord Byron) sing about their love for nature, while Lord Byron takes time out of his roguish schedule to tell us about one of his favourite fashion accessories. Elsewhere, Queen Victoria sings about her many prime ministers in Mambo Number 10, the GIs make a musical entrance to British shores during World War Two, we take a look at Puritan dating in Court Me Maybe, top boyband The Founding Fathers make America great for the first time, and we finish with a barnstorming look at the Victorians? invention of cinema.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a7d32417979eda694a408270d22642a</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface is secretly doing underpants laundry chores for Walter, hoping to help Dennis save up some cash. He urges the gang to audition for a replacement Pieface to make up for his mysterious absence.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0ced6f09c8a135c0107ac2cf9c4bc6b</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. A new shape-shifting agent tests DM and Penfold's partnership to the limit at the criminal world's annual convention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p75d9a248bd183f2d4eccae6a42e93c2e</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>While searching for the mysterious yeti, online adventurer Daiyu orders a can opener. However, as they try to deliver, the Ninjas realise the yeti doesn?t want to be found.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb85212eea0c23efdd61bd6c635d0d7e1</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>While playing in Mayan Temple, the Lemmings set off a cosmic phenomenon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pca3bcced1a9c602c5d934b4cffd1db83</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids accidentally destroy a beloved family photo and decide to make it up to Mom and Dad by hiring a photographer to take a new one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea9981e258355c4b97ba8632e168fa2c</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert receives a bottle of Goldenbeard to make his beard longer, stronger and more golden than ever ? and the results are dramatic! Everyone is talking about Herbert Goldenbeard, the great hero and quester, and Herbert is loving the attention. However, when he is kidnapped by the goblins and needs his friends to rescue him, Herbert soon realises that they are much more important than any golden beard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p86555ecedfb25de25cc47ca98336e9a0</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Odd Squad builds an exact replica of the villain?s vault to intercept a jetpack.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p49fb3592e61265209a5d9d350dd16e70</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>It's picture day, but a strange visitor has invaded daycare, turning the kids into zombies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbbf2fba0904f3b365ca720abcc6e2595</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Social media superstar Big Manny joins us for some mind-blowing science, along with his pal Big Danny from CBBC series Horrible Science! Meanwhile, Abby and Shini go head-to-head as they create crafts for Henry, and Joel tries one of the fastest racquet sports in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf4e659d70bd99bd5f5f5ef7d4f1720fc</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A totally wicked song about gravity, a T-rex going to see a doctor, vampires on holiday, and Sir Isaac Newton riding a rollercoaster - welcome to the bizarre world of Horrible Science.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p225ef60f63c5a1f6aa9ee4f55650c08d</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A container full of Yummy? What a dream for Grizzy and the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p73a561ce9a6c25c6c43ad3d39368d7fa</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Mrs Armitage on Wheels</title>
    <desc>A tale from Quentin Blake's Box of Treasures. Inventor extraordinaire Mrs Armitage and faithful dog Breakspear love adventurous hobbies like skydiving until an accident dents Mrs Armitage?s confidence. Recovered, she plans a short cycling trip, but keeps putting it off adapting her bike with horns, a tool kit, and even a sail! The ?land yacht? eventually launches, but a further accident leaves Mrs Armitage doubly nervous. Luckily, her Uncle Cosmo comes to the rescue gifting Mrs Armitage his old car and getting her finally back on the road.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c4f701d200c61799b15b87de59d749b</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. In order to heal Eldon's broken spirit, Emily agrees to go on a date with him. Riley overhears Emily talking about kicking Michelle out of the studio and decides to take action.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf5ac76b851c65e2aab439c9120df0dca</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Joel discovers the magic behind the scenes of Harry Potter on the West End stage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6bdf326912bbe6047ea0110b0b8733a5</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>10 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Word gets out that the best pizza is to be had from the Mossy Bottom Takeaway.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4abeb43aaa172fa5b0c7a278e0fa8739</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>In order to stop a deranged Victorian time-travelling chimp from uninventing the world, Danger Mouse and Penfold must arrive in the past just before the nick of time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb89086a78e1589c68cd9ddbc5eb06285</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis doesn?t realise that the pressure he?s putting on Rubi to excel in the school science fair is giving her a severe case of inventor?s block.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fbe541e3e6a3f2dc1a5b1b7edcecd7b</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Girl is failing science class, so Mouse offers to help her learn. However, Girl decides it will be easier to borrow one of his inventions and cheat instead. Everything is going to plan until the borrowed invention goes wrong and causes a scientific calamity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p387204adcf2e93aa73aa4d915551c7ae</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5039a41e0bc81125433ed2dbd3f8db04</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Two sisters arguing over tidying up their house end up with a bigger problem when the Ninjas deliver two cleaning robots from the future who are planning a robotic rebellion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7db05f3ffc7255bc464cfe0eb0754b3c</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. When the agents are accidentally transported to the future, they need to work out what day it is or risk a catastrophe.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e4b6368b02af4bdc50fbbdb8bf5c377</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds an electrode that controls a robot, and the Lemmings plot to take it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7d3bb9210c7f3d94d26cd09e76b33aa8</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:40AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face their enemy through time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p85b9915a72239c65cad8b4613d07dd25</image>
    <start>08:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Big Danny and Big Manny find science shocking, Da Vinci does a sound experiment, Newton rides again, Queen Vic shows off, and Dr Big Brain doesn?t see the attraction of electromagnets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p97ee5c7298a3039556c91b411575f529</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Zoe from Oxfordshire is mad about science and dreams of becoming a scientist one day. She loves to carry out messy, noisy experiments, but her dad works night shifts, which means she has to be quiet while he sleeps. She desperately wants her own space where she can pursue her passions and make a mess whenever she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1362ca6c17f3b744fcd72eef1ba4224c</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>We try out a crazy idea from science fiction to build a giant sphere around the sun and give us more energy than we'll ever need.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fa6e608ce7a4190b2cdc85bda0cf367</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors reveal why your body can't survive without oxygen for more than three minutes, and they find out what it's like to be 999 call handlers in Operation Takeover. Dr Xand investigates how Formula One race car technology can help hospitals, and Dr Chris hits the wards in Ouch and About On Call. Meanwhile in Accident and Emergency, one patient comes in after a bike accident and another has fallen on her wrist.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7035acbad8fd16c49d1a4f271d77dc59</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Absolute Genius with Dick and Dom</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom reveal the genius of Michael Faraday, a pioneer of electricity whose discoveries helped power the planet. Inspired by Faraday's genius ideas, Dick and Dom come up with their own genius idea, involving a cage and almost a million volts of electricity. The results are shocking.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03c63ea4c5364fe329b709dd44a64192</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to Norway to dive with the planet?s ultimate predator - the orca. He also witnesses the northern lights and gets up close to the mighty mouth of a humpback whale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbef90b5da80d45a3ea490398cf8e7c4</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Social media superstar Big Manny joins us for some mind-blowing science, along with his pal Big Danny from CBBC series Horrible Science! Meanwhile, Abby and Shini go head-to-head as they create crafts for Henry, and Joel tries one of the fastest racquet sports in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf4e659d70bd99bd5f5f5ef7d4f1720fc</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Over a board game, Captain O takes Ozzie and Orli back to her time at sea with the case of villain Dottie Dubloon and how she used dice to throw Odd Squad off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f35e3905fd5ed271f7f5df698090a46</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Orli has rescued a clam which needs to be returned to its home in the 60th dimension via a portal on the 60th floor. However, to get there, she must negotiate HQ?s odd lift network.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11c6ba8b45b8289f8bd5234f041ac147</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Mr Ludcomb wants to win the Best Headteacher Award, but his plans go wrong when Pickle?s magic accidentally turns the rubbish bins into monsters that end up terrorising the school.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p081c97c5c537d121a2f9de518bf239f4</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>While Lystra and Hendrick attend their first school parents? evening, Pickle, Mia and Roland become trapped in Pickle?s house, and her magic makes the floor turn to lava.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbbed6ec3c37cde1beb51843963bcbe75</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Queen Victoria's coronation doesn't go quite as planned, George IV pulls out all the stops to impress his guests on Historical Come Dine with Me, ancient Greek bighead Alexander the Great refuses to stop conquering things, and the HH Sport team report live from the horrible pirate races.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd992fa4f737bb2bab54bee156de8ae8f</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>X-Key are gearing up for their TV appearance, unaware of the traitor in their midst, and, after a shocking revelation, Astra must do everything they can to pull off the impossible.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0ec84c76f3c30275a965add2f7f1b6ae</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Tasked with letting go of items that might be holding them back, Lily struggles to shred Matt Furnish?s love letters, and Claire can?t sell her beloved merch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c8c057f5b92b690440da8b3d67e808a</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Young footballers Christina and Andrew dream of making it into Hawx United Academy. The odds are stacked against them - until Jamie Johnson decides to get involved.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p640fb876577b356d8527df9590bd90cf</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Izzy convinces the class she's the world's best advice giver and should heed her advice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2be08a7867a10c3b8ff44567fe6a565f</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>The kids confuse Chef by blaming Hoppy, a stuffed rabbit, for everything they do wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pefd8c699555e272663057fb43d22fdc8</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse and the Baron are forced to team up in order to defeat a cheese-obsessed villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc640fda27059d028e627a20d12c99338</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. In trying to prove he does not believe in magic, Danger Mouse accidentally unleashes an evil magical queen into the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd4935d86a65a4e2a8c44fe8bd4ffa0d5</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After her siblings accidentally insult her dreams of being a pop star, Cheese is bonked on the head and starts to believe she's a huge celebrity! Mouse says they all must play along, because if they ruin the illusion then there's a chance Cheese could go bonkers. Cheese turns into a diva, making outrageous demands from her siblings, and soon enough they're sick of it. But when they learn she was duping them all along, they set out to teach her a lesson..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4540d9337e6bd866504e38a486ddadec</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Boy, Girl and Cheese learn that their animal siblings have a tough time going through life with their unwieldy tails, they want to understand what it's like. So Mouse builds them mechanical tails to wear, and the three soon learn just how hard it is to do simple tasks. However, they come to master their tails well enough to attend the Curling Tail festival, where all tailed animals celebrate themselves. But when the kids turn their tails to full power to fit in better, they go haywire! They're now in danger of ruining the festival and being discovered as frauds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p017af7c6567e02c660ba97f085ca58db</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy wants to watch TV, but the Lemmings want to have fun playing music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb81dcd41f9b8627f90482e8dfa7df1a</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play with a baby ostrich that Grizzy found outside.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9b02f3095f1dc487cda4763f743454b5</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy confiscates the remote control device, but the Lemmings find another one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb088daed596447c6f2a8d8b5466f3892</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes and the Council of Happiness swap jobs, and when the council fail in their quest, the whole forest is at risk of being flooded by Stinkystuff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a544a2a926fb3c68c7a21626bc95543</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes are faced with the Goblin King moving into the Big Birch, they decide to invent a quest that will soon have him running back home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9987df26df4a4713222e9b576a9111f2</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Absolute Genius with Dick and Dom</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom reveal the genius of astronomer Caroline Herschel, the first woman to spot one of the most mysterious objects in our solar system, a comet. Inspired by her genius, they come up with their own genius idea when they make their own comet-inspired action movie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a9a374258d1ecd7ed7becd4992947da</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>The watch! The mobile phone! The microwave! The vibrating poo platform! Thomas Edison stage diving! It?s all here as Horrible Histories takes a journey through the history of tech.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p47dc3faecb87868365d4f3e006e9bd9c</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Mary Ploppins soothes those digestive ills, Dr Big Brain tries banana power, and Einstein reacts to Tim Peake. Fred Sirieix guest stars.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf49783d2e6385e72b2c3c2e59f954422</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors reveal the amazing army of germ fighters that make up your immune system, and they find out just how difficult it is to clean a baby's incubator in Operation Takeover. Dr Xand meets Alex, who has autism, and we catch up with Ouch Patients Holly and Haiden. Meanwhile, in Accident and Emergency, one patient has cut her nose and another has injured his toe.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8497a3a76e7108b55a2c45372ae086c5</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Bitzer misuses a drone when he tries to avoid carrying out work on the farm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcd11eb044caf8f67e02610ba8ec325f6</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>There's relief all around when Penfold's pilfering of Squawk's gadgets and clandestine late night trips to shady warehouses turns out to be preparation for his taking part in 'bot battles' - a fight club for homemade robots. Penfold hopes to enter his own creation, Geoff, into the competition but is sidelined by an overeager Danger Mouse and his own robot, the CRN 3000! When the CRN 3000 obliterates all challengers, DM's call for a worthy opponent is answered by Megahurtz. But Megahurtz may have a secret android army agenda..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde29da8858858630df09e3d74b98aad8</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis is blamed for a theft he didn't commit, and Mrs Creecher's new super-powered tech specs mean she can suddenly see way too well. She teams up with Sergeant Slipper to track down fugitive Dennis who has to somehow hide from the all-seeing tech specs so he can prove his innocence and find the real culprit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9454788f65f621ff9c917a2a87fdf112</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The gang want to win theme park tickets that are up for grabs in a robot fighting contest. They ask to use Mouse?s unbeatable robot, but he prefers to help them build their own.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pafe052db79735499dff691fceca1bb7c</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9edb88344e324659963ff862da143f71</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Desperate for peace and quiet, an alien leader orders an entertainer to take care of his planet's creatures. However, things nearly go wrong when Konpeki brings a giant cake.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5456763dfebacd2f3cd1490329ffc3f2</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Oswald has to go undercover as a robot to enter a villain warehouse run by robots.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9650307258ff3c58890c801ef70cee77</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle feels she is being taken for granted by the other heroes, so she joins the Fairy Squad when they arrive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa88b9a6c763d7c35c89b5f246f002e9f</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A rocket carries the cabin into space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c78219ad43711cd65fcc2202b9c6992</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:40AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>For the first time, the heroes have no-one to face.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c5dacb8a85052d8a9002aa0099aa4a5</image>
    <start>08:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Guy Mowbray narrates Elemental Gladiators, Judge Rinder has a science beef, and someone tries to steal the earth?s gold. Gladiator Steel and Big Manny guest star.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbdf6815053dbff6701c86636f9365c49</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Social media superstar Big Manny joins us for some mind-blowing science, along with his pal Big Danny from CBBC series Horrible Science! Meanwhile, Abby and Shini go head-to-head as they create crafts for Henry, and Joel tries one of the fastest racquet sports in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf4e659d70bd99bd5f5f5ef7d4f1720fc</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Out of This World</title>
    <desc>In this episode, Dr Maggie tells the story of the Space Race, what it was, the key missions involved and how the USA, competing against and then collaborating with the Soviet Union, got us to where we are today in space. Dr Maggie?s guest is Tim Peake, the first British astronaut to live on board ISS, who tells us how astronauts from different countries successfully work together in space. Dr Maggie also answers your space questions and unveils her top five 'firsts in space'. Buckle up, it?s time to go Out Of this World.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ae90359fda623e4c4cca90584ac5fec</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors reveal the special cells in your eyes which help you to see out of the corner of your eye, and they find out what it takes to be a hospital entertainer in Operation Takeover. Dr Chris heads to a laboratory where scientists are making blood from stem cells, and more medical mysteries are answered in Ouch and About On Call. Meanwhile in Accident and Emergency, one patient is brought in by air ambulance after cutting her chest and another has hit his head on a goalpost.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p63453458af02730d3c9fb9e7edeeff0a</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Absolute Genius with Dick and Dom</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom reveal the genius of Alexander Fleming, the man who discovered penicillin. Inspired by Fleming's discovery, they come up with their own genius idea, which involves an attempt to turn billions of germs into priceless works of art.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p309d30b8d42b09979b89d379f9ab2a99</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve gets strangled by a python on a night-time river expedition, climbs a 40-metre tree and finds out why our thirst for palm oil is threatening bears and orangutans.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67b94d84e46735230be43eeb3299950c</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Helena is 11 and an only child. She loves star-gazing, wants to be an astrophysicist when she's older and is passionate about girls getting into science. She lives above her mum and dad's bookshop where they often work seven days a week, which means she doesn't get the chance to get out and look at the night sky! Helena needs a den to help her reach for the stars and fulfil her science dreams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1f2e3b6974f015f6b0ca1ace8dbc4cd1</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch! Do Try This at Home</title>
    <desc>Did you know your body contains invisible ink! Find out how, and make your own in today?s Do Try experiment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa35bf10e668ea1de3cefedc98b1e2193</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>In Ouchology, the doctors end up in a ball-throwing fight with their kid quizmasters, and it all ends with a snot, snot, snotting! Dr Xand rolls out the crushing machine in the lab to do an experiment to find out how strong your teeth are. It?s a packed Ouch and About, with George wanting to know why we burp, Clark asking why we need to sleep, and Ana asking why people have different eye colours. We fly across New South Wales, Australia, with Jesse and the Flying Doctors, to attend his hospital appointment in Sydney. In the emergency department, Nathan has an injured arm after jumping off the slide at Edinburgh Zoo and accidentally landed it, and Isabella is there after bending her finger backwards when catching the ball in Gaelic football practice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p253932508603c60d14861f3f57c194fd</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Dara O Briain joins Rattus for a show marking the 1969 moon landings. The first use of rocket power, the Space Race, and poo floating in the Apollo 10 cockpit - it?s all here.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3b16feb8fe52de83be854e94c8528cc0</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Dani Dyer becomes Rattus? political advisor as we look at everything from the birth of democracy to Margaret Thatcher having to change her voice so she would be taken more seriously.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe182f6581902cd62ce7c49196c4794d8</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Phantom prank Fire at a kids' birthday party! The rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3eb6afc7027c8bfed2f443d8a7e7d70e</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Only Danger Mouse can save the world from chaos when the Baron stops the world spinning with a plague of traffic lights.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb74677422bfaddaf06495faaf5c7c649</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse must fight his own urge to be awesome to stop the world turning into a gigantic intergalactic tourist attraction. Attempting to prove his theory that what the world always needs is a hero, Danger Mouse fights off what appears to be an alien invasion of Earth - but his inflated ego soon becomes the real intergalactic threat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d43d2ca6490ff7c844b2a28644f5408</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. When the Baron rearranges the countries of the world, Danger Mouse reluctantly joins forces with his American counterpart Jeopardy Mouse and takes New Zealand for a spin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p360a767bfafedebd93220d5ac0d52736</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Convinced that Mrs Creecher is secretly a master of Blamjitsu, JJ persuades the gang to help trick her into revealing her blam credentials.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p631f5a239e4e0ec4323d1cb7272bc565</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Doctor Pfooflepfeffer covets the world-beating power of Gnasher?s indestructible teeth and will stop at nothing to get her hands on one of those doggy dental marvels.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59953623a390b0bb5924ff89d145ecab</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>In an attempt to deprive Gnasher of the food that fuels his active gnashy ways, Walter takes over Butch Butcher?s sausage-making business. His careless manufacturing produces a monster fatberg under Beanotown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb5164c803a844f8f80c3bae6cf0a997d</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert is starting to feel his age and secretly drinks from the Fountain of Youth. However, his desire to be young puts the whole quest in jeopardy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ecebebc10b6dd928dcf3e72f8f98353</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes are faced with the Goblin King moving into the Big Birch, they decide to invent a quest that will soon have him running back home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9987df26df4a4713222e9b576a9111f2</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>While questing to keep her hero safe on her long journey, superfan Blossom fusses and frets too much, making things awkward.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe6ab2dbb5103b7a559efd71238dac7b</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy wakes up, starving. But the last jar of Yummy chocolate spread is empty..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6249cd28fbebaf95201eaf78204e2ea2</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy tries to catch a fish despite the Lemmings kitesurfing and the presence of a shark.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb27ef18ffa8ce9017aca0bcd9ad70c9</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings search for a treasure to get food from a Yummy vending machine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb531860e4f8bc74791e6847b3f6060c</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>The Riders 'borrow' the bathysphere to rescue a dragon from the Giant Realm Sea.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p06f0734900052ca1f851c1ae74a1007b</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Phil threatens to shut down D?Angelo?s new dragon hospital and ban dragons from Icaris.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p197fcf1e4105851d58d47e7897bb38ad</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Absolute Genius with Dick and Dom</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom reveal the genius of Marie Curie, one of the most famous female scientists of all time. Inspired by Curie's genius ideas, they come up with their own, involving an exploding shed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3543cf785071a9fdbac6f7d09ff15d58</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Mankind's most ingenious inventors are given the Horrible Histories treatment, as we take in everything from the invention of the wheel to the crisp. Featuring the Gutenberg press and the man who invented both the dictionary (very successfully) and manned flight (less successfully). The Greeks and the Chinese battle over which of them are history's best inventors.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb40dd24edf30376dcde41e26f84f9d48</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Meet superheroes the Force Force, and some of the 17th century?s greatest minds star in Friends parody Colleagues.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4445e4f38acf7b7b10fc376fb94229f1</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>In the last episode of the series, the doctors reveal the amazing strength of your jaw, and they see if they can take the heat when they try their hands at being hospital ward chefs in Operation Takeover. Dr Xand joins the ear, nose and throat department to see how they fix their patients, and Dr Chris hits the wards answering questions for one last time in Ouch and About On Call. Meanwhile, in accident and emergency, one patient is treated for an injury to her neck, and another has cut his foot on a tin lid.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcdecb0a9327e2f8513f2c382caa36004</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>It's breakfast time and the Farmer discovers he has no fresh milk for his morning cup of tea. He sets off in great haste, only to become ensnared in a rush-hour traffic jam. Shaun and the flock are too impatient to wait for breakfast and take matters into their own hands.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p088b7d593b9612bc3c0ca56fc9be6700</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Professor Squawkencluck's mum comes to visit, a gigantic, enraged rubbish monster is not far behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b7ec02901562c8e1059c044cd0f4ea2</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>JJ's so keen to get Dennis the new bike she thinks he's desperate to have, that she agrees to make a deal with Walter, and without realising it, passes on information that could lead to a jelly-blasting rampage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa1bb76b218a457237dfce1e5ebc35333</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Girl gets the chance to put together the school fair, her friends and family jump at the chance to help - until she gets advice from a hardened businesswoman.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4cd9a8aad5a8972f434d9ccaeb212454</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2bd0988d13fb42595cb68c7b6aeca473</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy discovers a large medieval magic trunk that can blend two objects into one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pff242cee066692bb20051f5801aa4ba8</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings invent a whole bunch of bouncing games with spongy jelly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbb1b3cbed1ad523cc29301b3f302378</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When Ms O gets trapped in a mirror, an opposite Ms O enters the real world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b48182adb66613b0fc536f363f44734</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Blossom accidentally uses a witch?s broom to make sticks for toasting marshmallows, the owner of the broom casts a spell of squeaky voices on all the heroes. The spell will be lifted once the heroes have returned with new broomstick branches. A simple enough quest, think the heroes, until they realise that a witch?s broom can only be made from the branches of the Really Spooky Tree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe37511be85e501039449287ddef18d2b</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve searches for deadly animals living in the capital of Suriname, from snakes in people's gardens to snail-catching kites and one of the deadliest snakes on earth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe4132eb31df163e9d473abb7ca294ba5</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 9-11 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about trade around the world, depending on other countries, and fair trade.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb5416d2cc7e01e718b523b53fe4fa2e</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch! Do Try This at Home</title>
    <desc>The doctors investigate how your body digests fat and show you how to make bile art.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a1316004b0d4ec7b3297d91c06acabe</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Venus has acid rain, crushing pressure, and is hotter than an oven, so it might not sound like the ideal place to live. However, up in the clouds it's almost just like home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7f9b2b3d6a55c376803ef930bc3a47da</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>It?s the start of term, and the girls are arriving from all over the world to study. New student Cherry says goodbye to her family in Shanghai, and Spanish student Valentina swaps Barcelona for Bristol.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd1c86654d04488a7148708bae8da4c55</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ten Pieces</title>
    <desc>A classical music adventure with the theme of nature. Today?s celebrated artists are Hans Zimmer, Vivaldi and Mason Bates.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a862509d0b90eafb7b25a4dea3f1c42</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Prepare for some monster truck mayhem and very clever canines.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p71c270c4136679c25089e9e0d14a075d</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>The Horrible History of (sometimes literally) dressing to kill. Henry VIII has beef over whose armour is best and Louis XV dresses as a hedge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c7dbeb45cd739828723ad58e7a98425</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:25AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Goalkeeper and football fan Tristan had to take a break from playing with his local team due to illness. He wants a den to help him recover and to store all his football memorabilia.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd3ab6cc8075b80c38ce9f444d55923be</image>
    <start>11:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Bound for their world tour, the Odd Socks detour to Moxy?s old school to wish an old teacher farewell. However, seeing the school in dire straits, the Odd Socks agree to help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41734c8c3da718be74178e786f718043</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>Inspired by the statue of the Giant Buddha of Leshan, Ubercorn teaches the Go Jetters all about mindfulness to help them to concentrate, be calm and be kind to each other. They go to visit the massive thousand-year-old statue in China, which is carved into the mountainside by a river. Meanwhile, Grandmaster Glitch wants to have a statue of himself, but the Grimbots have made it too small. He takes them to Leshan to the Giant Buddha statue to show them how big his statue should be! But when he builds a giant viewing platform on top of a boat, he loses control of the boat and causes a whirlpool, putting the statue, tourists and himself at risk.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pca8bf0b9206a9ad3b8ea1c85fe2e7937</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Cosima and Big Lizard go paddleboarding, but Dunk and the river creatures are behaving strangely. Could it be something to do with Dad's desire for a cup of tea.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1d55fbcb09b03cf9ffa242d7d1336e80</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts must get two mantis shrimp to stop fighting before their powerful claw strikes destroy the Octopod.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7282a7a4575d47511dc5c86828447560</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When all the other danger agents become supersmart due to a batch of genetically enhanced celery, Danger Mouse might need to find a new job.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd3564fbdb5d3af356c096d2505f6a6f2</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>Connie and Ruby move into Maple Close with their dog, Jelly. Mrs Hobbs can't help but express her disapproval. She hates dogs and now there'll be another one living in close proximity. Waffle is not allowed to go on a family camping trip but accidentally goes on a different adventure.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8171a9400eb84ffa40515c124dd0a4eb</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Carrot is excited to show the Tato Team her new inventions, including an improved Robotato, who will help them protect the supermarket from Evil Pea. Unfortunately, Robotato still has a few glitches, so the veggies decide to test Carrot's new jetpacks instead, but Evil Pea sneaks in and commands Robotato to protect her. When Robotato continues to glitch, he becomes overly protective of Evil Pea and takes her to the top of Tato Tower to keep her safe. The Tato Team, led by the real Supertato, must use their new jetpacks to fly up and save her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p60d821ac09d4855c7a7bd5fbee4dc5b1</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis dresses Gnasher up as a rare breed of animal which he says is nesting in Bash Street School, hoping to get the school shut down on the day of a daunting and difficult test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf1530f2f032cd4d976fda5d61929b327</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Gnasher is practically immobile inside a full-body cast. When he goes missing, Dennis and the gang race all over Beanotown to find him, always one step behind the helpless hound.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd55d2e54635de7190d8ef7a9ff7d0bd0</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert has invented a new contraption to help him fly using an old set of bagpipes. The 'Herbecopter', as Herbert likes to call it, is rather noisy but extremely effective, and Twinkle is unhappy at no longer being the only flying hero. So, when the heroes quest to get Friendlyface?s priceless locket back from a dragon, Twinkle and Herbert become extremely competitive and risk completely failing the quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa955ab16670c700cec4ca1249af0b548</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A panicked factory owner asks the Ninjas for help to produce Xian Ye's action figure, but Konpeki's obsession with the soccer star makes it difficult to complete the task.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc2a8751c3ff7bce191db43b611b67043</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Tyler's plan to put on a great magic show leads him to a first love with Chanelle, the mysterious daughter of a magic shop owner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p591e916a619458ea37abeabbe37213b3</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Grace puts her plan in jeopardy when she tries to decide the alternates on the behalf of Ariana. Meanwhile, Pete makes a shocking discovery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb534467793dd86cf85aea38c9573eb1c</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A special show featuring some of history?s greatest firsts, including the first ever library, Olympic Games, people on the moon and rat roller-skating on TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe595a876ef9e17bc0b058bb214d6279</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s time for Gnasher?s annual bath, but the stinky hound will do anything to avoid the tub. Dennis and Gnasher go head to head in a town-wide game of cat and mouse ? or rather, tripe hound and wheelie bathtub.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cd3695300ecc962061ac4a3338675c2</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Penfold's chances of winning a Sidekickie award are in peril when Stiletto attempts to snatch the prize. Greenback plots to destroy the world with termites, and DM gets overly enthusiastic.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5dac06606cd79dcc8c7ef381fc1e28a0</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>In need of a ping-pong player for a charity competition, a coach orders one from the Ninjas, who deliver an unlikely duo to step in and save the match.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8a452a37a3bf824313780a28eb47d849</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy decides to teach the Lemmings how to behave in his presence.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p913be4806ad3e2c1689fd5eb48cd770b</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Stevie Smith challenges Boy in the mini-golf tournament. However, as they practice, they actually become fast friends and neglect their training to hang out! When the contest arrives, it is revealed Stevie was only pretending to be Boy's friend to keep him from practicing! But maybe Boy has a trick of his own up his sleeve..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6124bb0a527325104289dd14cfd0a09</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom is terrible at keeping secrets, and Trevor can?t help but point that out. To prove him wrong, Blossom refuses to reveal the secret hiding place for her piece of the Amulet of Protection, even though the heroes need it to stop Balthazar casting a weather spell on the forest. With a rain of crabs heading their way, the heroes must quickly persuade Blossom to reveal her secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96c570335130856ee7aaba63648a0da2</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia tries to win back a stolen gadget on a villain game show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb69a979896a239aad4b2ee7aff59854b</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Agent Olympia is not happy when an agent with the same name shows up at headquarters. Curriculum: Measuring temperature.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3dc5e187c321f7b4f6f77226abb9c3ea</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth sets out to get rid of all their old toys, hoping Chef will buy the new toy she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65f80c82e11fb083e3d726fe80ab11f0</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Riposte Prime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p46c6550b324a83053b88341b3ace3e0c</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Back on the Brave Olivine, Liko, Roy and Dot receive an unexpected challenge to battle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc610269f8f8b3a6cfce6acc923f40f3</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>An episode featuring everything from the creation of the number zero to the beginnings of the whole universe. The moon gets lonely, there's an ISS cookery competition, and DI Loofah arrests a banana.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd676881cb9166a7245a8568e8887284c</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. Eldon struggles to choose between Emily and Michelle as his partner for his duet performance. Meanwhile, West and Stephanie are at odds on how to proceed with their duet, leaving West wanting to quit altogether.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p04808ce7876b8c91c18ff4bcda0224b8</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>A new season at Hawx Academy brings new faces, new challenges and old rivalries.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e471a642d1c44ef35c378fd85b704e5</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The Farmer returns from the fair triumphant after winning a coconut. However, he soon discovers that getting into the coconut isn't as easy as it seems. Shaun and Bitzer take on the challenge and try every trick in the book, but it proves a tough nut to crack.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p875401599db042c3e7ce6c4b9d828786</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Squawkencluck reboots the now 100 per cent reliable Big Head base computer, which immediately locks up everyone in a maximum security prison.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p807580e7b44481f79c8475072cd446ef</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Pieface rescues Walter and Bertie from danger, Dennis leads the town in celebrating Pieface Day in his honour, and refuses to listen when Pieface tries to tell him it was all one big mistake. Walter uncovers the truth, proclaims himself the bigger hero, and declares it Walter Week.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb170db80b8ddebd1db3623d045ac81d7</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Dog has been hired as a security guard at the new community pool. When the kids discover the long line at the pool, they try to convince Dog to break the rules and let them in.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdce10fd8e03af26808250cfe9b70e50e</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56c50e78c083f332c64372c15fb617a3</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings happen upon a bracelet that increases the strength of its wearer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf0bbfcc8819c6d4070635c011e0c4b6</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy unwittingly brings to life some medieval armour.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p66d8b51df61953b017f9bc3cd78533e0</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents try to resolve a disagreement between Ms O and Oksana.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pec925f8ad8786901c400467620fa98d3</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to the Mexican island of Cabo Pulmo, where the people have worked tirelessly to bring their surrounding oceans back to life and make it a marine reserve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf3c3ce794d1e94b9e89b0164a58c3960</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Lean about identifying instruments, organising instruments, and playing untuned percussion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p64f03d4b7cd980886fb46e9bfa0f68f7</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch! Do Try This at Home</title>
    <desc>Your body?s largest organ is your skin ? find out how it works and how to make your own homunculus.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc6e11aa69711b02920406cab9bc587bd</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Find out how to shout from one side of the world to the other.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b2e79aec7951746d11fd0d4da203fd8</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>We go behind the scenes in the boarding house, where the girls take a weekend sightseeing trip to the historic city of Bath. House mistress Miss Hollingsworth gets more than she bargained for during Smoothie Night.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6021689dd0e5331656dd0d8881e2c00c</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ten Pieces</title>
    <desc>A classical music adventure with the theme of home. Today?s celebrated artists are Kerry Andrew, Dvorak and George Gershwin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc15225d011f909c7b5082004ce8d4ef</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Don't Blame Me, Blame My Brain</title>
    <desc>Ken's brain wants to know if it's possible to catapult yourself to the moon. Space expert Vinita Marwaha Madill and inventor Tom Stanton have answers - but Leila may have to test it out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p17291ddae7ecd3ea5e9f9bd9a7ccc1a4</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Best in the World is the entertainment clip show that invites CBBC viewers to playalong at home with Guinness World Records. We showcase the greatest and wackiest record breakers in hilarious guessing games - can you forecast the winner, solve what just happened or master how to take on a title at home? Coming up, REALLY big food and dogs that can skip! Take a seat and tune in.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p49f92e024981eb2e142c06ff9a86ceb9</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>History tells of great minds coming together to achieve great things. It also tells of idiots combining to make an unholy mess. HH looks at some of the best and worst collaborations.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3016ee01d6e84d546c92dfe8fc038985</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:25AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Emily from the Scottish Highlands, near Inverness, is crazy about crochet, and her crafty creations are taking over the house and driving Mum and Dad mad. She desperately needs a space where she can crochet to her heart?s content, store all her woolly wonders and hang out with mates.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p28bf82015f8004929ff36b77baeb5fb4</image>
    <start>11:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy is determined to make the Odd Socks into ?proper? teachers, but the band?s unique methods lead to chaos. Can they turn it around before the school day ends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8112d8a5b097c024da3a23604243c06c</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>It's a whirlwind of windmill excitement as the Go Jetters travel to Kinderdijk in the Netherlands to celebrate National Mill Day. A lot of the Netherlands is below sea level and there is a high risk of flooding, so here at Kinderdijk, ditches and pumps are used to drain away the water. This used to be done by windmills using wind power, but nowadays the pumping stations are powered by diesel fuel or electricity, but the old windmills still work too! Whilst also flying over Kinderdijk, Grandmaster Glitch's Grim HQ runs out of fuel and crashes into the water. Furious, he sends the Grimbots off to find some fuel. They hook in to the Kinderdijk pumping station and start taking the fuel. Once they've taken all the diesel fuel for Grim HQ, the pump stops working and the water level rises, threatening to flood the area! The Go Jetters need to get the windmills going again to bring the water level back down.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32e09a87c4384f929549a3ff96b40885</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When Big Lizard and Cosima get covered in nectar, they become unwilling house guests to some overfriendly beetles. Will Dunk come to their rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p524c511b14f3f403c4ed79db32c143e3</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts follow a strange song to a lonely humpback whale who is alone because he doesn't sound like the other whales.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4d9d5c2b0b1ef0f3b0a7738e42e00408</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Has Danger Mouse finally met his match? An evil version of the hero escapes from a parallel dimension and joins forces with Baron Greenback.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa755ac1daa2a711230c9321971439bf6</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>Waffle is sad that Mrs Hobbs and her cat, George, are soon to leave Maple Close. The Brooklyn-Bells call on Mrs Hobbs to persuade her not to move house, only to find that her cat, George, has fleas. They offer to help and discover a secret about Mrs Hobbs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe6cd8ff77b7b818eb51ab4c7108a7c09</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>All the fruit and veggies in the supermarket are enjoying Fruit and Veggie Friends Day, but Evil Pea is determined to ruin it. After Supertato inadvertently stops her from taking the friendship cards and launching attacks with her pea shooter and freezy hose, Evil Pea tries to cover the party in ice cream. But when her plan goes wrong, she's rolled away on the ice cream tub, and Supertato saves her. Supertato has been trying to give her a friendship card all day long - Evil Pea furiously accepts it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a4eef83b0ae13753f02449259a0fffc</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A classmate who Dennis and Walter barely know gets appointed as Class 3C?s late monitor, making it urgent that the boys find a way to pal up with him, whatever it takes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb4a96a66a98d1a34eb95c4f1dbe72396</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis was up most of the night and can barely stay awake. Gnasher and the gang work hard to help steer dozing Dennis through the day, when all he wants to do is continue to dream about battling Zombie-Spiders.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0cde7e1c096f93579aa55afb03c8a28</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Blossom accidentally uses a witch?s broom to make sticks for toasting marshmallows, the owner of the broom casts a spell of squeaky voices on all the heroes. The spell will be lifted once the heroes have returned with new broomstick branches. A simple enough quest, think the heroes, until they realise that a witch?s broom can only be made from the branches of the Really Spooky Tree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe37511be85e501039449287ddef18d2b</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When her superhero suit gets shrunk in the wash, Mega Hero Girl summons the Ninjas to find her a new one so that she can save a planet from an incoming asteroid.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p43b73bae7cd910ec88e39265c681b614</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Social media superstar Big Manny joins us for some mind-blowing science, along with his pal Big Danny from CBBC series Horrible Science! Meanwhile, Abby and Shini go head-to-head as they create crafts for Henry, and Joel tries one of the fastest racquet sports in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf4e659d70bd99bd5f5f5ef7d4f1720fc</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Everything is on the line as A-Troupe band together to dance their best for the internationals re-adjudication. Their international dreams could come to an end right here.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7aa95b2108b997a0d2b516428e67a3b3</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Doctors Chris and Xand van Tulleken join Rattus for a selection of old and new sketches relating to bodies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd1e3c6ee4d77f8aa381d5d9631f1907d</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The after-school art club is under threat of imminent demolition. In trying to save the club, the gang end up on the trail of the mysterious undercover urban artist known only as Pranksy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p361a97fdcd2b35beabb23cae8c4b65d6</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. DM and Penfold go back to school to thwart the plans of an evil food scientist and his killer hot dogs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb21a92b26ce148448dc51ad882cf481e</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Keen to join a race with her classmates, a cavegirl orders a tame T-rex from the Ninjas. But they must work together with her teacher to train the unruly dinosaur.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd34d7bee5af1cf2dfe9ae7b94e254c8f</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings and Grizzy collide with Santa's sled while fighting.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52b1e6f84ec56e979f7ae61d9ab6360d</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Sick of being overlooked by the family because of his small size, Mouse builds an invention to make him grow. However, the bigger he gets, the more unintentionally destructive he becomes, and now the family needs to shrink him back to normal before he accidentally destroys them all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcadd15f00352c8d0af7b6df012dae117</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Gnome Crystal Mine has ground to a halt, leaving the forest with no crystals, no power supply and melting ice lollies! The heroes are tasked with a quest to find out what has happened and to fix it. It turns out that a slimy beast named Smarg has made the mine her home. But with Hoofius?s fear of gunk getting the better of him, evicting the slippery Smarg is not going to be easy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p858de20cb9333a64f647c54c77975ddd</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Ms O tells Olympia and Otis a story about a famous villain duo. Curriculum: Adding, subtracting and multiplying by zero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf57f18551a75efc65bc912f7566e48af</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia and Otis are tasked with calling a truce between feuding guests. Curriculum: Using a Venn Diagram, 3D shapes: spheres and cubes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a7cc9c25316a9316d40d4a87c98e2f3</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When the last page of the story-time book is lost, Gwen steps in to create the ending.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11fb197af7d8998c4056abf304e72828</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face an invisible enemy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa159bd9b067167936a1a52cfe1fdcccb</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Roy and Crocalor accidentally switch places while exploring a festival in Kitakami.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81f2a223a60d16fe5b399233394f87f5</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Science goes too far in Fartenheimer, music goes too far in Heads, Shoulders, Knees, Toes and All the other Bones in the Body, and there's a Swiftian take on the water cycle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa83dcfd68984c53c5bff2b5550e247f5</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>The A-Troupe is selected to perform in a music video for the band Brighter Brightest. However, the dancers become divided over the routine that Emily has choreographed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1cebf96b6035361baef8cc6b75b9d892</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Phoenix Rise</title>
    <desc>New term, new head teacher, new rules. The gang face their toughest challenge yet ? can they stay united and prove that no matter what the adversity, friendship always wins.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paaa8cea97be89acfa657098f9a5bbdc2</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Torrential rain threatens to ruin the annual sheepdog trials, but the Farmer begs the judges for an opportunity to show off his talented flock. Things go smoothly until Timmy tries to learn to whistle. Will this stop the Farmer winning another cup to add to his prize collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p73a40f719261a972a7705015619559e0</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's attempts to boost Penfold's confidence backfire when they lead to a ferocious games monster escaping into the real world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p107003566b41bffd5346594c3f9d54eb</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang's efforts to help JJ master the ancient art of blamjitsu are ruined by Walter's plans to capture the Beanotown yeti. Dennis and the gang defend the yeti, and help JJ unleash her inner blam, in a gravity-defying blamjitsu face-off with the WilburCorp henchbot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7402f764d3e73fd8d184465e1f5760b5</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Ripped Ab-Man asks Boy to help him win a game show, his siblings worry that he is being taken advantage of and decide to investigate.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf914925c1b6b7702d013f14169a136b9</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9c35fdc0a983a34d1d5d6909fe55362c</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings have fun painting themselves alongside the noblemen on artwork.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c5fc548d220eb4c3ac974f498deb67d</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings meet fairies, one of which breathes life into their bagpipes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52ca24e90332e5cc7495b2699e4a3e40</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. It's party time for all the new agents at Odd Squad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf0a3057b49a3fac00f873c8c93ccec14</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Trevor is extremely proud of being the clever one in the gang and thinks that his smart mouth is his superpower. However, his friends feel that sometimes his jokes go too far - and they are right to be concerned! When Mr Friendlyface sends the heroes on a quest to prevent Toothgrinder the Ogre from messing up the village green, it?s Trevor?s smart mouth that puts all the heroes in danger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc10a55045431109408268b6cc99aaf5</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to meet some of the most endangered animals in southern Africa - wild dogs. He meets the people working to save them and explores why their survival is so important.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa86bff10b00032a9259c03724729dbc1</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about high- and low-pitched sounds, what pitch is, and what melody is.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf211cca0b9b7a7d8afa957869e0506f7</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch! Do Try This at Home</title>
    <desc>Did you know your body contains invisible ink! Find out how, and make your own in today?s Do Try experiment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa35bf10e668ea1de3cefedc98b1e2193</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>We try out three potential ways to become invisible and discover some surprising side effects.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p23c6809af5ddcda857f665178f5d8c5c</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>As the girls celebrate Chinese New Year, PE teacher Miss Elsley believes netball player Jina could be destined for sporting success. She has arranged a visit from a local scout, but will Jina prove her potential.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1def4e8561c1d0605c3a50d7cd92b047</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ten Pieces</title>
    <desc>A classical music adventure with the theme of being all around the world. Today?s celebrated artists are Ravi Shankar, Grazyna Bacewicz and Aaron Copland.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p26babf3b60b03f29fd61a40ffd17c51c</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Get ready for world-class bread-spreading and some super-charged water-sledding.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p135b1f22e016eb62c9054e13bf442e3d</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Fred Sirieix guides Rattus through the Horrible History of Manners, including the benefits of not holding farts in and Puritan dating,. And Jane Austen visits Historical Love Island.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa927d6a7a46abf6f1d31310fc03b008e</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:25AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Sea cadet Jonny became fascinated with naval history through his grandad and is now a huge fan. He wants a submarine-themed den where he can celebrate his passion, learn more and enjoy hanging out with mates.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ea18464ad22d082afcdbda42444b889</image>
    <start>11:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Pushed out of his comfort zone, Blu must tackle his inability to dance in order to put on a show and impress a celebrity judge. The whole school is counting on him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p44b1570c05248dbb219bc90913aa1ef5</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>Grandmaster Glitch has been invited to Djenn? in Mali, Africa, to visit the people and to see one of his favourite things at work - mud! He is especially impressed by the spectacular Great Mosque of Djenn?, the largest structure made from mud in the world. But mud brings problems, and during the rainy season the rain causes damage to the walls of the mosque and the mud houses, so the local people get together to help repair them. Glitch wants to help, but when he realises they have to do this job every single year, he makes a massive umbrella to try to keep the mosque dry so that the local people don't have to repair it again. Although Glitch was only trying to help, things start to go wrong. The huge Grimbrella swings too close to the mosque and goes out of control. The Go Jetters need to fix that Glitch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb948df4d839f129b32e45883fd963c9d</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Whilst Dad is stuck in the desert, D.O.R.I.S. tries to give Cosima and Big Lizard a lesson on friction. As things begin to heat up, a creature steals Cosima's only means to locate Dad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p97e3cc32ecc4e159bdc13c41b6495529</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated series. When a storm washes Peso onto a mysterious, rocky island, he meets a band of lobster-like insects thought to be extinct.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3c238e77822acd1056d91b7f91f7f1b</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold become reluctant parents when it appears the Baron has wiped his own memory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3e99b351aa4afb22052be158681eea93</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>It's Waffle's birthday and Mr Willow throws a huge party for him. As the Brooklyn-Bells prepare a surprise for Waffle, Connie and Ruby's dog, Jelly, leads the Wonder Dog astray.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2019991eb0dba729c1525e7376588aa3</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Supertato, Carrot and the Grape Kids are enjoying flying kites until Evil Pea arrives in her balloon and cuts them down so she can rule the supermarket skies! Supertato and Carrot must climb a display of chopsticks to retrieve the kites from the top. Evil Pea threatens to cut them down again, so Supertato and Carrot turn their kites into hang-gliders and embark on an epic aerial chase with Evil Pea, leading to her bursting her balloon on a chopsticks display sign. Supertato and Carrot land safely on the ground, ready to fly kites again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6eb6445bbe867844a72eca73179f9c21</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Determined to prove he can accomplish a task without getting distracted, Dennis takes on the simple job of bringing the class register to the school office. He instantly distracts himself on an epic scale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb20653e5b67a5132f1ebf7148c402cbf</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Miss Mistry arranges to tag along with Dennis and the gang after school, in an attempt to enhance her teaching skills and prevent school governor Pfooflepfeffer from banning her beloved teaching magazine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7390c9ba105b7ed1875a12a98670c204</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas bring superstar Jean Pascal to the aid of a princess who orders a talented musician to help in calming her difficult dragon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcf7f65ee4caa33a4d5430d34dd5b581b</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Carmen drops May-Li's valuable antique necklace down the toilet and is torn over whether she should try to get it back or lie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc48de8981174bde3e93018046c1a1f80</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Anthony is put in a tough position when Ariana asks to be let back on the team. Ethan works towards something new, and Ebby has her first date with Remy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e5fab11548fcca7b2bac6298a9fe378</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A pirate captain worries about an early bedtime, a soldier from World War I struggles to cook with fake food and the four King Georges form a boy band.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p044d9bfea34359a4b414a6d8c3906513</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Convinced that Mrs Creecher is secretly a master of Blamjitsu, JJ persuades the gang to help trick her into revealing her blam credentials.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p631f5a239e4e0ec4323d1cb7272bc565</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Part one of two. Danger Mouse faces his toughest challenge ever as a mysterious super-villain releases all the villains from Arkwright and plots the end of our hero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pad93a9194a1518da9967732539543b76</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A girl orders a beatboxing teacher after seeing a professional beatboxer in the park. However, the Ninjas must first figure out what beatboxing is.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a76925cb0e22cbb4f1bf4ee102b5b24</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy confiscates the remote control device, but the Lemmings find another one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb088daed596447c6f2a8d8b5466f3892</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After a bad haircut, Dog tries wearing a fancy tuxedo until his fur grows back. Unfortunately, his initial reaction to wearing clothes causes him and the gang to accidentally destroy the rich neighbour lady's fence. But while the others are forced to rebuild it, the neighbour lady gives tuxedo-clad Dog a pass, thinking someone of his style and class is too good for manual labor. Resentment grows as the gang breaks their backs in the hot sun while Dog lives the good life with the fancy lady. How long can this go on.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4bc957bb31fbb8983c5a8c2a4099f441</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is acting very strangely indeed. He refuses to stamp any of Admin Bunny?s documents, keeps getting distracted by butterflies, and seems oddly happy! The heroes are extremely suspicious and decide that someone must have swapped him with a doppelganger. Now they must quest to find out where the real Friendlyface is and get him back before the forest descends into total chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde2e0b6ed02cd81a52a1b5ae1f9bd3e8</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When Oona, Olympia and Otis accidentally change the past, they undo every odd case the Odd Squad have ever solved.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb80390acc70da483b912354957c5ff16</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth shares her slime recipe with her friends, and together they create a goo monster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p456343ae47a574c8929254e0297f6774</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug faces Argos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbd13e45abeae99a94910d22d293936f0</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Tinkatink puts up a fight when a wild Bombirdier tries to mess with its beloved hammer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4295ca2014165eb1ed34bee9ae4f69f4</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Fred Sirieix stars in Scientific First Dates, Marie Curie reacts to space, and the dinosaurs get an unwelcome musical meteor visitor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2a33358dcb8b4090c89b64ab78a468a</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>In an effort to spend more time with Riley, James accompanies her to pick up costumes for the troupe. At the studio, Stephanie takes part in a photoshoot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fb2bccc08f7b8cd3f6efd8edd116853</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Beaker Girls</title>
    <desc>Jess and Tracy Beaker are loving their new life by the seaside, but the arrival of teenage runaway Jordan is about to change everything for the Beaker Girls.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3befcf20b5a9613b723111a3eaad1961</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
