<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Miss Mistry arranges to tag along with Dennis and the gang after school, in an attempt to enhance her teaching skills and prevent school governor Pfooflepfeffer from banning her beloved teaching magazine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7390c9ba105b7ed1875a12a98670c204</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s Pieface?s turn to look after the class hamster, Space Captain Harrison McScruff-Butt. His own self doubt and Walter?s resolve to sabotage him lead to a rescue mission to free Scruff-Butt from Walter?s mansion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p030b103e478730d5108a53c51e2b4099</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang convince Mrs Creecher that Monday is actually Sunday in the hope of extending their weekend.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9b0399bee9f8bf2e99c10b04c972e7fe</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When a witch struggles to master her new wand, Twinkle decides to have a go, only to make her friends vanish. She must now go on a solo quest to find them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f70c51f662eb1e9f7b58d6b81511ec0</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes find treasure as they bid to save Merhaven from an angry seaweed. Blossom is delighted with her bath bomb treasure, but rather than use it, she insists on bringing it along on the watery quest to save it for a special occasion. But as the angry seaweed nears Merhaven, Blossom realises she must finally sacrifice her treasure to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4cabd4631ea30373511762999c2b1fe4</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes go on a quest to get Hoofius?s Toby Jug back from the depths of the Riddling Ruins and are faced with a series of puzzles and traps to solve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67fad6fb2cc188991a416f8965659da7</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings befriend a sheep.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3bdcab42cc0853f2c7b501f9fc8e0bd1</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings plot to remove the bear from the castle and prevent him from returning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p19d0bfe8e3ed2a98dca54b9d08058172</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Using a ring that lets their astral bodies travel, the Lemmings decide to haunt Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3d4c3cf119692497d318da30bb58dfed</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find magic books that make their story content appear in real life when opened.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p01c270a57a4691a1423701fd684d5433</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. Superhero Slippy Nana sort of saves a peach from a terrifying ordeal, Count Grape-ula strikes an unsuspecting victim, the maki and iso ambush a suspicious nigiri in a ninja sushi attack, deep in the back of the mouldy fridge, Frankfurter's monster comes to life, and the conjoined cherries attempt to start a band in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9748f75b43daf711134cae9dde0e143</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom struggles under the pressure of being the new Dragon Whisperer for Rakke Town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p40b188dbaa28ff3d308ffd24f4f71b58</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>When Felicity and Darrell debate that the Third should have the same freedoms as the Sixth, the sisters end up in a personal argument. Meanwhile, Gwen?s attempt at matronly duties ends in chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb6fdec0fbada5ff792b047fb4ded947f</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Inner truths are revealed at Addie?s first sleepover, but when Jenna asks awkward questions about Miss Murphy, Keedie clams up. In the 16th century, a jailbreak is planned.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ca0e8387a808e0802f004d03ff6ea5d</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Daisy?s return makes things more difficult for Heath. Eldon and Michelle consider parting ways as an injured Pete feels left out of the Brawl.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6b5147c4642565487a47814ae7a8a27</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupers begin to switch over to Team Brawl, but when Olive and Eldon figure out a way back into regionals, Anthony and Ethan have their loyalties tested.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdfbe47178e58aaec452002ff1f8d03b8</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:20PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Insecurity begins to eat away at the Scions, which is just the opening Graven needs to try to drive the team apart by targeting Glen as the weak link. With Myridell absent on her mission back on Gorm, the Scions and their Gormiti rally against Graven?s generals with the help of a surprising ally.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03dbde17445eafa7a9a32f7a2919bcff</image>
    <start>06:20PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A block containing Grizzy and the Lemmings' ancestors cracks during their fight.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paab6bbb0e446ab132a7752a6e81c4f9e</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. On a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. But Shaun's insatiable curiosity often leads him into the unlikeliest adventures. When the Farmer takes Timmy's favourite sheep dolly, the little lamb won't stop crying. So Shaun rallies the flock to get it back from Pidsley, the farm cat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p980c4dc12b84d9a7a61ee4e79fbaa5f1</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. In trying to prove he does not believe in magic, Danger Mouse accidentally unleashes an evil magical queen into the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd4935d86a65a4e2a8c44fe8bd4ffa0d5</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Walter attempts to ruin The Dinmakers' chance of reaching fame. He will stop at nothing - even wearing a frock and pretending to be a fan called Wanda who loves Dennis in order to break up the band.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p185b9baa4b788b368de5e75e2d93003b</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy and Girl discover that while they're at school, the others are home doing all kinds of fun things, leading to a serious case of FOMO.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6c4b8a4db5057d993a3e67d0f9eff0f1</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p581a0c090349490a7bfd910e5c811c33</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Law and order has a new face as the gang investigate who is responsible for a series of mysterious slimings in the neighbourhood - they are gonna crack this case wide open.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc58aa39feb97377485fec7559bdc35aa</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Owen and new recruit Ozlyn wait out a storm while transporting a creature. Curriculum: Measurement - Capacity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pffe634bacbb854317f13c699b7c5ac6a</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes aren?t really meant to do quests without Mr Friendlyface?s express permission. But when they come across a cute little squirrel queen, and she begs for their help, they find her impossible to resist. All they have to do is quest to the Tree of Certain Doom and pass his challenges. But the squirrel queen is not who she appears to be, and the heroes have to quickly un-quest their quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc66ead86a1798e4f31033a6bf01a29a</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Myl?ne?s father - aka the Mime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p251c17eff4ede68d7c602772a8bce0a6</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:55AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Challenges, celebrities, makes and adventures with the Blue Peter team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p25914fb03e19a1a9149bdab254697dcc</image>
    <start>08:55AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>It?s time to go head-to-head in Super Smash Bros! Guided by pro gamer Slogo, the teams face off in an epic showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p467af63634bc9b5fbc3b0e35787e6d64</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs serve up edible-looking 3D art, Nick Sharratt draws a supercool koala, and Harkiran Kalsi creates an amazing seaside sculpture.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10395f10329c32202cecdd6078c3aef3</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>4 O'Clock Club</title>
    <desc>Reiss hacks Clinton?s emails and finds a secret that risks Clinton?s future with Emily. Meanwhile, CJ hatches a plan to escape Elsmere, and Amber plots to get Isaac a pay rise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe7c27848a0d1e1f1019b6e646052f308</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Joy wants the sports hall turned into a dance ballroom for a 60th birthday party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5bc1e66f925aac8080233ee7880388a2</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:20AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It?s holiday time for Danny and Mick, but Joy has not approved their time off, and so they are not going anywhere! However, Mick's brilliant idea of bringing a caravan to work gets the boys in the holiday mood - but is there enough room for both of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6fe085c61da069134cdb67209f58ad8</image>
    <start>10:20AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Who is the froggiest frog? It?s time to find out as Adam and Joe spend the day as one! Featuring a disgusting diet, loudest ribbit and an obstacle course - only one frog can win.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f55dfa77aa8e40fcce40c3ec44de082</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The One Zoo Three brothers meet the zoo?s shyest animals as Cam is challenged to a game of spot the reptile, and Tyler tries to tempt Rambutan the binturong onto his new platform.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pffff201c450fdf3ded63fd4c337cf453</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall and the Deadly 60 team travelled to six continents in search of animals for Steve's Deadly 60 list. They saw creatures with killer teeth, claws, jaws and venom. In fact they met so many incredible critters on their travels that they couldn't fit them all on the Deadly 60 list. Steve didn't want his audience to miss out, so he has given them their own programme.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf1f0cd796a1ecaf3cdb399949f9d4241</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall looks back at some of his favourite animal encounters from the Deadly 60 series. From abseiling into the incredible Gomantong cave system in search of bats and deadly creepy crawlies to a breathtaking meeting with a hippo, Steve goes behind the scenes to show how they were filmed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pee070de25938c4c02580bfe72922271b</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The Operation Ouch! 3D cinema is open! But how do you see the world in three dimensions? Find out as the Doctors look at the incredible eye muscles that control how you focus on things close-up and far away. Join Dr Dan and Dr Raph for a mind-boosting woodland adventure to help you harness your own superpower, meet new Oucher Lewis, and who is getting snotted in Ouchology? Meanwhile, in the Emergency Department, Ted has a big cut on his head and Millie has a sore foot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa01c0d331a88f99560f8afd275d888e6</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Robert Walpole struggles to talk to England's German king, a Scottish sportsman attacks dead cows in the Highland Games, American inventor Paul Revere demonstrates his gunpowder toothpaste and the Roman emperors channel the King of Pop in their musical argument over who's baddest of all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p076b846f8fd749dd8396a7b15c73d3c8</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>HHTV reporter Mike Peabody gets caught up in the French Revolution, Henry VIII enjoys a highly dangerous sport for children, Saxon king Ethelred the Unready suffers online bullying from the Vikings, and the suffragettes set the record straight in song.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32a1e5318e510461efd57a3a9fea6c2e</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Phantom is pranked by Nitro and Steel when he believes he?s in a new Gladiators video game, and the other Gladiators have fun pranking the audience behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p236851b7e42258c7058fe0b17e13f20f</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. DM and Penfold go back to school to thwart the plans of an evil food scientist and his killer hot dogs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb21a92b26ce148448dc51ad882cf481e</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Part one of two. Danger Mouse faces his toughest challenge ever as a mysterious super-villain releases all the villains from Arkwright and plots the end of our hero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pad93a9194a1518da9967732539543b76</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Second of two parts. Danger Mouse faces his toughest challenge ever as a mysterious super-villain releases all the villains from Arkwright and plots the end of our hero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe62c1a98a6a993b1b609fda59528d5d</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Miss Mistry arranges to tag along with Dennis and the gang after school, in an attempt to enhance her teaching skills and prevent school governor Pfooflepfeffer from banning her beloved teaching magazine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7390c9ba105b7ed1875a12a98670c204</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s Pieface?s turn to look after the class hamster, Space Captain Harrison McScruff-Butt. His own self doubt and Walter?s resolve to sabotage him lead to a rescue mission to free Scruff-Butt from Walter?s mansion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p030b103e478730d5108a53c51e2b4099</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang convince Mrs Creecher that Monday is actually Sunday in the hope of extending their weekend.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9b0399bee9f8bf2e99c10b04c972e7fe</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When a witch struggles to master her new wand, Twinkle decides to have a go, only to make her friends vanish. She must now go on a solo quest to find them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f70c51f662eb1e9f7b58d6b81511ec0</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes find treasure as they bid to save Merhaven from an angry seaweed. Blossom is delighted with her bath bomb treasure, but rather than use it, she insists on bringing it along on the watery quest to save it for a special occasion. But as the angry seaweed nears Merhaven, Blossom realises she must finally sacrifice her treasure to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4cabd4631ea30373511762999c2b1fe4</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes go on a quest to get Hoofius?s Toby Jug back from the depths of the Riddling Ruins and are faced with a series of puzzles and traps to solve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67fad6fb2cc188991a416f8965659da7</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings befriend a sheep.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3bdcab42cc0853f2c7b501f9fc8e0bd1</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings plot to remove the bear from the castle and prevent him from returning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p19d0bfe8e3ed2a98dca54b9d08058172</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Using a ring that lets their astral bodies travel, the Lemmings decide to haunt Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3d4c3cf119692497d318da30bb58dfed</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find magic books that make their story content appear in real life when opened.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p01c270a57a4691a1423701fd684d5433</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. Superhero Slippy Nana sort of saves a peach from a terrifying ordeal, Count Grape-ula strikes an unsuspecting victim, the maki and iso ambush a suspicious nigiri in a ninja sushi attack, deep in the back of the mouldy fridge, Frankfurter's monster comes to life, and the conjoined cherries attempt to start a band in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9748f75b43daf711134cae9dde0e143</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom struggles under the pressure of being the new Dragon Whisperer for Rakke Town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p40b188dbaa28ff3d308ffd24f4f71b58</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>When Felicity and Darrell debate that the Third should have the same freedoms as the Sixth, the sisters end up in a personal argument. Meanwhile, Gwen?s attempt at matronly duties ends in chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb6fdec0fbada5ff792b047fb4ded947f</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Inner truths are revealed at Addie?s first sleepover, but when Jenna asks awkward questions about Miss Murphy, Keedie clams up. In the 16th century, a jailbreak is planned.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ca0e8387a808e0802f004d03ff6ea5d</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Daisy?s return makes things more difficult for Heath. Eldon and Michelle consider parting ways as an injured Pete feels left out of the Brawl.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6b5147c4642565487a47814ae7a8a27</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupers begin to switch over to Team Brawl, but when Olive and Eldon figure out a way back into regionals, Anthony and Ethan have their loyalties tested.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdfbe47178e58aaec452002ff1f8d03b8</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:20PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Insecurity begins to eat away at the Scions, which is just the opening Graven needs to try to drive the team apart by targeting Glen as the weak link. With Myridell absent on her mission back on Gorm, the Scions and their Gormiti rally against Graven?s generals with the help of a surprising ally.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03dbde17445eafa7a9a32f7a2919bcff</image>
    <start>06:20PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A block containing Grizzy and the Lemmings' ancestors cracks during their fight.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0d5165179a0e73d5c59456f7492fde8e</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>11 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Pumpkins mysteriously disappear one after another, leaving nothing but a trail of slime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6abffca1412150e0b8a491be688483e</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Clip show. The Danger Agency realises that a lack of accounting has left them bankrupt. Whilst the bailiffs are in collecting goods from HQ the team decide to hold a telethon, asking people to phone in and donate to order their favourite clips to be played. Their target is a whopping ten million pounds! Can they reach their target in time? And what clip is DM trying to hide.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p85c2dc0931075bbc11c3f53b5253b881</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Mrs Creecher uses the school's allotment to hold Class 3C's 'Biggest Veg' competition. Determined to outshine Walter, Dennis will do anything to grow the biggest veg. Little does he know that JJ's gran's special potion, when mixed with Walter's dad's V-V plant food, will transform their plants into giant living, walking, groaning veggies. They turn to Paul the Potato to help them 'smoothie' out the situation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f43826a07b6a52478a605bf5876bb34</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Cheese and Dog are teasing each other about the things they like to do. However, trying out each other's interests causes them to realise what they?ve been missing out on.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb63508683548e8c2e7b000bf9934c155</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38b577f15b3726d834bb1c0d55aa55f3</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings use cans and tins to build a beach slide, which annoys Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8b1c80062ef3eec9f3327c4a586001c4</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings turn into crab rescuers, but soon the house is full of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p20c34fe3859cc08a69a508d203bb7b27</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Shadow tries to convince villains to join her Villain Network.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pce70e810ea7db6f5ced4bd12225d6602</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>The gang is bugging out when Snorp grows gigantic with them on his back! Discovering a wild west town and a rogue monster itching to destroy them, Charlie must choose to either flee or fight.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfb50286db3a726ee32f9d119b45495e4</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When tasked with the simple quest of building a flat-packed wardrobe, the heroes fail to read the instructions and are whirled into a wonky world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb7deb542b557edde37b8d10af30afbd6</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>The leisure centre is hosting a roller disco later that afternoon and Joy tells Danny and Mick if they want to be at the disco they need to finish every job on her list first. Danny spots a way to get some skating practice in and finish the jobs in double quick time ? by doing all their work on wheels! Unfortunately, when a runaway Danny crashes through the disco it looks like the whole thing might be off. Can Mick save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52e4ee264a5d8048836ac7900ce9cffb</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs build magical fairy houses, internet star DanTDM shows how to draw a gaming pug, and artist Rong Bao?s inflatable art really pops.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42deaf4110220296e2fd24e6f307b55d</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy relaxes in the massage chair, but the electricity supply stops in the log cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8b95b3a4287e28006124b3827736c563</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: XY</title>
    <desc>When destruction rises, can life prevail.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5759394681a76c6ca755bf479f6e9373</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy struggles to pick coconuts, but the Lemmings find a magic conch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe790119cb595cbdc802925b6696f6fe0</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:45AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Bionic prank Athena as a massive broccoli at a fake healthy eating film shoot. Meanwhile, the other Gladiators are up to mischief behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0478823e97e8046f6ca16e39a89023b6</image>
    <start>10:45AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>When Pickle gets stressed about her birthday party, she unintentionally opens the magical portal to Kleftania, bringing evil Lord Clunkett to Earth and seeking revenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96ec8c1439beecfc1c976f03fff179f6</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>Astra and X-Key are about to debut, and while it seems like everything is going perfectly for X-Key, the girls are faced with issues that lead them to consider an unexpected offer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p608db94003a36aa723df17fcc7cc86eb</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Erin misses Mason and tries to find a new best friend, while mystery swirls around Max. A ?friendly? match against surprise opponents puts the cat amongst the pigeons.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4efe36de8dfab4fc699ecf4c68864a82</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>Steve is on a mission to unearth the sneaky dinosaurs that were far deadlier than they first appeared! We're learning new things about even the most notorious dinosaurs, and first up, Steve meets Sinornithosaurus - a dinosaur hiding a deadly dental secret. He then races a velociraptor in a climbing challenge, with a surprising result. Finally, Steve puts Argentinasaurus to the ultimate test to see how earth-shattering its stamp really was.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p22f646b5a649f16fb8aa6ca06b8ae032</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Blu?s nephew Cub has a monstrous odd job for the band - can they help this young adventurer track down the mysterious Beti? And can Whiff find a phone signal.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c74a7d2af919ff823afcde37b4c6c68</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum sends Big Bro Adam and his best mate Joe to the funfair to see if they can keep their minds focused while on the whizzy rides.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb47d54c4c20f1433c9fc0ee49c67968b</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>A shortage of cocoa sends Tunip and the Vegimals to the Amazon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p50785359a8c7ac31a34439b206a9ae05</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Rex is missing, but Dad, Cosima and Big Lizard need him to save them from a giant slug.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd05492cf93c8626bd0f248b5750c1ac2</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>There's relief all around when Penfold's pilfering of Squawk's gadgets and clandestine late night trips to shady warehouses turns out to be preparation for his taking part in 'bot battles' - a fight club for homemade robots. Penfold hopes to enter his own creation, Geoff, into the competition but is sidelined by an overeager Danger Mouse and his own robot, the CRN 3000! When the CRN 3000 obliterates all challengers, DM's call for a worthy opponent is answered by Megahurtz. But Megahurtz may have a secret android army agenda..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde29da8858858630df09e3d74b98aad8</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis recruits Grizzly Griller to help make school sports day more extreme, but as he and JJ get competitive against each other, who is sabotaging both their chances of winning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59a7ef36f278f1b30593801e12d27fc2</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes quest to stop Balthazar from turning forest folk into household objects, Herbert realises that he can defeat the wizard?s spell by using the magic tricks he has practiced. Blossom is particularly intrigued by Herbert the Peculiar?s tricks, not to mention his stage name, so when Herbert himself is transformed into a table lamp, it?s Blossom the Very Impressive to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p02b5755668bd5974ec3f672d77162daf</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe?s latest victory is cut short after an Absolute Dance rules change shakes things up. Now, winning regionals isn?t just about their reputation. It's also about saving the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7103b075fe967418318c8e3e24cdd05d</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>As Diana prepares to leave the Brave Olivine, Amethio battles Hamber to become stronger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p127394c77d83c5f36833b133285823b5</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Taffy</title>
    <desc>Bentley and Taffy are off on their holidays! Forsythe has promised Mrs Muchmore that they will leave at exactly noon and definitely won?t be late. Bentley thinks this is the perfect time to take Taffy for a walk in the garden?s maze.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03df078deefbcb7df8f5c12b55878419</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>The Nektons explore a floating island and find the final piece of the Ephemychron in a cave. When Ant assembles it, it works! Perhaps now they can find Lemuria! But why is this island moving? What is its terrible secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8223b4a36888df0963548c717d17ff3</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang are fed up with dinner lady Olive's completely inedible school dinners. In their mission to 'drop the slop', they discover a poster of her past career as a singer. The gang ask her to join The Dinmakers, hoping she'll swap a life in the kitchen for fame. However, after unleashing Olive's inner diva, their new mission is how to get Olive back into the kitchen.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbd5d1427de633c016391ca89ecdc571b</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When all the other danger agents become supersmart due to a batch of genetically enhanced celery, Danger Mouse might need to find a new job.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd3564fbdb5d3af356c096d2505f6a6f2</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A Perfumer asks the Ninjas to help him create a new and original scent for the Queen by finding the rarest flower in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf8aaecab844d9164013726aaa9448c22</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Intrigued by a horror film on television, Timmy wanders into the farmhouse late one night. Shaun's rescue mission convinces the Farmer that the place is haunted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69270eb66e8c141c109ea661f900dd4b</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings love sesame nougat, but Grizzy also adores this treat and steals their box.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p64a57734b6a24b062d71ddbece2023c7</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mum and the girls have an annual day where they do a bunch of fun stuff together. However, this year, Mum invites the boys and Dad to join them too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7d760942471cb9ca92fa86eb5e62543c</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes have found the Wishing Trident, which will help them on their quest to prevent the summoning of the legendary two-headed dragon, Iceburn. The problem is, Blossom has used one wish by mistake, and Herbert has accidentally used a second one. Now the heroes are left to defeat the dragon using only one wish, a never-ending ice cream cone (with sprinkles) and a giant spicy sausage hat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf940465ee4740a280d4541c1e5c9723d</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When Oona, Olympia and Otis accidentally change the past, they undo every odd case the Odd Squad have ever solved.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb80390acc70da483b912354957c5ff16</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When the daycare gets taken over by evil gnomes, Duncan finds himself on the wrong side.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p73b36f368f3d8e85b29e113b3483f52e</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Matagi-Gozen.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p18f08c583cd116217fe064ae45e0a90a</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Amethio searches for answers about his grandfather?s history and goals.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbe0538f170c612c9e6ff23aa6203f2b5</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>The Keeper Myridell arrives on Earth to recruit a new generation of Scions: superpowered warriors who will have to save her world Gorm from the nefarious Lord Graven. The four kids she is guided towards are unlikely heroes, but when they are thrown into danger, their hidden strengths surprise everyone.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde1984f1bf7703cb535a3ef904f00513</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>The fallout from the regionals qualifiers starts to settle. Izzy tries to join Brawl, Olive considers moving on to cheer, and Kenzie comes back to visit an injured Pete.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6d508b9fadc35407ab71cdbbe49faf5b</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>This time on Shark Bites, Steve Backshall reveals the positively prehistoric sixgill shark. It has barely changed in 200 million years. Living in deep waters they are also incredibly hard to see, but Steve knows one spot off Canada's mainland where they occasionally come to shallower depths. Armed with a remote underwater camera and some smelly bait to lure it in, he tries to catch it on camera. These sharks earn their name from their sixth pair of gills and back in his Shark Lab Steve explains how this ancient adaptation may help them to survive in these extremes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd12488ec075a03924e14937ec433c86f</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>12 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Despite warnings, the sheep have gobbled up the birthday cake Bitzer has baked for the Farmer. Realising the kitchen cupboards are bare, Shaun and the flock must try and source ingredients for a new one from around the farm before Bitzer realises. The result is certainly a surprise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52cad13186b4964b457432c0b79519b7</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>It?s staff appreciation day at Danger HQ, and Squawk and Danger Mouse have two very different ideas on where to go. Penfold has the deciding vote, so the pair are busy trying to convince Penfold to pick their choice. With Penfold busy inventing tasks so they can earn his favour, no one has noticed that a jam spillage in the professor?s experiment has brought a sticky surprise to life - a super-sized jam monster which might just ruin all of their plans.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf73bd23f2fd4d12eb0d932efbad73ff0</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis gets into a fluffy mess when he runs into Von Screwtop's hadron collider with the professor's pet hamster, Galahad. To stop Dennis from completely changing into a hamster, the gang must sneak him into Wilbur's lab to use his reverse hadron collider and change him back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80dfb84ec4b3edb443b7d8d57691f72a</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Mouse brings home an old ice cream truck, the kids start their own smoothie business. However, the town's lovable ice cream man, Uncle Bub, isn't happy about the competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7bbf029937d9754bf6213941d447763a</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p000426b095d35698eac5fd64b7f76bde</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play pirates on a beached boat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6daa38c7457a858d5904930fb10cd1a</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a school of crabs that live in an underwater city.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc70e9e8acaa52af511ac5db7db9185bc</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>A new villain named Mr Unpredictable challenges the Mobile Unit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf082986578bc9aa61cd3b151fd3a0214</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>After denting Helsing's car, Que and Pierce rocket away from the consequences - all the way into space! Meanwhile, Charlie is left behind to face Helsing's big book on growing up.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2fe394cc20ebadb77ebecd7b4e8dc3be</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface accompanies the heroes on a quest and makes everything worse by angering a Big Ole Worm, putting all their lives in danger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d5fc7b8eb10082814afe11d0b3dc7db</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>The centre needs to be decorated for a wedding later today, but Danny?s more interested in his new invention ? which unfortunately blows through every toilet roll in the centre. When Mick distracts him mid-order, he accidentally requests 10,000 toilet rolls instead of 100 by express delivery, and they arrive in a whole mountain of boxes. Fearing Joy?s reaction, the boys decide to hide the loo rolls.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3ecc6e1702eeac871d1350e3e6a88646</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs go full monster-mode as they make spooky costumes, David Shrigley builds a giant praying mantis, and comedian Katherine Ryan draws a cute cat with big eyes and serious sass.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62f1b53b7b5ee67bf6a33909def92bd6</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy dismantles the toboggan built by the Lemmings in the log cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pece724e3753f4168887a4fb9f89c515a</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangsta Granny</title>
    <desc>Ben hates spending time with his boring granny while his parents are off ballroom dancing. Little does he know that his granny has a secret. Together they go on an adventure and become the best of friends. Magical, heartwarming comedy drama based on David Walliams's best-selling children's book.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb2fbb67c89487604ebc595d7674fdbfe</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy wants to watch TV, but the Lemmings prefer to have fun playing music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb81dcd41f9b8627f90482e8dfa7df1a</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Phantom is pranked by Nitro and Steel when he believes he?s in a new Gladiators video game, and the other Gladiators have fun pranking the audience behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p236851b7e42258c7058fe0b17e13f20f</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>There?s a brand new slide at school, and Pickle really wants to try it out. However, things get complicated when Pickle's mood magic causes Mia and Mr Ludcomb?s hair to grow uncontrollably.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fdd46f4b3717baf8071605b9e07bf96</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>X-Key celebrates a successful debut, and Hannah helps the remaining Astra members move on before time runs out on their dreams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42ad08de8c256a49d3e9567f9b936a0e</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Leah?s mum pressures her to treat Christina as a rival, testing their friendship and leading to a spicy football game. Hawx CEO Gordon tries to keep the club?s new sponsors happy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbd464185d89a8c9fc7e2d6d01d495bee</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>If you thought that dinosaurs were the most dangerous things in the Jurassic, think again! There was actually something way worse and far more deadly! In this episode, Steve goes on a mission to uncover what was deadlier than the dinosaurs - from massive monsoons and supersized sandstorms to ballistic bacteria and gory gas. And in an epic finale, Steve ends with a bang as he recreates the dinosaur-killing asteroid impact in an experiment that's second to none.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62b48bd539c0f56d10edf32cb1449d91</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Siblings Artie and Xenon both want the garden shed for themselves. The band try to settle the argument but soon start taking sides - can Sheriff Andy sort out the mess.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf587c08da2882e1deb0d3a00946cde9b</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum challenges Adam and Joe to a shocking game of Buzz Words. No-one really knows the rules, but who cares when the end results are this electrifying.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdfa663b54977678ae1bcc756d5d904d4</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>When Paani goes missing in the desert, Dashi calls for back-up before he runs out of water.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c864ce953cdec0ca0eeb4429c18eb77</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When Dad's Lizard Translator malfunctions, Cosima is carried away by a giant beetle! Cosima and Big Lizard realise they don't need to speak the same language to be best friends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3cf532313614dbb34458c3f5f17ecaa</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold are in a training simulation when one of DM's flying kicks damages the holodeck with catastrophic consequences. They wake to find they have been in a three-year dream, that they aren't secret agents and work in IT instead, and the Danger Agency has been a figment of their imaginations! Whilst Penfold and Squawk quickly settle into a life of menial office work, DM struggles to accept life as Dane G Mouse.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2be9862d6d9621fc75eda5af2c518c22</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Power-hungry tiny alien Empress Miasma takes control of Gnasher from the inside and uses him in her attempts to take over planet Earth. But when Miasma breaks out of Gnasher into Beanotown for real and Walter helps her grow in size, mayhem really takes hold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf248fb354599260a283147e9ab8857c1</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Witch, who was trapped in a Merhaven clam shell while pinching a pearl, grants Blossom a single wish to thank her for releasing her and saving her life. Blossom excitedly chooses a mermaid?s tail to improve her swimming. However, when the Merqueen complains that her pearl is missing, and the heroes have to quest to get it back, Blossom soon realises how tricky a mermaid?s tail can become on land.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5de1c5363e6236bc3067ca23bed0355e</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe tries to stay focused on regionals as Heath and Pete learn more about the Brawl. Anthony helps Adele with an audition, while Ariana feels overworked.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94b47b6e93043d3706a6667076d8ec1b</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Friede and Captain Pikachu team up to rescue a lost Bramblin from Pok?mon hunters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2dfa7969e5f724914412719b3fe71500</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Taffy</title>
    <desc>The Manor is running low on caviar. There is only one can of caviar left for tomorrow?s guests! Mrs Muchmore puts it in a safe, so Taffy comes up with a plan to foil the security system and get it out. However, Bentley decides he will not let that happen.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2ab4c8dd9353a2a1b8289fb833a68a61</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>The Dark Orca pirates unwittingly steal a treasure that could awaken a monumential.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69baa5191ea14f5b5e4a313c804122e8</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Mrs Creecher confiscates Dennis's rare sour sweetie, the Tongue Destroyer! Dennis is desperate to get the sweet back and takes his friends on an adventure to the school's Confiscatorium, a secret place where all confiscated goods are hidden, in the depths of Bash Street School.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59345ded18b2ac0ee7e8394444da7b49</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Has Danger Mouse finally met his match? An evil version of the hero escapes from a parallel dimension and joins forces with Baron Greenback.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa755ac1daa2a711230c9321971439bf6</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When a genie gives the Ninjas three wishes in exchange for payment of his order, they each wish to swap roles. However, they quickly realise that they preferred it just the way it was.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p37b6fcf9d25e1e7b2cc1c7808b3750a4</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Shaun comes across some newly hatched chicks who think he is their mum. He is determined to get rid of them, but how.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56d4d38a872d8e76290e5e8a055759dc</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a mysterious stone, endowing them with the mastery of Shaolin Kung Fu.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe7690cdab092fb9368ec4408ae3dd01a</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids are excited about attending spy camp! However, their trainer is a bit of a dud, and the siblings are disappointed not to learn anything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p098a1bcf2cc8f81eee03999d57daf28a</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom draws the short cheese straw and, rather than join her friends on a picnic, she has to take a magic wand to the recycling centre. Faced with a long queue and a rumbly tummy, Blossom decides that life is too short for recycling - with disastrous consequences. The heroes must skip their picnic and go on a quest to save the forest from the magical mess Blossom has gotten them into.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38db6a019d90d683a5c507a27c6477df</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Oona, Olympia and Otis accidentally change the past, undoing every case they've ever solved. Curriculum: 3D shapes, sound, color, shape, letter and number patterns, skip counting and operations patterns.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4f86e3f4329d9b78eb8234984058e343</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When Harold's warnings not to mess with the clock go ignored, chaos ensues at daycare.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1963f917715f925190b73fcdb6ebad46</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Hoaxer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67813c59d73568d0e83966c42c041a90</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>The Rising Volt Tacklers visit a mountain town on the way to Laqua.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p943787fc74890412590cb780038bba67</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>The new Scions begin their training by bonding with their four Gormiti, the spirit warriors who empower and guide them. However, Myridell surprises the Scions with a trip to Gorm, where the teens must pass their first test - defending the Temple of Gorm from Graven?s vicious Skavs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3c720ec31a4d049f2df422ba713218ba</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Pascale and Heath try to repair their relationship, but the arrival of Daisy throws a wrench in their plans. Ariana and Michelle team up to get A-Troupe back to regionals.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41507428a41462306d3e9385cb6dba56</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Challenges, celebrities, makes and adventures with the Blue Peter team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peba2a0af5e7df4149b49e473141bd9e5</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>13 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When the Farmer accidentally drills a hole in a waterpipe while putting up a new shelf, Bitzer frantically tries to stop the leak from soaking the living room and prevent the Farmer?s precious teapots from sliding off the shelf.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d0dd9504a3c0f105eb983ecfaee021d</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Whilst waiting to pick up Penfold?s vacationing cousin from New Zealand, Pinfold, at the airport, Danger Mouse receives orders to stop Burt Badboy?s spree of mass statue defacement. When Penfold pops to the toilet moments before Pinfold arrives, a distracted DM mistakenly jets off with Penfold?s cousin in tow, leaving Penfold stranded at the airport. As DM races off to stop Badboy, unwittingly bringing Pinfold along for the ride, Penfold commandeers various modes of transport hoping to catch up with them at Nelson?s Column, a pristine tempting target for Badboy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p48702a55b43dadd413c297d2e66b4418</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis discovers that Ralf the janitor is the legendary Prankmaster General and is told he could become his successor. Walter won't let this happen and challenges him to a prank battle to win Ralf's book of pranking - the infamous Prankypedia.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fdd220cddb6e710107b2fa25d30a3c1</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the family visits a farm, Cheese bonds with Delilah the cow over all things dairy. However, bringing her home to live with the family leads to all sorts of problems.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69a2672618969229d48692833eab3c29</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10be233921707490ad98c9c982680697</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>It seems an epic battle took place in the cabin, and Grizzy is missing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f4173f642ff3256664f7a4cf0a08f74</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy struggles to pick coconuts, but the Lemmings find a magic conch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe790119cb595cbdc802925b6696f6fe0</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad tube system has mysteriously been shut down.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbf486f72bdf74993ba1d00cf053ae101</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Things are getting very un-chill when Helsing's magic fridge gets stuck open and a gigantic snowstorm fills the house.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4fc585712bce3f52831f325d4e0b6978</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When a witch struggles to master her new wand, Twinkle decides to have a go, only to make her friends vanish. She must now go on a solo quest to find them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f70c51f662eb1e9f7b58d6b81511ec0</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Danny is convinced it's Joy?s birthday and ropes Mick and Naomi into his plan to create a surprise party. Mick?s in charge of decorations, Naomi?s in charge of the cake, Danny?s in charge of making sure Joy doesn?t suspect a thing. What can go wrong? Everything ? it?s Danny and Mick! Soon it?s time to spring the surprise ? will Joy be thrilled, annoyed or simply confused? Hint: It?s all three.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p402ee913a23187366f49f610c50c5fd0</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs serve up edible-looking 3D art, Nick Sharratt draws a supercool koala, and Harkiran Kalsi creates an amazing seaside sculpture.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10395f10329c32202cecdd6078c3aef3</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings organise a drone race throughout the cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99e36baca382c0aca274cf8a0c5587ce</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Famous Five</title>
    <desc>The Five are reunited by mysterious letters sent by an old friend at the spooky Prospect Hotel. Their mission? To solve a murder. The twist? It hasn?t happened yet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd34eeca203bbb427c6f5cfba25d0f1ee</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A rocket carries the cabin into space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c78219ad43711cd65fcc2202b9c6992</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle wants to become school ambassador. When she accidentally clones herself, she thinks the second Pickle will help her win the day. Unfortunately, they soon fall out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21c352b54ad359875557e19af629a4b8</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>Determined to keep her idol dreams alive, Hannah convinces Astra to take a risk with an unconventional plan. Meanwhile, the mounting pressure on X-Key leads to Supreme injuring himself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf8d83f9552eda961eff38aa90f0a9bf8</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Alex struggles to adjust to 11-a-side football. Coach Byrne and Finn spend a day together trying to have fun, while Simon takes charge of the team, with mixed results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59a03483e17bd97927efbf3b7ed02f0e</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>In this special episode, Steve Backshall looks back at the most awesome experiments over the series and chooses his highlights. He then uses them to build the ultimate deadly dino and create a crazy hybrid! From ginormous herbivores to fierce scavengers and hunters, which traits would you pick? The ferocious jaws of the T rex, the brutal weapons of the Stegosaurus, or the imposing size of the Diplodocus.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p93015c98b6de828106c89cd23f00c854</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>The band want to surprise Andy?s mum for her birthday, but she almost discovers their secret plans. Can they manage to keep everything under wraps in time for her big surprise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p95d63706b6623269aa0529869e746a79</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Adam and Joe face a Queasy Quiz with the most ridiculous questions and the gungiest consequences. Who will win and avoid a forfeit from The Wheel of Doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf9e7d42f763f986e102d6e96d47df02</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Pearl and Periwinkle discover a giant carp wreaking havoc on the Great Plains ecosystem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p22cc365a2e53cf48eaef848696b3db41</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad gets trapped in the shower when D.O.R.I.S. decides to visit the sea. Can Big Lizard and Cosima stop her before she does herself permanent damage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0d1d9aac82bd92a8d9088f22af3f5cb2</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse faces the Queen of Weevils in a fearful Halloween special.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ff6788cafa5778e2972fb67508deb9d</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Walter leaves his pampered pet croc, Crunchzilla, to fend for itself, Dennis and the gang help him to get in touch with its wild side. Walter does his best to prevent them, as he needs to keep the croc tame in the hope of getting back his father's limo keys, which Crunchzilla has accidentally swallowed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p36aa0026c9269ac2ab44ef95ae38f0c0</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are on a quest to find the vault containing the Amulet of Answers and protect it at all costs. But the Riddlemaster is back, and he manages to trap them in his castle, tricking Herbert into handing the Amulet of Answers over to him. Now he has all the answers to every question ever asked, and the heroes must find a way to outwit him - even though he knows what they are going to do next.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe25fa88d8b5c74373b8dbfb32088efca</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Jett tries to find her place in A-Troupe but is feeling left out. Ethan reminisces about his time in Paris, while Adele looks to a new opportunity abroad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pff1e14bffa83ddee79bbc84502624ffd</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Nidothing, Liko and Roy help a female Oinkologne win the attention of a popular male.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p366517bec3e1d346254acfdf8901f325</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Taffy</title>
    <desc>There is a burglar in the neighborhood stealing meat. And aside from the burglar's mask, he looks exactly like Bentley! Taffy tries to get rid of Bentley by passing him off as the Masked Mutt at Mrs Muchmore's ball.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa412db3dc796005eb5d379ccd2297922</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>The internet being down is the worst thing imaginable for Ant and Fontaine ? until Ant finds the sea monster responsible for this! Can he save both.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa03de887f1d0ab02c3cec112bbe390e1</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis must escape detention and Bash Street School to make the Beanotown Brawny Bean Race before Walter wins it! With the help of a note placed in his desk, he must sneak past Mrs Creecher and make a run for it - unless the mysterious note-giver stops him first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9167fe1b5f9cceb7d9f064d5b1a19a74</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold become reluctant parents when it appears the Baron has wiped his own memory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3e99b351aa4afb22052be158681eea93</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A Viking Captain summons the Ninjas to find him a steady beat to get his oarsmen moving in time and outrun his rival, Captain Bullyson.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc098a56c9c36f47530d4c941bded98ca</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Set on a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. The Farmer decides it is time to give the flock a shearing. But when they see his first attempt, Shaun and the others plan their escape.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p68de1b538d8d94d881faa9857bdf78fc</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A peace missionary panda tries to calm down Grizzy and the Lemmings during a fight.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef857e1433114a38274dcf38670f76c6</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The CEO buys Jocko?s old amusement arcade and vows to tear it down. However, Boy loves the arcade and challenges her to an epic video game battle with the fate of the arcade at stake.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc17e2966539e643fd8f82043cb18b7d7</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>It?s been ages since their last quest, and the heroes are losing their edge, so Mr Friendlyface invents a strange and terrible monster that he says is stomping through the forest causing havoc, and sends the heroes on a fake quest to get rid of it. Friendlyface soon comes to regret his trickery when, with the heroes out of the way, the goblins decide to take over the forest for their jam jamboree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd73f5a342e51bd6aa4e1226b5b388fb</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents try and stop baby Agent Orson from getting kicked off the squad. Curriculum: Using bar graphs, pie charts and Venn diagrams to sort, classify and analyse data.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb7cd8f4c94c7c40d3964df087a8b0d70</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Oona gets zapped into an alternate dimension. Curriculum: Place value, number operations.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf30c5fe866d4f3672488024755c03fed</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen believes he has turned Harold into a housefly using a wand he found in the sandpit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2bb9e11eb2a1237736b929c457ef7975</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Reflekta again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f9e19260bb307be583812c9dbe63579</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Following a long journey, the Rising Volt Tacklers finally reach Laqua.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf896e931f045c1a61db1bc8914edea28</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Carter, Glen, Zane, and Skye must hide their secret identities from everyone. They are struggling with teamwork, when hot-headed Gormian Bors tries to prove the Scions don?t have what it takes. The Scions finally unite against him but, in so doing, they attract the attention of Graven.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p16497753ab657a2216c622950836aa27</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Daisy?s return makes things more difficult for Heath. Eldon and Michelle consider parting ways as an injured Pete feels left out of the Brawl.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6b5147c4642565487a47814ae7a8a27</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Challenges, celebrities, makes and adventures with the Blue Peter team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc735eec2b4419f24733980858c0b519e</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun tricks Bitzer into thinking he is unwell so that he can stay in the barn playing video games all day. However, before long, the other sheep are also pulling sickies, and Bitzer is starting to get suspicious. The threat of nasty medicine has everyone out of bed in a flash.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p859bcc0ba6d00ac73d3e8310a33597fe</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Penfold?s countless hours spent playing Giraffe Warriors pay off when he gets the highest score of all time. Before he can celebrate and convince Danger Mouse that a video game win is a real life win, the pair are whisked off to the planet which inspired the game, where Penfold is asked to defend it from an alien invasion! With DM sidelined Penfold must take up the mantle of the last giraffe warrior, a hero destined to save the planet from peril.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35cdb4911478918f91bc396dfce97610</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Mayor Wilbur passes a law to increase healthy eating in Beanotown, replacing all foods with peas...of the mushy variety! The gang must avoid the people of Beanotown who are rapidly turning into Zompeas after eating the green mush. Dennis uses the only ordinary peas in town to sabotage Wilbur's mush-making factory and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41d58d1465e51eb4de1792f354b29a85</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy is ecstatic to go on a tour of the bobbleheads factory, but the rest of the kids are bored and cross because the brochure lied. So they secretly make a one-of-a-kind bobblehead just for Boy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p44f8a7d0d8aaa45c1497e17e869fdbd3</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc2bac1c6fa7306ba7023b70176aa056c</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy wants to watch TV, but the Lemmings prefer to have fun playing music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb81dcd41f9b8627f90482e8dfa7df1a</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A rocket carries the cabin into space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c78219ad43711cd65fcc2202b9c6992</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit reports to the New York City Odd Squad to help with a big problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31393a6794de6f2a223001931d92464f</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Helsing's new floating security orb goes from BFF to frenemy when it ejects everyone onto the lawn and takes over Helsing's house! The gang must find a way in to give it the hard reboot it deserves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe5b06a4040ad9140beb3e833422e307f</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes find treasure as they bid to save Merhaven from an angry seaweed. Blossom is delighted with her bath bomb treasure, but rather than use it, she insists on bringing it along on the watery quest to save it for a special occasion. But as the angry seaweed nears Merhaven, Blossom realises she must finally sacrifice her treasure to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4cabd4631ea30373511762999c2b1fe4</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Naomi has asked for a raise, Joy?s advised her to take some time off to think about it, which is why Danny and Mick are in charge of the cafe. They?ve just about got the hang of it when a new automated smoothie maker arrives. The machine is supposed to make life easier, but that?s not how Danny and Mick see it. Soon smoothies are flying, and everyone is left with egg on their face. And strawberry. And a bit of banana?.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b4c9cf8f021ccd65862af8d996b9857</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs get noisy with homemade instruments, Aowen Jin paints UV art that glows, and Emily Steel - aka Gladiator Dynamite - flexes her muscles by drawing a weightlifting alpaca.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d00237a732b167e672df30111b12313</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings build an airborne craft made of Chinese umbrellas to steal the TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p20ddcb21d4ba305bb4c6980243857e09</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Great Barrier Reef, the world's largest structure of living organisms at 1,400 miles long, is home to the most diverse population of undersea life on the planet, and it's under attack! In an epic story torn from the headlines, the Octonauts embark on their largest, most complex rescue mission ever - saving the Great Barrier Reef and all the creatures that live there from an invasion of coral-hungry crown-of-thorns starfish. The Octonauts meet a tiny coral polyp looking to find a home on the very same reef where the Octonauts are deploying their new medical base, the Gup-W, and the Gup-P, a specialised first responder emergency vehicle. To save the reef and their new polyp friend, the Octonauts must combine forces with a diverse crew of zapping, splatting and claw-snapping reef creatures to fend off the spiky, coral-munching starfish.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c0dc458f6e97f617eb92df8b75313fa</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Angel Pavement</title>
    <desc>A tale from Quentin Blake's Box of Treasures. Corky and Loopy are two ordinary girls who happen to also be secret angels! With the aid of a magic pencil that can draw in the air, they go on 'angel patrol;, amazing people in their town with beautiful art and rescuing the odd animal. When they meet street artist Sid, they decide to help him take part in a local drawing competition by lending him the special pencil. Sid creates incredible drawings in the sky and brings joy and wonder to all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8427157182cecb41fc8f48d23a6b9123</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Apollo prank Dynamite, turning her into a singing banana! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99a45e9399b5fa5991e3b3eb060bfd42</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Can underdog Cranmede take on the mighty reigning champions Gorsforth at the Interschool Country Dance Championships? And can Tam overcome her dance demons in time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1485a447b6247106aa11cbbdb4498d5d</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>With Astra suspended, Hannah makes the impossible decision to leave. Can her friends convince her to stay.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc3693098adcc48114cd1a677f363492</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Skilful trialist Jay unsettles the other Hawx players and challenges Alex?s authority. Coach Byrne makes a difficult decision, and someone?s going to get cut? But who.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac68d2bda1346c66ea1477637fdfb6a2</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Mission Shark</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall is on a mission to create a new generation of shark saviours, but first he needs to find his team. In this episode, Steve takes 12 young UK hopefuls to boot camp with the challenge of choosing just six from the group. To earn their ticket to swim with sharks in a designated Shark Sanctuary in the Bahamas, the 12 have to complete a series of challenges, including swimming, a clifftop leap into water and a demanding abseil. With a weekend of training completed, who will Steve pick to be in his team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc258d9fd2ae84df2b435fa201e01761a</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Young Ben wants to win the Oddpool sandcastle competition. The band head to the beach, and Rio meets a sea genie who gives everyone a big surprise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7f84fa8da7522537bc61f7822db88abf</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Little bro Callum sends Adam and Joe to the seaside to see who can build the greatest sandcastle in a bid to avoid the wheel of doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa1e581c0b2edb0a8f4e62471b0976dfb</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>When birds cause trouble aboard the Octoray, Tweak uses her Octowatch to help with repairs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p36119280da16de9ca6a67955e506c3b9</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Finding an earth probe makes Dad homesick. When Big Lizard accidentally destroys it, Cosima knows what to do. She recreates the contents - Proxima-style.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe44fe6c98a91e76a5ce34a8afbff4b5</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Danger agents go undercover disguised as a family to find out why the world?s villains are heading to one holiday camp, Sidneyland. When Baron Greenback shows up, the team are convinced he?s up to no good, but can?t find any evidence of wrongdoing. When Penfold enters Squawk and DM in a dance competition they discover the prize is the fabled Helmet of Power, an ultimate invention bent on destruction.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b5ce7408b56f7960eb3b2cde7d508f8</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A snake bite causes Grizzly Griller to forget all his survival know-how, so it's down to his greatest fan Dennis to help him re-learn his survival skills and help them all make it safely back to Beanotown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d701f1ef35c0ede4ea972cfc0c218a6</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes discover that their latest quest - delivering 30 birthday balloons to Mr Friendlyface?s cousin - isn?t as easy as they expected.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10c7fd9b3be98e5feec3cbead7efdc69</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>As Adele says goodbye to The Next Step, she tries to mend fences with Olive. Things get complicated between Heath and Pascale as Anthony deals with Adele leaving.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12094601243ee9d32365dcaf717213be</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Fuecoco does its best to quell a group of angry wild Pok?mon with song and dance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p68fd577f4044d5539cdffb1037e8155c</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Taffy</title>
    <desc>Mrs Muchmore is chosen to represent April in the country club?s calendar. Fuffernin will be there in a few hours to take the best picture possible, and everyone has to be dressed in green, from bow to toe.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfb9308b349661db62565e480e8890f10</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Trying to rescue Jess Gorman in an underwater cave proves dangerous for Ant and Fontaine until a manatee comes to their aid. But is it too late.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb62124f1023aacdda64a83825676306e</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis's ultimate hero, Grizzly Griller, plans on trekking to the source of the River Beano, broadcasting the treacherous path on live TV. Dennis introduces him to his pet hamster Galahad - only to discover they are his biggest fear! Grizzly is so afraid that Dennis must disguise himself as his hero and go in his place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8740f186fd542531c6393457aada6f7e</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Count Duckula is back, and he is determined to take over the world, one terrible TV show at a time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p78f9f0a97c4d271042d27c59788eb11c</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Two sisters arguing over tidying up their house end up with a bigger problem when the Ninjas deliver two cleaning robots from the future who are planning a robotic rebellion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7db05f3ffc7255bc464cfe0eb0754b3c</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Set on a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. Shaun finds a camera which some ramblers have dropped and sets about taking snapshots of the flock. Bitzer is soon on the trail of the missing camera.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbfdf487e61bc85086eaec74349686a06</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings create a shadow puppet show where seven papercut lemmings confront a bear.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc86af08c9c02f6ba215273b5a0f148b3</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>K-Jam is moving into the neighbourhood and staying with the family for a while. However, Girl gets insecure and thinks that her awesome best friend is trying to take her place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbace25267391c527963e66f359240ab</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia discovers a secret about her partner. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs, data analysis and collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p487861630ae6473048dde909b125dabf</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia discovers a secret about her partner. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs, data analysis and collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p200888983017e30e8e27c57e31798c5b</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan sees an opportunity for a break from daycare when an angry skunk hunts down Chef.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p369231ecc447b57e864ac5d90b077f18</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face a revolutionary enemy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe794b82c94b5da3fc969d1d75fc5d92</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>The Rising Volt Tacklers and the Explorers battle over the fate of Laqua.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5cb0995236fa925e4cab08fc13f2b545</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Graven dispatches two of his generals to Earth to claim the Shard of the Soul of Gorm, forcing the Scions to accelerate their training and protect the artifact. However, with the Scions mired in personal problems, the Gormiti must help them discover their inner strengths on, and off, the battlefield.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f86d004a612bbcbb6bcf03d783df57e</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupers begin to switch over to Team Brawl, but when Olive and Eldon figure out a way back into regionals, Anthony and Ethan have their loyalties tested.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdfbe47178e58aaec452002ff1f8d03b8</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Does Joel have what it takes to pass the Royal Marines Commando Endurance course?! Squeezing through tunnels and getting soaked in water obstacles, followed by a gruelling run back to base, all against the clock.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3b4138df05292645a07b18a2fa96ced</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When a meteor shower is forecast to pass over Mossy Bottom, Bitzer really wants to see the shooting stars. However, he keeps getting distracted by the flock?s curiosity and the Farmer?s late-night picnic.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paed19956be0ae4e13e120b77e3af55ba</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold are introduced to Squawk?s latest invention ? a warp drive device that will transport HQ anywhere in the universe at a moment?s notice. Squawk?s demonstration seems to go without a hitch - that is until the gang notice an exact duplicate of the HQ across the road, with identical duplicates of the Danger Team inside. When the duplicate Big Head is activated and starts causing mayhem the two DMs join forces to try and stop her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf0691a04cfdc488c1f2a7e7040389e29</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Walter attempts to ruin The Dinmakers' chance of reaching fame. He will stop at nothing - even wearing a frock and pretending to be a fan called Wanda who loves Dennis in order to break up the band.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p185b9baa4b788b368de5e75e2d93003b</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>On a dark and stormy night, the kids tell a scary story about local legend Big Bad Ben! Mouse says he doesn't exist, but when a dark figure arrives at the house, they all believe it's Big Bad Ben - even Mouse! Who is this stranger in the storm? Can they work together to protect themselves? And, hang on, didn?t Cheese order pizza.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p79c9e0907c61ad532b85e1c481150b77</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf7bf21699d68cd6b40a859dbc3c2fa34</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>It's time for the racket game, where big scores mean big prizes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb4876fa452c0f93c5471f450963b20c9</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings adopt a cute insect that eats wood. And what's made of wood? The cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pff351cedb37a51b39f803f5886026822</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>An agent-in-training visits the Mobile Unit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p79d20441d3969ddc950988a6b3ed567c</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Trying to train Snorp is a complete catastrophe for the gang, leaving Charlie and Que 'feline' frustrated. As word spreads that he may become an 'outside pet', Snorp's enemies are coming for him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10c08a5cb66c677da06ea14a8b448809</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes go on a quest to get Hoofius?s Toby Jug back from the depths of the Riddling Ruins and are faced with a series of puzzles and traps to solve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67fad6fb2cc188991a416f8965659da7</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>All the Pottsfield Leisure Centre staff are raising money for Comic Relief. Danny and Lance, as always, turn it into a competition to see which of them can raise the most money! But between Danny?s disastrously defective charity calendar, and Mick?s frankly frightening fancy dress, the brothers only succeed in driving the totaliser lower than when they started. It?s going to take everybody putting aside their rivalries and working together as a team to turn this situation around. That, and a lot of soggy sponges.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6558aa7ce6fe7f9bca9a21e48a31ec28</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>08:55AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs set sail with homemade pirate ships, Sophie Ryder sculpts a huge Minotaur, and Harry Hill draws himself being chased by a very big, very blue cat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p950470bcf5000eb12035d467de5b8256</image>
    <start>08:55AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The mood of a raccoon becomes contagious to all those around him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7a5dd8a643af87b46b15270f98dd64c9</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: XY</title>
    <desc>A power unbound, a battle of legends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p322713452f73834fcb5c8c0ed070b808</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Phantom prank Fire at a kids' birthday party! The rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3eb6afc7027c8bfed2f443d8a7e7d70e</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>It?s Superhero Day, but not everyone chooses to embrace their unique superpower. Luca turns super villain, Claire shuns her superfan and Mr Malone makes a super-awkward gaff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6ca084bd2034a10047f1308f2941fd49</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>X-Key are gearing up for their TV appearance, unaware of the traitor in their midst, and, after a shocking revelation, Astra must do everything they can to pull off the impossible.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0ec84c76f3c30275a965add2f7f1b6ae</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Strange goings-on at Hawx Academy make the players worry the place is haunted. Jay struggles to settle in, while Alex is taunted by Hawx rivals Foxborough.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc4dac4e4d2b9c6a5707aa5ed62250768</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Mission Shark</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall has chosen his UK team of six to travel with him to Bimini in the Bahamas, where they learn how to scuba dive and become the next generation of shark saviours. The mission begins as soon as they land, and they have just two weeks to complete four training dives, but first it?s time to meet four local Bahamian children who are also joining Steve?s team. On board the dive boat, they encounter their first shark species ? the Caribbean reef shark ? a deadly predator engineered for hunting underwater. Then it?s off to the dive location to start the first series of tests. Some of the team take to diving with ease and soon pass the preliminary stage of their training. For others, it is a much harder challenge, with the tasks proving too much at their first attempt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4a212c329026bccbe3710eb188b9fae6</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>TV Stars Sam and Mark prank the Odd Socks, and there is an even bigger surprise when the lads start giving out awards for the best bits from the series - who will be the winners.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0afc03afb5404fcb89a061ba7b5bfa0c</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Online greeter extraordinaire Troy Hawke helps Callum challenge Adam and Joe to be the most complimentary to passers-by.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/ped8c9f4d688bddfc27d20814bdbcea8d</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>When Kwazii and Calico Jack get stranded on an island, the Octonauts must search for them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p711b28f057f24edc9450ca884c6ba142</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>It's been one year since Cosima crash landed on Proxima, but no-one else has remembered this anniversary! Can a perfect picnic jolt their memories.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52ef4f7288ee99b772ad68e542eb05a9</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When a sudden urge to fly the Mark IV hits, Penfold leads a confused Danger Mouse to a farm, from which he claims to feel an unexplained magnetic pull. An entranced Penfold is met by a shadowy figure - Granny Penfold! Penfold recounts his childhood years on Granny?s farm, where he was trained in the ancient martial art of Farm Fu; a farming based martial art. Granny needs Penfold?s help to retrieve the sacred Fung Farm Book of Farm Fu, which has fallen into the hands of her enemies, causing farm animals to turn evil and rise up against their owners.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5bc9fb86a9c9d89de3a6896036c3a7d9</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang train Bertie in the art of standing up to people so he can rebel against Walter's bossiness - but they train him too well and he becomes a dangerous rebel without a clue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ee81567708d80e99b9f35e4a420add2</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Whilst on a quest to return the Icicle of Destiny, Trevor topples into a cavern of tiny mushrooms who treat him like a king.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6587ed590db6ffbdbc38b906cd7ccb3a</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>An overprotective Heath accuses Grace of sabotage, while Grace and Jonah make a bet to make it on to A-Troupe. Meanwhile, Izzy grapples with keeping Anthony?s secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p98b58fbdb69531c7dbfb68abe1998543</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko, Mollie and their Pok?mon set out to save a Tandemaus pair separated by a storm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p941d680c0b29788ee2b02f98f587c4cd</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Taffy</title>
    <desc>Every time Bentley steals Taffy?s bow, Taffy seems to find another one from nowhere. Bentley tries to find the source of his supply so that he can destroy it and finally expose Taffy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc15dd1ec0725169209f3264096c5a87c</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>The Aronnax and Alpheus?s sub are trapped within a giant jellyfish! They?ve been eaten and the jellyfish won?t let food out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p916c85101eb07165f67a52271108d625</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface steals Professor Von Screwtop's Pastry-based Intelligent Espionage unit (PIE) after forming a strong bond with the pie-shaped robot. Pieface is dismayed when Walter steals it from him to protect his dad from the embarrassing footage the PIE's memory chip holds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4db578615381ab592eeaeea97d895804</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's plan to hold a surprise party for Professor Squawkencluck is undone when the Baron releases killer birthday presents into the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p142b27e7bb29436619c5a233aa8b58ec</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A fairy-tale princess being pestered by an annoying prince orders a new dragon from the Ninjas, who return with the most ferocious monster of them all - a T-Rex.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70302567796da86615c59a39a8a223b9</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. A circus sets up in a nearby field, and a spellbound Timmy wanders off to investigate. Can Shaun rescue him before the farmer notices he's gone.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a12f4a74e3e01355e1a8d436e474630</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy relaxes in the massage chair, but the electricity supply stops in the log cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8b95b3a4287e28006124b3827736c563</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the kids think that Mom may be pregnant, they set out to prove they will be great babysitters. Along the way, they learn that it's much harder to do it alone than it is together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb5bb5a7b40090762af8e629842f8f3e8</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are excited to visit Whizzpop?s Pop-Up Bakery and taste his magical cakes, but they are shocked to find that the protein bars have shouty raisins in them, the custard tarts are rock hard, and the floating sponges keep floating away! Trevor quests to solve the mystery, but having accidentally fallen into Whizzpop?s invisibility flour, how on earth will he get everyone?s attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe2faf77b85cf0b2852c9a1177edf9ab5</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf326fb9ddf1e4b8189998894cdaba294</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9219a4ed6990cdd4d9ec30d5d0a40f34</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Challenges, celebrities, makes and adventures with the Blue Peter team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4762ad46eff5636ad504a235887f92a3</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir unknowingly face Queen Mayor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ddd267d48b17366fafe68beb1bbb05b</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>After 100 years, the secrets of Laqua finally come to light.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0360f783a139b692684e52faf1554e8</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Just as the Scions start coming into their own, harnessing their potential as a team, all their hard-won progress comes to a halt when they attempt the ultimate Scion ability: Fusion. The unexpected outcome endangers both Carter and Myridell while giving Graven another strategic advantage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80370a7258c8348a620257f43a263566</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:20PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Kenzie helps Pete make a difficult decision. The Brawl?s love theme gets in the way of Heath and Daisy fixing their friendship, and Michelle turns to Eldon for Brawl advice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p78694b47d4acdfcbe0bbffab1b09836a</image>
    <start>06:20PM</start>
    <finish>06:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: Legend of the Boneknapper Dragon</title>
    <desc>Animated short. When Gobber's house burns down, the old Viking is convinced that his nemesis, the legendary Boneknapper dragon, is responsible. Bent on revenge, Gobber resolves to hunt it down once and for all, despite the fact that no one believes the dragon exists. Regardless, Hiccup and the gang decide to accompany him for his own good. On the sea voyage, Gobber tells the story of his rivalry with the beast, which gets sillier with each episode. When the gang find themselves shipwrecked on the suspected island of the beast, they finally learn the truth about the dragon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc74aefee6d25de383371feb7631f2a1</image>
    <start>06:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
