<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Panama is home to one of the largest and most impressive birds of prey in the world - the harpy eagle. But to track it down, Steve and the crew have to trek into a remote part of the Darien jungle. Along the way Steve chases a deadly racer snake downriver, and even faces his fears to handle some giant bullet ants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p279360d8f87d66e5da05f1614398370e</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 7-9 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about using musical structures, form and the blues.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb63cfd17186890401769413df2722c73</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch! Do Try This at Home</title>
    <desc>A camera pill shows Dr Chris?s digestive system at work squidging food, and the doctors show how to make your own fake stomach.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p15a57cfa9332c57da941fc276c3c1a5d</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>We find out what would happen if you shrank the earth. You could jump higher and move faster, but you would end up with altitude sickness even at sea level.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8c61af5c9976090668c55895b9e9d3cd</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Flo and Chloe make a new pen pal and invite her to school for a tour and a big surprise. This episode was filmed in 2021 before the death of HM the Queen.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4d8533017f3b15f4317f277e5e113df1</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>Cam, Tyler and Aaron explore the wonders of the wetlands and meet the wildlife heroes working hard to help protect its animal inhabitants. It?s an early start for Tyler as he heads to Devon hoping to bump into a beaver and discover why this furry eco engineer is having a huge impact on the land and its wildlife. Cam is on the outskirts of Manchester to lend a hand restoring a wetland habitat that is helping combat climate change, all thanks to a super-plant called sphagnum moss. On the Isle of Mull, the OZT brothers go head-to-head as they look to spot an otter. They find out how this wetland wonder is making a big comeback - but whose animal tracking skills will win the day? Back at OZT HQ, a mini murmuration of starlings is flying around, and Aaron is ready with some starling statistics, but he has the crowd guessing when it comes to playing Fact or Fake. Cam reveals an incredible scene from Sir David Attenborough?s Wild Isles and gives Tyler a real soaking as he demonstrates how they might film similar shots using a super slo-mo camera. And the brothers find out what has been going wild near you, in the OZT Gallery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6de71fcbc6af07329b3515a8342913e5</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Strap in tight as we see some ludicrously good leaping and fearless free-falling.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7b520f28f68bb72a86219acc64e4b753</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Alex Scott joins Rattus for a sport-themed special. Mary Queen of Scots goes grief-golfing, the H2 Freestylers take on a whole village, and sports-mad Henry VIII sings Get Sweaty.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c51af73f227c5f0d489a2caccb3374f</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:25AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Gregor from Aberdeenshire needs somewhere to practise, store and maintain his bagpipes. A keen player and member of a local pipe band, Gregor one day dreams of becoming a professional. However, his passion requires lots of practice and it?s just too loud for the rest of the family.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb84025645ef5490150e19a92fd2fea52</image>
    <start>11:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>With less an hour to go, the band and students launch into action to put on the best show possible to save the school. Little do they know that some rock star magic might help..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfb528bc9cfddff10c089d5cc48a67fca</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>At the Go Jet Academy, the Go Jetters are about to watch one of nature's most spectacular events - a solar eclipse. They watch in amazement through their pinhole projectors as the moon moves between the Earth and the sun and its shadow throws them into darkness. As the moon moves past the sun, things become light again, but all of a sudden they are thrown into darkness once more. But this time it's not the moon passing in front of the sun, it's a giant moustache! Grandmaster Glitch has made a giant solar panel shaped like a moustache to power his Grimbots. To fix this giant glitch there's only one thing for it - the Go Jetters need to head into space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc241e63e42cb7b89fe6a97f4bf5086a6</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Whilst Dad searches for a faulty wire, Cosima and Big Lizard play tag in the ship and accidentally break Big Lizard's bath bed! Where will he sleep now? And where's that pesky wire.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27b20bb3866865593fa592da4ecbf022</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Join Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers, The Octonauts, for more deep sea adventures. The Octonauts roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. Whether it's a perilous voyage to the bottom of the sea or the piratey pursuit of a giant squid, the Octonauts leap into action and always prove that eight heads are better than one. While exploring a dark and spooky cave, the Octonauts discover the fossil of a powerful, prehistoric fish... but it may be more than just a fossil.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa863db2afa889857eca8006005a6528f</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse and Penfold are sent on a rescue mission to a mysterious island, Danger Mouse's over-competitiveness borders on criminal.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94611482810f95a6584eec90dad349c5</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>Waffle isn?t allowed at school, so he?s being looked after by Connie, the Brooklyn-Bell?s neighbour, at her house. Connie has dressed as a dog and made a huge, doggy maze game from cushions and suitcases for her dog, Jelly, to race through with Waffle. Waffle asks for one more race through the maze at home but Jess explains that the time for noisy play is over and offers him a quiet cuddle instead. After dinner, Evie tells Jess she?s been given her first reading book at school and gets the book out of her school bag to show her Mum. Waffle sits next to Evie and watches her read. When he starts to say words from the book out loud, Evie wonders if he?s reading, but Jess and Simon refuse to believe it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p386d5267968f24dff4f8aa4f03eb7280</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>In the perilous plant aisle, Supertato and Evil Pea team up to find treasure as they have half a map each, but she tricks him and steals the map to find the treasure for herself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paa18a711a529a0126d45530dd61de0c2</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Convinced that Mrs Creecher is secretly a master of Blamjitsu, JJ persuades the gang to help trick her into revealing her blam credentials.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p631f5a239e4e0ec4323d1cb7272bc565</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is particularly tetchy this morning. He is packing for a skiing trip, but a dragon has pinched his golden fleece, and he urgently needs the heroes to quest it back ? how else will he stay warm and cosy on the slopes? However, when the heroes accidentally agree to let his niece Trixie tag along with them, they fear that her clumsiness and lack of hero skills will ruin everything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c3ff87984db3abc93407af293a6fe99</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A brave little girl orders a shield to protect her from a monster and sets off with the Ninjas, her scaredy-cat dad, a goblin, a troll and a dragon to find her missing aunt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p684f43d0b585056e21b15b866ae9630a</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Sparks fly when Tee recruits Jody to help her and Carmen win a street dance competition. But who's more out of their depth, Carmen or Jody.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf305b316b73159aad98d6b7faaae86f7</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A look at how World War II played out on the home front, featuring Churchill's secret loo, the heroic 'ATA Girls' and German spies being caught out by their delicious sausages.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34479d246837eb45065d27a320a85e07</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketch show. A Victorian inspector checks that school is suitably cruel, HHTV News reports live from the Great Plague, and Thumbelina drowns unpleasantly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p71a7989ead2c77a2da5a87e65e68b456</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang can?t wait for their all-day PE training day with Grizzly Griller and are baffled when their idol makes them learn a range of boring non-sports that only Walter excels at.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13014ffef7cef77e45cb02cd6a8721d2</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Having put the Danger Babies through their adorable paces, Professor Squawkencluck leaves it to Danger Mouse to settle them down with a nice soothing story. Unfortunately telling stories to children isn't one of Danger Mouse's strong points, and he ends up scaring his captive audience with a tale that reimagines him as an evil villain. Squawk returns to find Danger Mouse bound and gagged and that the Danger Babies have made off with the Danger Car and are on their way to Arkwirght Asylum to free the 'heroes' from Danger Mouse's topsy-turvy story.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8674b3e1d60465dd8263514a763f9227</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>To win the annual Golden Wand contest, Merlina summons the Ninjas to find her an amazing magic trick to impress the judges. But the final winner takes everyone by surprise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p24416808631b7fb8497c6fb022cb8ebe</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find an ultra-modern glowing cabin they can use for their party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb652f231f7d9980cc9d08668c1128c88</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Girl decides to write her school project about Cat as she is so mysterious and it would nice to know more about her. The gang decides to help, and soon everyone is following Cat from a distance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c294ff4f4dfcf66ec93fa2af4aea959</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Witch, who was trapped in a Merhaven clam shell while pinching a pearl, grants Blossom a single wish to thank her for releasing her and saving her life. Blossom excitedly chooses a mermaid?s tail to improve her swimming. However, when the Merqueen complains that her pearl is missing, and the heroes have to quest to get it back, Blossom soon realises how tricky a mermaid?s tail can become on land.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5de1c5363e6236bc3067ca23bed0355e</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Agents Opal and Omar uncover the location of a legendary odd artifact.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde5af9c73d0f8b081215c96f51015b55</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings use a frog with hypnotising powers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbd74eae5287515b461c9282bcc4d8e8</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>We have an exciting announcement ahead of the new series of Walking with Dinosaurs. Abby discovers dino footprints on the Isle of Skye, and the team come face-to-face with a walking T-rex in the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2e05b41d1ed7298c1d31fa894b13545d</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef tries to trick the kids into making his mother gifts after he forgets Mother's Day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb83be820d725d3dca24249aa7e59fa8</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: Gift of the Night Fury</title>
    <desc>Festive animated short featuring characters from How to Train Your Dragon. Hiccup and his friends are preparing for Snoggletog, the Viking equivalent of Christmas, when all of the dragons suddenly fly away and leave Berk. All, that is, except for Toothless, who cannot fly unaided. Hiccup has a solution for Toothless, but will the dragons return to Berk? Featuring the voices of Jay Baruchel, Gerard Butler and America Ferrera.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1a50b1b524f797da08ef2e7f67ef9476</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A weird and wonderful look at how gravity, magnetism and friction impact everything. With Fred Sirieix.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94fd45c10fe71cfd50c37b15a03b378a</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. Michelle decides to change the line positions, but Emily and Stephanie are not happy about it. Emily confesses a secret to Eldon that brings them a little closer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa22439632e1e3aa19a89d4961d676dbb</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The thrill-seeking eggs take up bungee jumping, the potato racers whizz around, and Mr Strawberry serenades Mrs Strawberry. Fearless Pete Parsnip comes face to face with a terrifying hairy spider, and Slippery Nana comes a cropper impressing the judges in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9af765987c32160992a5512af85bce81</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
