<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface?s hat has been stolen by a Big Ole Worm, and the heroes must quest to get it back. As they trail the worm through the Prickly Desert, Trevor accidentally spikes himself all over on a cactus. But all is not lost ? now that he is covered in sharp spikes, Trevor realises that he has a unique superpower, and when the time comes to confront the Big Ole Worm, it?s Spiky Trevor to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d893098488de351f2861251077cc5bc</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Taffy</title>
    <desc>Bentley and Taffy are off on their holidays! Forsythe has promised Mrs Muchmore that they will leave at exactly noon and definitely won?t be late. Bentley thinks this is the perfect time to take Taffy for a walk in the garden?s maze.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03df078deefbcb7df8f5c12b55878419</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>When Blink frames Mansour, the team run a reverse heist to clear his name.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa4d4d4908f9bfe9f729f89183152f859</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>When Mansour loses Sara?s pet rabbit, Blink causes havoc with lookalike robot rabbits.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4188cceb795ded19b383d5f480c083d2</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>The two teams go to war, firing cabbages from cannons at each other from their respective pirate ships. The first team to sink the other will be the winner, but someone takes a very personal interest in one specific target.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbba7214d4edf8d4ddc6ad9ddc13a5ddd</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Scroll</title>
    <desc>Fate brings five animals and their unique kung fu styles together to make the perfect team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p50cf34d9856a6c54a114461d7387c9b8</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
