<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The town has always revered the Smith twins' great-great-grandpa as a local hero. However, when the gang exposes him as a fraud, they need to find a way to cheer the twins up.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pad41075364923fdfbae55ade4bf74338</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2e578706eaed12b63b3989a583bdec96</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings are throwing a big birthday party, but Grizzy is not in the mood.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3db4fa9889189f0cc9220e9804405d6</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings decide to play hide-and-seek in the Savannah.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b103f5c6909d7e3276e3613f4e5eee3</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Ms O tells Olympia and Otis a story about a famous villain duo. Curriculum: Adding, subtracting and multiplying by zero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf57f18551a75efc65bc912f7566e48af</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>To avoid Herbert?s surprise visits via his tunnels in the Big Birch, the other heroes take any quest and must deal with an angry plant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1712e7d54bc565d7f40c59dd3788f999</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve and the crew have almost come to the end of their journey to find the Deadly 60. They are in Peru, searching for elusive giant river otters. Steve has a chance encounter with the largest reptile in South America, and nothing prepares him for the animal that takes the last place on the Deadly 60 list.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paa176bb1dbd3e8f9d6873537dfdc3892</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 7-9 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about designing and creating concertina books, and how to add a surprise to one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21c43dc3bb198660acfe030170df9764</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ricky Wilson's Art Jam</title>
    <desc>Online sensation and Olympic medal winner Nile Wilson visits the Art Jam studio to show Ricky three items that mean the world to him - a black and white painting of Nile in action, a Commonwealth Games gold medal and some precious fan art containing an inspiring quote. While chatting to Ricky, Nile shares amazing stories about how he got into gymnastics, his elite career, the 100 medals he has won, his love of making online videos and how he stays positive during tough times.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pca860f7c5b34c50cc85c52fb2e95d566</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Gladiator Dynamite is back to make sure things don?t get too explosive when Dr Dan and Dr Raph get into a Body Battle in a planktastic challenge to test their core muscles. On the basketball court, we meet Joel Henry, our Brilliant Bodies slam-dunk champion, to find out how he jumps so much higher than Dr Chris. It?s game on in the lab when Dr Xand becomes Saliva Man and Dr Chris tries everything he knows to overcome his superpowers as the doctors show us what spit is for. In an amazing Bodytricks, six kids surprise themselves by lifting Dr Ronx off a chair using only two fingers! And in the emergency department in Edinburgh, we follow the treatment of Niamh, who has broken her elbow doing a back handspring at gymnastics, and Adhya, who took a whack on the thumb during a hockey match. Ouch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p08db54266af2514592094cbe1c2c13cd</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Britain's Best Young Artist</title>
    <desc>Vick and Ricky look back on their favourite moments from the series, looking at the best bits of art, tips and inspiration days. And there is an exclusive chat with the winner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd8ddfefa93abdf2fd7d18616915adfe0</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Strap in for some records that will send you head over heels and puzzle-solving that is turned literally on its head.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6781f005ba701e57c0438ec22671336b</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>Ricky can be a joker, but his art is no joke. He shows how to draw Dennis from Dennis and Gnasher Unleashed, splats a giant picture with cream pies, and the Grand Master plays a prank with a squeezy joke bottle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p552ea58e63f68cac426ea2d2e28ebbc3</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A special guide to working scientifically, whether that involves drinking black vomit, measuring people?s farts, or firing arrows into their bum.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p353c0c51ff7efe9e6d78587b0b2209b1</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>History buff Hector from Wigan is a huge fan of William Shakespeare. He needs a space of his own where he can store all his history books, write plays and enjoy his hero?s works.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56419dd18492f3b2b04d21c575ea2426</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>It?s Mum?s birthday, but Adam and Joe have forgotten to sort her surprise party! Who can decorate the house and bake her a cake in this birthday blackout bonanza.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pce2cf20f8b5fff85d77c8470b7e98176</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>In order to help protect a sandcastle that he and Tala built, Glitch uses a giant vacuum to suck up the sand from the Academy's beach, exposing the illusive ghost crabs to the hungry seagulls up above. To make matters worse, Glitch and his Grimbots lose control of the vacuum, causing chaos in the ocean. Can the Go Jetters protect the crabs while also returning the sand to its proper place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p58ccdb0aa256df2a89bfea29ca2fc7fe</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>A triple solar eclipse is about to happen! Cosima and Big Lizard race down the volcano and hitch a lift on a dragonfly so that they can get vital equipment to Dad in the nick of time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3620d0f17b180290a41ba17a09aedaf8</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Peso?s little brother Pinto gets into trouble with a bombardier beetle and a hot geyser.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p888b59fc8cf3bd2e1fdbabed1476aa5a</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>Brinicle tries to turn the Krispy Krill shack into a top restaurant to impress a secret reviewer, but chef Pancake?s cooking proves unpopular, and Looph?s plate machine misfires.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p16294e9bc9892b1b6550b2fb824d2407</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Supertato shows the Grape Kids how to camp Supertato-style, but Evil Pea arrives and wows them with her ice camping. Before long, the Grape Kids need to be rescued by Supertato.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c301a9316d93ec3089ac523d51666e2</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Playtime is over as Danger Mouse battles an army of vengeful soft toys. Pink Dawn's henchman teddy bear Snuggles is on an angry rampage. He is zapping cuddly toys, bringing them to life as rage-filled criminals. He will annihilate anyone who refuses to be his friend. Danger Mouse spots the source of Snuggles's power - Pink Dawn's tiara! When Penfold's beloved teddy, Bernard, rejects his owner to join Snuggles's new gang, Danger Mouse and the distraught Penfold rush to confront Dawn. They are shocked to discover that Dawn has ditched pink in favour of a superpowered goth darkness. Can DM reunite Dawn and Snuggles and put a stop to this rampage? Will Bernard ever return to the ever-loving Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9dfcc413a353c078b8d6f7e592c273fa</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>New teacher Miss Mistry is taking Class 3C on a trip to Flumes o' Doom theme park. If anyone is a nano-second late, the bus leaves without them. Walter pulls out all the stops to make Dennis late for the bus.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb1a2b6da96c302dbf59dd322ca1e52b3</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface is secretly doing underpants laundry chores for Walter, hoping to help Dennis save up some cash. He urges the gang to audition for a replacement Pieface to make up for his mysterious absence.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0ced6f09c8a135c0107ac2cf9c4bc6b</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are lured away by a cloaked figure to compete for the title of Quester of the Year, leaving the forest with no-one to protect its scones.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p26e2fcb5c6b4f009308c94a8aaa4a124</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A frantic bride needs a romantic ice sculpture to appease her nervous groom, so the Ninjas travel to the north pole to deliver a wedding day she will never forget.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4244299fed08c9f23c9ffa18cc4ee1d7</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>From William the Conqueror making rules about chopping off body parts to Elizabeth I in court over some swan-related mischief, Horrible Histories takes a look at some history?s most ridiculous rules.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf8b647553d5301c96fbb3b498573cdeb</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>The Ug and Ugio families go head to head on Stone Age Family Fortunes, mad King George III's doctors are even madder than he is and Emperor Elagabalus launches his pranktastic Roman lottery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0704c616b31b6a06bd7554855d5a13bb</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Rattus considers a career change, and luckily he has the whole of history to look through for ideas. Could he be an inventor like Babbage, or is the pirate life for him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p36ab2258988e42edeaab688e5066b407</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Paul the Potato is love-struck by the poster girl potato advertising WilburCorp?s new line of super-posh chips. The gang stage a daring potato rescue in the WilburCorp factory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p509b952fbaf1e149740c52cc753d1901</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Baron Greenback brews a plot to steal every beverage on the planet and mix them all together, making an undrinkable, disgusting sludge. By depriving the population of their much-needed drinks break he'll cause worldwide exhaustion. Danger Mouse seems unfazed, but without his cherished tea Penfold wilts on their rescue mission. Can Danger Mouse thwart the baron's thirsty plot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf917845bd542156a5514c0aea46c08e</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A school girl orders a wish-granting vase so she doesn't have to go to school, but the Ninjas must face a series of tests set by the vase's guardian in order to get it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6b01e1206010854040758ec2d81ae7d</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A football, a biscuit, a sofa bed and a pair of shoes are among the items getting the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf1786c5e1632112d437a33a96c3312d</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds a polar bear and realises they are from the same species.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1cb689afd001542531ecfbda6e5efcfc</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Cheese tells Boy he has been the victim of a weredog staredown, he becomes convinced he will turn into a weredog too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6cc7f43074fc2f3ea13127028d4a1f88</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are relieved that the loud, threatening voice they can hear actually belongs to a small slug named Zorgoth, who is armed with a megaphone. However, when Zorgoth uses his Orb of Compression to shrink the heroes down to the size of ants, their relief evaporates. They must now embark on a long and dangerous quest, through their picnic items and beyond, to warn the Council before Zorgoth shrinks the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe50df153eaba594e89a65c54ae953f0c</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. When things in town get covered in jam, the agents turn to Odd Todd for help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p726b89ae063ad65d16421a22195bbb76</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When the agents go to lunch, they struggle to relax and to ignore the oddness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb6cc581c0c982d431e1e4959cb49c9f0</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen struggles with the idea that he is about to lose his BFF Noah to a gifted military school.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9071f37e1942b65e7987bb64753f9acb</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>The heroes team up with a discreet ally to face Rocketear.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db45b15f5dbd9d1d2828dbc97a7b081</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs get noisy with homemade instruments, Aowen Jin paints UV art that glows, and Emily Steel - aka Gladiator Dynamite - flexes her muscles by drawing a weightlifting alpaca.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d00237a732b167e672df30111b12313</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Tracy Beaker Returns</title>
    <desc>Drama set in a children's home. Justine Littlewood arrives at the Dumping Ground, wanting Mike to give her away at her wedding. Tracy reverts to her old competitive self, but is Justine's perfect fiance who he pretends to be.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fb3fe5b63e8a9c4f9233098863427fb</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>As Adele says goodbye to The Next Step, she tries to mend fences with Olive. Things get complicated between Heath and Pascale as Anthony deals with Adele leaving.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6b1be36aa0e94cecaeba7f3f1ecfc8f4</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Abby and Shini go head-to-head in a powerchair football challenge! Using specially designed powerchairs as part of four-a-side teams, who will come out on top.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe198144b1c57887ed93fb809b7488166</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>27 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun steps in a can of red paint, and his resulting red hoof makes him a style icon on the farm. Before long, the rest of the flock try their own new looks and soon steal the limelight. As the outfits become more and more outrageous, Shaun wonders if less might sometimes be more.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5311608370a06605a09997e8b42e43c8</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Jeopardy Mouse are on a mission in space - will they work together as a team? In the midst of an interstellar team-up, a bickering Danger Mouse and Jeopardy Mouse crash-land on a desolate planet. While Penfold, Squawkencluck and King Kong Brunel search for a way to bring the pair back to Earth, the stubborn pair split up in their new surroundings. DM and Jeopardy Mouse are brought back together when they're captured by a horde of Fly People - the planet isn't deserted after all! The Fly People's hatred of DM is explained when our hero is reunited with Lionel the huge World Wide Spider, who he accidentally sent to the planet of the flies. Lionel's fondness for snacking on the local population has landed him a place on the menu - he's going to be fed to the terrifying pit-dwelling 'Beast', and now DM and Jeopardy are going to be eaten too! Will DM and JM finally resolve to cooperate to get out of this perilous position.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6d72d4eed999a80d4b929f9cf71a337</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Professor von Screwtop gets mistaken for the new kid in school and joins Class 3C for the day. Rubi is so embarrassed at her dad?s antics that she resorts to pranking to get him into trouble and out of the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p060c373a4ae75d174dc60fc03089f42e</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Girl, Cheese and Dog start a babysitting business, but their first client is a real handful! If they want to please him, they might just need to take Boy's advice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p72f1944bc02f139f094ac17ac13220a7</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa162247cdc70652310a18d561fc566aa</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings organised a mega-party, leading to the cabin being invaded by bats.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p017dac7b4c386b657d1c3d9999e8170c</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings activate the air conditioner's AI, causing it to fall in love with the fridge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54e09a09adf7855a626c534a8050680a</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia and Otis are tasked with calling a truce between feuding guests. Curriculum: Using a Venn Diagram, 3D shapes: spheres and cubes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a7cc9c25316a9316d40d4a87c98e2f3</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert has invented a new contraption to help him fly using an old set of bagpipes. The 'Herbecopter', as Herbert likes to call it, is rather noisy but extremely effective, and Twinkle is unhappy at no longer being the only flying hero. So, when the heroes quest to get Friendlyface?s priceless locket back from a dragon, Twinkle and Herbert become extremely competitive and risk completely failing the quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa955ab16670c700cec4ca1249af0b548</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Ever wondered how Deadly 60 gets made? This programme goes behind the scenes to see just how the series is filmed. From where the team eat and sleep to the extreme measures they have to take as they travel the world filming some of its deadliest predators, this special tells all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p22af49ca7eb35a9412e4ad499da57f28</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 7-9 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about typography, font shapes and how to design a font.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p695cc5d6600ea442889e7b5645df3fa7</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ricky Wilson's Art Jam</title>
    <desc>Award-winning pop star Nadine Coyle visits the Art Jam studio to show Ricky three items that mean the world to her - her make-up palette, a lucky ring from India and a very special family picture. While chatting to Ricky, Nadine shares amazing stories about being in one of the biggest girl bands of all time Girls Aloud, her incredible sleeping ability, having a big family and enjoying cooking with her daughter.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf583d620357967c79c73d544ce16360</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Dr Xand?s favourite cold virus is the rhinovirus: that?s one that gets right up your nose and gives you the sniffles. So when the doctors get a question in the lab asking why your nose runs when you have a cold, they decide to become rhinoviruses and attack the body?s defences through a giant nose. We also get a chance to see right inside Dr Xand?s nostrils when he sticks a camera up his nose to show Dr Chris a real-life, flapping bogey specimen - gross alert! Dr Ronx makes a whole class of schoolchildren forget where their elbows are with a mind-blowing body trick you can try on your friends, and in Ouch and About, Ethan wants to know which is the strongest bone in his body. Over in Australia, six-year-old Jakobi is flown by helicopter to Sydney by the Flying Doctors because his local hospital thinks he needs specialist care. Lucy goes to the hospital in Edinburgh to find out why she?s woken up with a swollen face. And in Liverpool, Michael?s foot has been run over by a car, so no surprise that he?s ended up in the emergency department. Ouch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34f2cd8ab93746b25f8c0c8dc409b964</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>In this episode, we meet nine-year-old twin sisters Kiki and Queenie. We also follow U11 boys Teddy and Miles in their biggest tournament of the year.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32db01aaffdf41be1b2b695848d338ff</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Tune in for crazy catches and a countdown of the best records to try with your mates.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69ee252952549d256f831d63d35b5d24</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>Ricky is inspired by artist Iris Scott to paint with his fingers. He prints on a t-shirt using a box and string, and the Grand Master plays a prank with a finger in a box.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd52444db7d52ca6214e0b6de502a6cea</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A weird and wonderful look at how gravity, magnetism and friction impact everything. With Fred Sirieix.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94fd45c10fe71cfd50c37b15a03b378a</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Angel from London is an aspiring tap dancer who has nowhere to practise her moves. She is always scuffing her mum?s floors and annoying her brother with the noise. She needs a tip-top tap dance space where she can train properly, store her costumes and display her medals.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa65b8dd6e224d29f6d3a9d0a6cc891e4</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Joe and Adam take on a rip-roaring rodeo challenge. Can they gain their cowboy credentials and lasso like a pro, or will they fall off their high horse.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81924ba3c2fdfdb3684d4afee36821a5</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>The Go Jetters are finding out about an incredible fishy adventure called the salmon run. Every year, salmon swim from the oceans where they live all the way upstream to calm, shallow rivers to lay their eggs. On the way they have to leap up waterfalls, jump fish ladders and dash past hungry bears who try to catch them. Kyan thinks these fish are even better at fantastic gymnastics than he is! Ubercorn sets those co-ordinates for the Kenai River, Alaska and the Go Jetters make their way to see the salmon run for themselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb721c2fff166edfcf99b515b3f31bf4</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Big Lizard has found an epic crystal, and Cosima is jealous. Their squabbling reaches its peak at the top of the volcano! Will they learn to share before it's too late.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7ace19447157a50909b56f2858ea89d2</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts use the Terra-Gup 2 to rescue creatures from a Rocky Mountain rockslide.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe22ce8f631d40b6a75a8e76e572721b3</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>The shadow of a monster causes panic among the Piris, apart from Nugget, who is keen to investigate a new mystery. She finally tracks down the creature, but is all exactly as it seems.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12ee0530347db8a14a3049cf60e54317</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Supertato, Carrot and Tomato are exploring in the plant aisle when they hear a strange noise. They follow the noise and meet the famous Kiwi the Explorer, who needs their help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd396f361369939366ee89e3d31292284</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron and Penfold are stranded on a desert island. In the skies above, there is a race to snatch Brunel's All Encompassing Remote Control.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa7b8e966b5c6c306f3a119bdf3118798</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s time for Gnasher?s annual bath, but the stinky hound will do anything to avoid the tub. Dennis and Gnasher go head to head in a town-wide game of cat and mouse ? or rather, tripe hound and wheelie bathtub.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cd3695300ecc962061ac4a3338675c2</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The after-school art club is under threat of imminent demolition. In trying to save the club, the gang end up on the trail of the mysterious undercover urban artist known only as Pranksy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p361a97fdcd2b35beabb23cae8c4b65d6</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>To avoid Herbert?s surprise visits via his tunnels in the Big Birch, the other heroes take any quest and must deal with an angry plant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1712e7d54bc565d7f40c59dd3788f999</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Needing a rocking horse for his daughter?s birthday present, a dad asks Ninja Express for help, only for them to return with the legendary Trojan Horse.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbbaa2421fa7d34bde857fdf9d1e6a1e8</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>How long does it take to build a pyramid? Why didn?t people like the Statue of Liberty? Why are there pineapples on St Paul?s? Horrible Histories takes a tour of the world?s greatest landmarks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pececa102ff23adbbf7211f5e5f2cfbc5</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketch show. Barmy Roman emperor Caligula fails to invade Britain, King Henry VIII plays tennis while Anne Boleyn is executed, and some Saxon monks throw a party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd0af2c7887e8b62742cc5dd446c9fb7d</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories serves up the history of foul feasting, from Stone Age lentils to Queen Victoria?s anti-fart bread.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e982b093453009b01fec984d6d98fb7</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>A mishap on a mission leaves Danger Mouse confused - why is Penfold not talking to him? It might be because today is Penfold's birthday and he hasn't remembered it again! Squawk sprays DM with her experimental empathy gas in the hope that he will find it easier to care about other people. The newly empathetic DM is a changed mouse! One who seems to think breaking the Baron out of prison is a great idea.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa906b53f7371fff74d44e2194a58bf1b</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A witch orders a mango to finish off her monster soup. However, when Konpeki greedily gobbles up the soup, Kiro and the witch must take on a daring rescue mission.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11f12531c4146a9d46ec97a0b0025fe5</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The ninja sushi are back, and fearless Pete Parsnip comes face to face with a terrifying snake. Star bar attempts another trip to the moon, the toast soldiers try again to ambush an egg, and Mrs Strawberry takes part in the talent show, with shocking consequences.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3d57600bad43f4c9d41bd1369535c13b</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover an ancestral tree that casts maledictions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p853fe031bd6f16e817a884125beb3883</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Everyone is excited for the annual camping trip with Gramps, but when Cheese wins an invitation to a big movie premiere, she lies and says she has to stay home for charity work.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa9f68c8c20c4d3ca7eb8e7eaaa3c57ec</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes quest to stop Balthazar from turning forest folk into household objects, Herbert realises that he can defeat the wizard?s spell by using the magic tricks he has practiced. Blossom is particularly intrigued by Herbert the Peculiar?s tricks, not to mention his stage name, so when Herbert himself is transformed into a table lamp, it?s Blossom the Very Impressive to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p02b5755668bd5974ec3f672d77162daf</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Security agents Owen and Ohio secretly provide backup on a case so they can have a pizza party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p381ec3a509038761d2b7800cc4d40f2e</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen and Beth decide they must defend the ants that Courtney and Leshawna want to harm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31b289722eba2b0fc5112c5ea20ab77f</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Ahead of the Women?s Euros, we visit St George?s Park, the home of England?s national teams, to meet some future stars of the game! Welsh footballer Ella Powell and Euros champion Ella Toone answer your questions, and Joel and Abby go head-to-head in a goalball challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2bac12a256d2d65f269b3bed18e91e58</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Bionic prank Athena as a massive broccoli at a fake healthy eating film shoot. Meanwhile, the other Gladiators are up to mischief behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0478823e97e8046f6ca16e39a89023b6</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs set sail with homemade pirate ships, Sophie Ryder sculpts a huge Minotaur, and Harry Hill draws himself being chased by a very big, very blue cat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p950470bcf5000eb12035d467de5b8256</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Tracy Beaker Returns</title>
    <desc>It's rewards time again - the annual event at the town hall at which all the local young people in care get an award for the one thing that makes them special. Tracy's doing the certificates for the Dumping Ground, but can't think of one for Johnny. She asks Tee to help, but Johnny overhears them discussing his lack of special qualities.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe79c245acddd1cd4d3ef9798793f554</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>An overprotective Heath accuses Grace of sabotage, while Grace and Jonah make a bet to make it on to A-Troupe. Meanwhile, Izzy grapples with keeping Anthony?s secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5b4c76f289d443a95cb05ffbadf7a365</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall meets the most ravenous shark in the sea, the tiger shark. Known for eating tin cans and even car number plates, these sharks are in fact perfectly honed hunters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p902af30bdff6c5ddb583c4b3c641df45</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>28 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Realising that Bitzer has a series of whistles which can control the flock?s movements, Shaun steals them and soon has the flock dancing to his tune. When the Farmer finds the whistles stuck together like a harmonica, his dreadful playing gives Shaun a taste of his own medicine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd628dfaf91a3937f6bfffaccd0302e0a</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>In order to stop a deranged Victorian time-travelling chimp from uninventing the world, Danger Mouse and Penfold must arrive in the past just before the nick of time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb89086a78e1589c68cd9ddbc5eb06285</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>On the first day of a new school year, Dennis and the gang imagine all the things that might be new and unfamiliar at Bash Street School. By the time they reach the front gates, they are all expecting the worst.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3faada4acf7db9d5c697dcdb4bf0045a</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse's latest experiment goes horribly wrong when he swaps brains with a house fly! With his sibling?s help, Mouse frantically tries reversing the wacky situation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc9a62ab07918a2510fd95a0b876404e</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcda1664f4010d08fa2e609a3bcc6c3ad</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Desperate to learn magic, Merlin's apprentice, Merlina, orders a magic wand. However, mayhem ensues when the inexperienced wizard transforms everyone around her including the Ninjas.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0af67c14a68062ce733ef922bb35e15c</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Special agents from the Big O's office threaten to shut down Odd Squad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peac60c353b30408f095960017890b648</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are excited to visit Whizzpop?s Pop-Up Bakery and taste his magical cakes, but they are shocked to find that the protein bars have shouty raisins in them, the custard tarts are rock hard, and the floating sponges keep floating away! Trevor quests to solve the mystery, but having accidentally fallen into Whizzpop?s invisibility flour, how on earth will he get everyone?s attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe2faf77b85cf0b2852c9a1177edf9ab5</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Hoaxer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p61aa45f412d3df9681233ef3650c91fe</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Reflekta again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p208e51df6d4fee55a48137e167bb8424</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: XY</title>
    <desc>Bonnie makes some new friends who are a force to be reckoned with.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd069b149ff938d6128110eb2f1f6acf</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy struggles to pick coconuts, but the Lemmings find a magic conch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe790119cb595cbdc802925b6696f6fe0</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>It's time for the racket game, where big scores mean big prizes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb4876fa452c0f93c5471f450963b20c9</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings adopt a cute insect that eats wood. And what's made of wood? The cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pff351cedb37a51b39f803f5886026822</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Girl enters a cosplay costume contest to win a trophy and meet her favourite TV star, but needs somebody to wear the back end of her enormous costume. Boy is horrified at dressing as the character?s bum, but he doesn't want to let his sister down. Can he put aside his embarrassment to help Girl win the competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p39a709d325b91d9a6c575a2c63275204</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mum and Dad take the TV away until the kids learn to behave, and the siblings realise they need some rules. Mouse is the judge and decides how to settle family arguments, putting wrongdoers into a homemade jail. However, when Mouse also behaves badly, he puts himself in jail, and the family realise they are all locked in.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5af69310c8cbf603b3cf4dfefd47c1df</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Girl is failing science class, so Mouse offers to help her learn. However, Girl decides it will be easier to borrow one of his inventions and cheat instead. Everything is going to plan until the borrowed invention goes wrong and causes a scientific calamity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p387204adcf2e93aa73aa4d915551c7ae</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Harold is determined to keep everyone safe on the class camping trip by catching Bigfoot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p941d3fc9842083f030dbb05ab461f301</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>The class camping trip turns into a treasure hunt, while Harold looks to trap a Bigfoot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4317ddecad9de25b04544978ce824b51</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>The bros are on a rescue mission to save a giant rubber duck while captaining a raft and a paddleboard. And the Lewis Sisters help take some selfies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p977f0c3fddf5a0975458c1844b0921f2</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>It?s time for the interschool sports day! However, Moxy?s hyper-competitiveness starts to overshadow the events on the field, causing the Odd Socks to make a stand.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b91003b8bac40331972a43ba9ad0bd2</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Ahead of the Women?s Euros, we visit St George?s Park, the home of England?s national teams, to meet some future stars of the game! Welsh footballer Ella Powell and Euros champion Ella Toone answer your questions, and Joel and Abby go head-to-head in a goalball challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2bac12a256d2d65f269b3bed18e91e58</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When the exclusive Club 37 opens up in HQ, Orli and Ozzie set out to crack 37 cases so they can enter it. But with more fun clubs opening, will the agents? club obsession get the better of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe464d88f764c10fa67e3614ac3c1a289</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. Olive and Otto must stop zeroes from disappearing before the town is destroyed and Otto turns into a baby.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96d501f432d04d9f3634f7432cfb185d</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Spooky Files</title>
    <desc>The Johns run a talent quest that puts Spooky HQ at risk, but a song-stealing Spooky takes the Crew?s voices, forcing Bert to face his fear of singing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03b8f89212814f573e81d79680e2075a</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Spooky Files</title>
    <desc>Sunny Valley?s Swimming Carnival is ruined by an Octo-Spooky that takes over the pool ? can swimming champ Derek find a way to lure the Spooky out and save the event of the year.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5b159c0886cfe4930bf05431b7a436e0</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Some of history's greatest characters serenade us with tales of their lives. Featuring the all-conquering Alexander the Great, the cash-loving Crassus, the feisty Joan of Arc, the brilliant but miserable Charles Dickens and the very determined Rosa Parks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2ad5c572a27ed56a3c7c514e2ae96b30</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Science goes too far in Fartenheimer, music goes too far in Heads, Shoulders, Knees, Toes and All the other Bones in the Body, and there's a Swiftian take on the water cycle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa83dcfd68984c53c5bff2b5550e247f5</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>It?s teachers v students week - can the Vipers help win the cup, become school heroes, and impress Aoife?s new crush, Jamie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0174069b4479aab09bd6e163ba4c3a41</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>When a figure from Alex?s past reappears and threatens to turn his life upside down, Coach Byrne steps in to help. But his actions have unintended consequences.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7d527457695c5ed8ace87f3e247808fd</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Jude befriends a chicken with an attitude when an unusual petting zoo visits the school.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6564b7f9b1833bcbeba99b1e6168d336</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>The kids invent an admirer for Chef, hoping to make him happy enough to order them pizza.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5dae45673597e1b242e164fac620cb54</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan and Courtney make a quick escape to try and replace Chef's special energy drink.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c72638973d6a4d44d7073e5bfea39ee</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Our dynamic duo take on a shoddy army of knock-offs when alien Quark's latest money-making scheme is to create cheap copies of Danger Mouse and Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc3534acab020f64bb5ca220b64ae15c1</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold must travel to the Twystyverse to stop the evil tyrant Baron Silas von Penfold from taking over both versions of the Earth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96bd7bb99d9e77929da195732a4166fb</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Our dynamic duo take on a shoddy army of knock-offs when alien Quark's latest money-making scheme is to create cheap copies of Danger Mouse and Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc3534acab020f64bb5ca220b64ae15c1</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids accidentally destroy a beloved family photo and decide to make it up to Mom and Dad by hiring a photographer to take a new one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea9981e258355c4b97ba8632e168fa2c</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Stevie Smith challenges Boy in the mini-golf tournament. However, as they practice, they actually become fast friends and neglect their training to hang out! When the contest arrives, it is revealed Stevie was only pretending to be Boy's friend to keep him from practicing! But maybe Boy has a trick of his own up his sleeve..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6124bb0a527325104289dd14cfd0a09</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Stevie Smith challenges Boy in the mini-golf tournament. However, as they practice, they actually become fast friends and neglect their training to hang out! When the contest arrives, it is revealed Stevie was only pretending to be Boy's friend to keep him from practicing! But maybe Boy has a trick of his own up his sleeve..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6124bb0a527325104289dd14cfd0a09</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings decide to play hide-and-seek in the Savannah.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b103f5c6909d7e3276e3613f4e5eee3</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a hidden mechanism on the Great Wall of China.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e9b40eecda303f7fa1885c29e9016b1</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle feels she is being taken for granted by the other heroes, so she joins the Fairy Squad when they arrive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa88b9a6c763d7c35c89b5f246f002e9f</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are excited to visit Whizzpop?s Pop-Up Bakery and taste his magical cakes, but they are shocked to find that the protein bars have shouty raisins in them, the custard tarts are rock hard, and the floating sponges keep floating away! Trevor quests to solve the mystery, but having accidentally fallen into Whizzpop?s invisibility flour, how on earth will he get everyone?s attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe2faf77b85cf0b2852c9a1177edf9ab5</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Blink hacks Sofia?s graffiti project, but Mansour paints the mystery artist into a corner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1b50764251ffb8540552a111f6f7c0a9</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Blink takes control of Mansour's body using nanobots during his school music recital.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p77d13708ef94d1ad9c095e4bcdc4887d</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>After an all-bean breakfast, the teams must cross the island in silence to avoid being eaten by raptors. The first team to reach the other side claims victory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6fbeef74714a9c1645e4cd02791e91c</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Kung Fu Panda: Secrets of the Scroll</title>
    <desc>Fate brings five animals and their unique kung fu styles together to make the perfect team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p50cf34d9856a6c54a114461d7387c9b8</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Renovations force Bitzer to camp out for the night. When the flock are shut out of the barn, they must also pitch up in the field. The sheep are loving their trendy glampsite at first, but as the weather worsens and batteries run low, the appeal of Bitzer?s practical tent grows.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pafb9f5e97e87624c52f00acead3f6773</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When all the other danger agents become supersmart due to a batch of genetically enhanced celery, Danger Mouse might need to find a new job.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd3564fbdb5d3af356c096d2505f6a6f2</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The kids of Beanotown decide that they can run the town far better than the grown-ups. However, they discover it isn?t nearly as easy or fun as they had hoped.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa15e18ace150b21c21fc62dda6a4fddb</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy is afraid of being honest in case he hurts other people's feelings and finds himself doing things he doesn?t like just to keep others happy. Mouse and Cheese encourage him to be totally honest, only to find that Boy?s total honesty can be rather blunt. Can the gang rein him in before Boy alienates the entire town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p266389173e1520b4e65cb4c48680fe55</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a02b44ba4d2329692f806f8b64eb172</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After breaking a carriage belonging to his beloved Princess, a besotted Prince orders another one from the Ninjas - but the Princess only has eyes for the Ninja Van.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p136094f61bb9c90e90770dffeab20d62</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Oona meets Dr O's replacement.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p76c55ca2fff4f99fa7904424a74aa04a</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Stinkweasel drops a rain of yukkiness onto the forest, the Fairy Squad, with their excellent flying skills, decide they are the ones for the job. However, Hoofius insists this should be their quest, even if he does hate ick! And when the Fairy Squad get their wings gunked and are unable to fly, the heroes can resume their quest to end Stinkweasel?s reign of stinky nonsense - no flying required.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d85af1ed37a16cec54b2e5a529e9bbc</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face a revolutionary enemy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe794b82c94b5da3fc969d1d75fc5d92</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:55AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Retrieving data. Wait a few seconds and try to cut or copy again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5182ecf611fd5ff1885769a76c91b757</image>
    <start>08:55AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Ahead of the Women?s Euros, we visit St George?s Park, the home of England?s national teams, to meet some future stars of the game! Welsh footballer Ella Powell and Euros champion Ella Toone answer your questions, and Joel and Abby go head-to-head in a goalball challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2bac12a256d2d65f269b3bed18e91e58</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>Dragons, dinos and divas! The Kwapongs craft fire-breathers, Romesh Ranganathan draws a rapping T-rex, and Bristles dives into the bold, brilliant world of Frida Kahlo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35625862ebe527b01a7c825cbdc1577a</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>4 O'Clock Club</title>
    <desc>Polly?s perfect day with Evan suddenly goes horribly wrong. Meanwhile, Eli thinks Owen has a secret girlfriend? but gets a shock when he learns who Owen is really hanging out with.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc8a08870ff7cca77d2708fc602258ca8</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>April Fool?s day at the leisure centre can only mean one thing - more pranks than normal! Sharon tries to ban them, but there is a mystery pranker whose identity not even Danny knows. Meanwhile, Mick has his own idea of what an April fool is.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81690ef994195308e5212654f9e03359</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It is the annual sports day competition at Pottsfield and this time around it's Danny v Lance. They compete in a selection of events, including the classic sport of who can put on the most clothes and who can pop the balloon fastest with their bum.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p04aeb7dbdd9bbc1f4e4e2a50d738cdff</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>The bros are back with a splash, kicking off with a blockbuster challenge and ThatsWatson. And it?s time to race around the ultimate obstacle course - on water.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p273992b281d4844fc3c8ea7a6a01a8c5</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The brothers visit Belgium?s Pairi Daiza Zoo to meet pandas, walruses, penguins and the golden takin, all animals that have adapted to survive in the coldest climates.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6007b983866314343f318b332185c159</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall finds himself quite literally in deep water as he goes in search of underwater animals for his Deadly 60 list. The idyllic waters off the coast of Borneo hide a wealth of lethal predators, but just who is worthy of a place on the list? Camouflage, stealth and serious weaponry are the order of the day as Steve comes face to face with a highly venomous scorpion fish and witnesses the formidable spear mantis impaling its supper with its retractable spear-like arms. Just when Steve thinks he has seen it all, he finds himself surrounded by a gigantic shoal of barracuda in one of the most awesome animal encounters of the series.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pec9963c765ac0ad376845eec75ab276b</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>The action shifts to Steve's home turf as the Deadly 60 team scour the UK in search of its lethal beauties. From the wild seas off the Pembrokeshire coast to the New Forest, Steve proves that British wildlife is anything but boring. Gannets prove to be more than a match for Steve in a diving competition. He battles with the elements to reach the birds but the rough seas are determined to stop him. He then has to confront his past as he comes face to face with the only venomous snake that has hospitalised him. The Deadly team also have a close call as they uncover a hornets' nest in a loft, and Steve gets a taste of what it is like to be prey for a day as he is hunted through a forest by a hungry goshawk.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b9df1a4eb9baf1f38f30a4bbfad536e</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Dr Xand tries to sleep standing up, then finds out how virtual reality can help in surgery. Doctors Chris and Xand count down five things that make the skin crawl.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p60a06fe61d14b150321112335dbcb4bf</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>The Ug and Ugio families go head to head on Stone Age Family Fortunes, mad King George III's doctors are even madder than he is and Emperor Elagabalus launches his pranktastic Roman lottery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0704c616b31b6a06bd7554855d5a13bb</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Joan of Arc gets a visit from a confused angel, a pirate captain tries to make his crew dress like ladies, and Mrs Celt enjoys being a Roman on Historical Wife Swap.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7f69823d065dc077d857475c7fb68a31</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Viper with a fake interview that ends with an unexpected splashdown, but he doesn?t find it funny! The other Gladiators have sneaky behind-the-scenes fun at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d2e22d45141442e761e7181750d3d5d</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. In trying to prove he does not believe in magic, Danger Mouse accidentally unleashes an evil magical queen into the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd4935d86a65a4e2a8c44fe8bd4ffa0d5</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Jeopardy Mouse wins the Agent of the Month competition, Danger Mouse and Penfold are forced to travel to New York for a lesson and to take on the criminal organisation known as Hydrant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9bea4a009f4a743a746eef2582c505df</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Penfold's addiction to social media helps the Baron turn all of Danger Mouse's secrets against him in a plot to deflate the planet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6f7ce120fee94baea61d80208ee3e590</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Miss Mistry and Mrs Creecher clash over the best way to teach Class 3C about butterflies. The gang just want to get through the lesson so they can get out of school in time for a Grizzly Griller Wildlife Event.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f724fc607801733f58ba35ac017e5a6</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:45PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Paul the Potato is love-struck by the poster girl potato advertising WilburCorp?s new line of super-posh chips. The gang stage a daring potato rescue in the WilburCorp factory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p509b952fbaf1e149740c52cc753d1901</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Olive surprises herself and everyone around her by actually becoming a good cook, Dr Pfooflepfeffer tries to cash in by turning the school canteen into an exclusive and super-expensive dining experience.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdee355ef68772da8fcf20dd134fad956</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom is terrible at keeping secrets, and Trevor can?t help but point that out. To prove him wrong, Blossom refuses to reveal the secret hiding place for her piece of the Amulet of Protection, even though the heroes need it to stop Balthazar casting a weather spell on the forest. With a rain of crabs heading their way, the heroes must quickly persuade Blossom to reveal her secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96c570335130856ee7aaba63648a0da2</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Gnome Crystal Mine has ground to a halt, leaving the forest with no crystals, no power supply and melting ice lollies! The heroes are tasked with a quest to find out what has happened and to fix it. It turns out that a slimy beast named Smarg has made the mine her home. But with Hoofius?s fear of gunk getting the better of him, evicting the slippery Smarg is not going to be easy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p858de20cb9333a64f647c54c77975ddd</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is acting very strangely indeed. He refuses to stamp any of Admin Bunny?s documents, keeps getting distracted by butterflies, and seems oddly happy! The heroes are extremely suspicious and decide that someone must have swapped him with a doppelganger. Now they must quest to find out where the real Friendlyface is and get him back before the forest descends into total chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde2e0b6ed02cd81a52a1b5ae1f9bd3e8</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Seeking a source of heat, Grizzy moves into a greenhouse - but the Lemmings are coming too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf78e2d3fe779b52026926ad622ed6751</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings dream up a scheme where Grizzy would submit to their will.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p77c50ae87c24cd07881d14c862040015</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings build a giant ice slide in the cabin. However, Grizzy makes sure the fun doesn't last long.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe53ec0323ebf5de44c74426dbdc1214c</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings dream up a scheme where Grizzy would submit to their will.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p77c50ae87c24cd07881d14c862040015</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>While punished, Tom must sneak out to rescue the Riders from Buzzsaw.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p23bb87f015d41bec01f6c7798132e094</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Darrell?s final year starts with a fierce argument with Gwen, but she knows they need to work together. Meanwhile, French student Celeste joins the Third and plays a prank on the teachers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5f56dd0f62ae77c0e4472811ae4950e</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Addie has a meltdown on a school trip and finds a strange witch jar. It?s the start of a life-changing adventure full of friendship, frenemies and a mystery that must be solved.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdeca9d41b1ccd1a1af6ef33971afe46c</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe?s latest victory is cut short after an Absolute Dance rules change shakes things up. Now, winning regionals isn?t just about their reputation. It's also about saving the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f6d0ad53ea164a011d86ea9249440f0</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe tries to stay focused on regionals as Heath and Pete learn more about the Brawl. Anthony helps Adele with an audition, while Ariana feels overworked.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p336464e8bf363b3c4bfb27e13123602e</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>The Keeper Myridell arrives on Earth to recruit a new generation of Scions: superpowered warriors who will have to save her world Gorm from the nefarious Lord Graven. The four kids she is guided towards are unlikely heroes, but when they are thrown into danger, their hidden strengths surprise everyone.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde1984f1bf7703cb535a3ef904f00513</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings end up lost after misplacing their jar of Yummy in a labyrinth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6adf7709b4293ae1023ab4a70b88ad6</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>30 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The Farmer tasks Bitzer with baling up a fresh haystack, but the hungry sheep have hidden inside and are turned into moving bales. A wild game of chase the bale results as Bitzer tries to restore order to the hay field.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4444e15b78e6d89ea5864146f236628b</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The baron's true love threatens to bring Danger Mouse to his knees.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfcaae47453a9f3c1541b759fb60634cb</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>JJ applies for an elite sporting school. However, not realising it's miles away from Beanotown, he needs to do badly in the sporting assessment to get out of it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p25f8c727ad716ff6332cb203cd3afeab</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Dog finds out he has fleas! But when he befriends them, he must hide them from his family to prevent them from getting zapped.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p06176b1ed385e0a4f53417001f70afba</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pecd3cbb6d2622d287dbd0891dcbec1ed</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds a polar bear and realises they are from the same species.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1cb689afd001542531ecfbda6e5efcfc</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover an ancestral tree that casts maledictions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p853fe031bd6f16e817a884125beb3883</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Ms O leaves headquarters in the hands of an unlikely crew. Curriculum: Spatial Sense: Mapping, Position, Location and Direction.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd794773fd1ca66f3bb6c8d6344136323</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle feels she is being taken for granted by the other heroes, so she joins the Fairy Squad when they arrive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa88b9a6c763d7c35c89b5f246f002e9f</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve demonstrates how reading the tracks and signs left by an animal can lead to fantastic encounters. Lions, octopuses and badgers all feature in this special as Steve and his trusty crew travel the planet reading the signs they leave behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p91e5c5f7e19870766e698ce536590ece</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Cooking Buddies</title>
    <desc>Kicking off the series in Buddy?s den, the gloves are on as Buddy and Conker are joined by Jackson, a young boxer who wants to learn a recipe that can pack a punch to keep his energy up! Buddy knows that Jackson loves a big-stacked sandwich, so what better than a homemade fish finger sandwich topped with crunchy lettuce and a simple two-ingredient delicious sauce, all packed into a soft bun?! Learning to cook means that you can make your meals exactly how you like them, so Jackson chooses to use cod and Buddy uses salmon, and things get messy when they breadcrumb the fish! Taking time out from the kitchen, Buddy is kept on his toes by Jackson as he gives him a lesson in boxing. Buddy learns to be light on his feet, throw a punch and read his opponent? Join Buddy, Conker and Jackson in this tasty episode of Cooking Buddies that certainly packs a punch! You can get all of Buddy?s recipes, and LOADS more, at bbc.co.uk\/food.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf6b49e93ab8e5ef954d4c8ca9c008794</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ricky Wilson's Art Jam</title>
    <desc>TV presenter and DJ Kem Cetinay visits the Art Jam studio to show Ricky three items that mean the world to him - his first pair of hairdressing scissors, his dog Rocky?s collar and his grandfather?s shepherd whistle. While chatting to Ricky, Kem shares amazing stories about how learning to be a hairdresser boosted his confidence, how his dog Rocky has helped improve his mental health, his incredible family history and the fun he has as a TV presenter.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p68d0670d216776982c935ba363cbb061</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>How does the body know when it needs to wee? The doctors find out in the lab! An optical illusion turns Dr Xand?s face green in Mindbenders, and it's time to check in on the Ouchers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p606bfd8db9fbe0868ccda1f1a227d8da</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>We meet small-for-his-age Gavers, who has always had a tough battle against much bigger kids his own age, and four academy players watch the first team play.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf231f55c7a2154610aff5d8541b2f372</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Witness crazy, record-breaking collections, and discover the tallest giraffe.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p71e08baeb2142cd2aeac4fce67233db4</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>Ricky gets into the groove making a Dance Decision Maker and demonstrates how to draw a trainer. Street dance brings a giant painted robot to life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe537899a6a5ff291b113e6cc00fe9d8c</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A prank-loving emperor hosts a dinner party on Roman Come Dine with Me, the Durham Home Guard injure themselves while learning first aid, and a Viking rock band paint the town red... literally.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pebaf7ddda728c89b94b339b937125a17</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Duncan from Glasgow is passionate about protecting orangutans and wants to raise awareness of their plight within his local community. He wants a den where he can hang out, learn more about his favourite primates and how to help them, and share his passion with friends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf7a107877c2eb098db94fe5f6e374e6a</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Big Manny joins for an icy challenge, and it?s time to jump in with both feet as Callum sets Adam and Joe an extreme puzzle challenge 15,000 feet in the air.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9a701649d51ea5ca3e7aace4c4c6a9a9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>When the Go Jetters find the Grimbots shipping overripe tomatoes into the Spanish town of Bunol, they put a stop to whatever Glitch is up to - until they find out that the tomatoes were destined for the famous Tomatina Festival, the biggest food fight in the world. Can the Go Jetters fix their own 'glitch' and save the festival.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p49f468899da5af80f874377e31884882</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>A dragonfly steals a bee cocoon that Cosima had vowed to keep safe. Cosima and Big Lizard give chase, leading to a surprising solution with a vacuum cleaner and some sticky vines.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38d7f486741c7d3312638b3a61c5a338</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Octo-Agent Min discovers a decimated bamboo forest ? a habitat crucial to pandas.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p278a9498580a521ece05b4e3880586f6</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>The Piris take refuge in grumpy Millie the Squid?s cave during a storm but accidentally damage a painting. Can they find a clever way to fix it before Millie finds out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p393bb9bb2139875856dc4e7e716f2346</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Evil Pea pretends to help Supertato and Carrot train for crime prevention, but she tricks them and steals a mobile phone. Supertato and Carrot have a clever plan to get it back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p263d79925d27d4104e2ee7819133f5d7</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Colonel K disappears on a free holiday, Danger Mouse pulls rank and assumes the mantle of caretaker colonel. However, the role is much less exciting than he anticipated, as world-saving missions make way for endless paperwork. Meanwhile, K's freebie spa retreat happens to be a diversion tactic in Greenback's latest plot to take over the world, with the baron banking on the Danger Agency falling apart without its figurehead and the world descending into disarray.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paef6868cdecdac98504d06f4fc8a956a</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Convinced that Mrs Creecher is secretly a master of Blamjitsu, JJ persuades the gang to help trick her into revealing her blam credentials.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p631f5a239e4e0ec4323d1cb7272bc565</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Doctor Pfooflepfeffer covets the world-beating power of Gnasher?s indestructible teeth and will stop at nothing to get her hands on one of those doggy dental marvels.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59953623a390b0bb5924ff89d145ecab</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is particularly tetchy this morning. He is packing for a skiing trip, but a dragon has pinched his golden fleece, and he urgently needs the heroes to quest it back ? how else will he stay warm and cosy on the slopes? However, when the heroes accidentally agree to let his niece Trixie tag along with them, they fear that her clumsiness and lack of hero skills will ruin everything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c3ff87984db3abc93407af293a6fe99</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>In order to crown a new king, Merlin summons the Ninjas to pull the legendary sword from the stone. After a few tries, they realize the solution is right under their noses.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcbca7621e76f54ad4a7abff2f2b3e1ed</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>From camels to space rockets, via Dandy Horses, actual horses, royal train rides, cars, balloons and planes, it's the Horrible History of travel.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p06c6afc5fc3e4960da9728051b785654</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>After learning the story of the Ancient Adventurer, Liko is faced with a decision.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef0f9aeb35160bf8fea618ed8f6079d6</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>From Cleopatra?s hairdo to Elizabeth I?s flushing loo, meet history?s biggest Influencers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa43f5b553ccb063ef53c4295f6a7a85e</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Olive surprises herself and everyone around her by actually becoming a good cook, Dr Pfooflepfeffer tries to cash in by turning the school canteen into an exclusive and super-expensive dining experience.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdee355ef68772da8fcf20dd134fad956</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's over-reliance on gadgets prompts Colonel K to send his top agent on a tech-free nature retreat. Unbeknownst to Danger Mouse, Greenback has the same plans for his daughter, Delilah, whose social media obsession has also spiralled out of control. Back at HQ Penfold is tasked with protecting the entire world from the threat of super-villainy. Stripped off his gadgets, DM struggles to adapt to life in the wilderness and, when a talking pine cone called Conni begins to offer him survival tips, he begins to question his own sanity. Soon enough, Delilah catches wind of DM's presence and she plots to destroy him as a means of getting back into her Dad's good books.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p75c10893273f4622c94d4cf5fb696d17</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Yin and Yang are missing one brick to finish the Great Wall of China. With the minister quickly approaching to see the completed wall, Yang orders a brick from the Ninjas.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3d4e0f4f517467e77515c8efbc52ce0b</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Despite warnings, the sheep have gobbled up the birthday cake Bitzer has baked for the Farmer. Realising the kitchen cupboards are bare, Shaun and the flock must try and source ingredients for a new one from around the farm before Bitzer realises. The result is certainly a surprise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52cad13186b4964b457432c0b79519b7</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a futuristic underground site.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0fe3e513d4fe1b37a13702add7b05620</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse's latest experiment goes horribly wrong when he swaps brains with a house fly! With his sibling?s help, Mouse frantically tries reversing the wacky situation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc9a62ab07918a2510fd95a0b876404e</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Witch, who was trapped in a Merhaven clam shell while pinching a pearl, grants Blossom a single wish to thank her for releasing her and saving her life. Blossom excitedly chooses a mermaid?s tail to improve her swimming. However, when the Merqueen complains that her pearl is missing, and the heroes have to quest to get it back, Blossom soon realises how tricky a mermaid?s tail can become on land.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5de1c5363e6236bc3067ca23bed0355e</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Oscar attends a gathering of Odd Squad scientists called Lab-Con at Odd Squad Academy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7f63d75b1d1188b09db2957ce5863357</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Oscar is it a gathering of Odd Squad scientists at Odd Squad Academy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41ab725bc27766c761d59f4b26968386</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen and Noah unwittingly become cookie moguls but must hide their odd secret ingredient.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7b36e0088a88364992dad45f01c42442</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Wishmaker.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p890797912c603fbf7c0fe00b717351f3</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs get festival-ready as they craft carnival headwear, artist Lakwena Maciver makes a grey rooftop pop with paint, and Abi Clarke draws a pirouetting otter in a tutu.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0953a9c9704625e78726ab7d76ad8ed3</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>When Felicity and Darrell debate that the Third should have the same freedoms as the Sixth, the sisters end up in a personal argument. Meanwhile, Gwen?s attempt at matronly duties ends in chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb6fdec0fbada5ff792b047fb4ded947f</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>With A-Troupe all in on regionals, Pete takes his eyes off the Brawl and auditions for dance captain. Olive looks for a place where she belongs, while Grace dreams of joining A-Troupe.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e554040d8151175d38b78010cb1824d</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Joel takes on his scariest challenge yet as he camps in a tent overnight 500ft in the sky! And to get there he must climb and navigate his way through the slate mines of Honister Pass.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p637ee2f793c8360ab78162132370fb71</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>01 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Realising that Bitzer has a series of whistles which can control the flock?s movements, Shaun steals them and soon has the flock dancing to his tune. When the Farmer finds the whistles stuck together like a harmonica, his dreadful playing gives Shaun a taste of his own medicine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd628dfaf91a3937f6bfffaccd0302e0a</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse makes short work of Burt Badboy and his newly acquired band of fanatical feline followers, the group's leader Mandy and her cult of cats immediately trade in their colourful mohican hairstyles for eyepatches and become Danger Mouse worshippers. At first Danger Mouse is having too much fun to take notice of Penfold's warnings about his new-found cult status, but even he is forced to act when the cats follow his example a little too literally and live life a little too dangerously. Danger Mouse's attempt to disown the cats goes down like a lead balloon, and they use mouse-fu skills and a superpowered amulet stolen from Tutenkamoo to show their idol the error of his ways. Danger Mouse battles the frenzied feline onslaught and saves HQ from becoming a giant scratching post. However, this only reaffirms the idea that he is the chosen one in the minds of Mandy and the cult of cats. Danger Mouse realises that the only solution is to find a new obsession for the cats.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cecc13bc26e14071dc1ed1bb687eebf</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang take on the power of WilburCorp to stop Walter?s new line of collectable toys ruining the Beanotown environment with all its wasteful plastic packaging.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c44a8d584dd7a07558e7563e65f62b0</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>To celebrate Christmas, Mum and Dad suggest that the siblings make each other gifts.?When Dog is assigned to give a gift to Cheese, she sneaks to find out what the gift is.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p281f32aaafd23ca825b0cb1dffad639a</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7f4f80c2f925a08f23e84beccf1cc165</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a futuristic underground site.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0fe3e513d4fe1b37a13702add7b05620</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a magic stick that functions as a Yummy divining rod.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p16fa51bb776109875ebe265c75d998d8</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents try and stop baby Agent Orson from getting kicked off the squad. Curriculum: Using bar graphs, pie charts and Venn diagrams to sort, classify and analyse data.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb7cd8f4c94c7c40d3964df087a8b0d70</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The tired heroes must quest to find out and stop whatever is making the loud wailing noise that has kept the residents of the forest up all night.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe737598843036feb34240aa725c51adc</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve and the team are at the Museum of Natural History in Oxford. Steve takes a look inside some of the top predators featured on Deadly 60 to find out what makes them so deadly. The skeletons and jaws of crocodiles, snakes and some of the most lethal sharks on the planet hold the key as to their deadly prowess.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p051251efc5b4b54a3312be886cce0c60</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Cooking Buddies</title>
    <desc>Buddy Oliver and his dog, Conker, invite Aiyla to join them in their kitchen den to cook up some tasty food and share some of the skills and hobbies that they both love! A black belt in karate, Aiyla loves food that has a kick, so Buddy shows her how to make her very own homemade pasta, tossed with a spicy tomato sauce ? all made from scratch with fresh ingredients in super simple steps. It will be the perfect meal before her karate competitions! In return, Aiyla teaches Buddy some of the skills needed for karate; from balance to breathing to having power in his moves, before bringing it all together. Join Buddy, Conker and Aiyla in this super tasty episode to learn how to chop in the kitchen AND in the dojo! You can get all of Buddy?s recipes, and LOADS more, at bbc.co.uk\/food.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f6691779d2231a8b25c93bd5a5cd355</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ricky Wilson's Art Jam</title>
    <desc>Fifteen-year-old TV presenter, vlogger and motivational speaker Tilly Lockey visits the Art Jam studio to show Ricky three items that mean the world to her - her hi-tech bionic arm, a special trinket box and some amazing fan art. While chatting to Ricky, Tilly shares amazing stories about the design of her bionics, her love of spreading positivity, the busy house she shares with 11 pets and giving motivational speeches alongside people such as Dalai Lama.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27749fdcc4fb82a68d4c73c4f9e2766b</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Dr Xand arm wrestles the world?s strongest woman to help find out how muscles grow. And the doctors reveal the top five bizarre things your body can do.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p98e68483f61ef6e64531983d60fb2a23</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>In this episode, the focus is on U13s goalie Keanu, who is in remission from leukaemia and back to his best. We also meet 14-year-old midfield dynamo Libby.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc51c937c7a46f3fc15cced1c4e773c36</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>It's time for some spectacular sponging and box-office body rolling.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p92a2cc73c2ef4bed2d1d81645f7d373b</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>It's time for Ricky to spin around the world. Inspired by artist Tom Purvis he creates an art deco travel poster, uses colour swatches to make an Egyptian mummy and art erupts when he shows us how to draw an exploding volcano.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p476f1f3cf96f72766da74c1a1198910e</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A pirate captain regrets stealing a herd of seasick cows, a Georgian sportsman invents a whole new way of boxing, King Charles II raps about his party lifestyle, and the Georgian army goes to war against a bunch of naughty schoolboys.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e5f4295938a4955551888a20c3e6f03</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Zoe from Oxfordshire is mad about science and dreams of becoming a scientist one day. She loves to carry out messy, noisy experiments, but her dad works night shifts, which means she has to be quiet while he sleeps. She desperately wants her own space where she can pursue her passions and make a mess whenever she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1362ca6c17f3b744fcd72eef1ba4224c</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Celebs Viggo Venn and Phil Green come to the aid of Adam and Joe as they try to prove to Callum who is the most talented. With impressions and dad dancing, what?s not to like.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p957c5bfbca86c719e8a1a2eb81ec77ee</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>Ubercorn, Glitch and the Go Jetters all head to the Dwarkadhish Temple in Dwarka, India, for the Holi Festival of Colour. This Hindu celebration involves people throwing a colourful powder called gulal all over one another. Glitch plans to bring a huge flag he and Ubercorn made as cadets for the top of the temple. But after he accidentally washes all the colour out of it, he orders his Grimbots to bring him gulal powder to dye it again. The Grimbots do this rather too well, however, and soon there is no more powder left for the festival! It's up to the Go Jetters to fix Glitch's mistake and save the celebration.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8cca6da0e497682b4e69c245b75f8a6d</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When Cosima wrongly accuses Big Lizard of eating Dad's birthday cake, he vanishes. Has he run away, or is he planning a special surprise to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9275dc7eb988b5bd7c97e75c33b3cb0b</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Dashi survives a crash in the Octoray just as a hurricane nears the Florida Everglades.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p845dcff01c4ab24aed8fe59d0aef0eac</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>Nugget annoys Pancake with constant demands while ill in bed. To say sorry, she makes him a special bracelet. But Nugget is upset when others get ?nuglets? too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p323236925cf9b40bb041418e094dfb68</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Evil Pea asks for flying lessons when Broccoli flies her paper plane into her freezer. Evil Pea doesn?t let Broccoli know that she intends to fly high to take over Tato Tower.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe89aa484de9cf88df1ea213d9694aa28</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Envious at Danger Mouse's ever-growing medal collection, Penfold questions whether he will ever be deemed special enough to receive a prize of his own. Seconds later, a knock at the door reveals a holographic Quark, who anoints Penfold as 'the chosen one' in a suspiciously automated message that culminates in an overawed Penfold receiving his very own magic wand. Penfold's joy is short-lived however - as he and DM step outside of HQ to find that the streets of are London teeming with hundreds of wannabe wizards, all brandishing identical wands. After discovering that the wands are mass-produced shavings from Merlin's legendary staff, the pair set out to stop Quark's latest money-making scheme by reuniting the staff with its rightful owner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p323dc2e8e64fccd5de7990c027816ff5</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Fed up with Dennis pulling the wool over Mrs Creecher's eyes, Walter orchestrates a robot to take over Class 3C - with disastrous results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p09cd14a7c66d70b97a06114b327de9ed</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A bungled attempt at a stunt leads to Dennis accidentally becoming an internet star and Beanotown celebrity! But his moment of fame is short and Dennis is soon replaced by Walter's cat, who can play the piano. Dennis has to stage the best stunt yet to gain back his audience.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2448826bf08a8b69aefa3652e97decf5</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle feels she is being taken for granted by the other heroes, so she joins the Fairy Squad when they arrive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa88b9a6c763d7c35c89b5f246f002e9f</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>With his crew on the verge of a mutiny, a pirate captain and his parrot order a treasure trove to placate them, leading the Ninjas on a trip to the Egyptian pyramids.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ab01993316b04e4743c31d214e9c2da</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Ahead of the Women?s Euros, we visit St George?s Park, the home of England?s national teams, to meet some future stars of the game! Welsh footballer Ella Powell and Euros champion Ella Toone answer your questions, and Joel and Abby go head-to-head in a goalball challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2bac12a256d2d65f269b3bed18e91e58</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>While the Brave Olivine has its computer system rebooted, it?s picnic time for the crew.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p697852332e9fca7096ad064896f1fda5</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>Eggs, sausages, a freezer and toilet roll are among the items getting the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pca10d3e982537144c48ab02c8dd7731c</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>From Henry VIII?s wine fountain, to Empress Dowager?s marble boat, Horrible Histories talks money, jewellery and untold treasures.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p982e883af197d680a1af3659f4e21f14</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Professor von Screwtop gets mistaken for the new kid in school and joins Class 3C for the day. Rubi is so embarrassed at her dad?s antics that she resorts to pranking to get him into trouble and out of the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p060c373a4ae75d174dc60fc03089f42e</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Snowman is hired as Danger Mouse's new sidekick, leaving Penfold without a job.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb9a8b62eb1f051a7a86e10437f9214c</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After the battery dies on her laser shoe, special agent Gloria Hope calls on the Ninjas to help her find a new one and foil criminal mastermind Pam D'Terre.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10d3013b50db1457cc92c2ac34d58fdc</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When the Farmer accidentally drills a hole in a waterpipe while putting up a new shelf, Bitzer frantically tries to stop the leak from soaking the living room and prevent the Farmer?s precious teapots from sliding off the shelf.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d0dd9504a3c0f105eb983ecfaee021d</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a magic stick that functions as a Yummy divining rod.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p16fa51bb776109875ebe265c75d998d8</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy is afraid of being honest in case he hurts other people's feelings and finds himself doing things he doesn?t like just to keep others happy. Mouse and Cheese encourage him to be totally honest, only to find that Boy?s total honesty can be rather blunt. Can the gang rein him in before Boy alienates the entire town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p266389173e1520b4e65cb4c48680fe55</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are on a quest to find the vault containing the Amulet of Answers and protect it at all costs. But the Riddlemaster is back, and he manages to trap them in his castle, tricking Herbert into handing the Amulet of Answers over to him. Now he has all the answers to every question ever asked, and the heroes must find a way to outwit him - even though he knows what they are going to do next.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe25fa88d8b5c74373b8dbfb32088efca</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When an unlucky coin is accidentally released into the public, the agents must retrieve it before the world ends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e794a83b3d2c55eec5e8e9ab3734047</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When a new room opens up in headquarters, all the agents want a piece.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p48d81a5a15782933c7172775a48d0f89</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Izzy wants to play a superhero game but has difficulty persuading her friends to join in.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70d5282f53657d0ee3c0c5e0137de88b</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Simplificator.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2db79bb10b78cc075f41d666ec980654</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs bowl into space with DIY alien skittles, Emma Stothard weaves a wicker dog, and Kiell Smith-Bynoe draws a ghost so spooked, it?s nearly see-through.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe84a9fb444c89c3b7b8033f116add9f6</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Matron arrives with Nancy, her young ward, and Gwen tells her to ask Matron to stay, which annoys Matron. Nancy joins the third formers as they search for the missing time capsule.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p49ad384923660547da1815e89ea7bbfb</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>No longer dance captain, Anthony finds following orders difficult. Jett and Ariana try to be friends again, while Heath?s history with Daisy complicates things with Pascale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfba3f0a5c1730f35b314ede0c813a92f</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Abby and Shini go head-to-head in a powerchair football challenge! Using specially designed powerchairs as part of four-a-side teams, who will come out on top.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe198144b1c57887ed93fb809b7488166</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
