<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Hoofius plays his grandfaun?s old magical panpipes, his friends do exactly what he asks them to do - perfect for leading a quest... or so he thinks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbada50b36a9303ac56775c369e7c2be0</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A Viking Captain summons the Ninjas to find him a steady beat to get his oarsmen moving in time and outrun his rival, Captain Bullyson.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc098a56c9c36f47530d4c941bded98ca</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>The DG residents are excited about the prospect of going camping, so why is Ryan so anxious to sabotage it? Chloe stands by her brother but soon discovers that she and Ryan have quite different ideas about loyalty.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2633573958cd0c6529d346c03805fa09</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>While the rest of the crew goes shopping, Liko ramps up her efforts to befriend Dot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe5cd151d30f4a07810bf8343231d8e1f</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A bunch of bananas, a door handle, a fridge and a tortilla are among the items get the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb38bf8d208dac138f723a8719cab4286</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Rapping science teacher Matt Green becomes the first human being ever to visit Quark when he joins Pipette on her home planet to help host this special episode about Earth and space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc7de445b1ca12b41b36ae36d7c7a831a</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis dresses Gnasher up as a rare breed of animal which he says is nesting in Bash Street School, hoping to get the school shut down on the day of a daunting and difficult test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf1530f2f032cd4d976fda5d61929b327</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse inherits the ancient but sprightly MK3 car after the beloved MK4 gets jammed-up. But Penfold is suspicious when the MK3 is determined to have DM all to himself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paafdc13fd551ca2258f2e20f604f4d55</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas battle a hungry space blob as they try to fulfill an order for a flag for astronaut Lewis Weaklegs to plant on the moon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa72aa11d357947a4eb9393e0f89a1c2e</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When two different pieces of flat-pack furniture are delivered to the Farmer and Bitzer, confusion ensues as they start to mix up the pieces. Shaun and the flock are forced to give them a lesson in following instructions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6faba19999bdaf0067c3c03224597602</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings adopt a cute insect that eats wood. And what's made of wood? The cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pccf019a4a8ccbb39739735ecabb2e164</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids audition for a movie that's shooting in town, and a reluctant Cat lands the role as lead alien. However, Cat would rather just go to the circus.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p796b12621c8125783afd7d121c86b2d5</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Gnome Crystal Mine has ground to a halt, leaving the forest with no crystals, no power supply and melting ice lollies! The heroes are tasked with a quest to find out what has happened and to fix it. It turns out that a slimy beast named Smarg has made the mine her home. But with Hoofius?s fear of gunk getting the better of him, evicting the slippery Smarg is not going to be easy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p858de20cb9333a64f647c54c77975ddd</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Orla shares the story of how she was chosen to protect the 44-leaf clover.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb3abfb7429de3b68c2b57dca2dd5bc7</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>With the Mobile Unit agents in trouble, Oxley and Olanda must come to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9e6c0af516fbd239eed35cfa5e5f3814</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When Owen gets cheated out of a much-wanted ice cream, the kids unite to right the wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0e0faa507faa293dac67782cacaa6f8</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>The heroes team up with a new ally to face Crocoduel.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p17a98b3dbec70d9fe815b34b8a8e94c3</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>Family portraits get personal! The Kwapongs try a clever painting hack, Tom Allen draws a super fancy unicorn, and Maisie Matilda paints a mini masterpiece on the edge of a book.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f120992cce42bd242375db26a42d6ec</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Tracy Beaker Returns</title>
    <desc>Tracy's ability to conquer fear is tested when a storm knocks out the electricity and phone line at the DG, leaving Carmen worried about an escaped prisoner on the loose. Looking after the YP on her own, Tracy gets them telling each other scary stories. Tyler's story frightens Johnny giving everyone a good laugh at Johnny's expense. Meanwhile, Tee sets about solving an old riddle she finds in the junk cupboard, but the solutions only lead to more hidden riddles. After Tracy locks up and everyone is in bed, Liam and Frank find the front door open. Fearing someone has come in, Tracy instigates a search. No-one is found. Later, Carmen thinks she sees a stranger and screams. It is put down to imagination but Gus wakes up to find his room has been disturbed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p76ed4530d92c9876f115195458204379</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Summer receives a letter offering a life-changing opportunity that would ruin Cleo's plans and wrestles with the decision of whether to follow her heart or stick with Cleo. Meanwhile, Winnie tries to convince Nick to use tap in a routine, but an injury forces her to recruit other dancers who don?t share her passion. And Richelle begins to question her own dance future.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcf5b037035d25c0dedd129cf7b365420</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight for the last jar of Yummy with magic Mayan bracelets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3350d31a4a867d7f6c51ff44d720bdd</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>18 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun escapes through a ?portal? inside Shirley?s wool to flee an annoying Bitzer, only to emerge into a chaotic version of the farm without him. Desperate to escape, he repeatedly jumps back inside Shirley, emerging somewhere worse each time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf16b08345a1961859b72812290930739</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Second of two parts. Danger Mouse faces his toughest challenge ever as a mysterious super-villain releases all the villains from Arkwright and plots the end of our hero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe62c1a98a6a993b1b609fda59528d5d</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and Gnasher accidentally do good deeds for the people of Beanotown. Intrigued by the new sensation of being thanked and appreciated, they go on a 'helping rampage', leaving a wake of mayhem behind them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8a5033f5d7b0f34dcc6198f2e6ce3ea</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Lila becomes a sci-fi fan and asks Girl to help keep it a secret. Girl helps by making a costume to help hide her while at the sci-fi convention - what could go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe40c4ac069c93dca01b4bef9c96565fa</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p998c475638c7fdd5dc94b01292e63b79</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy exchanges his indifferent fish with the Lemmings' affectionate and lively fish.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p07e8c90f4bc95e6cc138af9db789ccd7</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings use cans and tins to build a beach slide, which annoys Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8b1c80062ef3eec9f3327c4a586001c4</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Owen and new recruit Ozlyn wait out a storm while transporting a creature. Curriculum: Measurement - Capacity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pffe634bacbb854317f13c699b7c5ac6a</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert is starting to feel his age and secretly drinks from the Fountain of Youth. However, his desire to be young puts the whole quest in jeopardy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ecebebc10b6dd928dcf3e72f8f98353</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve is in the Philippines for more deadly encounters. He goes nose-to-nose with a living dinosaur, meets an arachnid with legs four times longer than its body and has a night-time jungle encounter with a predator who has more armour than Iron Man.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p928f655155129589ce4d33e978ab3a13</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 9-11 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about experimenting with rhythms, ostinato and samba.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde23c20f2c47922990a4e36134780ad9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>Things get surreal in the Art Ninja flat when Gav and Sarah's pets start speaking. There's beastly art with some crazy collage creatures and Ricky's challenged by the ninja apprentices to make something purr-fect from garden wire.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdc3973a87762c62133d404558852bee0</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>We imagine becoming unbreakable by removing our bones, turning our skin to metal and finally by becoming completely elastic, but indestructibility isn't everything we hoped for.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52efa786a6b2092d6f95c9e2b7f61704</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>What would it look like if a lifetime?s tears fell in one massive drop? That?s what Dr Chris and Dr Xand are determined to find out in Don?t Try This at Home! Gladiator Dynamite is back to put Dr Dan and Dr Raph?s lungs to the test in an unusual Body Battle. In Investigation Ouch, Dr Xand makes a poo donation in the name of medical science, and minds are bent by Dr Chris and Dr Xand, who use pictures by the mysterious street artist Xandsy to trick the eyes and brains of passers-by. At the emergency department in Liverpool, Elinor arrives with a knee injury after falling during a hurdles race at her athletics club, and Naveah has accidentally swallowed a 20 pence piece on a visit to the swimming pool.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p990249fe802d7201ec6d3b879b4b1dd2</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Britain's Best Young Artist</title>
    <desc>It?s the portrait round, and three artists must create a portrait of a triplet. But who will impress the judges and go through to the semi-finals.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4f2656eb6e470261bddc4f744bbf8d07</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>From eggs on rollercoasters to chart-topping Christmas crackers - come and see these records for yourself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa0c3087b24c31c5225fc12961816c46a</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>Ricky prepares for take-off, creating a Fortune Flamingo. He demonstrates how to draw a flying dragon and goes foraging in the woods to make a magnificent owl.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p17e04f8f176682e26fdbaca2e02f1e97</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Fred Sirieix stars in Scientific First Dates, Marie Curie reacts to space, and the dinosaurs get an unwelcome musical meteor visitor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2a33358dcb8b4090c89b64ab78a468a</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Joe and Meryl take a look back at some of the fun moments and amazing dens from the series.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80743a2d18e31d09457e1a33a3f7e15d</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>A prickly guest turns up at Joe and Adam?s house and needs a lot of care, but Callum hasn?t made it easy for them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ff62c8636adb7a5a6dd42bc11f1c7fa</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>Glitch's plans to open a hotel on an unspoilt beach in Thailand go horribly wrong when a group of macaque monkeys steal his Grim-o-freeze gun. It doesn't take long for the trouble to spread across Monkey Bay, so the Go Jetters leap into action to help save the beach, its tourists and Glitch himself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2487d795f86e8218d7a1e308c92003a3</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Cosima, Big Lizard and Ammon are squabbling over Dad's precious explorer notebook when disaster strikes. Only by working together can they save it from being lost forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1479bec572292be454fdcc37bf461ecc</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>While rescuing Paani's gear from an icy river, the Octonauts discover a frozen salamander.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69ac7ba09f05b8bede6ab8135d7476e0</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>Nervous about public speaking, Looph builds a robot to deliver a science talk in her place, but her friends are determined to help her do it herself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbe9350728e2af30e3469ac612d64716f</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Evil Pea captures Supertato, but Carrot finally masters the ultimate flip kick and rescues her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94afc2269321f58c0b6807b283bbaceb</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Duckula kidnaps the writers and Danger Mouse faces being written out of his own show! Can DM call on the help of the sound department to fight back before Duckula changes the world forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa49a2f94ca890a1640782da819493ada</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A classmate who Dennis and Walter barely know gets appointed as Class 3C?s late monitor, making it urgent that the boys find a way to pal up with him, whatever it takes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb4a96a66a98d1a34eb95c4f1dbe72396</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis was up most of the night and can barely stay awake. Gnasher and the gang work hard to help steer dozing Dennis through the day, when all he wants to do is continue to dream about battling Zombie-Spiders.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0cde7e1c096f93579aa55afb03c8a28</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Hoofius plays his grandfaun?s old magical panpipes, his friends do exactly what he asks them to do - perfect for leading a quest... or so he thinks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbada50b36a9303ac56775c369e7c2be0</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A Viking Captain summons the Ninjas to find him a steady beat to get his oarsmen moving in time and outrun his rival, Captain Bullyson.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc098a56c9c36f47530d4c941bded98ca</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>The DG residents are excited about the prospect of going camping, so why is Ryan so anxious to sabotage it? Chloe stands by her brother but soon discovers that she and Ryan have quite different ideas about loyalty.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2633573958cd0c6529d346c03805fa09</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>While the rest of the crew goes shopping, Liko ramps up her efforts to befriend Dot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe5cd151d30f4a07810bf8343231d8e1f</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A bunch of bananas, a door handle, a fridge and a tortilla are among the items get the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb38bf8d208dac138f723a8719cab4286</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Rapping science teacher Matt Green becomes the first human being ever to visit Quark when he joins Pipette on her home planet to help host this special episode about Earth and space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc7de445b1ca12b41b36ae36d7c7a831a</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis dresses Gnasher up as a rare breed of animal which he says is nesting in Bash Street School, hoping to get the school shut down on the day of a daunting and difficult test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf1530f2f032cd4d976fda5d61929b327</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse inherits the ancient but sprightly MK3 car after the beloved MK4 gets jammed-up. But Penfold is suspicious when the MK3 is determined to have DM all to himself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paafdc13fd551ca2258f2e20f604f4d55</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas battle a hungry space blob as they try to fulfill an order for a flag for astronaut Lewis Weaklegs to plant on the moon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa72aa11d357947a4eb9393e0f89a1c2e</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When two different pieces of flat-pack furniture are delivered to the Farmer and Bitzer, confusion ensues as they start to mix up the pieces. Shaun and the flock are forced to give them a lesson in following instructions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6faba19999bdaf0067c3c03224597602</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings adopt a cute insect that eats wood. And what's made of wood? The cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pccf019a4a8ccbb39739735ecabb2e164</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids audition for a movie that's shooting in town, and a reluctant Cat lands the role as lead alien. However, Cat would rather just go to the circus.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p796b12621c8125783afd7d121c86b2d5</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Gnome Crystal Mine has ground to a halt, leaving the forest with no crystals, no power supply and melting ice lollies! The heroes are tasked with a quest to find out what has happened and to fix it. It turns out that a slimy beast named Smarg has made the mine her home. But with Hoofius?s fear of gunk getting the better of him, evicting the slippery Smarg is not going to be easy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p858de20cb9333a64f647c54c77975ddd</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Orla shares the story of how she was chosen to protect the 44-leaf clover.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb3abfb7429de3b68c2b57dca2dd5bc7</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>With the Mobile Unit agents in trouble, Oxley and Olanda must come to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9e6c0af516fbd239eed35cfa5e5f3814</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When Owen gets cheated out of a much-wanted ice cream, the kids unite to right the wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0e0faa507faa293dac67782cacaa6f8</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>The heroes team up with a new ally to face Crocoduel.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p17a98b3dbec70d9fe815b34b8a8e94c3</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>Family portraits get personal! The Kwapongs try a clever painting hack, Tom Allen draws a super fancy unicorn, and Maisie Matilda paints a mini masterpiece on the edge of a book.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f120992cce42bd242375db26a42d6ec</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Tracy Beaker Returns</title>
    <desc>Tracy's ability to conquer fear is tested when a storm knocks out the electricity and phone line at the DG, leaving Carmen worried about an escaped prisoner on the loose. Looking after the YP on her own, Tracy gets them telling each other scary stories. Tyler's story frightens Johnny giving everyone a good laugh at Johnny's expense. Meanwhile, Tee sets about solving an old riddle she finds in the junk cupboard, but the solutions only lead to more hidden riddles. After Tracy locks up and everyone is in bed, Liam and Frank find the front door open. Fearing someone has come in, Tracy instigates a search. No-one is found. Later, Carmen thinks she sees a stranger and screams. It is put down to imagination but Gus wakes up to find his room has been disturbed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p76ed4530d92c9876f115195458204379</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Summer receives a letter offering a life-changing opportunity that would ruin Cleo's plans and wrestles with the decision of whether to follow her heart or stick with Cleo. Meanwhile, Winnie tries to convince Nick to use tap in a routine, but an injury forces her to recruit other dancers who don?t share her passion. And Richelle begins to question her own dance future.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcf5b037035d25c0dedd129cf7b365420</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>While playing in Mayan Temple, the Lemmings set off a cosmic phenomenon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pca3bcced1a9c602c5d934b4cffd1db83</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>19 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Despite warnings, the sheep have gobbled up the birthday cake Bitzer has baked for the Farmer. Realising the kitchen cupboards are bare, Shaun and the flock must try and source ingredients for a new one from around the farm before Bitzer realises. The result is certainly a surprise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52cad13186b4964b457432c0b79519b7</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Playtime is over as Danger Mouse battles an army of vengeful soft toys. Pink Dawn's henchman teddy bear Snuggles is on an angry rampage. He is zapping cuddly toys, bringing them to life as rage-filled criminals. He will annihilate anyone who refuses to be his friend. Danger Mouse spots the source of Snuggles's power - Pink Dawn's tiara! When Penfold's beloved teddy, Bernard, rejects his owner to join Snuggles's new gang, Danger Mouse and the distraught Penfold rush to confront Dawn. They are shocked to discover that Dawn has ditched pink in favour of a superpowered goth darkness. Can DM reunite Dawn and Snuggles and put a stop to this rampage? Will Bernard ever return to the ever-loving Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9dfcc413a353c078b8d6f7e592c273fa</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Tricked into a town-wide clean-up, Dennis and Walter are paired up against their will. However, they are forced to cooperate to survive in the wilderness of Beanotown Woods.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3ef773c3acd502b8561d2420b5ac7c83</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Cheese's short stories get published in the local newspaper. The only problem is that the details of the stories were 'borrowed' from her siblings' day-to-day lives.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb225c7967fc940cfdf8206cdd46c8cf</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc999d679b1ade07422e4e12695527fa6</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings turn into crab rescuers, but soon the house is full of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p20c34fe3859cc08a69a508d203bb7b27</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play pirates on a beached boat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6daa38c7457a858d5904930fb10cd1a</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Otis and Olympia stop werewolf Olaf from turning back into a boy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pad08afc73b96e3560d6cab85228c21be</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Much to Trevor?s irritation, a rare phoenix woodpecker takes a liking to him - so he demands an immediate quest to return the bird to its real home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd460f05ee8f6efe98ada93b746aa74d</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve dives in the beautiful waters of the Philippines to check out a shark that spends most of the day 550 metres below the surface. He swims with one of the deadliest snakes on the planet and searches the jungle for a tarsier, a lethal predator who eats his victims head first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p813d5eac674499a98220abe9cc246be9</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 9-11 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about technology and sounds, looping and samples and using music technology.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p573e107d094560665ad556dc6da2df5d</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>Not everything is as it seems, as the Grand Master makes art that colours itself. Ricky makes a silhouette look 3D and two pictures appear as one in an amazing animation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p176e5e670a412da8f6a5a39860a04cca</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Sometimes you want to go surfing, but it's too far to the beach, so we try surfing on land with the help of a volcano and some giant fans.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p39c5e25b15dcfc220f647268d2f1ef5b</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Dr Chris and Dr Xand delve into the Cupboard of Everything and find the Fart Machine 5000, to help them explain why farts can sound so different to each other. Turns out it?s a combination of gas pressure along with sphincter and buttock tightness that determines whether your fart is a trump or a squeak. And on the Fart Machine 5000, those settings are all adjustable, so the doctors get ready to make a bum noise symphony! When the farts have stopped, it?s time to meet some of our new Ouchers, so let us introduce you to Elyana and her hearing dog, Gordon, and Alfie, who likes planes and canoeing. Dr Ronx explains hiccups in Ouch and About. Together with Dr Chris and Dr Xand, Dr Ronx is using only touch to solve a medical mystery in Ouchology, in the hope of avoiding a snotting. At the emergency department in Liverpool, Maya has injured her knee playing rugby. While in Edinburgh, Reuben has pushed a sewing needle right into his finger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf1b8da0a2f2f43545382e8e7a98a6de5</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Britain's Best Young Artist</title>
    <desc>It?s the cartoon round, and three young artists must create a cave-dwelling magical cartoon character. But who will impress the judges and go through to the semi-finals.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc24f766685e5da82f17b2db09e22bd13</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Join in with the biggest bangs and the shiftiest socks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa4150cb9d89ac17a2f82c87e7b8bc94e</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>Ricky creates some legendary ideas, including a gargoyle doorstop and shows how to draw a mythical unicorn. He also constructs a pair of ancient giant dinosaurs out of card at Bristol Museum.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2d49ea51e5c12b7ad3de421a7fc950b</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Revolting space travel, evolving cows, pet mushrooms, and Einstein watches a car on a trampoline.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7998a04b3556c531c826aa1df0c638e1</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Joe and Meryl take a look back at some of the amazing dens from past series and catch up with some of our Dengineers to see how the dens have changed their lives.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc5522b89d4e586b85865eb13e379cd8a</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Adam and Joe break out the superhero costumes for another round of this hilarious competition. But who will Little Bro Callum choose to take a forfeit from the Wheel of Doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fc75d405fb4e972315f29ad22dd4426</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>The Go Jetters are exploring Cheddar Gorge and enjoying its rocky slopes. But Glitch, learning about the town's love of cheese, pays a visit to the gorge in order to share his fondue with the locals. This backfires horribly when he accidentally floods the gorge with the cheesy mixture. It's up to the Go Jetters to rescue the tourists, the sheep and the Grimbots - but will Foz be able to overcome his fear of heights and save a lost lamb.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82b45464c0676a523e34fe7d4873e121</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When a giant beetle steals D.O.R.I.S.'s brain, thinking it's a nut, Cosima and Big Lizard give chase through the forest. Big Lizard uses unique skills to rescue poor D.O.R.I.S.'s superbrain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p492be5463b1d6b2c3e592e63d528999e</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts brave the harsh Himalayan weather on the Terra-Gup-1 to relocate a snake.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa2728ab6626c56fe04b09e91718d7079</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>After a spate of unfortunate accidents, Pancake is convinced that rubbing a lucky icicle will bring him good luck but panics when it?s rubbed away, until his friends step in.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8b8c4805e004cf82b73c768e8ed4babf</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Supertato is delighted when Evil Pea becomes his sidekick, but it?s all a trick, and Evil Pea captures him! Evil Pea is forced to do a good deed because one of the cobs needs help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb29f7478feb7dc74c3b60b59b3357a4e</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. A new shape-shifting agent tests DM and Penfold's partnership to the limit at the criminal world's annual convention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p75d9a248bd183f2d4eccae6a42e93c2e</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Determined to prove he can accomplish a task without getting distracted, Dennis takes on the simple job of bringing the class register to the school office. He instantly distracts himself on an epic scale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb20653e5b67a5132f1ebf7148c402cbf</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Miss Mistry arranges to tag along with Dennis and the gang after school, in an attempt to enhance her teaching skills and prevent school governor Pfooflepfeffer from banning her beloved teaching magazine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7390c9ba105b7ed1875a12a98670c204</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert is starting to feel his age and secretly drinks from the Fountain of Youth. However, his desire to be young puts the whole quest in jeopardy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ecebebc10b6dd928dcf3e72f8f98353</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Two sisters arguing over tidying up their house end up with a bigger problem when the Ninjas deliver two cleaning robots from the future who are planning a robotic rebellion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7db05f3ffc7255bc464cfe0eb0754b3c</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>When Kazima starts behaving strangely, her friends don't understand what's got into her. Then the truth emerges, the Dumping Ground descends into chaos and Kazima's left with a tough decision to make.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe318f5969dd836ee01ff9970a916eb4</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Rattus has enlisted the help of Richie - the Horrible Histories songwriter - to help him present a special song-filled show by making every one of Rattus?s bits a song too! Rattus has even brought a triangle along with him to add some musical flair. Along the way, there is a gross song about boils, a tune about warring brothers and a fabulous footy tune. Queen Victoria takes a break by the ocean, and viewers learn why early police had a 'hard cops? life'. Plus, pay tribute to the NHS, and take a trip to the Tower of London.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1215c0fea4571350671662f2833d9739</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A special guide to working scientifically, whether that involves drinking black vomit, measuring people?s farts, or firing arrows into their bum.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p353c0c51ff7efe9e6d78587b0b2209b1</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis can?t get Grizzly?s new animal training method to work on a wilful Gnasher. However, when they realise that Gnasher can use the method to get humans to obey him instead, they exploit this new power to the max.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p965cb1910091f1f086e689ad9c5309e4</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse arrives in ancient Greece and befriends Zeus who grants him godly powers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pccc67fffbc56a07a3ea6d76b511f35c9</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When an exhausted mother orders a replacement for her daughter's lost cuddly toy, the Ninjas must travel to a seaside fairground and stand up to some delinquent dolphins.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3b5020e9a073546a256fef3123b5f68</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>An all-night gaming session turns the Farmer and Bitzer into sleep-deprived zombies the next day. Shaun takes the chance to change Bitzer?s checklist to suit himself, but he manages to miss the final item: shearing time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3f60727be2d84e2a3113f71146047e4</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play with a baby ostrich that Grizzy found outside.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9b02f3095f1dc487cda4763f743454b5</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Dog is housebound with an injured paw, Mouse links a teddy bear to Dog's mind so that through the teddy, Dog can at least experience the great outdoors virtually.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0047017617f34383caac458a234028f4</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is acting very strangely indeed. He refuses to stamp any of Admin Bunny?s documents, keeps getting distracted by butterflies, and seems oddly happy! The heroes are extremely suspicious and decide that someone must have swapped him with a doppelganger. Now they must quest to find out where the real Friendlyface is and get him back before the forest descends into total chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde2e0b6ed02cd81a52a1b5ae1f9bd3e8</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit heads to Australia to stop The Shadow from causing worldwide oddness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6b3bf94639e8bef2b554573964dd012</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit heads to Australia to stop The Shadow from causing worldwide oddness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9685b1adc8ff4c00b9e6f581d29e8201</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Noah tries to rescue the chocolates Owen forgot outside before something else steals them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe990410924ceb1db2243b7a84a432d8e</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Style Queen is back - but is there a hero to stop her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p874cffad54143b45d67e3989315d77b3</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs take flight with stained-glass wings, Jill Scott MBE draws a footballing big cat, and Bristles gives the juicy lowdown on artist Giuseppe Arcimboldo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3df0fbebb2280bb7ac68e32c6cd4ccac</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Tracy Beaker Returns</title>
    <desc>Liam gets scammed with some pirate DVDs and wrecks the stall where he bought them. Fleeing, he bumps into a woman who thinks he is a mugger. The stallholders leave him to get arrested and Liam is punished with a curfew and an electronic tag - if the alarm goes off three times, Liam will go to a youth offenders' institute. Liam is angry that Mike doesn't believe he is innocent, and Elektra wants her DVD money back. A frustrated Liam tries to saw off his tag and make an escape, but Tracy arrives with a letter from someone called Jack who claims to be Liam's brother. A shell-shocked Liam doesn't want to meet him. Nor does he want Mike to know about the letter. So Tracy and Frank go to meet Jack instead. Meanwhile, Elektra's failure to get her money back from Liam culminates in her moving the entire contents of his bedroom out into the garden - beyond the perimeter of his tag.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9bc26f87094b316402297d1fadbbfbde</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe reels from the news that they have lost their best dancer and turn to a familiar face to replace them. As Emily mulls over her enticing offer, Nick makes a counter offer, making it impossible for Emily to decide. Piper worries that Finn?s chronic lateness may spell trouble for A-Troupe's chances at success.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4899b38505212c7c3421aa55cbded97b</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The thrill-seeking eggs take up bungee jumping, the potato racers whizz around, and Mr Strawberry serenades Mrs Strawberry. Fearless Pete Parsnip comes face to face with a terrifying hairy spider, and Slippery Nana comes a cropper impressing the judges in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9af765987c32160992a5512af85bce81</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When the Farmer accidentally drills a hole in a waterpipe while putting up a new shelf, Bitzer frantically tries to stop the leak from soaking the living room and prevent the Farmer?s precious teapots from sliding off the shelf.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d0dd9504a3c0f105eb983ecfaee021d</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron and Penfold are stranded on a desert island. In the skies above, there is a race to snatch Brunel's All Encompassing Remote Control.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa7b8e966b5c6c306f3a119bdf3118798</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang produce a hand-drawn comic which is a surprise hit all round Beanotown. Envious of their success, Walter embarks on a mission of cartoon-drawing sabotage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a49050e52f6494391bec7f241f68794</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After accidentally destroying Ms Rodriguez's flowers, Girl enlists her siblings to help her cover up the accident.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4615ee002e64bd6c224b1b27c9e288ca</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42e52e2774bb53e8f28db6b2456750d9</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a school of crabs that live in an underwater city.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc70e9e8acaa52af511ac5db7db9185bc</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>It seems an epic battle took place in the cabin, and Grizzy is missing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f4173f642ff3256664f7a4cf0a08f74</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Otis struggles with his new high-tech agent?s jacket.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9878b8435735e7a646f5da8225e6c791</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes and the Council of Happiness swap jobs, and when the council fail in their quest, the whole forest is at risk of being flooded by Stinkystuff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a544a2a926fb3c68c7a21626bc95543</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve takes a close look at dogs and their distant relatives, wolves. He heads to the Arctic Circle where a pack of huskies show him a thing or two about stamina. Steve is then rescued by an avalanche dog whose incredible nose sniffs him out from deep beneath the snow. Finally he comes face-to-face with one of his favourite animals, the wolf.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0e6c0fa20561c48a287cf9808f47cd6b</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 9-11 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about early music, making a timeline and music between 1750 and the 20th century.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0d7426275d4bd23ed516f348c0513d74</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>Gav's keeping guard as Ricky gets gifts from a mystery superfan. Meanwhile Ricky makes an expensive-looking selfie and the Grand Master makes a magic wallet that will blow your mind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p340dfe09286c0040280f3ba446bccb1f</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>We try out a crazy idea from science fiction to build a giant sphere around the sun and give us more energy than we'll ever need.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fa6e608ce7a4190b2cdc85bda0cf367</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>You?re making bogies in your nose all the time. To show this, Dr Xand uses the Ouchcam to give us an exclusive close-up of one of his freshly picked beauties, before he and Dr Chris use a supersized nose to make gloopy snot into something more crusty. We?ve got a Top 5 countdown of the Longest Longy Long Things Ever, including the mind-blowingly long, longest-ever burp. Gladiator Dynamite is back making sure Dr Dan and Dr Raph play by the rules as they go toe-to-toe in a body battle ? it?s all fun and games until the loser has to get into the ice bath! We get a chance to follow Dr Ronx through the whole of their hospital shift in Doctors on Duty. Emilia has cut her lip at school and goes to the emergency department in Liverpool, and Jake is in hospital in Edinburgh after injuring his neck when a pal picked him up and accidentally dropped him on his head.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe812a9e18f268a5aa8b7b0ce8266c308</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Britain's Best Young Artist</title>
    <desc>It?s the first of the semi-finals, and three artists must create a piece of art for Lindsey Russell. But who will impress the judges and go through to the Grand Final.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfa4049b038dc6434220fc46548b7d232</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Strap in tight as we see some ludicrously good leaping and fearless free-falling.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7b520f28f68bb72a86219acc64e4b753</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>Ricky is inspired to make art using wool. He creates a bogie-faced knitting kit and a woolly dancer on acetate to brighten up his window.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1f231ebef40a8153a20e495b9768129e</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>The Real Mutants assemble, people are drinking vomit and electrocuting themselves for science, and the earth and moon have an earworm about the solar system.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdad153ab81fb68e8962c09f25134220e</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Joe and Meryl take a look back at some of the amazing dens from past series and catch up with some of our Dengineers to see how the dens have changed their lives.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6c9bc6b8708818fbb42065e4ae7a9f1</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum sends his Sharky mate to Joe and Adam?s house with a request to paint his portrait. But can the boys do it wearing glasses that make everything topsy turvy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbf538936f317ca7795bc522641e33f5</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>When a cold-ridden Glitch's sneezing breaks his TV, the Grimbots take him to the Virunga National Park in the Democratic Republic of the Congo to see a real mountain gorilla. But Glitch doesn't realise how dangerous his cold germs can be, so the Go Jetters will have to stop him from making a baby gorilla sick - all while trying to keep it safe from dangerous traps left by hunters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03df12006ac84f651faa14b420e991cf</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Cosima and Big Lizard have a camping sleepover with a friendly little crab. In the morning, their new friend is missing, but why.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa3d7ad903dbff81c078d54acee3f8857</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts help pupfish in the Nevada Desert when their aquatic home is in trouble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p05c179ef657e3efc40156547a16248ea</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>When Nugget?s favourite teddy bear gets accidentally washed by Pancake, the Piripenguins try to restore its unique smell by painstakingly recreating Nugget?s happiest memories.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p30ae0fd844e5202704904752c1b009e9</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Supertato and Evil Pea get stuck inside a giant bubble together. They float through the air until Supertato and Evil Pea pop the bubble by driving it into a supermarket sign.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf3052b5b014c916f5f9d533f041775f5</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Penfold's chances of winning a Sidekickie award are in peril when Stiletto attempts to snatch the prize. Greenback plots to destroy the world with termites, and DM gets overly enthusiastic.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5dac06606cd79dcc8c7ef381fc1e28a0</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s Pieface?s turn to look after the class hamster, Space Captain Harrison McScruff-Butt. His own self doubt and Walter?s resolve to sabotage him lead to a rescue mission to free Scruff-Butt from Walter?s mansion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p030b103e478730d5108a53c51e2b4099</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang convince Mrs Creecher that Monday is actually Sunday in the hope of extending their weekend.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9b0399bee9f8bf2e99c10b04c972e7fe</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Much to Trevor?s irritation, a rare phoenix woodpecker takes a liking to him - so he demands an immediate quest to return the bird to its real home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd460f05ee8f6efe98ada93b746aa74d</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A fairy-tale princess being pestered by an annoying prince orders a new dragon from the Ninjas, who return with the most ferocious monster of them all - a T-Rex.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70302567796da86615c59a39a8a223b9</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Things start disappearing on Carmen and Tee's last day at the Dumping Ground. Some of the residents decide to track down the thief - but they're not the ones who catch them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p86f9926235d19012b5e308712ee533bd</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Featuring a new sketch with Elizabeth I searching for a successor in her show England?s Got Monarchs, and Rattus is the guide through some of HH's most regal sketches.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p814259309fafad92fb9d172280992dc9</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A weird and wonderful look at how gravity, magnetism and friction impact everything. With Fred Sirieix.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94fd45c10fe71cfd50c37b15a03b378a</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse is left gadgetless when an unappreciated Squawk leaves the Danger Agency to work for tech genius Elon Muskrat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p30bdd1caee31eaf2db44d36613261332</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Desperate to prove he is still needed, Mega Powerful Man asks the Ninjas to find him a worthy villain to battle against.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p616e4c01756f32c11215949abe04f2ce</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Bitzer is horrified when the Farmer scribbles all over his map showing the location of his buried bone, fearing he will never rediscover his treasure. The flock are on hand to help him search, even if their methods are unorthodox.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde8c349f04c3c64ef16ec18f49455bce</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings are throwing a big birthday party, but Grizzy is not in the mood.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3db4fa9889189f0cc9220e9804405d6</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The gang is ready to celebrate Narwhal Day, one of their favourite holidays. However, they discover that it isn't a real holiday, just something Dad made up.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe286fc92135ff18ad00220a3098be4b8</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is particularly tetchy this morning. He is packing for a skiing trip, but a dragon has pinched his golden fleece, and he urgently needs the heroes to quest it back ? how else will he stay warm and cosy on the slopes? However, when the heroes accidentally agree to let his niece Trixie tag along with them, they fear that her clumsiness and lack of hero skills will ruin everything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c3ff87984db3abc93407af293a6fe99</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit must bring a villain to The Big O?s safe house.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p502bc9755c6146dac5bacc1d162eb9d4</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Courtney must go all day without correcting her friends, regardless of what they do wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe12d009fb4b08949cdf975f6bbb47a8</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>We head to Trentham Monkey Forest to hang out with hundreds of free-roaming Barbary macaques! Joel is challenged to become a guide, Abby checks the primates are all present and correct with a monkey register, and Shini discovers the importance of poo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65b592849763de3d4cdabe033c01ccba</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Diamond prank Comet at a fake Christmas calendar photoshoot. The other Gladiators have sneaky fun pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5cd8bf081d5ab1bc368bae668e80dd2d</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs build 'Kwembley', their DIY table football pitch, Mandy Barker wows turning plastic waste into art, and comedian Aisling Bea draws a puffin with a potato waffle problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1500fcc3c13870d2b9e03edb99166eb0</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Tracy Beaker Returns</title>
    <desc>Drama set in a children's home. Tracy gets tangled up in Lily's plan to reunite Poppy and Rosie with their dad. Meanwhile a stray dog becomes attached to Frank.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p267c04dfc0959a5e3327529974868429</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>After staying up all night to prep, Finn makes a major misstep and Emily is left scrambling to fix it. A-Troupe lets off some steam the night before their performance, but their fun is cut short when they discover their former teammate at their door. Discouraged about Summer?s decision, Cleo abandons her plans and it?s up to Jude to remind her what made them special in the first place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32e04c7fc3dfd49dd481b5389c1a16ab</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy decides to teach the Lemmings how to behave in his presence.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p913be4806ad3e2c1689fd5eb48cd770b</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun steps in a can of red paint, and his resulting red hoof makes him a style icon on the farm. Before long, the rest of the flock try their own new looks and soon steal the limelight. As the outfits become more and more outrageous, Shaun wonders if less might sometimes be more.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5311608370a06605a09997e8b42e43c8</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Shortly after Danger Mouse's biggest fan comes to visit, members of the team start to disappear.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p802a8ae5995df356a97d1d477738819a</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>There?s a new tripe hound in Beanotown, and Gnasher falls head over paws in love with her. Bertie is looking after the visiting dog, Ginger, and is determined to keep her away from riff-raff like Gnasher.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c6935906c9fad8f02b717eec4e4caaa</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Cheese tells Boy he has been the victim of a weredog staredown, he becomes convinced he will turn into a weredog too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6cc7f43074fc2f3ea13127028d4a1f88</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0fb10fb4f3eb2fd16b22f5cfb3585420</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Two sisters arguing over tidying up their house end up with a bigger problem when the Ninjas deliver two cleaning robots from the future who are planning a robotic rebellion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7db05f3ffc7255bc464cfe0eb0754b3c</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Delivery Debbie goes undercover to stop a group of villains.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5e6cdbd8326e2e1c8699847e0481dc4f</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>It?s been ages since their last quest, and the heroes are losing their edge, so Mr Friendlyface invents a strange and terrible monster that he says is stomping through the forest causing havoc, and sends the heroes on a fake quest to get rid of it. Friendlyface soon comes to regret his trickery when, with the heroes out of the way, the goblins decide to take over the forest for their jam jamboree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd73f5a342e51bd6aa4e1226b5b388fb</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face an invisible enemy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa159bd9b067167936a1a52cfe1fdcccb</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug faces Argos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbd13e45abeae99a94910d22d293936f0</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: XY</title>
    <desc>Clemont revisits his school days and meets up with a couple of old friends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p354cd653808c35f4439f945b092ace9f</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>It seems an epic battle took place in the cabin, and Grizzy is missing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f4173f642ff3256664f7a4cf0a08f74</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy wants to watch TV, but the Lemmings want to have fun playing music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb81dcd41f9b8627f90482e8dfa7df1a</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A rocket carries the cabin into space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c78219ad43711cd65fcc2202b9c6992</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse wants the other kids to stop being lazy and achieve some goals - in the form of breaking world records. With Mouse's relentless coaching, the family soon gets carried away. Can Mouse get things back to normal before anyone gets hurt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p952612adea8a4c9c25efe350e0b666cf</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When one of Mouse?s inventions accidentally sticks Cat?s discarded fur to Boy?s face, his new 'beard' suddenly makes him the most popular kid in school! Seeing her chance to stop her enemy Lila Bird from becoming class president, Girl convinces Boy to run for president too. It looks like Boy might win, until another accident causes Cat?s whole body to get stuck to his face. Can he win the election with such a strange new beard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p914a4dbe62695432e7ae7da249569069</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The Girls and the Boys compete to get to the top of Bear Mountain, using very different styles of camping. But when the legendary bear appears, they have to team up to survive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb67492964d5542c23a8c00dc0f1fb470</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan and Leshawna try to take advantage of Izzy's love for the game of Simon Says.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6aaf405756a724290c20cdc97d40c5e9</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:45AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef tries to trick the kids into making his mother gifts after he forgets Mother's Day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb83be820d725d3dca24249aa7e59fa8</image>
    <start>10:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Adam and Joe are joined by their dogs to help them in the kitchen! What could go wrong? The fluffy sous chefs get to work on baking Callum?s dog Bailey a doggy treat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67c4553efcdb7e3501f85dfc88999f22</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Attempting to shake things up in the school, Andy introduces Swapsies Day. However, when Emerald calls asking for a song to be recorded that day, Andy?s idea backfires dramatically.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p66b08333c40ad36d74888b14f94f2706</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>We head to Trentham Monkey Forest to hang out with hundreds of free-roaming Barbary macaques! Joel is challenged to become a guide, Abby checks the primates are all present and correct with a monkey register, and Shini discovers the importance of poo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65b592849763de3d4cdabe033c01ccba</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Orli has rescued a clam which needs to be returned to its home in the 60th dimension via a portal on the 60th floor. However, to get there, she must negotiate HQ?s odd lift network.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11c6ba8b45b8289f8bd5234f041ac147</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Opie leads her first public tour through HQ, but when Orwell discovers one member of the tour group is a villain, they must work out who it is before it?s too late.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d059ee6a76702046cbe248518e43706</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Spooky Files</title>
    <desc>A Spooky with a hypnotic dance runs amok at a school excursion ? can the Crew pull themselves together to retrieve the Spooky Files before they fall into the wrong hands.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p97ebfdff08824e140b2d8bb7b39beed0</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Spooky Files</title>
    <desc>Billie and Bert?s baby sibling is due, just as an angry baby Spooky turns everyone into tantrum-throwing toddlers. Can Bert stop avoiding responsibility and take control.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p530e2e6c0d1766963219558566f1fbd4</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Featuring a female dinosaur expert who sells seashells down on the seashore, Brian the handsome scientist reveals the weird wonders of the Greek Universe, TV's fastest-talking pensioner, Bob Hale, tries to explain the Space Race between the USA and the USSR, and there's a fitting musical finale to the end of the series.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65fa5a38288cbf044b6f619202d13eba</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>An episode featuring everything from the creation of the number zero to the beginnings of the whole universe. The moon gets lonely, there's an ISS cookery competition, and DI Loofah arrests a banana.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd676881cb9166a7245a8568e8887284c</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>The Vipers are not getting along, so Aoife blags them onto a team-building weekend. The only thing is that it?s at school, military style and with the boys - what could go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p15dc335e196d0bebf4629f17a317b53c</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Erin sticks to her injury rehab, but Alex gets increasingly frustrated at not being allowed to play football. A chance encounter makes him decide to take matters into his own hands.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd0da99de76a4d87f740cc4a9d8023553</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen believes he has turned Harold into a housefly using a wand he found in the sandpit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pec10d8ea3bb50d987394b2db81bb865c</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan sees an opportunity for a break from daycare when an angry skunk hunts down Chef.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p369231ecc447b57e864ac5d90b077f18</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen has his superball confiscated, so the gang set off to retrieve it from Chef?s office.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p73436548f2765fadaa07495786f981bd</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse must fight his own urge to be awesome to stop the world turning into a gigantic intergalactic tourist attraction. Attempting to prove his theory that what the world always needs is a hero, Danger Mouse fights off what appears to be an alien invasion of Earth - but his inflated ego soon becomes the real intergalactic threat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d43d2ca6490ff7c844b2a28644f5408</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Our dynamic duo take on a shoddy army of knock-offs when alien Quark's latest money-making scheme is to create cheap copies of Danger Mouse and Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc3534acab020f64bb5ca220b64ae15c1</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse is responsible for Professor Squawkencluck losing her job his clumsy attempts to get her back help the Baron steal half the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3bb8928291651f97c9f27761acb6a515</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Cat decides that she wants to become a superhero, and the other kids decide to help her follow her dream. Girl makes her a cool costume and Mouse creates some superhero gadgets, now all Cat has to do is find somebody to save.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcd18456db7fd3391240cf9c7ebdda66f</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids accidentally destroy a beloved family photo and decide to make it up to Mom and Dad by hiring a photographer to take a new one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea9981e258355c4b97ba8632e168fa2c</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mum and Dad take the TV away until the kids learn to behave, and the siblings realise they need some rules. Mouse is the judge and decides how to settle family arguments, putting wrongdoers into a homemade jail. However, when Mouse also behaves badly, he puts himself in jail, and the family realise they are all locked in.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5af69310c8cbf603b3cf4dfefd47c1df</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings are throwing a big birthday party, but Grizzy is not in the mood.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3db4fa9889189f0cc9220e9804405d6</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a jewel that gives them total control over the fireflies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p441f9d3dc8cbcbd950cad86aa8c0bc2f</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings' magic keyring has the incredible power to miniaturise any object.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb27dcfd8726d57770d12974b12ca129c</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert takes his failed cooling hat invention along on a quest, using it to save the day after being faced with the Riddlemaster?s jibes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa71b4703dab60fe05f881ddc78ac43d6</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom draws the short cheese straw and, rather than join her friends on a picnic, she has to take a magic wand to the recycling centre. Faced with a long queue and a rumbly tummy, Blossom decides that life is too short for recycling - with disastrous consequences. The heroes must skip their picnic and go on a quest to save the forest from the magical mess Blossom has gotten them into.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38db6a019d90d683a5c507a27c6477df</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When a witch struggles to master her new wand, Twinkle decides to have a go, only to make her friends vanish. She must now go on a solo quest to find them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f70c51f662eb1e9f7b58d6b81511ec0</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Mansour stops Blink from causing a disaster at the science competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa45e4169977b912a2ccc11bc62edfc0a</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:05PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>When Blink spoils Sargon's Palace, Mansour creates another version to trap him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p18b12934e61cecbc7a510c0c334f40f9</image>
    <start>06:05PM</start>
    <finish>06:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>It?s just a normal game of capture the flag, except the flag is a skull, and the opponents are armed with fire hoses, toilet plunger harpoons and giant rolling boulders.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd793d0a5c9a1738fb36da664f0fffe84</image>
    <start>06:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Apollo prank Dynamite, turning her into a singing banana! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99a45e9399b5fa5991e3b3eb060bfd42</image>
    <start>06:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>22 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The Farmer tasks Bitzer with baling up a fresh haystack, but the hungry sheep have hidden inside and are turned into moving bales. A wild game of chase the bale results as Bitzer tries to restore order to the hay field.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4444e15b78e6d89ea5864146f236628b</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The heroes find themselves fighting for their lives on an alien world in Quark's latest money-spinning sports event.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a349849bdee1e607399cc7c77be8b24</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>An order mix-up leads to a delivery of hyperactive tentacles at Bash Street School. However, no-one wants the job of looking after the pesky things, and attempts to duck out of the tentacle-care duties lead to chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd04f790a2a06b0b64f43ec40406c119c</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Everyone is excited for the annual camping trip with Gramps, but when Cheese wins an invitation to a big movie premiere, she lies and says she has to stay home for charity work.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa9f68c8c20c4d3ca7eb8e7eaaa3c57ec</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd38ed0e315de01b04e4e441e5a4deed</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A fairy-tale princess being pestered by an annoying prince orders a new dragon from the Ninjas, who return with the most ferocious monster of them all - a T-Rex.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70302567796da86615c59a39a8a223b9</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When Olympia finds out Dr O is leaving, she struggles to throw the best goodbye party ever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9e2f9677922d0435de76741d1f949392</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Matagi-Gozen.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pec4db67c7cd2d11508b88677936d017d</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings search for a treasure to get food from a Yummy vending machine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb531860e4f8bc74791e6847b3f6060c</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>We head to Trentham Monkey Forest to hang out with hundreds of free-roaming Barbary macaques! Joel is challenged to become a guide, Abby checks the primates are all present and correct with a monkey register, and Shini discovers the importance of poo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65b592849763de3d4cdabe033c01ccba</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs make a bug jungle, Chris Howarth makes sand art waves, and Rob Biddulph shows how to draw a furry monster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p37672a63f7ec87e89f34fc36ae95bc34</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>4 O'Clock Club</title>
    <desc>Bell is booked at a magic conference ? but the real trick is how to sneak out without Mrs Morgan knowing. Meanwhile Nunn finds himself in a running battle with Isaac?s pet goat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a7672a7d5aa08efa98b8b7f15fcf83c</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It's staff charity cabaret night at the Pottsfield Leisure Centre and special guest and ventriloquist Paul Zerdin is performing. When his sidekick Sam goes missing. Danny and Mick have to step up to perform their own ventriloquist act.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7994c29c48222559183f36600d7e659f</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Clive has forgotten to book an audience for wrestling night and two of the wrestlers have pulled out. That means only one thing - it's time for Danny and Mick to showcase their wrestling skills.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6269e5f35f7cf9431216f1f7634dd66d</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Attempting to become young again, Whiff accidentally turns the Odd Socks into babies! With Whiff as their babysitter, how will the baby-faced band do an interview and play a gig.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd14a034b0e534d441e226129c8a7bd4c</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>After Moxy?s drums go missing, Andy concludes it was their rival band, Sandy and the Same Socks! Getting paranoid, a chase ensues as Andy accuses them of stealing everything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb25b473cf84269836f676090139fbcec</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Wildlife presenter Steve Backshall is in India on the search for the biggest of all the big cats, the truly awesome tiger. With limited time in which to find such a rare and endangered animal, the Deadly 60 team are taking a huge risk. Steve needs the help of the locals, but who can help him sniff out these elusive felines? Enter the elephants. After several days of searching, the crew eventually get a sighting and the cameraman has a much closer encounter than anyone expected. Steve also comes face to face with another animal that is on the endangered list, the gharial crocodile. With its long snout and bulbous nose, it has to be one of the strangest crocodiles in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8da6de940685664d489a426b73df9fa</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall abseils into the darkness of the incredible Gomantong cave system. Here, he encounters thousands of cockroaches and one of the scariest creepy-crawlies to go on the Deadly 60 list, the scutigera centipede. Thousands of wrinkle-lipped bats call this cave their home. In order to show how amazing they are, Steve hangs like a bat from the cave ceiling. It is a truly awesome sight as the bats leave the cave in their thousands to hunt for bugs in the night sky. Steve also scours the waterways of the Borneo jungle for a reticulated python, and the team get munched on by tiger leeches. Not an episode for the faint-hearted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p230a73cef02d4273d43299c02ff0c4da</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Gladiator Dynamite keeps the peace as doctors Dan and Raph work their chests. Meanwhile, Dr Chris and Dr Xand find out why blood tastes like metal.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1eb027d79e58622d9cfde3f6b4aa512</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Britain's greatest sailor, Admiral Nelson, turns out to be horribly seasick, and two doctors from the Middle Ages argue over how to treat a patient. Plus, discover the many uses for an Incan llama, and the World War Two Girls sing about girl power on the Home Front.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p183c52c86f4ce6bcb7a4de76b7e0a5b9</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>An Incan kid has the worst birthday ever, a Roman farmer meets a door-to-door poo salesman, and King George IV embarks on a solo musical career.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa2c1304b7416a9da50aaf00217adcfef</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Apollo again - this time he thinks he is filming for a Gladiator video game set in ancient Greece. And the other Gladiators have sneaky fun backstage at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6d9da00ac22d5e0a9d007d2346ce8512</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse and Penfold are sent on a rescue mission to a mysterious island, Danger Mouse's over-competitiveness borders on criminal.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94611482810f95a6584eec90dad349c5</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse's uncontrollable laughter annoys a race of clown aliens so much that they invade Earth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p71ad5c62d44a3d366830c3351b73c1ce</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse and the Baron are forced to team up in order to defeat a cheese-obsessed villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc640fda27059d028e627a20d12c99338</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Tricked into a town-wide clean-up, Dennis and Walter are paired up against their will. However, they are forced to cooperate to survive in the wilderness of Beanotown Woods.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3ef773c3acd502b8561d2420b5ac7c83</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang produce a hand-drawn comic which is a surprise hit all round Beanotown. Envious of their success, Walter embarks on a mission of cartoon-drawing sabotage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a49050e52f6494391bec7f241f68794</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Deep in the caverns below Beanotown town hall, a mysterious species of over-sized hamsters may or may not exist, so may or may not be at risk of being hunted down and turned into fluffy slippers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbd0702cc5afebf8a17005c88036a955a</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Trevor is extremely proud of being the clever one in the gang and thinks that his smart mouth is his superpower. However, his friends feel that sometimes his jokes go too far - and they are right to be concerned! When Mr Friendlyface sends the heroes on a quest to prevent Toothgrinder the Ogre from messing up the village green, it?s Trevor?s smart mouth that puts all the heroes in danger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc10a55045431109408268b6cc99aaf5</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are questing to find out who is behind a string of cake thefts, and go into detective mode. After questioning the baker, they decide to stage a stakeout at the bakery. However, when they spy cakes apparently walking off by themselves, they realise that there is more to this mystery than meets the eye - and a quest to find some missing cakes soon turns into a quest to save the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5645751379a5d59cdd33d1d6bc3124d3</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert receives a bottle of Goldenbeard to make his beard longer, stronger and more golden than ever ? and the results are dramatic! Everyone is talking about Herbert Goldenbeard, the great hero and quester, and Herbert is loving the attention. However, when he is kidnapped by the goblins and needs his friends to rescue him, Herbert soon realises that they are much more important than any golden beard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p86555ecedfb25de25cc47ca98336e9a0</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings transform the ice field into an open-air discotheque.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f06f9cbceff3fdffb587982bedc67b7</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings come up with a ride worthy of a county fair in the living room.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc5ca0446f5b7a01f0879450c3aac0187</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings perform acrobatic high jumps, competing for the winning prize.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbceb34cff7926fc79529e5fea7f726cf</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A penguin decides to help Grizzy catch piles of fish, and the pair strike up a friendship.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p782529c432d87dbd62b376749b3264f4</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Seeking a source of heat, Grizzy moves into a greenhouse - but the Lemmings are coming too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf78e2d3fe779b52026926ad622ed6751</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>A miscalculation by Tom has left the fate of the Realms in jeopardy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p409f01ea66d21c9a82a7ca249310945b</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>X-Key are gearing up for their TV appearance, unaware of the traitor in their midst, and, after a shocking revelation, Astra must do everything they can to pull off the impossible.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0ec84c76f3c30275a965add2f7f1b6ae</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Emily finds a staggering fact that could spell the end of A-troupe's chances at nationals and the end of one dancer's spot on the team. Fearful of jeopardizing her friendship with Amy, Piper attempts to keep her feelings secret, but Finn uncovers what she has been trying to hide. Meanwhile, Henry learns a hard lesson about honesty after he reveals his true feelings about Kingston's latest news.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7cd07e5c4eb7b98d64df80f20b38cf04</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>Having found fame around the world as a young child, talented teen drummer Nandi Bushell sets out on a new musical path.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p72a61a393180e6e77e7017d8203cad5a</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Coming to England</title>
    <desc>A story of a Windrush generation girl who came to Britain in 1960 from the Caribbean. Adapted from the book Coming to England, which was written for children everywhere.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf4b17b8946d65884795d1d280e6f54f7</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun tricks Bitzer into thinking he is unwell so that he can stay in the barn playing video games all day. However, before long, the other sheep are also pulling sickies, and Bitzer is starting to get suspicious. The threat of nasty medicine has everyone out of bed in a flash.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p859bcc0ba6d00ac73d3e8310a33597fe</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Colonel K disappears on a free holiday, Danger Mouse pulls rank and assumes the mantle of caretaker colonel. However, the role is much less exciting than he anticipated, as world-saving missions make way for endless paperwork. Meanwhile, K's freebie spa retreat happens to be a diversion tactic in Greenback's latest plot to take over the world, with the baron banking on the Danger Agency falling apart without its figurehead and the world descending into disarray.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paef6868cdecdac98504d06f4fc8a956a</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Deep in the caverns below Beanotown town hall, a mysterious species of over-sized hamsters may or may not exist, so may or may not be at risk of being hunted down and turned into fluffy slippers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbd0702cc5afebf8a17005c88036a955a</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>It's time for the First Day of Summer Festival, and Cheese is ready to perform for the whole town. However, she is so excited that she refuses to listen to warnings about an imminent heatwave.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e34d62f8fd44838aa3d1c6a0cc6dc1e</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d4750c0d50a5563dca546f1ad72cf31</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy struggles to pick coconuts, but the Lemmings find a magic conch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe790119cb595cbdc802925b6696f6fe0</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy wants to watch TV, but the Lemmings want to have fun playing music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb81dcd41f9b8627f90482e8dfa7df1a</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Odd Squad builds an exact replica of the villain?s vault to intercept a jetpack.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p49fb3592e61265209a5d9d350dd16e70</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are made to clean the Cave of Mirrors as punishment for frolicking before a quest is complete, and they accidentally release the Party Harpy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf80b921c507ca0e99023f7222f1a27bf</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve and his trusty team head to the frozen north of Norway. He follows the tracks of Europe's largest cat, the elusive lynx, up into the hills in the hope of seeing one, and gets a little nervous when he meets some in captivity. Arctic foxes and musk oxen are also on the menu in this deadly snowy episode.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4306a970f4cb7d43e2af9b54350eba00</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 9-11 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about traditional Japanese, North Indian classical and traditional Malian music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe4a54f71391c7bffdb4d160eeadd39a1</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ricky Wilson's Art Jam</title>
    <desc>Vlogger and Strictly star Joe Sugg visits the Art Jam studio to show Ricky three items that mean the world to him - a sketch pad full of his own incredible drawings, a model campervan and a homemade clay monster. While chatting to Ricky, Joe shares amazing stories about his online career, a lifelong love of art and childhood memories of growing up in the countryside with sister Zoe - aka Zoella.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5439050fba3a1b9d914ea92abf8f130f</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors test how strong stomach acid really is, and will it be Dr Chris, Dr Xand or Dr Ronx who gets snotted in Ouchology.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9171da2f98f621006e40a25a80861581</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Britain's Best Young Artist</title>
    <desc>It?s the second of the semi-finals, and three artists must create a piece of art for Dr Alex George. But who will impress the judges and go through to the Grand Final.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p20531ba2b47cb2dcf119c1d8a4420e20</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Brace yourself for high-wire walking and high-calibre hooping.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa024d9ff4adb2ca10c574ab4a12f82d9</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>Ricky explores a world of colour, making paint from flour. the Grand Master gets in a spin with a colour wheel and the gang use mops to paint a gigantic upside-down picture.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf452a5ec7b6b0c2f7131bdb5d32104ab</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Big Brain has a chemical catastrophe, Sir Isaac Newton rides a coaster again, with shocking results, Loofah is after a murderer, and Dr Henry VIII on call.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peee6d9a3675c97b17d21716f58b7d6ed</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Ballroom dancer Harry from Dudley is a huge fan of Strictly Come Dancing and wants a den full of glitz and glamour to help him celebrate his favourite TV show, practise his dance moves and store his trophies! Packed with sequins, sparkles and stunning celebrity surprises, this episode has more ups and downs than a Strictly show dance - but will the den score a ten with Harry.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe77cb54769d93c2714a8bdaad6ca5990</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Little Bro Callum sets Adam and Joe another epic quest: become a king, build the best cardboard castle, and defend your kingdom against the destructive dragon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p378c2ff8e857aa5d5929292f3eeac3c4</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>With the help of his hero Ron Allum, Lars plans to dive to the bottom of the Mariana Trench in a submersible called the Deep Sea Challenger. Glitch plans to beat him there by sending a Grimbot in his Grimsub, but it can't withstand the heavy pressure of the water. Lars and Xuli must work together to mount a rescue operation at the bottom of the sea.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc09ec0161094a7a96275e0e453d2269e</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Cosima is so excited to tell Big Lizard about her life on earth that she doesn't realise he has something exciting to say to her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94f580d3fd1efc6e09a4dbb9cae92256</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Dashi and Koshi look for a mystery crab before a flash flood hits the Australian outback.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0cb63b4b8865de57e4f470830c44f767</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>The Piripenguins vow to change shopping-mad Brinicle?s wasteful ways. But when their clever recycling plan proves too exhausting, Looph comes up with an alternative solution.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8704829cf218d23922ba1cfc7808c80</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Evil Pea tricks Supertato into believing that he has no superpowers without his red cape. When he rescues his friends without it, he discovers that he has superpowers - cape or no cape.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p909fb20ad00bbd2eac4ff3daca31868b</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. DM and Penfold go back to school to thwart the plans of an evil food scientist and his killer hot dogs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb21a92b26ce148448dc51ad882cf481e</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis can?t get Grizzly?s new animal training method to work on a wilful Gnasher. However, when they realise that Gnasher can use the method to get humans to obey him instead, they exploit this new power to the max.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p965cb1910091f1f086e689ad9c5309e4</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis is mega-excited to trial a pair of hi-tech Smarty Pants - underpants with all the capabilities of a smartphone. However, whenever he and the gang test the pants, Walter is always one step ahead of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa879352069255fc7bf2e01b1a28abf51</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes and the Council of Happiness swap jobs, and when the council fail in their quest, the whole forest is at risk of being flooded by Stinkystuff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a544a2a926fb3c68c7a21626bc95543</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Desperate to learn magic, Merlin's apprentice, Merlina, orders a magic wand. However, mayhem ensues when the inexperienced wizard transforms everyone around her including the Ninjas.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0af67c14a68062ce733ef922bb35e15c</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Jody finds out that following your heart can lead to danger - will her friends be able to save her? Meanwhile, Ryan confesses his darkest secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9de9018a878d7dbc23ffbb70ef013c1c</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Back in Paldea, the time has come for Liko to part ways with the Rising Volt Tacklers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9240cdb036117f9ada27c2fbb87fd1c5</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories charts the contribution of Black people to British life throughout history. How did African soldiers come to be guarding Hadrian?s Wall? Why was a West African diver asked to help salvage Henry VIII's ship, the Mary Rose? And the actor Ira Aldridge tells us how he came to leave New York to find fame in 19th-century England.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p441abcab60b2d1eba0176e49cc05c430</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang produce a hand-drawn comic which is a surprise hit all round Beanotown. Envious of their success, Walter embarks on a mission of cartoon-drawing sabotage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a49050e52f6494391bec7f241f68794</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Penfold takes a trip inside Danger Mouse's body to save him from a deadly aversion to his own heroism.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ce6cb7f273c50dec13b586f423e47c3</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>With their juice bar empty, a grandma and granddaughter ask the Ninjas for a mariachi band to entice customers - but Konpeki?s trumpet playing threatens the delivery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e9de281c0545e24081fbb0bf73b711a</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Bitzer is embarrassed when his dad makes a surprise visit and finds the farmyard in a mess. Feeling sorry for Bitzer, Shaun and the flock make a real show of tidying up. Bitzer and his dad get some bonding time, but the place descends into anarchy once more as soon as his dad leaves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc89b0464e9cc1fd517b24759df90d650</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings decide to play hide-and-seek in the Savannah.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf9e5d0e92f425b61f10975f413a530d3</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Boy's school Bobblehead Head Club is closed down due to not having enough members, his siblings help make the boring club more fun.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8a246e3d307e2977a693732f80d795e9</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert is really proud of the plants he has grown ready for a visit from The Complete Gnome Gardener magazine. However, when a Wind Dragon flies through the forest destroying all his hard work, Herbert turns to desperate measures ? a barrowful of Stinkweasel?s stinkiest compost! Now, the whole forest is at risk of being overwhelmed by the smell, and the heroes must quest to get rid of it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6fbe790ae4282b14265104a8bedddd57</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Mobile Unit goes undercover as villains to try and stop The Shadow.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ebfdfbb072657180925f4f7cabdae13</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents try to escape from a time loop.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae025c43ad493f0de739ac8970e53148</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>A walkie-talkie hidden inside a chili dog causes Harold to worry an alien has arrived.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd55181ac1b0277a6a03b77b9b2b7602a</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug, Cat Noir and Rena Rouge face Sentibubbler.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p04621e80d004ccdf5b7dc735de199288</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs build magical fairy houses, internet star DanTDM shows how to draw a gaming pug, and artist Rong Bao?s inflatable art really pops.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42deaf4110220296e2fd24e6f307b55d</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Angry about not receiving a present from Paris, Celeste hides in the stables. However, she is trapped there with Matron when the stables catch fire.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p50ffa7aba1d1d5de0aa5d12e06c9749f</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe?s latest victory is cut short after an Absolute Dance rules change shakes things up. Now, winning regionals isn?t just about their reputation, it's also about saving the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f6d0ad53ea164a011d86ea9249440f0</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Gladiators? stars Apollo and Electro surprise children in a Salford school when they lead a PE lesson with a difference.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd9807d54b258071ad8fa7ee08110d3f1</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
