<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is particularly tetchy this morning. He is packing for a skiing trip, but a dragon has pinched his golden fleece, and he urgently needs the heroes to quest it back ? how else will he stay warm and cosy on the slopes? However, when the heroes accidentally agree to let his niece Trixie tag along with them, they fear that her clumsiness and lack of hero skills will ruin everything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c3ff87984db3abc93407af293a6fe99</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A brave little girl orders a shield to protect her from a monster and sets off with the Ninjas, her scaredy-cat dad, a goblin, a troll and a dragon to find her missing aunt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p684f43d0b585056e21b15b866ae9630a</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Sparks fly when Tee recruits Jody to help her and Carmen win a street dance competition. But who's more out of their depth, Carmen or Jody.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf305b316b73159aad98d6b7faaae86f7</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A look at how World War II played out on the home front, featuring Churchill's secret loo, the heroic 'ATA Girls' and German spies being caught out by their delicious sausages.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34479d246837eb45065d27a320a85e07</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketch show. A Victorian inspector checks that school is suitably cruel, HHTV News reports live from the Great Plague, and Thumbelina drowns unpleasantly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p71a7989ead2c77a2da5a87e65e68b456</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang can?t wait for their all-day PE training day with Grizzly Griller and are baffled when their idol makes them learn a range of boring non-sports that only Walter excels at.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13014ffef7cef77e45cb02cd6a8721d2</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Having put the Danger Babies through their adorable paces, Professor Squawkencluck leaves it to Danger Mouse to settle them down with a nice soothing story. Unfortunately telling stories to children isn't one of Danger Mouse's strong points, and he ends up scaring his captive audience with a tale that reimagines him as an evil villain. Squawk returns to find Danger Mouse bound and gagged and that the Danger Babies have made off with the Danger Car and are on their way to Arkwirght Asylum to free the 'heroes' from Danger Mouse's topsy-turvy story.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8674b3e1d60465dd8263514a763f9227</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>To win the annual Golden Wand contest, Merlina summons the Ninjas to find her an amazing magic trick to impress the judges. But the final winner takes everyone by surprise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p24416808631b7fb8497c6fb022cb8ebe</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find an ultra-modern glowing cabin they can use for their party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb652f231f7d9980cc9d08668c1128c88</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Girl decides to write her school project about Cat as she is so mysterious and it would nice to know more about her. The gang decides to help, and soon everyone is following Cat from a distance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c294ff4f4dfcf66ec93fa2af4aea959</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Witch, who was trapped in a Merhaven clam shell while pinching a pearl, grants Blossom a single wish to thank her for releasing her and saving her life. Blossom excitedly chooses a mermaid?s tail to improve her swimming. However, when the Merqueen complains that her pearl is missing, and the heroes have to quest to get it back, Blossom soon realises how tricky a mermaid?s tail can become on land.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5de1c5363e6236bc3067ca23bed0355e</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Agents Opal and Omar uncover the location of a legendary odd artifact.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde5af9c73d0f8b081215c96f51015b55</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings use a frog with hypnotising powers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbd74eae5287515b461c9282bcc4d8e8</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>We have an exciting announcement ahead of the new series of Walking with Dinosaurs. Abby discovers dino footprints on the Isle of Skye, and the team come face-to-face with a walking T-rex in the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2e05b41d1ed7298c1d31fa894b13545d</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef tries to trick the kids into making his mother gifts after he forgets Mother's Day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb83be820d725d3dca24249aa7e59fa8</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: Gift of the Night Fury</title>
    <desc>Festive animated short featuring characters from How to Train Your Dragon. Hiccup and his friends are preparing for Snoggletog, the Viking equivalent of Christmas, when all of the dragons suddenly fly away and leave Berk. All, that is, except for Toothless, who cannot fly unaided. Hiccup has a solution for Toothless, but will the dragons return to Berk? Featuring the voices of Jay Baruchel, Gerard Butler and America Ferrera.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1a50b1b524f797da08ef2e7f67ef9476</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A weird and wonderful look at how gravity, magnetism and friction impact everything. With Fred Sirieix.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94fd45c10fe71cfd50c37b15a03b378a</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. Michelle decides to change the line positions, but Emily and Stephanie are not happy about it. Emily confesses a secret to Eldon that brings them a little closer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa22439632e1e3aa19a89d4961d676dbb</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The thrill-seeking eggs take up bungee jumping, the potato racers whizz around, and Mr Strawberry serenades Mrs Strawberry. Fearless Pete Parsnip comes face to face with a terrifying hairy spider, and Slippery Nana comes a cropper impressing the judges in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9af765987c32160992a5512af85bce81</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
