<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids watch a scary old horror movie where a character speaks a certain ancient-language phrase meant to curse the victims to the shadow realm. That phrase? Greb-nefual e-neg! The movie scares some of the kids, but Girl calls it all a bunch of hocus-pocus and speaks the phrase aloud herself. Nothing happens. But one by one, the siblings start disappearing, leaving only a superstitious Boy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p733aee91005bd56c0e5fa17f845aa883</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5947310802f7cddb39f6e7dc886cee1</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings are fighting over a crown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38da76867021476c0c21a33b4ec809f9</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>After touching a mysterious tooth, a lemming turns into a were-lemming.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa5eb91ad6825bc4f46c8da62199c9e14</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Oswald must learn everything he can about the Mobile Unit van before an important interview.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p989e8842b92e69acede05e6f730147a0</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>It?s been ages since their last quest, and the heroes are losing their edge, so Mr Friendlyface invents a strange and terrible monster that he says is stomping through the forest causing havoc, and sends the heroes on a fake quest to get rid of it. Friendlyface soon comes to regret his trickery when, with the heroes out of the way, the goblins decide to take over the forest for their jam jamboree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd73f5a342e51bd6aa4e1226b5b388fb</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward</title>
    <desc>A feature-length riot of an episode as Lily?s quest for global fame goes hilariously wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p84ea302ef0d72daeb681c01433a2658d</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Sabre prank Steel at a fake Halloween photoshoot with a huge spider costume, bats and a surprising ghost! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc407a164e4a84b300e7549772a4bf81</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Revolting space travel, evolving cows, pet mushrooms, and Einstein watches a car on a trampoline.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7998a04b3556c531c826aa1df0c638e1</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve and the team head to New Zealand for the first time. Steve descends deep into the Waitomo caves to find an unusual predator that lures insects to their death with a lethal lightshow, the glow-worm. Then he heads to South Island, to get an aerial view of one of the biggest animals on earth, the sperm whale, before driving inland to meet a very curious bird armed with deadly intelligence. The kea may be just a parrot, but its big brain makes it a hunter to be reckoned with. Finally, Steve returns to the ocean in search of sperm whales, and uses his kayak to get an awe-inspiring close view of this leviathan of the deep.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6997b321227e6e506b8d53e9f2e71382</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>There?s a snot-tastic dose of Ouchology as the doctors face tough medical questions, and a VIP guest is due in the lab to help explain why DNA is a funny, twisty shape.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3485a21336d3fa08d5a13ef9b1f52a97</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>U13s defender Jamie, who can only train with his team once a week due to living over 100 miles away, gets a much-needed chance to bond with his team at an overnight away camp.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p44a5b54ea35090c83627c9c9ec937d87</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve is in search of one of the most spectacular events on earth - bait balls. These wildlife events are so epic that they can be seen from space - but they won?t be easy to find.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p827a1b20bf80354baaa0351ac629ad29</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It doesn't look like Pottsfield stand a chance of winning a recycling award. However, Danny and Mick hatch a plan to host a rained-out golf tournament in the leisure centre, using all the recycling they have.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc7ae76e4e952e5e2839c8819e7596256</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy?s mum has an Odd Job for the band ? to stop the local cinema from being shut down. Trying to persuade councillor Hattie Hardface is tougher than they had bargained for.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0dd254785d90a0d88c741ec5955f4dd</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>A prickly guest turns up at Joe and Adam?s house and needs a lot of care, but Callum hasn?t made it easy for them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ff62c8636adb7a5a6dd42bc11f1c7fa</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>A west African savannah storm intrigues Paani until a mudslide forces Tunip into a ditch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb472d5a8f0dd128feb2b9ea71f8271e5</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Cosima and Big Lizard find some fascinatingly slippery fruit, but bringing it safely back to the ship is more challenging than they imagined.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f770807e1c9b4adae5c07afc1c11262</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's addiction to challenges threatens the world. Quark tricks Danger Mouse into transporting a ticking time bomb back to Earth. This device threatens to turn the entire world into gold within hours. Quark's face print is the key to deactivating the bomb, and while dragging the extra-mouthed extraterrestrial across space wouldn't usually pose much of a problem to DM, Quark aims to see his plan through by exploiting his captor's recently diagnosed 'Compulsive Challenge Disorder'. With the HQ in sight and minutes to spare, DM's 'CCD' takes hold at the worst possible moment, and he abandons the mission in order to battle an army of bounty hunters. Can DM come to his senses and channel his affliction into saving his friends and stop the planet from turning into a huge gold bauble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a0eba2335e392bf6d0c015b6b6474e7</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The world-famous Wonder Sausage is on show in Butch Butcher's shop. Walter realises the sausage has a strange hypnotic effect on Gnasher so uses it to make him perform his every whim! Dennis can't understand why Gnasher has turned against him and has to use all his heartfelt pleas and happy memories to try and win Gnasher back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p93927ea16ff71a540a684fc3eefb4435</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom draws the short cheese straw and, rather than join her friends on a picnic, she has to take a magic wand to the recycling centre. Faced with a long queue and a rumbly tummy, Blossom decides that life is too short for recycling - with disastrous consequences. The heroes must skip their picnic and go on a quest to save the forest from the magical mess Blossom has gotten them into.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38db6a019d90d683a5c507a27c6477df</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors test how strong stomach acid really is, and will it be Dr Chris, Dr Xand or Dr Ronx who gets snotted in Ouchology.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9171da2f98f621006e40a25a80861581</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko, Roy and their Pok?mon receive some red-hot training from Gym Leader Kabu.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7b192b99a4477050b8b0eb9a98ae4a15</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. Fearless Pete Parsnip takes on some pasta bats and then star bar sets off on another trip to the moon. Mr and Mrs Strawberry get ready for a romantic night in front of the telly, the toast soldiers attempt to ambush an unsuspecting egg, and a pear and an apple amuse the judges with their strongman talent show act.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p087ca9b89296332866bf1e8492e127a2</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>To find a piece of the mysterious Ephemychron, the Nektons have to fight off whirlpools, zero visibility and giant robotic jellyfish. Is Nereus doing this to them? If not, who is really behind this unusual test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac458d0a2f19eb52e40883fcb8bf2f05</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>While helping Sergeant Slipper prove that he has what it takes to remain Beanotown?s policeman, the gang unknowingly become entangled in Doctor Pfooflepfeffer?s real theft.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc05891fb066c59115954c3de0a3c01f0</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Clip show. The danger agents are at the annual Supies awards show, eagerly awaiting the results. But as Duckula calls out Danger Mouse?s name time and time again Penfold, Squawk and Colonel K?s hopes of winning anything slip away.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a572df6eeb2e2d8d4f4ded581df1b00</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When Pam D?Terre and her giant rabbit sidekick confiscate all the potatoes in the world, the Ninjas must go on a rescue mission to get them back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5b0ff086652d29157b3522733883604</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>After the Farmer manages to drive his tractor into a mud patch, Shaun, Bitzer and the flock try to rescue it from the quagmire. Before long, however, the stranded vehicle sinks far beyond their reach.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p48863823b752a00185efd1d51b78cf84</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings lay hands on an ancient console, and Grizzy is transported into the game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31177e19b22b7b6fd1c283788e89e3f8</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Boy and Girl start receiving lavish gifts addressed to ?two great kids?, Mouse thinks it must be a mistake. He and Dog set out to investigate whether these presents are meant for someone else, but the other kids don't like that idea at all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p83183b454813d61ba000f321722fff50</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Hoofius plays his grandfaun?s old magical panpipes, his friends do exactly what he asks them to do - perfect for leading a quest... or so he thinks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbada50b36a9303ac56775c369e7c2be0</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents try to resolve a disagreement between Ms O and Oksana.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pec925f8ad8786901c400467620fa98d3</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. It's party time for all the new agents at Odd Squad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf0a3057b49a3fac00f873c8c93ccec14</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Gwen accidentally brings her Princess Poodle toy to daycare and denies that it's hers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ad44aaf03ec3f9c89081570ee98718b</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>For the first time, the heroes have no-one to face.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c5dacb8a85052d8a9002aa0099aa4a5</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>A trip to Olivine City gives Ludlow a chance to reminisce about his home town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d7ab649823e9cd39338b1517a2500d4</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Home Sweet Rome</title>
    <desc>Lucy spends the night at home alone while Dad is the rock star at an archaeology conference.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p74d0ad023b5e8f3cb8608683f2119a48</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Daisy?s return makes things more difficult for Heath. Eldon and Michelle consider parting ways as an injured Pete feels left out of the Brawl.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6b5147c4642565487a47814ae7a8a27</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Beaker Girls</title>
    <desc>Jess and Tracy Beaker are loving their new life by the seaside, but the arrival of teenage runaway Jordan is about to change everything for the Beaker Girls.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3befcf20b5a9613b723111a3eaad1961</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>17 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Can Bitzer keep the Farmer?s new sneakers spotlessly clean.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe87f6aa0d6a4272c01e9e16da1ca914a</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>On seeing his adopted goldfish get busted for stealing top-secret documents, Penfold bewails the fact he has never had a pet of his own to love and cherish. He gets his wish when Danger Mouse and Squawk discover the Baron's plans to brainwash the world's pets into becoming his personal army of slaves, and they hand him the responsibility of babysitting the Baron's own pet Nero, having craftily swapped him with a robotic impersonator as a means of getting to the Baron's mind control device - the Pet Whistle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pda092f5371bdaf387f43f04cace63c4b</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Determined to prove he can accomplish a task without getting distracted, Dennis takes on the simple job of bringing the class register to the school office. He instantly distracts himself on an epic scale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb20653e5b67a5132f1ebf7148c402cbf</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Everybody gets jealous when Boy bakes amazing cookies that he only shares with his new pen pal, Gretchen. They band together and pretend to be Gretchen, writing letters to Boy and asking him to send more cookies, which they then intercept and eat for themselves. However, when Boy asks to meet Gretchen in person, Girl, Dog, Cat, Mouse and Cheese come up with a plan to impersonate her and steal Boy's cookie recipe once and for all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe291887f2a9c4ec6e7d05bed8a5b45b6</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc01d8a83132164d1876b8e891a6c96aa</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy uses a hen to protect some Yummy jars from the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa5b246dbc4d33b694533bc526f36adb0</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a jar of jelly that gets stuck in a high-up spot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p20fc70ddc4e0f10bae41278fc0610631</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit must return a blob to London, but their van has run into trouble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pecd6ed31183b9e0a0b51735f2ba5d64d</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Gruffalo's Child</title>
    <desc>Animated film based on the best-selling children's picture book by author Julia Donaldson and illustrator Axel Scheffler. One wild and windy night, the Gruffalo's child ignores her father's warnings and bravely tiptoes out into the snow in search of the Big Bad Mouse. She meets Snake, Owl and Fox, but there is no sign of the fabled Mouse. He doesn't really exist... or does he.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paaf866e037885f5ab44992d25cf3d482</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Captain Barnacles runs into an old friend - an arctic fox named Professor Natquik - in Antarctica. They must work together to prevent a group of penguins from falling into an ice chasm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p48c2ef767eff617341385b62b07def67</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Zagazoo</title>
    <desc>A tale from Quentin Blake's Box of Treasures. Happy couple Bella and George are surprised to receive a strange parcel containing a baby named Zagazoo, who unexpectedly transforms into a series of badly behaved animals, including a vulture, an elephant, a warthog and a hairy monster, mirroring the various tricky stages of childhood and testing their parental skills to the limit as they try to adapt to their challenging offspring. A touching and hilarious story about growing up and the bond of love that keeps a tight family together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf1aecbb012e266834ffbe3cb76220af5</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:50AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Fury prank Cyclone, who thinks she is filming an animal-themed exercise video dressed as a turtle. The other Gladiators have fun pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14568fca763cea3c2d50d63ef4e99370</image>
    <start>09:50AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>The Real Mutants assemble, people are drinking vomit and electrocuting themselves for science, and the earth and moon have an earworm about the solar system.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdad153ab81fb68e8962c09f25134220e</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve and the crew are back in South Africa, one of the deadly capitals of the world. He is taken out by the fastest feet on the planet when he goes up against a couple of cheetahs in a 'friendly' game of football, before heading out to see them in action in the wild. He also meets a monkey-snatching crowned eagle that uses its dagger-like rear talon to snatch up unsuspecting treetop primates. Steve turns the latest camera technology on a trio of Africa's deadliest snakes, giving a unique view of the venom-spitting cobra, the supersensitive boomslang and the split-second striking puff adder.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p00ce1b03ec44e6bfe8ca4a0f8e51f156</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors demonstrate the power of the pelvis by going head-to-head in a man v monkey contest! And there is ice cream for Mr Grumbles when the Time Machine zooms back to the 1950s.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21f88cef89ed4c2c83d4f7455445ca81</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>The U11 boys go to the National Futsal finals at the home of English football, St George's Park. Can midfielder Mitch and attacker Albie bring home glory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4bae5242f2b6f6066281056897da0d1f</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve goes in search of the deadliest cats in Africa in the carnivore capital of Zambia. He gets up close to the rulers of the Savannah - the lions and leopards.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcb8030afcc5bc05bed71d47079401638</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Danny and Mick have to play Romeo and Juliet after a theatre company leaves them in the lurch - this time with Danny playing Romeo and Mick playing Juliet, the role he was born to play.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2e8c77eb0009ebee9e8dd79aeb5ebf59</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>When Odd Sock Tyler needs to replace his missing dance crew, Andy and the band put their best feet forward, with some help from Cousin Mac?s Super Sneakers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc6996fefa2167c60b0313827aba5f4ea</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Adam and Joe break out the superhero costumes for another round of this hilarious competition. But who will Little Bro Callum choose to take a forfeit from the Wheel of Doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fc75d405fb4e972315f29ad22dd4426</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts find a threatened tree that must be moved - the creatures inside disagree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34aa4c5c3bda3550112ae08ac9f623d9</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Big Lizard wants to have a go with Dad's new drone, but first he has to prove that he can go a whole day without breaking something precious. Good luck, Big Lizard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p850b309749660e2b38b39d00c45b2933</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. When Penfold scores a date with superstar Scarlett Johamster, Danger Mouse and the Professor provide conflicting advice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51f838bce388f3f2659ed47b1785f54f</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Gnasher finds a Gnashersaurus rex thigh bone while digging in Beanotown Park! A long-lost relative! It's not long before Walter and Dr Pfoofleffer hatch a plan to create a whole new living dinosaur from the bone! Dennis and his pals must save Gnasher's ancestor and hide him in a place where no-one will notice a fully grown dinosaur..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5e81ba61aef0e09080d7a4612028affb</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>It?s been ages since their last quest, and the heroes are losing their edge, so Mr Friendlyface invents a strange and terrible monster that he says is stomping through the forest causing havoc, and sends the heroes on a fake quest to get rid of it. Friendlyface soon comes to regret his trickery when, with the heroes out of the way, the goblins decide to take over the forest for their jam jamboree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd73f5a342e51bd6aa4e1226b5b388fb</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>When Dr Chris realises that the horrendous cheesy smell in the lab is coming from Dr Xand?s feet, the race is on to find out why they are so pongy. Is it the feet, the sweat, the trainers?! Turns out it isn?t as simple as you might think! Elsewhere, Dr Dan and Dr Raf square up in Body Battles as they put their quad muscles to the test by trying to squat to lay an egg in a nest. Thankfully, Gladiator Dynamite is there to stop anyone cracking up and make sure that the loser gets in the ice bath. As we count down our Top 5 Silliest Named Body Parts, you can check if you have Greek feet and discover where you can find your ginglymus. In Doctors on Duty, Dr Xand goes to hospital with Maddox, who has an appointment at the cystic fibrosis clinic at the Royal Brompton. Elsewhere, Victoria has slipped and fallen on her arm at school, so she is at the emergency department in Edinburgh, while Sorin has cut his face after colliding with his classmate?s cat ear hairband.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62239a19d50e5c2eb6f68d4f4acdfcba</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Mark and Lauren get the help of experts to design dream dens for children. Dancing through life together, Jazz and Katelyn have been best friends since nursery school. They love all types of dancing and want to put a dance studio in Jazz's mum's cellar. Until now Jazz hasn't had her own space as her mum fosters children, so their house is constantly busy. The cellar is the only option. However it's full of rubbish and the walls are very damp - so turning this space into Jazz and Katelyn's dream den is a big job! Keith, Tracey and Neil can't offer much help either - they're the family's well-dressed dogs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb47a99074e15212821182b01ed287cf7</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A football, a biscuit, a sofa bed and a pair of shoes are among the items getting the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf1786c5e1632112d437a33a96c3312d</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Huge, prehistoric crocodiles still inhabit an underwater cave system the Nektons are exploring. Ant befriends a new hatchling, much to the annoyance of its mother.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p028e54b19974d00f9b8308040d598ae7</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis dresses Gnasher up as a rare breed of animal which he says is nesting in Bash Street School, hoping to get the school shut down on the day of a daunting and difficult test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf1530f2f032cd4d976fda5d61929b327</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When the Danger Agency?s public approval ratings plummet, Colonel K brings in a truly out-of-this-world PR guru to help put things right. Alarmingly for Danger Mouse and Penfold, that guru turns out to be the galaxy?s biggest trickster ? Quark! DM is soon won over after seeing Quark demonstrate his Exaggerator Device: an invention that spins even the most mundane event into an outrageously overblown display of awesomeness. With the help of the Exaggerator, DM?s popularity skyrockets to dizzying heights, but fame comes at a price. And when Quark starts making Danger Mouse look villainous, DM will have to convince the world he?s not the criminal everyone thinks he is.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd763cabc9e8e3aa61b784d938853858a</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After some playful gnomes take her phone, a mum and her son ask the Ninjas for help. However, a game of magical tag ensues when the gnomes also take the Ninjas' delivery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e6614daa2f8b7a97e30b3497c60c300</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When two different pieces of flat-pack furniture are delivered to the Farmer and Bitzer, confusion ensues as they start to mix up the pieces. Shaun and the flock are forced to give them a lesson in following instructions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6faba19999bdaf0067c3c03224597602</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a mask that terrifies anyone who looks at it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1940c1b33ce8f0692bb0dbf611d37b6</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy and Girl discover that while they're at school, the others are home doing all kinds of fun things, leading to a serious case of FOMO.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6c4b8a4db5057d993a3e67d0f9eff0f1</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert is starting to feel his age and secretly drinks from the Fountain of Youth. However, his desire to be young puts the whole quest in jeopardy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ecebebc10b6dd928dcf3e72f8f98353</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Delivery Doug needs help with an egg situation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81bc422655d801eb4c8da27734ca4a22</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Agents recall how a beloved gadget helped them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5b770379da21069fe152a72f50b4a8c</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth gets gum stuck in Leshawna?s hair and must find a way to remove it inconspicuously.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ecea2a6ae153ce7b9f787cf48b3170d</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>What if Monarch showed up at Marinette?s home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcff1a87b47c73b1f5078e2b442f7e280</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>The Rising Volt Tacklers work together to battle Entei after finally tracking it down.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p37313d12dbc98bbf0a817067b44ac590</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Home Sweet Rome</title>
    <desc>Lucy desperately wants a moped of her own. Francesca?s harmless white lie causes trouble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5bdc30fb995a85bb7a16ab4f4dc3803d</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupers begin to switch over to Team Brawl, but when Olive and Eldon figure out a way back into regionals, Anthony and Ethan have their loyalties tested.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdfbe47178e58aaec452002ff1f8d03b8</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Life on the farm becomes a hive of athletic activity as Shaun and friends stage their very own sporting extravaganza. In heroic style Shaun, Bitzer and friends compete for victory whenever the Farmer's back is turned. Busby Barkley meets the Sheep Dip.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1deef9002a8beaf6737aed3467cf882f</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>18 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Under the guise of superhero Super Sheep, Shaun tries to restore peace to the farm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbaf5d15386d7ac24cea90e3793fc7fdd</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When a teenage Squawk goes on the rampage, DM summons her Twistyverse counterpart to talk some sense into her. But he overlooks one vital thing - a twisty Squawk is an evil Squawk.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8860fb41ad02630190f69eceef15b408</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Miss Mistry arranges to tag along with Dennis and the gang after school, in an attempt to enhance her teaching skills and prevent school governor Pfooflepfeffer from banning her beloved teaching magazine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7390c9ba105b7ed1875a12a98670c204</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Cheese accidentally begins writing her new fantasy novel inside Boy's diary, Boy is inspired to live out the life of the novel's great hero! By applying the story to his life, Boy is soon one of the cool kids, making Girl jealous. When she sees Cheese's novel-writing is the cause, Girl helps her write the next chapter to take Boy down a peg or two.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62fb1ea3b82ef516c198dd565a53c8b0</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0fbeb539a94ced844a30f0549f513ee</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings play a game: it's the Lemmings Knights v the Bear Magician.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0ed9e82e3ba0d61d2f02762acf46458c</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy's sample of Yummy is mysteriously crushed - but who is the culprit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p93597cfcd6284d4eff680bc3ccf8bda1</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit must return a blob to London, but their van has run into trouble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1e8563eead5d242fde0102c3a53c9fa</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are excited to visit Whizzpop?s Pop-Up Bakery and taste his magical cakes, but they are shocked to find that the protein bars have shouty raisins in them, the custard tarts are rock hard, and the floating sponges keep floating away! Trevor quests to solve the mystery, but having accidentally fallen into Whizzpop?s invisibility flour, how on earth will he get everyone?s attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe2faf77b85cf0b2852c9a1177edf9ab5</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: Diamond and Pearl</title>
    <desc>The struggle of time and space, of distorted worlds and alternate dimensions, continues to rage, with Ash and friends once again caught in the middle! Michina Town has a long history and chequered past in relation to the mighty Arceus. Ash and his friends, accompanied by their new companion Sheena, travel in time with Dialga?s help to correct the mistakes of the town?s ancestors before the world crumbles under the power of Arceus' rage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d31f491ad84717f48c75f2fb72e4925</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A cucumber, a golf ball, a phone and a pan of sprouts are among the items getting the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p377f26eccae4b6c77348125df3b73973</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Big Brain has a chemical catastrophe, Sir Isaac Newton rides a coaster again, with shocking results, Loofah is after a murderer, and Dr Henry VIII on call.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peee6d9a3675c97b17d21716f58b7d6ed</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve and the crew are back in Australia for one of Steve's most dramatic encounters ever as he dangles beneath a helicopter and is dropped into the nest of giant, wild saltwater crocodiles. He also goes in search of the most venomous animal on earth, the box jellyfish - one sting could be fatal, so caution is an absolute must. Finally, he enters a snake-infested marshland on a hunt for two lethal contenders for his list - the tiger snake and the copperhead snake.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1f6afce13d488d712bf0dbfa1caeef5f</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Dr Xand turns fire juggler to reveal the body's secret sense ? proprioception, but will Dr Chris spot something is up? Dr Dan investigates organs on chips, with no salt and vinegar.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd260dd34f7f0a87c3af2de51ff7a4060</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>After impressing in her own age group, U16s attacking midfielder Dream gets the chance to play for the senior U18s team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62a39a4c85da3791e5ee0f6c137f945c</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to Zambia for the first time. He hears hippo communication on a whole new level, spots a high-diving croc and meets some incredible sniffer dogs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3986f49991a9204dc06d5907226e9e8c</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Pottsfield is hosting a cake decorating masterclass with guest judge Mary Croissant, but after she catches Danny insulting her, she leaves in a grump. It's up to Danny to convince the class he's Mary, teach Lance's judo class and have a performance review with Sharon... all at the same time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcdec286656e46168f59700ae7e5c4e91</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Odd Sock Theo needs help to save some snails, so Andy and the Band come out of their shell to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p95663a521d729d75a6df6b533b3073b8</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum sends his Sharky mate to Joe and Adam?s house with a request to paint his portrait. But can the boys do it wearing glasses that make everything topsy turvy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbf538936f317ca7795bc522641e33f5</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Rising water endangers some albatross nests, so the Octonauts help to relocate them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32e65ef090750ae9b86c49441a0b72ef</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Whilst playing doctors, Cosima discovers an animal with no heartbeat! Can Cosima and Big Lizard save the poor creature with Dad's medical kit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf9b94285e316e30a3c7316c3dad21135</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Penfold is assisting Danger Mouse, testing the security system at the British Cheese Museum. Everything is going swimmingly until a temporal glitch strikes and the pair discover the museum's prized pink parmesan has somehow vanished, with a baffled Danger Mouse left cradling the crumbs! There's barely enough time for DM to question what is going on before Danger Hedgehog and Danger Mole arrive on the scene to arrest him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p64794cf202f8df91f630a2596393369b</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Rubi worries that her dad is lonely, so the gang try to find Professor von Screwtop a girlfriend! Dr Pfooflepfeffer seems the perfect match, or does she really only want him for his atomic toaster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ad6a5bcf25d255f125082a2774c934f</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>In Ouchology, the doctors end up in a ball-throwing fight with their kid quizmasters, and it all ends with a snot, snot, snotting! Dr Xand rolls out the crushing machine in the lab to do an experiment to find out how strong your teeth are. It?s a packed Ouch and About, with George wanting to know why we burp, Clark asking why we need to sleep, and Ana asking why people have different eye colours. We fly across New South Wales, Australia, with Jesse and the Flying Doctors, to attend his hospital appointment in Sydney. In the emergency department, Nathan has an injured arm after jumping off the slide at Edinburgh Zoo and accidentally landed it, and Isabella is there after bending her finger backwards when catching the ball in Gaelic football practice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p253932508603c60d14861f3f57c194fd</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Mark and Lauren get the help of experts to design dream dens for children. Cooking eggs since he joined his adoptive dads at the age of seven, 11-year-old Nathan has turned up the heat and wants to be a chef. Of course, every chef needs a kitchen, but Nathan can never get into his as his dad is always using it as a workshop. So he is after a kitchen hangout in his back garden where he has space to whip up his own culinary creations.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65a6bb6703c88ef2f77bee3feef7a166</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A plane, a chair, a pencil and a watering can are among the items getting the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0d5d2e7d4842b2c21e80016f342a3fcc</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Ant and Fontaine hunt for the rarest of ocean creatures: the colossal squid. But what happens when it turns out to be smarter than you and thinks you look tasty.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2339b47abf0975efdcd102b9f61c0d33</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Stuff is going missing all over the world, but the team are distracted, fascinated by Squawk?s new Futuroid camera, which incredibly spits out snaps of future events. DM is aghast when the camera produces a photo of him and Squawk kissing! When Penfold is abducted by an alien tractor-beam, Squawk and Danger Mouse must overcome their mutual disgust to work together. Their search for Penfold leads them to Flarg, the alien who?s been nabbing the world?s missing items. Chained upside down, and with Flarg intent on stealing everything in existence, the situation looks hopeless.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb5d035b9e0550524db3394d94a29b61e</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A brave little girl orders a shield to protect her from a monster and sets off with the Ninjas, her scaredy-cat dad, a goblin, a troll and a dragon to find her missing aunt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p684f43d0b585056e21b15b866ae9630a</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>An all-night gaming session turns the Farmer and Bitzer into sleep-deprived zombies the next day. Shaun takes the chance to change Bitzer?s checklist to suit himself, but he manages to miss the final item: shearing time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3f60727be2d84e2a3113f71146047e4</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings crack the codex system of a mysterious box and are sucked into it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e5fff82fda3d97623ba81a31c11afdb</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy has planned a perfect sleepover with best friend Tuck that will feature bobblehead-themed activities. However, Boy gets jealous when Tuck keeps getting distracted by his siblings' antics.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pca58c27786c5b455593adeac12c4cfce</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Much to Trevor?s irritation, a rare phoenix woodpecker takes a liking to him - so he demands an immediate quest to return the bird to its real home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd460f05ee8f6efe98ada93b746aa74d</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents bring someone with an odd problem back to headquarters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p68cae65ead64454d95150e06cb856e32</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>It's picture day, but a strange visitor has invaded daycare, turning the kids into zombies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbbf2fba0904f3b365ca720abcc6e2595</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Football freestyle world champion Lia Lewis joins us in the BP garden with some incredible skills you can try at home, plus Abby and Shini take on a tasting challenge with an ice cream man whose flavours have gone viral.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54259cd8c39f2352bcde8eda26856a60</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Wallace &amp; Gromit: The Wrong Trousers</title>
    <desc>Oscar-winning animated adventure featuring Wallace and Gromit. The duo are plunged into a hilarious tale of skulduggery involving an extraordinary pair of automated trousers and a villainous penguin. Featuring Peter Sallis as the voice of Wallace.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4893406d6cf1556b0ee48a2c8e59618c</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy exchanges his indifferent fish with the Lemmings' affectionate and lively fish.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p07e8c90f4bc95e6cc138af9db789ccd7</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Home Sweet Rome</title>
    <desc>At the Empire Europe Cup, Lucy makes a friend. Francesca fends off nerves... and Emilia.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8a8ceeb25c65c1a590bd5ccfd4a53647</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Kenzie helps Pete make a difficult decision. The Brawl?s love theme gets in the way of Heath and Daisy fixing their friendship, and Michelle turns to Eldon for Brawl advice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p78694b47d4acdfcbe0bbffab1b09836a</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>A new season at Hawx Academy brings new faces, new challenges and old rivalries.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e471a642d1c44ef35c378fd85b704e5</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>19 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Bitzer is horrified when the Farmer scribbles all over his map showing the location of his buried bone, fearing he will never rediscover his treasure. The flock are on hand to help him search, even if their methods are unorthodox.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde8c349f04c3c64ef16ec18f49455bce</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Professor Squawkencluck's mum comes to visit, a gigantic, enraged rubbish monster is not far behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b7ec02901562c8e1059c044cd0f4ea2</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis must escape detention and Bash Street School to make the Beanotown Brawny Bean Race before Walter wins it! With the help of a note placed in his desk, he must sneak past Mrs Creecher and make a run for it - unless the mysterious note-giver stops him first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9167fe1b5f9cceb7d9f064d5b1a19a74</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>A photographer is coming to take snaps of Girl's latest cosplay creation. She needs the others' help building it and agrees to do a series of favours for them in return. However, chaos breaks out when sneaky Girl starts secretly trading off these favours among the gang themselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf228ff0628556fe4a73703f510b527c0</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb87df767ab8c45cc0c4f5a334ed59fe2</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>With his crew on the verge of a mutiny, a pirate captain and his parrot order a treasure trove to placate them, leading the Ninjas on a trip to the Egyptian pyramids.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ab01993316b04e4743c31d214e9c2da</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When Ms O leaves to conduct a super-secret mission, the agents compete to figure out who is in charge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p869126efa5973de5da9e29546dc380d7</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are questing to find out who is behind a string of cake thefts, and go into detective mode. After questioning the baker, they decide to stage a stakeout at the bakery. However, when they spy cakes apparently walking off by themselves, they realise that there is more to this mystery than meets the eye - and a quest to find some missing cakes soon turns into a quest to save the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5645751379a5d59cdd33d1d6bc3124d3</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Cat Noir?s evil twin, Copycat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p308415545169102e2a3fc972a96116d9</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Alix - aka Timebreaker.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd28c76e93aedbc23aa79d3ea56e67169</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Roy and Crocalor accidentally switch places while exploring a festival in Kitakami.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81f2a223a60d16fe5b399233394f87f5</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover an ancestral tree that casts maledictions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p853fe031bd6f16e817a884125beb3883</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a futuristic underground site.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0fe3e513d4fe1b37a13702add7b05620</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a magic stick that functions as a Yummy divining rod.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcee1931a27a2dfd300dfe45402832d2b</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Cheese and Dog are teasing each other about the things they like to do. However, trying out each other's interests causes them to realise what they?ve been missing out on.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb63508683548e8c2e7b000bf9934c155</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Mouse brings home an old ice cream truck, the kids start their own smoothie business. However, the town's lovable ice cream man, Uncle Bub, isn't happy about the competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7bbf029937d9754bf6213941d447763a</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the family visits a farm, Cheese bonds with Delilah the cow over all things dairy. However, bringing her home to live with the family leads to all sorts of problems.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69a2672618969229d48692833eab3c29</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef almost ruins National Hotdog Day when he forgets to book the Hot-Diggity-Doggity Dog.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa0aac1dd1681a527aae9c418a5fe84d4</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef brokers a truce with lice by selecting three kids to 'host' them on their heads.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p300a4c3a34f447193e6a22be19fcab31</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum sends the bros to the racetrack for a bumpy ride! Adam and Joe?s driving skills are put to the test as they strap into some Power Turn Buggies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ba7345b81feed2c5dbf12ae30ab4227</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>Dragons, dinos and divas! The Kwapongs craft fire-breathers, Romesh Ranganathan draws a rapping T-rex, and Bristles dives into the bold, brilliant world of Frida Kahlo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35625862ebe527b01a7c825cbdc1577a</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Football freestyle world champion Lia Lewis joins us in the BP garden with some incredible skills you can try at home, plus Abby and Shini take on a tasting challenge with an ice cream man whose flavours have gone viral.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54259cd8c39f2352bcde8eda26856a60</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. Debbie from Debbie's Pizzeria has doubled... not once, but twice, creating four Debbies! When one of the four Debbies goes missing, Olive and Otto need to find her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a30aee0211d8e7bb41fb568084b8772</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. Olive and Otto are called in to help when objects and then people start disappearing inside an Italian restaurant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa2acfba8934b5409d676f692e0538657</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Can underdog Cranmede take on the mighty reigning champions Gorsforth at the Interschool Country Dance Championships? And can Tam overcome her dance demons in time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1485a447b6247106aa11cbbdb4498d5d</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Mr Ludcomb wants to win the Best Headteacher Award, but his plans go wrong when Pickle?s magic accidentally turns the rubbish bins into monsters that end up terrorising the school.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p081c97c5c537d121a2f9de518bf239f4</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>To investigate why tummy rumbles are so loud when you?re hungry, the doctors call in the supersized stomach of Mega Xand! When Dr Chris and Dr Xand count down the Top 5 Bizarre-est Body Parts You Never Knew You Had, you will discover that the mysterious palmaris longus is so bizarre that you might not have it at all! The big question in Ouchology is whether it will be Dr Chris, Dr Xand or Dr Ronx who gets snotted by their kid quizmasters. If the doctors can put all the organs in the right place on their own bodies, they could win enough points to avoid the snot - but someone has to come last! Elsewhere, for Investigation Ouch!, Dr Chris finds out why real doctors are doing fake operations on fake organs inside fake patients in Nottingham. At the emergency department in Edinburgh, Alice has hurt her head and arm by accidentally running into a fence. And when Finlay arrives with burns on his forearms, the medics think it might have something to do with parsnips.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe8147477dc78b233d22fec7bfd20d4eb</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Revolting space travel, evolving cows, pet mushrooms, and Einstein watches a car on a trampoline.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7998a04b3556c531c826aa1df0c638e1</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>Aoife and Clanger run head-to-head for school president. When power-mad Clanger?s supporters fall for his free donuts, begging Jessica for help might be Aoife?s only hope.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7364ccddbdc87d7ed3e9750f1e246e6e</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>As the players embrace their new positions, Christina helps Andrew train to be a striker. However, an anonymous message leaves her facing an impossible decision.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1444817816479a2ec3ae0de4e77894e9</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Courtney must go all day without correcting her friends, regardless of what they do wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe12d009fb4b08949cdf975f6bbb47a8</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>A walkie-talkie hidden inside a chili dog causes Harold to worry an alien has arrived.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd55181ac1b0277a6a03b77b9b2b7602a</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When Courtney refuses to share her valuable rare toy, friends join forces to question her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e518a8dee62348a4c879f5a681603a2</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron releases a new strain of elephant flu. Can DM and Penfold find the cure before everyone is turned into a snotty elephant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51f8cb9515674180a911e9981fe74ee0</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Queen of Weevils returns and magically convinces Danger Mouse he is a medieval knight on a quest to rescue a fair maiden.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd28414b63d33d861786886ff541d1233</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Duckula kidnaps the writers and Danger Mouse faces being written out of his own show! Can DM call on the help of the sound department to fight back before Duckula changes the world forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa49a2f94ca890a1640782da819493ada</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids' mean neighbour Wanda has started enforcing a dogs-on-leashes law. Boy, Girl, Cheese and Mouse each come up with ideas about how to show that Dog is special and doesn?t need a leash.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf8723c8d7f782d6c8c671fa9819a3ba</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Dog reveals he's colour blind, the kids rally to help him see the world like they do. Mouse makes him some colour-correction glasses, and Dog is blown away by colour. He becomes an artist and neglects the family as he focuses on his painting career. But when the day of his art gallery premiere comes, Dog will have to choose between art and family.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcf67c683814674b034097cf82bfe82d8</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse is bored of always doing the same things the same way, so Girl suggests he starts thinking outside the box and lives his life differently. Boy and Dog don?t agree, but Mouse, Cat and Cheese follow Girl's lead and it's fun! But when things get out of control, Girl turns to Boy and Dog for help getting things back to normal. With so much chaos in the house, maybe it's time everyone lives back inside the box again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd58240466c21a6b26183b09425e4d16c</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings activate the air conditioner's AI, causing it to fall in love with the fridge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42dd0368414c1fcd0af910a94e7b785f</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds a polar bear and realises they are from the same species.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1cb689afd001542531ecfbda6e5efcfc</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Blossom accidentally uses a witch?s broom to make sticks for toasting marshmallows, the owner of the broom casts a spell of squeaky voices on all the heroes. The spell will be lifted once the heroes have returned with new broomstick branches. A simple enough quest, think the heroes, until they realise that a witch?s broom can only be made from the branches of the Really Spooky Tree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe37511be85e501039449287ddef18d2b</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Trevor is extremely proud of being the clever one in the gang and thinks that his smart mouth is his superpower. However, his friends feel that sometimes his jokes go too far - and they are right to be concerned! When Mr Friendlyface sends the heroes on a quest to prevent Toothgrinder the Ogre from messing up the village green, it?s Trevor?s smart mouth that puts all the heroes in danger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc10a55045431109408268b6cc99aaf5</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Salam City goes dark when the power goes out, but Mansour finds a clever solution.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf9fc7e52810177a3801b603b4cf0b803</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Mansour and friends have a surprising and confusing encounter with a very different Blink.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d071457a6abec7f0701d8494f703c07</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>Chris responds to the network?s request for a holiday special by making the campers hunt for eggs. Who cares that it?s not Easter? And who cares if the hunt is for Cassowary eggs? With the teams now merged, it?s all about being the first one back with an egg and winning immunity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc760bf686edd8f6771aabfec957d9833</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gremlins: Secrets of the Mogwai</title>
    <desc>Sam must choose between keeping Gizmo safe or returning to his normal life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb02e2c477a23bbf8b99db971076c81ae</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Bitzer is embarrassed when his dad makes a surprise visit and finds the farmyard in a mess. Feeling sorry for Bitzer, Shaun and the flock make a real show of tidying up. Bitzer and his dad get some bonding time, but the place descends into anarchy once more as soon as his dad leaves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc89b0464e9cc1fd517b24759df90d650</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Squawkencluck reboots the now 100 per cent reliable Big Head base computer, which immediately locks up everyone in a maximum security prison.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p807580e7b44481f79c8475072cd446ef</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis's ultimate hero, Grizzly Griller, plans on trekking to the source of the River Beano, broadcasting the treacherous path on live TV. Dennis introduces him to his pet hamster Galahad - only to discover they are his biggest fear! Grizzly is so afraid that Dennis must disguise himself as his hero and go in his place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8740f186fd542531c6393457aada6f7e</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The annual town-wide Hide &amp; Seek contest is here! The family always hides together, but Girl points out that Boy stinks at hiding and is bound to make them lose. Nobody else minds, but Ace Hider Girl decides to go it alone, leaving her family at the mercy of the relentless seeker, Wanda! Will Girl realize the error of her ways and lead her family to victory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa62483ec1128c5362231112f093a148d</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9aa8a77e90ffafa510f07322e7cdef3e</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When a parrot steals a fisherman?s lucky captain's hat, the Ninjas search for a replacement on a cruise ship, only for Konpeki and Aka to get distracted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e8f614bd723264869f90ef1bf1f4b24</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Otis and Olympia are stuck with a new robot partner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf79ba2a92eacf194943621245c0db54</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert receives a bottle of Goldenbeard to make his beard longer, stronger and more golden than ever ? and the results are dramatic! Everyone is talking about Herbert Goldenbeard, the great hero and quester, and Herbert is loving the attention. However, when he is kidnapped by the goblins and needs his friends to rescue him, Herbert soon realises that they are much more important than any golden beard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p86555ecedfb25de25cc47ca98336e9a0</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Alix?s brother - aka Pharaoh.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcec722f62a03e2fef5cfb6b83c53a128</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy snares a swordfish, but the Lemmings lure it out to sea. The cabin starts to slide.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0968970dcc0d4cd006f82ccdcaade21d</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Football freestyle world champion Lia Lewis joins us in the BP garden with some incredible skills you can try at home, plus Abby and Shini take on a tasting challenge with an ice cream man whose flavours have gone viral.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54259cd8c39f2352bcde8eda26856a60</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs build 'Kwembley', their DIY table football pitch, Mandy Barker wows turning plastic waste into art, and comedian Aisling Bea draws a puffin with a potato waffle problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1500fcc3c13870d2b9e03edb99166eb0</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>4 O'Clock Club</title>
    <desc>Bell's staff training session is ruined by Chester's disastrous fire safety inspection. Meanwhile, Owen and Evan sneak into school to avert a disaster of their own.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1102411937b3ce4af286187460aad743</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Danny and Mick are waiting in reception for a package to be delivered. While they wait, they reminisce about the hilarious things they have been through together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p46a3512a1ae3c201f64bd175fa11669d</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It?s Danny and Mick?s first day at the new leisure centre, and they are surprised to be greeted by their old boss Joy. She wastes no time in making sure they stay out of trouble by getting them to dust the sports hall ceiling. How can such a simple task go so wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6187a5321578c00a0603c2ff008d8789</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Max and Harvey host the Queasy Spa quiz, where the bros face some nauseating treatments! And can they pilot their own water jet packs in the Ultimate Memory Test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0c7b3f50db472fef03c655a2f172fd2</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>Looking to help protect the planet, Cam, Tyler and Aaron take inspiration from the zoo?s animal eco-heroes, including pygmy marmosets, Amur tigers and orangutans.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe74b7e32ca68358013cf2fa1dead5e7b</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Naturalist Steve Backshall heads to the Bahamas in order to get up close and personal with a whole bunch of sharks. There are plenty of shark species to choose from and Steve has his work cut out deciding which ones are worthy of a place on his Deadly 60 list. Hooking up with shark scientists helps him decide and gives him an opportunity to release some baby sharks into the wild, and he learns how to hypnotise them with his bare hands. Getting mobbed by hungry reef sharks and swimming with a four-metre tiger shark are all in a day's work for Steve and the team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9349cfce16e0015173b853597176fe6b</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>A helicopter trip over the vast expanse of Brazil's northern savannah helps adventurer Steve Backshall find his next contender for the Deadly 60. He is in search of the elusive giant anteater, but can he get close enough to film one for his list? A chance encounter with a tough little owl with an ingenious way of catching its supper captures Steve's attention and the rainforest lives up to its name as a very wet team ventures out at night looking for some of the world's deadliest bugs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62a22e4c0f29e059eb199874aea74982</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Find out how fast your nerves work in a snotty experiment that sees Dr Xand blow a fuse, and the Cupboard of Everything is time travelling to a very smelly Victorian street.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p155f6685236c638b082ef5a70126b243</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Including an annoying French prankster from the Middle Ages, bizarre Aztec food on Historical MasterChef, what happens when Queen Elizabeth I needs the toilet, and how not to impress a woman in Victorian times.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p536197083060eeb5509b64ea9b1043f0</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Some medieval knights discover the most disgusting way to attack a castle, the Saxons demonstrate the stupidest way to lose a battle, a Georgian goes shopping in a modern pet shop, and the kings and queens of England demonstrate how to remember them all - through the power of song.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6d0fd4365a2744c2c39cf41273d17e63</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Electro at a fake fashion photoshoot when her fabulous, precious dress is ruined. Meanwhile, the other Gladiators are up to mischief behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd1bbc15f7e13b3dc2f66637f66d3cf9d</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Cute kittens are infiltrating positions of authority all around the world. Are they the feline equivalent of the illuminati, or do they just want to make napping compulsory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9f4b865a30bb897fdb78127e21f8077</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse goes undercover as the fifth member of Quark's mega-popular boy band, discovering his inner performer and a musical plot to destroy the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p77a97761345f53edbf51556bc28c35eb</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse must battle Quark again, but this time in the weirdest and most dangerous of places: Penfold's dreams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef370659f818656714ea292bc7ca5e2e</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis leads the gang on the baffling trail of a mysterious Beanotown secret society.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbe40fbbd57946697982b8c481f8009a4</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Walter and Dennis go head to head in a sponsored silence. Being quiet doesn?t come naturally to either of them, as they struggle to make it through a chaotic school day and keep schtumm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f774701f77fb51f6357283a8b30f9ef</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang find out that JJ has a set of pre-match good luck rituals. In the run-up to an important Blamjitsu event, Walter deviously throws bad luck omens into JJ?s path, threatening her chances of success.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3c30a8458c845f0ca547fee6492f559c</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Witch, who was trapped in a Merhaven clam shell while pinching a pearl, grants Blossom a single wish to thank her for releasing her and saving her life. Blossom excitedly chooses a mermaid?s tail to improve her swimming. However, when the Merqueen complains that her pearl is missing, and the heroes have to quest to get it back, Blossom soon realises how tricky a mermaid?s tail can become on land.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5de1c5363e6236bc3067ca23bed0355e</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are on a quest to find the vault containing the Amulet of Answers and protect it at all costs. But the Riddlemaster is back, and he manages to trap them in his castle, tricking Herbert into handing the Amulet of Answers over to him. Now he has all the answers to every question ever asked, and the heroes must find a way to outwit him - even though he knows what they are going to do next.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe25fa88d8b5c74373b8dbfb32088efca</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes discover that their latest quest - delivering 30 birthday balloons to Mr Friendlyface?s cousin - isn?t as easy as they expected.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10c7fd9b3be98e5feec3cbead7efdc69</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a magical djembe that possesses whoever listens to it through the demon of dance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80ca80a7640d6c97370cbe76034ce69d</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>In the midst of a heatwave, Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over the fridge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa972752e707eb996f7a33d53ae54e9e5</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a mask that can control dreams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc98e754619fbce788aed0f57aa420690</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy watches TV, while the Lemmings want to dance. TV v music - the sonic war has begun.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p109f3debefb996fbde2e14eed1d526c0</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced madcap, stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The potato racers are driving each other round the bend, the DIY doughnuts attempt to fix the bathroom, the cavemen mushrooms come face to face with some big, hairy mammoth pots, fearless Pete Parsnip takes on a ferocious foe, and Slippery Nana takes on a pizza-cutting unicycle in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc75a0813855bf2fc00f9eb5e7b778651</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom and the Riders must work together to rescue Eugene from a dragon?s nest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc467185a7cc7a0405c3a8a6a7a34f905</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Irene offers to help Ron with his band, who are playing that afternoon, forgetting she has to take an important music exam. Meanwhile, Felicity and June find clues to the missing time capsule.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7244e2997a67495eda0c16ca981f82a7</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>A trip to the big city leads to a shocking discovery about Maggie?s disappearance, and Nina and Keedie build a shaky truce while party shopping.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb6421909aa03af91feccab45bb170d8c</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>No longer dance captain, Anthony finds following orders difficult. Jett and Ariana try to be friends again, while Heath?s history with Daisy complicates things with Pascale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6fe3d3df235a0aa0979d15b7a930a0bf</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Keeping Team Brawl?s secret leaves Ariana torn. Michelle and Eldon take a look back at their past as Anthony avoids confronting his present.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p53e3f6af7ef3bf04ac1208a8601ad694</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Graven dispatches two of his generals to Earth to claim the Shard of the Soul of Gorm, forcing the Scions to accelerate their training and protect the artifact. However, with the Scions mired in personal problems, the Gormiti must help them discover their inner strengths on, and off, the battlefield.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f86d004a612bbcbb6bcf03d783df57e</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds a compass that indicates the direction of one's own desires.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf8a424f541389746fb3b18354fe81b45</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>An out-of-shape Farmer is encouraged to get fit using an improvised exercise bike.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2bcdad5eb5939559349ac3168491441</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse inherits the ancient but sprightly MK3 car after the beloved MK4 gets jammed-up. But Penfold is suspicious when the MK3 is determined to have DM all to himself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paafdc13fd551ca2258f2e20f604f4d55</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s Pieface?s turn to look after the class hamster, Space Captain Harrison McScruff-Butt. His own self doubt and Walter?s resolve to sabotage him lead to a rescue mission to free Scruff-Butt from Walter?s mansion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p030b103e478730d5108a53c51e2b4099</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the boys and girls get sick of having to share the bathroom, they split it into two! The girls' side becomes one big party with no rules, but on the boys' side Dog makes many rules! Boy and Mouse hate it, but they don't want to hurt Dog's feelings. Girl tries to lure them over to the girls' side with all the things they love to play with. Eventually Boy and Mouse sneak over to the girls' side to join in the fun - until Dog confronts them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ef23b470a33dca1bbcf9dae735dcd3c</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52093f4fc97c71b54b830256f4c2aa42</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The cabin comes to life and wants to return to Canada without Grizzy or the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd3bf809eba7aa4ce014113e511d0efb6</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>While falling, Grizzy performs a series of acrobatics that amazes the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p941b78c23a09776a0ea01141c7222e36</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Omar and Oswald search for the perfect gifts for Orla?s 500th birthday.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pddc3735175da55b667a8dd31e211c24d</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Watch the mud (and food) fly as sheep take on pigs in the fight to end all fights.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p58526dc6683d56458587390dfeba0dbc</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Something wicca this way comes when Witchy is released early, trading a bottle in the archive room for a new broom with a view and leaving Pierce disenchanted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5badf274218ccc4f3bcba74374228182</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Pro gamer Jelly guides the teams through the speedy world of Sonic Superstars. Who will race through the course and cross the finish line first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c5b667c20c88c120e93b9d6710dc734</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe?s latest victory is cut short after an Absolute Dance rules change shakes things up. Now, winning regionals isn?t just about their reputation. It's also about saving the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7103b075fe967418318c8e3e24cdd05d</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: Black and White</title>
    <desc>A vast Pok?mon habitat amid the hustle and bustle of the big city seems like the perfect new home for a group of five Genesect. The arrival of these mythical Pok?mon quickly becomes a problem, though, as their nest threatens the city?s power supply and they keep attacking anyone who approaches it. On top of that, they have attracted the attention of the legendary Pok?mon Mewtwo, who sympathizes with them because its own origins also involve human tampering. Their leader, a red Genesect, doesn?t trust Mewtwo, and their confrontation quickly rages out of control! Can Ash and his friends stop these two powerful Pok?mon before they destroy the city.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdba3419dfa18d08b2ea84574987c588a</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play marbles, and it's driving Grizzy crazy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6da67b82a65bfa51ab80ff34f6cbd6a4</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Diamond when the guest on a live TV show can?t stop pumping! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes, pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p124aa384cfc9de9b57a6c0777805b147</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle Storm and her parents flee the magical land of Kleftania and end up on Earth, where everything is strange and confusing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8be65ec0a511423024da890d9e1df73f</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Darrell?s final year starts with a fierce argument with Gwen, but she knows they need to work together. Meanwhile, French student Celeste joins the Third and plays a prank on the teachers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5f56dd0f62ae77c0e4472811ae4950e</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Young footballers Christina and Andrew dream of making it into Hawx United Academy. The odds are stacked against them - until Jamie Johnson decides to get involved.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p640fb876577b356d8527df9590bd90cf</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to Suriname, a country with more forest than anywhere else on earth. He kayaks upriver in search of some deadly critters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae61be0573c4be4246d27fa124cbcdc0</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Odd Sock Georgia can?t get her PE kit from a strange lost property cupboard at school, so Andy and the Band take on a daring and delicate operation to retrieve it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb9d30541d6a2b81eabad2a368e392c8</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Little Bro Callum sets Adam and Joe another epic quest: become a king, build the best cardboard castle, and defend your kingdom against the destructive dragon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p378c2ff8e857aa5d5929292f3eeac3c4</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>A honey badger claims a watering hole, so Kwazii challenges her to a digging contest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7757ef7eefe587e166c20e0c5d9f23bc</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When Dad runs out of marmalade, Big Lizard shows Cosima a plant that's growing Proximan oranges. The leaves turn out to be giant bugs, who aren't happy about sharing their fruit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p85d68fe5a114ec11ba06667d09c34f99</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>A late-night scary movie makes Penfold extra jittery, forcing Danger Mouse to make his sidekick sit out the latest mission to stop the Baron from flooding the entire world. When his search for Greenback proves fruitless, things go from bad to worse when Danger Mouse realises that the Baron has headed to the planet's only 100 per cent waterproof building and Penfold's current location - Danger HQ.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p409d62d6c8428e64f9af154a3cc6c776</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface's all-time hero, Cherry Bakewell, is coming to Beanotown to judge the annual bake-off. Pieface wants to make the best pie ever and win the competition, but when Dennis discovers Pieface has never actually baked a pie before, he does everything he can to ensure a win, with pie-splattering results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0410786c047c999e04107f9e22bc39f3</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are excited to visit Whizzpop?s Pop-Up Bakery and taste his magical cakes, but they are shocked to find that the protein bars have shouty raisins in them, the custard tarts are rock hard, and the floating sponges keep floating away! Trevor quests to solve the mystery, but having accidentally fallen into Whizzpop?s invisibility flour, how on earth will he get everyone?s attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe2faf77b85cf0b2852c9a1177edf9ab5</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Gladiator Dynamite is back to make sure things don?t get too explosive when Dr Dan and Dr Raph get into a Body Battle in a planktastic challenge to test their core muscles. On the basketball court, we meet Joel Henry, our Brilliant Bodies slam-dunk champion, to find out how he jumps so much higher than Dr Chris. It?s game on in the lab when Dr Xand becomes Saliva Man and Dr Chris tries everything he knows to overcome his superpowers as the doctors show us what spit is for. In an amazing Bodytricks, six kids surprise themselves by lifting Dr Ronx off a chair using only two fingers! And in the emergency department in Edinburgh, we follow the treatment of Niamh, who has broken her elbow doing a back handspring at gymnastics, and Adhya, who took a whack on the thumb during a hockey match. Ouch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p08db54266af2514592094cbe1c2c13cd</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>After rescuing a wild Hatenna, Liko contemplates her own feelings and makes a new friend.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pff951c4649af6afe59446542efe9f731</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A bunch of bananas, a door handle, a fridge and a tortilla are among the items get the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb38bf8d208dac138f723a8719cab4286</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Nektons meet online superstar Devil Daniels, who will stop at nothing to reach the fame that he seeks - but can the Nektons protect a creature that he has his sights on in particular.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf77d7e9636f2bbe54a5b35b9750ee6d6</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Gnasher is practically immobile inside a full-body cast. When he goes missing, Dennis and the gang race all over Beanotown to find him, always one step behind the helpless hound.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd55d2e54635de7190d8ef7a9ff7d0bd0</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse is forced to choose between dedication to duty and friendship when he battles the Baron in his underwater Toadlantis base.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0e99707170c40698f2e2e60ec597982e</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A nightwatchman at a museum is baffled when an Egyptian exhibition keeps moving around, so he asks the Ninjas to deliver a detective who can solve the mystery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb73d44474f0cb29f7895a3f396cd28bd</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Bitzer is horrified when the Farmer scribbles all over his map showing the location of his buried bone, fearing he will never rediscover his treasure. The flock are on hand to help him search, even if their methods are unorthodox.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde8c349f04c3c64ef16ec18f49455bce</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds a giant home cinema screen.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p57083d29e406f3a34c2e18fb2182864b</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When a horrible smell ruins everyone's day at the beach, Cheese mistakenly believes she is growing stinky and is too embarrassed to go out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa104c1d0f02f523766fc02546729ae21</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes and the Council of Happiness swap jobs, and when the council fail in their quest, the whole forest is at risk of being flooded by Stinkystuff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a544a2a926fb3c68c7a21626bc95543</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents bring someone with an odd problem back to headquarters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03a2f1563cb1b025b7340bc27a3233c4</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. It's villain report card day at Odd Squad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9dae7f88c4e057d5a1eacff1e5e09570</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth sets out to get rid of all their old toys, hoping Chef will buy the new toy she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65f80c82e11fb083e3d726fe80ab11f0</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>The heroes face a jubilating villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f73dc0af7a7a65511dc1d3a5c051b5c</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Chairwoman Geeta challenges Liko, Roy and Dot to a battle to test their strength.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9c4ff1cec6ec6ad912e1a36b842dfc84</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Home Sweet Rome</title>
    <desc>Lucy meets Francesca?s parents and learns more about her family. Kyla teams up with Jimmy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p83abe12205850a2611be7419414ba29f</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Brawl pits Ariana and Michelle against each other as Lucien shakes up regionals rehearsals. Meanwhile, Izzy tries to overcome their dance captain doubts.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42174bc16570e4662a26b95b81208e65</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Life on the farm becomes a hive of athletic activity as Shaun and friends stage their very own sporting extravaganza. In heroic style Shaun, Bitzer and friends compete for victory whenever the Farmer's back is turned. A vigorous table tennis match sends Shaun around the world in his attempts to return the ball to his opponent.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe0e17bb9eb837650f0d88cf3d7324be2</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
