<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>In this episode, the focus is on U13s goalie Keanu, who is in remission from leukaemia and back to his best. We also meet 14-year-old midfield dynamo Libby.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc51c937c7a46f3fc15cced1c4e773c36</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>It's time for some spectacular sponging and box-office body rolling.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p92a2cc73c2ef4bed2d1d81645f7d373b</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>It's time for Ricky to spin around the world. Inspired by artist Tom Purvis he creates an art deco travel poster, uses colour swatches to make an Egyptian mummy and art erupts when he shows us how to draw an exploding volcano.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p476f1f3cf96f72766da74c1a1198910e</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A pirate captain regrets stealing a herd of seasick cows, a Georgian sportsman invents a whole new way of boxing, King Charles II raps about his party lifestyle, and the Georgian army goes to war against a bunch of naughty schoolboys.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e5f4295938a4955551888a20c3e6f03</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Zoe from Oxfordshire is mad about science and dreams of becoming a scientist one day. She loves to carry out messy, noisy experiments, but her dad works night shifts, which means she has to be quiet while he sleeps. She desperately wants her own space where she can pursue her passions and make a mess whenever she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1362ca6c17f3b744fcd72eef1ba4224c</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Celebs Viggo Venn and Phil Green come to the aid of Adam and Joe as they try to prove to Callum who is the most talented. With impressions and dad dancing, what?s not to like.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p957c5bfbca86c719e8a1a2eb81ec77ee</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>Ubercorn, Glitch and the Go Jetters all head to the Dwarkadhish Temple in Dwarka, India, for the Holi Festival of Colour. This Hindu celebration involves people throwing a colourful powder called gulal all over one another. Glitch plans to bring a huge flag he and Ubercorn made as cadets for the top of the temple. But after he accidentally washes all the colour out of it, he orders his Grimbots to bring him gulal powder to dye it again. The Grimbots do this rather too well, however, and soon there is no more powder left for the festival! It's up to the Go Jetters to fix Glitch's mistake and save the celebration.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8cca6da0e497682b4e69c245b75f8a6d</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When Cosima wrongly accuses Big Lizard of eating Dad's birthday cake, he vanishes. Has he run away, or is he planning a special surprise to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9275dc7eb988b5bd7c97e75c33b3cb0b</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Dashi survives a crash in the Octoray just as a hurricane nears the Florida Everglades.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p845dcff01c4ab24aed8fe59d0aef0eac</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>Nugget annoys Pancake with constant demands while ill in bed. To say sorry, she makes him a special bracelet. But Nugget is upset when others get ?nuglets? too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p323236925cf9b40bb041418e094dfb68</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Evil Pea asks for flying lessons when Broccoli flies her paper plane into her freezer. Evil Pea doesn?t let Broccoli know that she intends to fly high to take over Tato Tower.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe89aa484de9cf88df1ea213d9694aa28</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Envious at Danger Mouse's ever-growing medal collection, Penfold questions whether he will ever be deemed special enough to receive a prize of his own. Seconds later, a knock at the door reveals a holographic Quark, who anoints Penfold as 'the chosen one' in a suspiciously automated message that culminates in an overawed Penfold receiving his very own magic wand. Penfold's joy is short-lived however - as he and DM step outside of HQ to find that the streets of are London teeming with hundreds of wannabe wizards, all brandishing identical wands. After discovering that the wands are mass-produced shavings from Merlin's legendary staff, the pair set out to stop Quark's latest money-making scheme by reuniting the staff with its rightful owner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p323dc2e8e64fccd5de7990c027816ff5</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Fed up with Dennis pulling the wool over Mrs Creecher's eyes, Walter orchestrates a robot to take over Class 3C - with disastrous results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p09cd14a7c66d70b97a06114b327de9ed</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A bungled attempt at a stunt leads to Dennis accidentally becoming an internet star and Beanotown celebrity! But his moment of fame is short and Dennis is soon replaced by Walter's cat, who can play the piano. Dennis has to stage the best stunt yet to gain back his audience.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2448826bf08a8b69aefa3652e97decf5</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle feels she is being taken for granted by the other heroes, so she joins the Fairy Squad when they arrive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa88b9a6c763d7c35c89b5f246f002e9f</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>With his crew on the verge of a mutiny, a pirate captain and his parrot order a treasure trove to placate them, leading the Ninjas on a trip to the Egyptian pyramids.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ab01993316b04e4743c31d214e9c2da</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Ahead of the Women?s Euros, we visit St George?s Park, the home of England?s national teams, to meet some future stars of the game! Welsh footballer Ella Powell and Euros champion Ella Toone answer your questions, and Joel and Abby go head-to-head in a goalball challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2bac12a256d2d65f269b3bed18e91e58</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>While the Brave Olivine has its computer system rebooted, it?s picnic time for the crew.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p697852332e9fca7096ad064896f1fda5</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>Eggs, sausages, a freezer and toilet roll are among the items getting the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pca10d3e982537144c48ab02c8dd7731c</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>From Henry VIII?s wine fountain, to Empress Dowager?s marble boat, Horrible Histories talks money, jewellery and untold treasures.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p982e883af197d680a1af3659f4e21f14</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Professor von Screwtop gets mistaken for the new kid in school and joins Class 3C for the day. Rubi is so embarrassed at her dad?s antics that she resorts to pranking to get him into trouble and out of the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p060c373a4ae75d174dc60fc03089f42e</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Snowman is hired as Danger Mouse's new sidekick, leaving Penfold without a job.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb9a8b62eb1f051a7a86e10437f9214c</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After the battery dies on her laser shoe, special agent Gloria Hope calls on the Ninjas to help her find a new one and foil criminal mastermind Pam D'Terre.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10d3013b50db1457cc92c2ac34d58fdc</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When the Farmer accidentally drills a hole in a waterpipe while putting up a new shelf, Bitzer frantically tries to stop the leak from soaking the living room and prevent the Farmer?s precious teapots from sliding off the shelf.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d0dd9504a3c0f105eb983ecfaee021d</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a magic stick that functions as a Yummy divining rod.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p16fa51bb776109875ebe265c75d998d8</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy is afraid of being honest in case he hurts other people's feelings and finds himself doing things he doesn?t like just to keep others happy. Mouse and Cheese encourage him to be totally honest, only to find that Boy?s total honesty can be rather blunt. Can the gang rein him in before Boy alienates the entire town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p266389173e1520b4e65cb4c48680fe55</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are on a quest to find the vault containing the Amulet of Answers and protect it at all costs. But the Riddlemaster is back, and he manages to trap them in his castle, tricking Herbert into handing the Amulet of Answers over to him. Now he has all the answers to every question ever asked, and the heroes must find a way to outwit him - even though he knows what they are going to do next.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe25fa88d8b5c74373b8dbfb32088efca</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When an unlucky coin is accidentally released into the public, the agents must retrieve it before the world ends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e794a83b3d2c55eec5e8e9ab3734047</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When a new room opens up in headquarters, all the agents want a piece.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p48d81a5a15782933c7172775a48d0f89</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Izzy wants to play a superhero game but has difficulty persuading her friends to join in.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70d5282f53657d0ee3c0c5e0137de88b</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Simplificator.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2db79bb10b78cc075f41d666ec980654</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs bowl into space with DIY alien skittles, Emma Stothard weaves a wicker dog, and Kiell Smith-Bynoe draws a ghost so spooked, it?s nearly see-through.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe84a9fb444c89c3b7b8033f116add9f6</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Matron arrives with Nancy, her young ward, and Gwen tells her to ask Matron to stay, which annoys Matron. Nancy joins the third formers as they search for the missing time capsule.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p49ad384923660547da1815e89ea7bbfb</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>No longer dance captain, Anthony finds following orders difficult. Jett and Ariana try to be friends again, while Heath?s history with Daisy complicates things with Pascale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfba3f0a5c1730f35b314ede0c813a92f</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Abby and Shini go head-to-head in a powerchair football challenge! Using specially designed powerchairs as part of four-a-side teams, who will come out on top.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe198144b1c57887ed93fb809b7488166</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
