<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>As the girls celebrate Chinese New Year, PE teacher Miss Elsley believes netball player Jina could be destined for sporting success. She has arranged a visit from a local scout, but will Jina prove her potential.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1def4e8561c1d0605c3a50d7cd92b047</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ten Pieces</title>
    <desc>A classical music adventure with the theme of being all around the world. Today?s celebrated artists are Ravi Shankar, Grazyna Bacewicz and Aaron Copland.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p26babf3b60b03f29fd61a40ffd17c51c</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Get ready for world-class bread-spreading and some super-charged water-sledding.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p135b1f22e016eb62c9054e13bf442e3d</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Fred Sirieix guides Rattus through the Horrible History of Manners, including the benefits of not holding farts in and Puritan dating,. And Jane Austen visits Historical Love Island.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa927d6a7a46abf6f1d31310fc03b008e</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:25AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Sea cadet Jonny became fascinated with naval history through his grandad and is now a huge fan. He wants a submarine-themed den where he can celebrate his passion, learn more and enjoy hanging out with mates.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ea18464ad22d082afcdbda42444b889</image>
    <start>11:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Pushed out of his comfort zone, Blu must tackle his inability to dance in order to put on a show and impress a celebrity judge. The whole school is counting on him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p44b1570c05248dbb219bc90913aa1ef5</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>Grandmaster Glitch has been invited to Djenn? in Mali, Africa, to visit the people and to see one of his favourite things at work - mud! He is especially impressed by the spectacular Great Mosque of Djenn?, the largest structure made from mud in the world. But mud brings problems, and during the rainy season the rain causes damage to the walls of the mosque and the mud houses, so the local people get together to help repair them. Glitch wants to help, but when he realises they have to do this job every single year, he makes a massive umbrella to try to keep the mosque dry so that the local people don't have to repair it again. Although Glitch was only trying to help, things start to go wrong. The huge Grimbrella swings too close to the mosque and goes out of control. The Go Jetters need to fix that Glitch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb948df4d839f129b32e45883fd963c9d</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Whilst Dad is stuck in the desert, D.O.R.I.S. tries to give Cosima and Big Lizard a lesson on friction. As things begin to heat up, a creature steals Cosima's only means to locate Dad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p97e3cc32ecc4e159bdc13c41b6495529</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated series. When a storm washes Peso onto a mysterious, rocky island, he meets a band of lobster-like insects thought to be extinct.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3c238e77822acd1056d91b7f91f7f1b</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold become reluctant parents when it appears the Baron has wiped his own memory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3e99b351aa4afb22052be158681eea93</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>It's Waffle's birthday and Mr Willow throws a huge party for him. As the Brooklyn-Bells prepare a surprise for Waffle, Connie and Ruby's dog, Jelly, leads the Wonder Dog astray.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2019991eb0dba729c1525e7376588aa3</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Supertato, Carrot and the Grape Kids are enjoying flying kites until Evil Pea arrives in her balloon and cuts them down so she can rule the supermarket skies! Supertato and Carrot must climb a display of chopsticks to retrieve the kites from the top. Evil Pea threatens to cut them down again, so Supertato and Carrot turn their kites into hang-gliders and embark on an epic aerial chase with Evil Pea, leading to her bursting her balloon on a chopsticks display sign. Supertato and Carrot land safely on the ground, ready to fly kites again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6eb6445bbe867844a72eca73179f9c21</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Determined to prove he can accomplish a task without getting distracted, Dennis takes on the simple job of bringing the class register to the school office. He instantly distracts himself on an epic scale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb20653e5b67a5132f1ebf7148c402cbf</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Miss Mistry arranges to tag along with Dennis and the gang after school, in an attempt to enhance her teaching skills and prevent school governor Pfooflepfeffer from banning her beloved teaching magazine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7390c9ba105b7ed1875a12a98670c204</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas bring superstar Jean Pascal to the aid of a princess who orders a talented musician to help in calming her difficult dragon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcf7f65ee4caa33a4d5430d34dd5b581b</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Carmen drops May-Li's valuable antique necklace down the toilet and is torn over whether she should try to get it back or lie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc48de8981174bde3e93018046c1a1f80</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Anthony is put in a tough position when Ariana asks to be let back on the team. Ethan works towards something new, and Ebby has her first date with Remy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e5fab11548fcca7b2bac6298a9fe378</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A pirate captain worries about an early bedtime, a soldier from World War I struggles to cook with fake food and the four King Georges form a boy band.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p044d9bfea34359a4b414a6d8c3906513</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Convinced that Mrs Creecher is secretly a master of Blamjitsu, JJ persuades the gang to help trick her into revealing her blam credentials.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p631f5a239e4e0ec4323d1cb7272bc565</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Part one of two. Danger Mouse faces his toughest challenge ever as a mysterious super-villain releases all the villains from Arkwright and plots the end of our hero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pad93a9194a1518da9967732539543b76</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A girl orders a beatboxing teacher after seeing a professional beatboxer in the park. However, the Ninjas must first figure out what beatboxing is.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a76925cb0e22cbb4f1bf4ee102b5b24</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy confiscates the remote control device, but the Lemmings find another one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb088daed596447c6f2a8d8b5466f3892</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After a bad haircut, Dog tries wearing a fancy tuxedo until his fur grows back. Unfortunately, his initial reaction to wearing clothes causes him and the gang to accidentally destroy the rich neighbour lady's fence. But while the others are forced to rebuild it, the neighbour lady gives tuxedo-clad Dog a pass, thinking someone of his style and class is too good for manual labor. Resentment grows as the gang breaks their backs in the hot sun while Dog lives the good life with the fancy lady. How long can this go on.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4bc957bb31fbb8983c5a8c2a4099f441</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is acting very strangely indeed. He refuses to stamp any of Admin Bunny?s documents, keeps getting distracted by butterflies, and seems oddly happy! The heroes are extremely suspicious and decide that someone must have swapped him with a doppelganger. Now they must quest to find out where the real Friendlyface is and get him back before the forest descends into total chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde2e0b6ed02cd81a52a1b5ae1f9bd3e8</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When Oona, Olympia and Otis accidentally change the past, they undo every odd case the Odd Squad have ever solved.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb80390acc70da483b912354957c5ff16</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth shares her slime recipe with her friends, and together they create a goo monster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p456343ae47a574c8929254e0297f6774</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug faces Argos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbd13e45abeae99a94910d22d293936f0</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Tinkatink puts up a fight when a wild Bombirdier tries to mess with its beloved hammer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4295ca2014165eb1ed34bee9ae4f69f4</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Fred Sirieix stars in Scientific First Dates, Marie Curie reacts to space, and the dinosaurs get an unwelcome musical meteor visitor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2a33358dcb8b4090c89b64ab78a468a</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>In an effort to spend more time with Riley, James accompanies her to pick up costumes for the troupe. At the studio, Stephanie takes part in a photoshoot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fb2bccc08f7b8cd3f6efd8edd116853</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Beaker Girls</title>
    <desc>Jess and Tracy Beaker are loving their new life by the seaside, but the arrival of teenage runaway Jordan is about to change everything for the Beaker Girls.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3befcf20b5a9613b723111a3eaad1961</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
