<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan stages a small coup to oust Courtney as their new official class fire officer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p36154bf09ccd9ec599297aaf44b3a88a</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel meets the stars of the new Superman film, we show you how to make your very own garden using just a jam jar, and Shini attempts martial arts.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc100e7f2b34fc4f2fa79872acb61360f</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>12 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Wallace &amp; Gromit: A Matter of Loaf and Death</title>
    <desc>Wallace and Gromit have opened a new bakery - Top Bun - and business is booming, not least because a deadly Cereal Killer has murdered all the other bakers in town. Gromit is worried that they may be the next victims, but Wallace does not care, as he has fallen head over heels in love with Piella Bakewell, former star of the Bake-O-Lite bread commercials. So Gromit is left to run things on his own, when he would much rather be getting better acquainted with Piella's lovely pet poodle Fluffles. But then Gromit makes a shocking discovery which points to the killer's true identity. Can he save his master from becoming the next baker to be butchered? And does Fluffles know more than she is saying? It all adds up to a classic 'who-doughnut' mystery, as four-time Academy Award-winning director Nick Park creates a hilarious new masterpiece in the tradition of 'master of suspense' Alfred Hitchcock. Featuring the voices of Peter Sallis (Wallace) and Sally Lindsay (Piella Bakewell).</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p08cbbb70e710e5c8032baa11e049b287</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>12 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play marbles, and it's driving Grizzy crazy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6da67b82a65bfa51ab80ff34f6cbd6a4</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Home Sweet Rome</title>
    <desc>Lucy reinvents herself on a field trip. Francesca gets distracted from a big opportunity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p697489a957d30713091b1154a0dd0e92</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>12 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Now that B-troupe is officially going to the nationals, Cleo isn?t so sure they have earned it. Nick has concerns of his own, but an A-Troupe legend visits and shares that there is another, controversial, way to ensure the very best team represents the studio at the competition. As Cleo turns on her teammates, Richelle relies on hers after an upsetting run-in with a certain someone, and Ozzy speculates as to whether there is someone leaking private information about TNS.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e742e8b065ff2e30ef86aa70dcb2454</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>12 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Experience the most extraordinary ride in the universe ? falling into a black hole.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa561a213adf41071149e12e7759f39fd</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>12 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When two different pieces of flat-pack furniture are delivered to the Farmer and Bitzer, confusion ensues as they start to mix up the pieces. Shaun and the flock are forced to give them a lesson in following instructions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6faba19999bdaf0067c3c03224597602</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Count Duckula is back, and he is determined to take over the world, one terrible TV show at a time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p78f9f0a97c4d271042d27c59788eb11c</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang are fed up with dinner lady Olive's completely inedible school dinners. In their mission to 'drop the slop', they discover a poster of her past career as a singer. The gang ask her to join The Dinmakers, hoping she'll swap a life in the kitchen for fame. However, after unleashing Olive's inner diva, their new mission is how to get Olive back into the kitchen.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbd5d1427de633c016391ca89ecdc571b</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the kids wonder about what they?ll be when they grow up, Mouse?s enhanced online career quiz leads Boy to think he is destined to be an astronaut, with Girl thinking she will end up a boring safety inspector. Both struggle to embrace their fates - but Mouse?s science can?t be wrong, can it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4905b446520109c731d611286b667d14</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1bed2246b467d85e2f2a79c7a7954ed4</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Needing a rocking horse for his daughter?s birthday present, a dad asks Ninja Express for help, only for them to return with the legendary Trojan Horse.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbbaa2421fa7d34bde857fdf9d1e6a1e8</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Olympia and Otis are forced to babysit Baby Genius.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p974f250c0a921f69903be20fe21bae38</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug faces Monarch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6455015a67e68bcfcbdb7a80e4a0db6a</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:55AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Stormy Weather - aka Aurore Bor?ale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p46e354ffdf97b682b4acb0e2971f158e</image>
    <start>08:55AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Back on the Brave Olivine, Liko, Roy and Dot receive an unexpected challenge to battle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc610269f8f8b3a6cfce6acc923f40f3</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings decide to play hide-and-seek in the Savannah.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b103f5c6909d7e3276e3613f4e5eee3</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings organise a mega-party, leading to the cabin being invaded by bats.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p017dac7b4c386b657d1c3d9999e8170c</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings activate the air conditioner's AI, causing it to fall in love with the fridge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54e09a09adf7855a626c534a8050680a</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Cheese and Dog are teasing each other about the things they like to do. However, trying out each other's interests causes them to realise what they?ve been missing out on.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb63508683548e8c2e7b000bf9934c155</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel meets the stars of the new Superman film, we show you how to make your very own garden using just a jam jar, and Shini attempts martial arts.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc100e7f2b34fc4f2fa79872acb61360f</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Mouse brings home an old ice cream truck, the kids start their own smoothie business. However, the town's lovable ice cream man, Uncle Bub, isn't happy about the competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7bbf029937d9754bf6213941d447763a</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the family visits a farm, Cheese bonds with Delilah the cow over all things dairy. However, bringing her home to live with the family leads to all sorts of problems.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69a2672618969229d48692833eab3c29</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Veiled Victories. A-Troupe discover they must compete in regionals and save the studio from financial ruin. [S,AD.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef almost ruins National Hotdog Day when he forgets to book the Hot-Diggity-Doggity Dog.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa0aac1dd1681a527aae9c418a5fe84d4</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef brokers a truce with lice by selecting three kids to 'host' them on their heads.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p300a4c3a34f447193e6a22be19fcab31</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Dreamers in Tune. A-Troupe tries to stay focused on regionals as Heath and Pete learn more about the Brawl. Anthony helps Adele with an audition, while Ariana feels overworked. [S,AD.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum sends the bros to the racetrack for a bumpy ride! Adam and Joe?s driving skills are put to the test as they strap into some Power Turn Buggies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ba7345b81feed2c5dbf12ae30ab4227</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>Dragons, dinos and divas! The Kwapongs craft fire-breathers, Romesh Ranganathan draws a rapping T-rex, and Bristles dives into the bold, brilliant world of Frida Kahlo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35625862ebe527b01a7c825cbdc1577a</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Find Our Way. Jett tries to find her place in A-Troupe but is feeling left out. Ethan reminisces about his time in Paris, while Adele looks to a new opportunity abroad. [S,AD.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel meets the stars of the new Superman film, we show you how to make your very own garden using just a jam jar, and Shini attempts martial arts.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc100e7f2b34fc4f2fa79872acb61360f</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>All We Need. As Adele says goodbye to The Next Step, she tries to mend fences with Olive. Things get complicated between Heath and Pascale as Anthony deals with Adele leaving. [S,AD.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. Debbie from Debbie's Pizzeria has doubled... not once, but twice, creating four Debbies! When one of the four Debbies goes missing, Olive and Otto need to find her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a30aee0211d8e7bb41fb568084b8772</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. Olive and Otto are called in to help when objects and then people start disappearing inside an Italian restaurant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa2acfba8934b5409d676f692e0538657</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>The Big Storm. An overprotective Heath accuses Grace of sabotage, while Grace and Jonah make a bet to make it on to A-Troupe. Meanwhile, Izzy grapples with keeping Anthony's secret. [S,AD.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Can underdog Cranmede take on the mighty reigning champions Gorsforth at the Interschool Country Dance Championships? And can Tam overcome her dance demons in time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1485a447b6247106aa11cbbdb4498d5d</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Do It for Myself. Pete auditions for dance captain, and Olive and Grace search for their place on the team. [S,AD.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Mr Ludcomb wants to win the Best Headteacher Award, but his plans go wrong when Pickle?s magic accidentally turns the rubbish bins into monsters that end up terrorising the school.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p081c97c5c537d121a2f9de518bf239f4</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Game Face. No longer dance captain, Anthony finds following orders difficult. Jett and Ariana try to be friends again, while Heath's history with Daisy complicates things with Pascale. [S,AD.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>To investigate why tummy rumbles are so loud when you?re hungry, the doctors call in the supersized stomach of Mega Xand! When Dr Chris and Dr Xand count down the Top 5 Bizarre-est Body Parts You Never Knew You Had, you will discover that the mysterious palmaris longus is so bizarre that you might not have it at all! The big question in Ouchology is whether it will be Dr Chris, Dr Xand or Dr Ronx who gets snotted by their kid quizmasters. If the doctors can put all the organs in the right place on their own bodies, they could win enough points to avoid the snot - but someone has to come last! Elsewhere, for Investigation Ouch!, Dr Chris finds out why real doctors are doing fake operations on fake organs inside fake patients in Nottingham. At the emergency department in Edinburgh, Alice has hurt her head and arm by accidentally running into a fence. And when Finlay arrives with burns on his forearms, the medics think it might have something to do with parsnips.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe8147477dc78b233d22fec7bfd20d4eb</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Inside Out. Keeping Team Brawl's secret leaves Ariana torn. Michelle and Eldon take a look back at their past as Anthony avoids confronting his present. [S,AD.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Revolting space travel, evolving cows, pet mushrooms, and Einstein watches a car on a trampoline.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7998a04b3556c531c826aa1df0c638e1</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Let's Dance Tonight. Pete tries to juggle regionals and the Brawl, while Ethan and Olive become suspicious. [S,AD.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>Aoife and Clanger run head-to-head for school president. When power-mad Clanger?s supporters fall for his free donuts, begging Jessica for help might be Aoife?s only hope.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7364ccddbdc87d7ed3e9750f1e246e6e</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Super Massive Mega Star. As the regionals qualifier clashes with the Brawl's, A-Troupe struggle under the weight of all the secrets they have kept from each other. [S,AD.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>As the players embrace their new positions, Christina helps Andrew train to be a striker. However, an anonymous message leaves her facing an impossible decision.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1444817816479a2ec3ae0de4e77894e9</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>New: The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Hard to Live. The fallout from the regionals qualifiers starts to settle. Izzy tries to join Brawl, while Olive considers moving on to cheer, and Kenzie comes back to visit an injured Pete. [S.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>New: The Next Step</title>
    <desc>To the Wolves. Pascale and Heath try to repair their relationship, but the arrival of Daisy throws a wrench in their plans. Ariana and Michelle team up to get A-Troupe back to regionals. [S.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Courtney must go all day without correcting her friends, regardless of what they do wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe12d009fb4b08949cdf975f6bbb47a8</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>A walkie-talkie hidden inside a chili dog causes Harold to worry an alien has arrived.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd55181ac1b0277a6a03b77b9b2b7602a</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When Courtney refuses to share her valuable rare toy, friends join forces to question her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e518a8dee62348a4c879f5a681603a2</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>New: The Next Step</title>
    <desc>The Comeback. Daisy's return makes things more difficult for Heath. Eldon and Michelle consider parting ways as an injured Pete feels left out of the Brawl. [S.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron releases a new strain of elephant flu. Can DM and Penfold find the cure before everyone is turned into a snotty elephant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51f8cb9515674180a911e9981fe74ee0</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Queen of Weevils returns and magically convinces Danger Mouse he is a medieval knight on a quest to rescue a fair maiden.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd28414b63d33d861786886ff541d1233</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>New: The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Take Control. A-Troupers begin to switch over to Team Brawl, but when Olive and Eldon figure out a way back into regionals, Anthony and Ethan have their loyalties tested. [S.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Duckula kidnaps the writers and Danger Mouse faces being written out of his own show! Can DM call on the help of the sound department to fight back before Duckula changes the world forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa49a2f94ca890a1640782da819493ada</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids' mean neighbour Wanda has started enforcing a dogs-on-leashes law. Boy, Girl, Cheese and Mouse each come up with ideas about how to show that Dog is special and doesn?t need a leash.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf8723c8d7f782d6c8c671fa9819a3ba</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>New: The Next Step</title>
    <desc>They Say Love. Kenzie helps Pete make a difficult decision. The Brawl's love theme gets in the way of Heath and Daisy fixing their friendship, and Michelle turns to Eldon for Brawl advice. [S.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Dog reveals he's colour blind, the kids rally to help him see the world like they do. Mouse makes him some colour-correction glasses, and Dog is blown away by colour. He becomes an artist and neglects the family as he focuses on his painting career. But when the day of his art gallery premiere comes, Dog will have to choose between art and family.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcf67c683814674b034097cf82bfe82d8</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse is bored of always doing the same things the same way, so Girl suggests he starts thinking outside the box and lives his life differently. Boy and Dog don?t agree, but Mouse, Cat and Cheese follow Girl's lead and it's fun! But when things get out of control, Girl turns to Boy and Dog for help getting things back to normal. With so much chaos in the house, maybe it's time everyone lives back inside the box again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd58240466c21a6b26183b09425e4d16c</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>New: The Next Step</title>
    <desc>The Music Made Me Do It. Brawl pits Ariana and Michelle against each other as Lucien shakes up regionals rehearsals. Meanwhile, Izzy tries to overcome their dance captain doubts. [S.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings activate the air conditioner's AI, causing it to fall in love with the fridge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54e09a09adf7855a626c534a8050680a</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds a polar bear and realises they are from the same species.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1cb689afd001542531ecfbda6e5efcfc</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Blossom accidentally uses a witch?s broom to make sticks for toasting marshmallows, the owner of the broom casts a spell of squeaky voices on all the heroes. The spell will be lifted once the heroes have returned with new broomstick branches. A simple enough quest, think the heroes, until they realise that a witch?s broom can only be made from the branches of the Really Spooky Tree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe37511be85e501039449287ddef18d2b</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>New: The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Always Dramatic. The Brawl kicks off, and A-Troupe is there to support the Brawlers. Meanwhile, Daisy is confronted by her old team as Eldon confronts his nerves. [S.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Trevor is extremely proud of being the clever one in the gang and thinks that his smart mouth is his superpower. However, his friends feel that sometimes his jokes go too far - and they are right to be concerned! When Mr Friendlyface sends the heroes on a quest to prevent Toothgrinder the Ogre from messing up the village green, it?s Trevor?s smart mouth that puts all the heroes in danger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc10a55045431109408268b6cc99aaf5</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>New: The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Got Your Back. Ethan wrestles with an important decision that could impact both the studio and his relationship, while Daisy's plan to save Heath and Pascale's relationship backfires. [S.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:05PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Salam City goes dark when the power goes out, but Mansour finds a clever solution.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf9fc7e52810177a3801b603b4cf0b803</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Mansour and friends have a surprising and confusing encounter with a very different Blink.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d071457a6abec7f0701d8494f703c07</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>New: The Next Step</title>
    <desc>End of the Road. It's the final day of the Brawl, and Team Micheldon are going head-to-head with the Masked Sancers as The Next Step's last hope to save the studio. [S.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:05PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>Chris responds to the network?s request for a holiday special by making the campers hunt for eggs. Who cares that it?s not Easter? And who cares if the hunt is for Cassowary eggs? With the teams now merged, it?s all about being the first one back with an egg and winning immunity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc760bf686edd8f6771aabfec957d9833</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>New: The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Finale. With the Brawl concluded, The Next Step use their recent fame to fundraise, while Lucien plots to destroy the studio once and for all - but not if A-Troupe has anything to say about it! [S.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>13 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>An all-night gaming session turns the Farmer and Bitzer into sleep-deprived zombies the next day. Shaun takes the chance to change Bitzer?s checklist to suit himself, but he manages to miss the final item: shearing time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3f60727be2d84e2a3113f71146047e4</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's plan to hold a surprise party for Professor Squawkencluck is undone when the Baron releases killer birthday presents into the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p142b27e7bb29436619c5a233aa8b58ec</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Mrs Creecher confiscates Dennis's rare sour sweetie, the Tongue Destroyer! Dennis is desperate to get the sweet back and takes his friends on an adventure to the school's Confiscatorium, a secret place where all confiscated goods are hidden, in the depths of Bash Street School.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59345ded18b2ac0ee7e8394444da7b49</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy gets his dream job at the collectibles store, but when a family of screeching birds makes the store entrance their home, the customers stay away. It's Boy's job to move the birds, but Girl discovers they?re endangered and have to stay. If Boy can't get rid of the birds he'll be fired! But what's more important - his job or the birds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d56a7d28e8f920ef9622a88ac8f08de</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6053a7360d74f8d87f0ceb1c0a23cb16</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>In order to crown a new king, Merlin summons the Ninjas to pull the legendary sword from the stone. After a few tries, they realize the solution is right under their noses.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcbca7621e76f54ad4a7abff2f2b3e1ed</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Oona tells the story of when she switched bodies with a fly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p22925506da8094ca8edb1d14348f8800</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Trevor is extremely proud of being the clever one in the gang and thinks that his smart mouth is his superpower. However, his friends feel that sometimes his jokes go too far - and they are right to be concerned! When Mr Friendlyface sends the heroes on a quest to prevent Toothgrinder the Ogre from messing up the village green, it?s Trevor?s smart mouth that puts all the heroes in danger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc10a55045431109408268b6cc99aaf5</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug faces Adrien?s friend Nino, now known as The Bubbler.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p79f738d543f24014bb26a44ee0898c02</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings are determined to train Grizzy, who would rather lounge around.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ca463f9ae9f9317a00cc20392ad8fe1</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel meets the stars of the new Superman film, we show you how to make your very own garden using just a jam jar, and Shini attempts martial arts.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc100e7f2b34fc4f2fa79872acb61360f</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs take flight with stained-glass wings, Jill Scott MBE draws a footballing big cat, and Bristles gives the juicy lowdown on artist Giuseppe Arcimboldo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3df0fbebb2280bb7ac68e32c6cd4ccac</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>4 O'Clock Club</title>
    <desc>Polly has helped Evan with his family - but can he ever forgive her for revealing his secret? Meanwhile, Owen and Chester compete to see who will win the Pupil of the Year trophy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3567df068fd85e6c3a4a4983a19f8e79</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Someone has been eating the cookies in the caf?, and there is a rodent-shaped hole in reception. Thinking that there is a rat in the leisure centre, Danny and Mick put a plan into action to catch the illusive rodent. They will do whatever they can to find the culprit, including making a human-sized mouse trap.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c19cbcdf2d2f8f4c009ed8ccaab4ed1</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>After last year?s staff photo ended in messy disaster, Sharon is determined to make sure this one goes without a hitch. So she tasks Danny and Mick with keeping the leisure centre and themselves totally clean until the photo takes place. With extra uniforms and all the cleaning equipment needed, surely they surely can?t fail at this simple task - can they.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4556df7ddaac0f4308f2b9445fee756e</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>The bros go back to school as undercover teachers but have to do as the other says! Luckily, Glow Up Star Axel is there to help disguise the Bros as Mr Longgrass and Mr Pickles.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p571d409f63a245f1e5501a801ed99804</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The brothers learn about animals that like to take things slowly. They discover the top speed of a giant African land snail and see just how slow a sleepy sloth can get.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9388fc35c97163db3530f348127eb5ec</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall and the team brave the intense heat of the Arizona desert as they go in search of more incredible animals for the Deadly 60 list. In order to demonstrate the awesome hunting skills of the Harris hawk, Steve becomes their prey for the day. Some state-of-the-art technology helps Steve track down deadly rattlesnakes and a real monster. It is then off to the mountains in search of a very elusive cat, the cougar. After seeing pictures captured by remote cameras, the team know the cats are there, but can they find them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e7c902e33117911e163afd1b54ce833</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve and the team are on the search for deadly animals in the steaming swamps of the southern USA. The contenders are everywhere, not least the alligators that live in just about every pond and lake. But the first animal on the list is a complete surprise, a monster fish with two rows of sharp fangs that certainly keeps Steve on his toes. The crew find themselves up to their armpits in a swamp hoping to find a deadly snake with the unusual name of cottonmouth. Last but not least, Steve and his team come face to face with an enormous record-breaking predatory turtle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8963833a0703ec6ebc11ba5dc0132d4a</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Things get explosive when Dr Chris and Dr Xand look at how spots are made, plus an incredible emergency service at work in Australia: the Flying Doctors.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b4c137dff0cf46b799270e7eb64b46d</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketch show. King Charles I sends someone else to get married for him, a new recruit regrets joining the Georgian army, and Queen Cleopatra reveals her beauty secrets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf1cf98d0967e2d2e5471d0911a918075</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketch show. Barmy Roman emperor Caligula fails to invade Britain, King Henry VIII plays tennis while Anne Boleyn is executed, and some Saxon monks throw a party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd0af2c7887e8b62742cc5dd446c9fb7d</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Bionic ends up dressed as a rabbit when Nitro pranks him at a fake photoshoot, and the rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes as they prank the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf7d7f9299d05e5c92784905daf4991d</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold must travel to the Twystyverse to stop the evil tyrant Baron Silas von Penfold from taking over both versions of the Earth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96bd7bb99d9e77929da195732a4166fb</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When the Baron speeds up the rotation of Earth using windmills, Danger Mouse and Penfold age 300 years and must take on their nemesis as very, very, very old men.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b0704c5d4df92b6473d98abf4e56522</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Penfold saves a celebrity from certain doom he becomes a media sensation. DM smells a rat... or at least some evil villainous hamster from another dimension.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8296206497ab04e0f3f7e8b912dfd6ee</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Rubi?s dance machine gets accidentally muddled up with Crusty the Robot Pie?s coding. Dennis and Gnasher have to dance on it all day in perfect sync, or Crusty?s entire persona will be wiped forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc196d03c4998053896105cc5f5c04bc8</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A patch of wet cement, a boy and a dog itching to put their prints into it and a policeman determined not to let that happen. Can Dennis and Gnasher muddle Sergeant Slipper long enough before the cement sets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3cbcc2b42f737a35aae5268e19aff3be</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Dennis thinks Gnasher has trashed a valuable piece of hideous art, the gang try desperately to cover up the damage and produce a decoy that is as convincingly terrible as the original.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4fc5d89880a983b655e137d80434250a</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The blossom has gone missing. No, not Blossom the unicorn, the blossom on the trees! The heroes are sent on a quest deep into the heart of the forest, where legend has it you can see a face watching you from the trees. Twinkle doesn?t believe in legends, but when help comes from nowhere as they try and stop the scoundrel that is stealing the blossom, she is forced to reconsider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2f8d2357ef662dfdfa8453de1222ecd1</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are relieved that the loud, threatening voice they can hear actually belongs to a small slug named Zorgoth, who is armed with a megaphone. However, when Zorgoth uses his Orb of Compression to shrink the heroes down to the size of ants, their relief evaporates. They must now embark on a long and dangerous quest, through their picnic items and beyond, to warn the Council before Zorgoth shrinks the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe50df153eaba594e89a65c54ae953f0c</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes quest to stop Balthazar from turning forest folk into household objects, Herbert realises that he can defeat the wizard?s spell by using the magic tricks he has practiced. Blossom is particularly intrigued by Herbert the Peculiar?s tricks, not to mention his stage name, so when Herbert himself is transformed into a table lamp, it?s Blossom the Very Impressive to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p02b5755668bd5974ec3f672d77162daf</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a pig who has the ability to find food using his snout.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1ce8e7ccc147b0ae527c57d37725d16</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings take part in a safari photo competition on an animal reserve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p87591ace945bfdf453a92c3829fd0bc0</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings are trapped in a ball, and an ostrich sits on it, mistaking it for an egg.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd360edab947bab57be77ecad7762ad6c</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The savannah animals bow down before whoever sits on the throne-shaped boulder.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e3bcdf201997d8e0f31003c453c9d11</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The band get a new trumpet player, with disastrous consequences. Also, the apple dropouts hatch an explosive plan to break free, and superhero Slippery Nana comes to the rescue to save a tomato... sort of! Deep in the back of the fridge, Frankfurter's monster is on the rampage, and Dr Rhu-barb surprises the judges with his white rabbit trick in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9d8cc7f011cc4e57ef694c747ebd22f</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>A mischievous new breed of dragons called Vine Tails steal the Book of Dragons.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31be02cdee0c0389b82f418d2ad9cf2a</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>The girls try to cheer up Celeste, who wants to get expelled so she can go home to see her mother. Meanwhile, Mary-Lou finds herself facing a snail invasion when she takes an art class.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p01f62a429f0c9978d02fb2772f4513ae</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Addie and Audrey?s friendship blossoms as they go door-to-door to spread the word about Juniper?s witches. Maggie starts a secret rebellion, putting her at odds with Elinor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fe90bee762eed019908d0b716da7059</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>An overprotective Heath accuses Grace of sabotage, while Grace and Jonah make a bet to make it on to A-Troupe. Meanwhile, Izzy grapples with keeping Anthony?s secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5b4c76f289d443a95cb05ffbadf7a365</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>With A-Troupe all in on regionals, Pete takes his eyes off the Brawl and auditions for dance captain. Olive looks for a place where she belongs, while Grace dreams of joining A-Troupe.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e554040d8151175d38b78010cb1824d</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Carter, Glen, Zane, and Skye must hide their secret identities from everyone. They are struggling with teamwork, when hot-headed Gormian Bors tries to prove the Scions don?t have what it takes. The Scions finally unite against him but, in so doing, they attract the attention of Graven.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p16497753ab657a2216c622950836aa27</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings use a frog with hypnotising powers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbd74eae5287515b461c9282bcc4d8e8</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
