<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Jackie needs help getting her horse to jump. However, Hugh is no ordinary horse ? he's a pantomime horse! It?s when the band discover that Hugh loves dancing that they save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbcc938140d2c5b9a2f14e938d192c5a7</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Little bro Callum challenges Adam and Joe to bring out their inner sloths in order to avoid facing a forfeit on the Wheel of Doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3e4ac01bb9021818eb7a55a4f25ff05c</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Periwinkle strays during a Bialowieza Forest mission and discovers a rare European Bison.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5cfcadb351b0d4704df34ba5d5a139ba</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad and Cosima both think they're the best at pranking. Their prank war quickly spirals out of control, until Big Lizard finally reveals Proxima's real pranking champion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea0f60cf71247ea3d276941d6971e477</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's over-reliance on gadgets prompts Colonel K to send his top agent on a tech-free nature retreat. Unbeknownst to Danger Mouse, Greenback has the same plans for his daughter, Delilah, whose social media obsession has also spiralled out of control. Back at HQ Penfold is tasked with protecting the entire world from the threat of super-villainy. Stripped off his gadgets, DM struggles to adapt to life in the wilderness and, when a talking pine cone called Conni begins to offer him survival tips, he begins to question his own sanity. Soon enough, Delilah catches wind of DM's presence and she plots to destroy him as a means of getting back into her Dad's good books.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p75c10893273f4622c94d4cf5fb696d17</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The class dig up a mysterious time capsule which sets them off on a race to find hidden treasure before Walter or a greed-crazed Paul the Potato can find it first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p659edd59775ca7523bb64a0d16d30e47</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The blossom has gone missing. No, not Blossom the unicorn, the blossom on the trees! The heroes are sent on a quest deep into the heart of the forest, where legend has it you can see a face watching you from the trees. Twinkle doesn?t believe in legends, but when help comes from nowhere as they try and stop the scoundrel that is stealing the blossom, she is forced to reconsider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2f8d2357ef662dfdfa8453de1222ecd1</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>Having found fame around the world as a young child, talented teen drummer Nandi Bushell sets out on a new musical path.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p72a61a393180e6e77e7017d8203cad5a</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko comes up with a plan for confronting Lapras of the Six Heroes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p492011ee27c5adfb7d000b0355f1123c</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>A weird glowing fish has lured every fish in the area to its bioluminescence. When Kaiko and Will also fall under its spell, Ant and Fontaine must rescue their parents - while wearing blindfolds against the hypnotic glow.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p61cdb386fec3ad084876177dea337b41</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Fed up with Dennis pulling the wool over Mrs Creecher's eyes, Walter orchestrates a robot to take over Class 3C - with disastrous results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p09cd14a7c66d70b97a06114b327de9ed</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The heroes find themselves fighting for their lives on an alien world in Quark's latest money-spinning sports event.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a349849bdee1e607399cc7c77be8b24</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Felix asks the Ninjas for a superpower so that he can meet Mega Powerful Man. However, when villainous Lance traps every superhero, the Ninjas and Felix must step in and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81c0111f0dd84eb090eb31b4ef54b492</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. Shaun finds the farmer's old record player on the dump and organises a rave in the barn, but trouble looms when the naughty pigs gatecrash the party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d85e8a5e8a7604eacfba23dddab4e8d</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The cabin comes to life and wants to return to Canada without Grizzy or the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd3bf809eba7aa4ce014113e511d0efb6</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Gramps tells the kids about a heavenly clearing in the woods, and they decide to make it their hang-out spot for the summer. However, the Smith twins find out about it too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1b4ca7a59f2228a8a82b61b74bf242b1</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The forest has run out of bath sponges and is becoming very stinky. Their latest order never arrived, and so the heroes must quest under the sea to Merhaven to collect them. However, Hoofius, whose singing stinks worse than his armpits, decides to enter the annual Merhaven Song Contest and accidentally causes a simple quest to collect bath sponges to turn into something much more perilous.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ed5d646aa33c0f016a4f842cc22d80c</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Agent Olympia is not happy when an agent with the same name shows up at headquarters. Curriculum: Measuring temperature.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3dc5e187c321f7b4f6f77226abb9c3ea</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Ms O tells Olympia and Otis a story about a famous villain duo. Curriculum: Adding, subtracting and multiplying by zero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf57f18551a75efc65bc912f7566e48af</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef almost ruins National Hotdog Day when he forgets to book the Hot-Diggity-Doggity Dog.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa0aac1dd1681a527aae9c418a5fe84d4</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face an invisible enemy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa159bd9b067167936a1a52cfe1fdcccb</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>The Rising Volt Tacklers locate Entei of the Six Heroes, but something seems off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8596d2d582588aa0f3912eab1985f024</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>The winning teams return to the arena to take on Mario Kart in the Grand Final. Who will win the competition and claim the Game on Grandparents trophy and GOAT title.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc965b4b97374457007445f0dd4a65bf1</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Pete tries to juggle both the Brawl and regionals, but it may be too much. Ethan discovers a huge secret within A-Troupe, and Olive is suspicious of Ariana and Grace?s friendship.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1b7576d62429f4032216d555f0bfb517</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Abby takes on a wheelchair motocross challenge ? can she perform the tricks and stunts taught to her by world champion, Tomas Woods.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54135eb056632874cbaba8a329c5925c</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The Farmer opens a petting zoo but loses control of the customers. Can Shaun restore order.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p98cb08547b6cab15d2f88c4e8b2a223b</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When a sudden urge to fly the Mark IV hits, Penfold leads a confused Danger Mouse to a farm, from which he claims to feel an unexplained magnetic pull. An entranced Penfold is met by a shadowy figure - Granny Penfold! Penfold recounts his childhood years on Granny?s farm, where he was trained in the ancient martial art of Farm Fu; a farming based martial art. Granny needs Penfold?s help to retrieve the sacred Fung Farm Book of Farm Fu, which has fallen into the hands of her enemies, causing farm animals to turn evil and rise up against their owners.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5bc9fb86a9c9d89de3a6896036c3a7d9</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface steals Professor Von Screwtop's Pastry-based Intelligent Espionage unit (PIE) after forming a strong bond with the pie-shaped robot. Pieface is dismayed when Walter steals it from him to protect his dad from the embarrassing footage the PIE's memory chip holds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4db578615381ab592eeaeea97d895804</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The family have been telling their deepest, darkest secrets to Cat for years. But when Cat finds one of Mouse?s inventions that gives her intelligence and speech, she threatens to tell all their secrets if they don't do everything she asks. The kids must decide between living under their feline pharaoh's thumb or confessing their secrets to each other.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfed16d83f85eb7f2591ee30d5e8a513b</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p61dd694df56fdab7c28daaacef9942b6</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play marbles, and it's driving Grizzy crazy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6da67b82a65bfa51ab80ff34f6cbd6a4</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy exchanges his indifferent fish with the Lemmings' affectionate and lively fish.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p07e8c90f4bc95e6cc138af9db789ccd7</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit is called to Odd Squad?s top-secret security facility.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pce45058c1f25d13694109f555e8b4a3b</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Helsing should never have trusted the gang with his mind swap ray. Now, Charlie is a kettle, Pierce is a phone, and Snorp has stolen his body.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4049d564b490860df3677dc6ab0d2388</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>An angry Swampclops follows the heroes back from their quest for a giant raspberry, so Hoofius must abandon his chances of winning the bake-off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3dcc908834fa89d31657019c7b692113</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Danny and Mick?s dad Clive has turned up with his latest in a long line of ?sure-fire? money making schemes: washing customers? cars in the car park while they use the leisure centre. The boys are happy to help and are soon scrubbing away, but when Joy finds out and demands a free wash, the boys clean her beloved old banger so hard it falls to bits. Don?t worry lads, Clive knows how to fix this? or at least replace one problem with a much bigger problem. Yeah, thanks dad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cf1ec3aa72fe269d49ee1c868538607</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs build 'Kwembley', their DIY table football pitch, Mandy Barker wows turning plastic waste into art, and comedian Aisling Bea draws a puffin with a potato waffle problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1500fcc3c13870d2b9e03edb99166eb0</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings create a shadow puppet show where seven papercut lemmings confront a bear.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc86af08c9c02f6ba215273b5a0f148b3</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: Sun and Moon</title>
    <desc>When Ash Ketchum oversleeps on his tenth birthday, he ends up with a stubborn Pikachu instead of the first partner Pok?mon he wanted! Together with new friends Verity and Sorrel, Ash must journey across the land to return the Rainbow Wing to the Legendary Pok?mon Ho-Oh. However, they must face off with arrogant Trainer Cross and the mysterious Mythical Pok?mon Marshadow. Will they succeed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcc3c89cf3bdb0c6aa17ba489732e14f6</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Tubes</title>
    <desc>Olympia shows viewers how to solve an odd problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd96c9fb1a748407ad7e7f561bbc8cdd9</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Swumpy sneaks into school, and Pickle accidentally makes him super clever so that she comes top in her test! This backfires when she has to represent the school in a maths competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9907bc19c58d6741f49861caa644601d</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>Ken assigns everyone the task of filming a promo to introduce themselves to the world, but it brings up unexpected connections and jealousies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p496de0671a31835b94228fcc25875a55</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>New girl Leah helps Christina with her nerves, but will a talent show derail their friendship? A new welfare officer at Hawx pushes Coach Byrne out of his comfort zone too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb0246254a7a8987821c13b46adf316d</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>Steve's on a mission to find dinosaurs that have something a little special... fearsome killers, with incredible abilities! Get ready for a sensory sensation! His quest sees him race in the dark like a troodon and track prey from miles away taking tips from the daspletosaurus, and finally he gets his hands on a real-life caiman to show how their pressure pits are just like that of the spinosaurus. Strap yourself in for a sensory overload.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6201883edcbd2ef25e7761ad149708e</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>The band turn detective and go in search of Rosie?s lucky flying disc which she needs for a competition. While cracking the case, they discover a surprising secret about Whiff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd466b430d7261385636385604b35fe4</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Adam and Joe take to the streets to become living statues in Callum?s latest challenge - but who will be the best man standing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae94f7750320dd3374c20dbb2662af9d</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>A storm carries sharks into a swamp so the Octonauts must help all the creatures coexist.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pca63cb1cc42fdbf159b0303cc05620d1</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Cosima takes over Dad's mission to film a unique underwater plant. But his special camera proves harder to operate than she'd thought, and Big Lizard keeps getting distracted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p978b38140949d563c78029d0cfe54f3e</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Snowman is hired as Danger Mouse's new sidekick, leaving Penfold without a job.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb9a8b62eb1f051a7a86e10437f9214c</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Dennis and the gang think they have caused Ralf to lose his job, they're determined to make his last day at Bash Street School totally blam by setting up the greatest prank Ralf's ever known.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3d939c9462f01933b550eae67571eb8</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are relieved that the loud, threatening voice they can hear actually belongs to a small slug named Zorgoth, who is armed with a megaphone. However, when Zorgoth uses his Orb of Compression to shrink the heroes down to the size of ants, their relief evaporates. They must now embark on a long and dangerous quest, through their picnic items and beyond, to warn the Council before Zorgoth shrinks the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe50df153eaba594e89a65c54ae953f0c</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>Jack is just 13 years old, but he is already one of the best young darts players in the world. As the British youth darts champion, he has his sights set on an even bigger title: world champion. Jack travels to Gibraltar for the World Junior Open, where he will compete both in the singles and as part of the England squad. However, the road to victory won?t be easy, as Jack has previously lost a world final against Luke Littler, who has since gone on to become professional world champion at just 17. Can Jack turn the tables and bring home the gold? We follow Jack as he trains, competes and faces off against his biggest rivals, including his England teammate Archie, currently ranked number one in the world. With fast-paced action, nail-biting matches and the pressure of playing for his country, we follow the highs and lows of Jack?s road to the top.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p78959b3cdf19b2ba7a972b96f195fadb</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Amethio challenges the black Rayquaza, and Terapagos displays some of its true power.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p362de3d9335cc2d2ba79ff8660f6238a</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>While fighting over Viking treasure, the Nektons take over the Dark Orca. But the pirates in turn take over the Aronnax. Neither side is happy about strangers in their homes, but neither side is willing to back down.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p182d1acdf3f80be57cabbfbb24b20c7e</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A bungled attempt at a stunt leads to Dennis accidentally becoming an internet star and Beanotown celebrity! But his moment of fame is short and Dennis is soon replaced by Walter's cat, who can play the piano. Dennis has to stage the best stunt yet to gain back his audience.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2448826bf08a8b69aefa3652e97decf5</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>In order to stop a deranged Victorian time-travelling chimp from uninventing the world, Danger Mouse and Penfold must arrive in the past just before the nick of time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb89086a78e1589c68cd9ddbc5eb06285</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas must use their imagination when Anna orders a new toy as a birthday present for her father - a toymaker who's already invented every toy imaginable.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb22bbd3bc21c3ae9f1950c247833d48</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. The flock think they are in for fun when a kite blows into their field.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef5d96d96f8e8c29656c5a6cab5c2c7c</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a box filled with fortune cookies close to the Great Wall of China.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pba2796334e942468921c463b1c433065</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The gang want to win theme park tickets that are up for grabs in a robot fighting contest. They ask to use Mouse?s unbeatable robot, but he prefers to help them build their own.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pafe052db79735499dff691fceca1bb7c</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Only wood elves have ever defeated the mighty Eye of Vernon hat, so when the Riddlemaster wears the eye to take over the forest, the heroes quest to Wood Elf Wood to get help. However, Twinkle really doesn?t want to, as wood elves are so stuck up! Struggling to contain her irritation with their high-and-mighty ways, Twinkle still manages to offend them, and the heroes wonder how they will ever save the forest now.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32df456943a31359aa3e76648f081c8f</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia and Otis are tasked with calling a truce between feuding guests. Curriculum: Using a Venn Diagram, 3D shapes: spheres and cubes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a7cc9c25316a9316d40d4a87c98e2f3</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Ms O leaves headquarters in the hands of an unlikely crew. Curriculum: Spatial Sense: Mapping, Position, Location and Direction.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd794773fd1ca66f3bb6c8d6344136323</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef brokers a truce with lice by selecting three kids to 'host' them on their heads.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p300a4c3a34f447193e6a22be19fcab31</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug faces Argos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9dd5da959e11c2622285ca2b471cc2ec</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>The Rising Volt Tacklers finally get a rematch with the Black Rayquaza.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p76a6cd10b0dd4098d3f8b997309657ba</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Top Minecraft and Mario Kart tips to help you turn your grandparent into a gaming legend. Plus Jelly, Yammy and Slogo face off in the ultimate Minecraft build showdown! Who will be crowned the Pro Gamer Champion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pefa6da1af07a4d5e59f2a20d30b7e1d1</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>As the regionals qualifier clashes with the Brawl?s, A-Troupe struggle under the weight of all the secrets they have kept from each other.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe113b7e440701120dd4668cb899cf7d1</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Joel tries Kite Foiling with Olympic Gold medallist Ellie Aldridge ? can he navigate a board across the waves using the wind power of a kite.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7cfd6fd223c9ab06eead334bd48901a4</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. Shirley the sheep has put on weight, so Shaun helps her get in shape with a rigorous exercise regime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62965f8ec13c5343b9a20d521aff8707</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse and the Baron are forced to team up in order to defeat a cheese-obsessed villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc640fda27059d028e627a20d12c99338</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Mayor Wilbur passes a law to increase healthy eating in Beanotown, replacing all foods with peas...of the mushy variety! The gang must avoid the people of Beanotown who are rapidly turning into Zompeas after eating the green mush. Dennis uses the only ordinary peas in town to sabotage Wilbur's mush-making factory and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41d58d1465e51eb4de1792f354b29a85</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Boy and Girl start receiving lavish gifts addressed to ?two great kids?, Mouse thinks it must be a mistake. He and Dog set out to investigate whether these presents are meant for someone else, but the other kids don't like that idea at all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p83183b454813d61ba000f321722fff50</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p98f168df5f29f37ae0a42de84dfafe1c</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>When Charlie ignores the rules of Pierce's magical board game, the living pieces escape, creating a dicey situation that the gang must roll with.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a09de134fc0b8e65bb5078672a8bec2</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad is haunted by a ghost.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf0052df934f22523e5b7eb4e5673e7d2</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert is really proud of the plants he has grown ready for a visit from The Complete Gnome Gardener magazine. However, when a Wind Dragon flies through the forest destroying all his hard work, Herbert turns to desperate measures ? a barrowful of Stinkweasel?s stinkiest compost! Now, the whole forest is at risk of being overwhelmed by the smell, and the heroes must quest to get rid of it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6fbe790ae4282b14265104a8bedddd57</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Learn how the heroes became Ladybug and Cat Noir.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13756d1dd4ab40bb9be92476adfabee1</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Marinette refuses to become Ladybug, but Paris needs her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb927ed3d5e60f64acbd5dc7b1b44ebf</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Joined by Perrin, the Rising Volt Tacklers set out to find Kleavor on Tengu Mountain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d673cc286577b672f953048a7f66c0a</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a silkworm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb2a4455efc0d2ba913ad4e4083bbf47b</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings use all the electricity for their phones - now Grizzy can?t watch TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p465df138cba7e7ae123993705a66a905</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings catch a grasshopper that can give you whatever your heart desires.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e0fd7c58b3a252cdfc561d821057d41</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The siblings try to break their annoying habits for the sake of family peace. At first they offer each other support, but then one-by-one they start to give up. Only Boy and Girl keep going, but can they make it to the end of 24 hours.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf01ab48424de754588783a2e22e48b0b</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>A dog show is coming up, and cool prizes are given to the winning dog and its trainer. Cheese, Girl and Mouse all have great ideas for how to train Dog for the grand finale. And if Dog picks one of their finales, that sibling gets to be the trainer who shares in the prize! Boy also wants to help but gets shunned for having a less impressive idea on how to win. The contest arrives, but Dog is torn when it comes to his finale. Whose idea does he choose? Can Boy jump in with his 'unimpressive' idea and help save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbdaeec7627628d03ca2742675670ed96</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After her siblings accidentally insult her dreams of being a pop star, Cheese is bonked on the head and starts to believe she's a huge celebrity! Mouse says they all must play along, because if they ruin the illusion then there's a chance Cheese could go bonkers. Cheese turns into a diva, making outrageous demands from her siblings, and soon enough they're sick of it. But when they learn she was duping them all along, they set out to teach her a lesson..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4540d9337e6bd866504e38a486ddadec</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen has his superball confiscated, so the gang set off to retrieve it from Chef?s office.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p73436548f2765fadaa07495786f981bd</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Jude befriends a chicken with an attitude when an unusual petting zoo visits the school.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6564b7f9b1833bcbeba99b1e6168d336</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Online potato sensation Spudman is joined by Joe-bot as he tries to program this malfunctioning robot to serve baked potatoes, and Adam B-bot gets to work in an ice cream shop.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ff06053d24e3c937fdcc22f2c716252</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Challenges, celebrities, makes and adventures with the Blue Peter team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c2dad280d7a573302baf70e15a69a2e</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:25AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs build 'Kwembley', their DIY table football pitch, Mandy Barker wows turning plastic waste into art, and comedian Aisling Bea draws a puffin with a potato waffle problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1500fcc3c13870d2b9e03edb99166eb0</image>
    <start>11:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Elijah and Sue go head to head with Finley and Graham as they compete for the chance to make it to the Grand Final and become ultimate Game on Grandparents champion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f52fbedfee0801094153a91aa6b57df</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. When people in town can no longer count down, Olive and Otto must uncover who is causing the problem and why.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd79a2406943b710052f6477ad3ae2c2</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. When several of Oscar's robots made in his own image become lost in town, Olive and Otto must help him find them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfba44b98c725830596050a280ce1966a</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Alien zombies, space monks, a demon clown, an evil knight and a world record attempt -it's just another day at Cranmede Academy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a4f6570cbeeb3d53adb000b54c1d578</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle wants to win first prize at her school's sports day. However, she gets paired with Roland, who refuses to take part, and her magic accidentally makes him super strong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8594fcb13a3ba08d43e7d627d93cd4f</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>You?re making bogies in your nose all the time. To show this, Dr Xand uses the Ouchcam to give us an exclusive close-up of one of his freshly picked beauties, before he and Dr Chris use a supersized nose to make gloopy snot into something more crusty. We?ve got a Top 5 countdown of the Longest Longy Long Things Ever, including the mind-blowingly long, longest-ever burp. Gladiator Dynamite is back making sure Dr Dan and Dr Raph play by the rules as they go toe-to-toe in a body battle ? it?s all fun and games until the loser has to get into the ice bath! We get a chance to follow Dr Ronx through the whole of their hospital shift in Doctors on Duty. Emilia has cut her lip at school and goes to the emergency department in Liverpool, and Jake is in hospital in Edinburgh after injuring his neck when a pal picked him up and accidentally dropped him on his head.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe812a9e18f268a5aa8b7b0ce8266c308</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Dr Big Brain has an electrical short circuit, Marie Curie is wowed by a rocket man, some of the great women of science are celebrated, and 200 monks get electrocuted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21daa97d981587de14f8ff3ad8bddf40</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>When Ken suggests that Hannah tries living a day in the life of a trainee, she quickly struggles to find her footing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p528bd48683e536eac40e921ac19bef05</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>It?s the last match of the season, and everyone?s future is on the line. Can Hawx United cause an upset against Foxborough? Who will be cut and who will be saved.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1a43e485d56ecf7acb6dce9e1dc1358</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef takes the kids on a trip to a museum, and Duncan goes on a mission to scare Courtney.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc72751ce3c887c4b03b0417d2a8bca7d</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan convinces Owen to start misbehaving to show him how much fun their timeouts can be.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p64cdbe54e04dd37f4adbf42b4a490149</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Bridgette gets the hiccups for the first time and tries desperately to get rid of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb93d6040b77fd2f1a2b5d7d46d15ace1</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron and Penfold are stranded on a desert island. In the skies above, there is a race to snatch Brunel's All Encompassing Remote Control.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa7b8e966b5c6c306f3a119bdf3118798</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Colonel K disappears on a free holiday, Danger Mouse pulls rank and assumes the mantle of caretaker colonel. However, the role is much less exciting than he anticipated, as world-saving missions make way for endless paperwork. Meanwhile, K's freebie spa retreat happens to be a diversion tactic in Greenback's latest plot to take over the world, with the baron banking on the Danger Agency falling apart without its figurehead and the world descending into disarray.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paef6868cdecdac98504d06f4fc8a956a</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Envious at Danger Mouse's ever-growing medal collection, Penfold questions whether he will ever be deemed special enough to receive a prize of his own. Seconds later, a knock at the door reveals a holographic Quark, who anoints Penfold as 'the chosen one' in a suspiciously automated message that culminates in an overawed Penfold receiving his very own magic wand. Penfold's joy is short-lived however - as he and DM step outside of HQ to find that the streets of are London teeming with hundreds of wannabe wizards, all brandishing identical wands. After discovering that the wands are mass-produced shavings from Merlin's legendary staff, the pair set out to stop Quark's latest money-making scheme by reuniting the staff with its rightful owner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p323dc2e8e64fccd5de7990c027816ff5</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the siblings try to make an awesome Christmas surprise for their parents, things go wrong every step of the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pce5c4f9b0f49d66f108cb37d0a045fdf</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Gramps comes to stay, the kids tell him the story of how Mum and Dad almost didn?t get married. When the kids first met each other, neither family could get used to the other?s funny ways and just didn?t get along. They fought so much that the wedding planner quit! Will the six kids figure out a way to be a family, or will Mum and Dad be forced to call off their wedding.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8835247f164916b34101aa26f1a0da50</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>In this second part of the flashback story of Mum and Dad?s wedding, the kids realize how unhappy they were apart, but they can't see how to fix things. Then a bird-based emergency sees both groups of kids leap into action to work together and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e535fd2fee7b3b090c7ca871cc213c7</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a magic stick that functions as a Yummy divining rod.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcee1931a27a2dfd300dfe45402832d2b</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a jewel that gives them total control over the fireflies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p441f9d3dc8cbcbd950cad86aa8c0bc2f</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes aren?t really meant to do quests without Mr Friendlyface?s express permission. But when they come across a cute little squirrel queen, and she begs for their help, they find her impossible to resist. All they have to do is quest to the Tree of Certain Doom and pass his challenges. But the squirrel queen is not who she appears to be, and the heroes have to quickly un-quest their quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc66ead86a1798e4f31033a6bf01a29a</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The blossom has gone missing. No, not Blossom the unicorn, the blossom on the trees! The heroes are sent on a quest deep into the heart of the forest, where legend has it you can see a face watching you from the trees. Twinkle doesn?t believe in legends, but when help comes from nowhere as they try and stop the scoundrel that is stealing the blossom, she is forced to reconsider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2f8d2357ef662dfdfa8453de1222ecd1</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are relieved that the loud, threatening voice they can hear actually belongs to a small slug named Zorgoth, who is armed with a megaphone. However, when Zorgoth uses his Orb of Compression to shrink the heroes down to the size of ants, their relief evaporates. They must now embark on a long and dangerous quest, through their picnic items and beyond, to warn the Council before Zorgoth shrinks the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe50df153eaba594e89a65c54ae953f0c</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Blink takes over a huge beach cleaning drone, and Grandpa and Mansour unite to tackle it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c7b711065be5e3e02e19304ccd08631</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Mansour, Obaid and Salem fall out with Shamma during a VR game, and Blink takes advantage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b5c36c82cb1d483084df97d9f3aaee1</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>One member from each team must spend the day balancing on a pole under the hot sun, and with no food in their tummy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34bd78ea1bfc532d7fc78ae8e9422045</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gremlins: Secrets of the Mogwai</title>
    <desc>Sam, Elle and Gizmo's nerves are tested as they follow Grandpa's map.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b6733dc58cc2df194e355a8116e17d9</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
