<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve and the team are on the search for deadly animals in the steaming swamps of the southern USA. The contenders are everywhere, not least the alligators that live in just about every pond and lake. But the first animal on the list is a complete surprise, a monster fish with two rows of sharp fangs that certainly keeps Steve on his toes. The crew find themselves up to their armpits in a swamp hoping to find a deadly snake with the unusual name of cottonmouth. Last but not least, Steve and his team come face to face with an enormous record-breaking predatory turtle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8963833a0703ec6ebc11ba5dc0132d4a</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Things get explosive when Dr Chris and Dr Xand look at how spots are made, plus an incredible emergency service at work in Australia: the Flying Doctors.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b4c137dff0cf46b799270e7eb64b46d</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketch show. King Charles I sends someone else to get married for him, a new recruit regrets joining the Georgian army, and Queen Cleopatra reveals her beauty secrets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf1cf98d0967e2d2e5471d0911a918075</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Historical sketch show. Barmy Roman emperor Caligula fails to invade Britain, King Henry VIII plays tennis while Anne Boleyn is executed, and some Saxon monks throw a party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd0af2c7887e8b62742cc5dd446c9fb7d</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Bionic ends up dressed as a rabbit when Nitro pranks him at a fake photoshoot, and the rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes as they prank the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf7d7f9299d05e5c92784905daf4991d</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold must travel to the Twystyverse to stop the evil tyrant Baron Silas von Penfold from taking over both versions of the Earth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96bd7bb99d9e77929da195732a4166fb</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When the Baron speeds up the rotation of Earth using windmills, Danger Mouse and Penfold age 300 years and must take on their nemesis as very, very, very old men.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b0704c5d4df92b6473d98abf4e56522</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Penfold saves a celebrity from certain doom he becomes a media sensation. DM smells a rat... or at least some evil villainous hamster from another dimension.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8296206497ab04e0f3f7e8b912dfd6ee</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Rubi?s dance machine gets accidentally muddled up with Crusty the Robot Pie?s coding. Dennis and Gnasher have to dance on it all day in perfect sync, or Crusty?s entire persona will be wiped forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc196d03c4998053896105cc5f5c04bc8</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A patch of wet cement, a boy and a dog itching to put their prints into it and a policeman determined not to let that happen. Can Dennis and Gnasher muddle Sergeant Slipper long enough before the cement sets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3cbcc2b42f737a35aae5268e19aff3be</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Dennis thinks Gnasher has trashed a valuable piece of hideous art, the gang try desperately to cover up the damage and produce a decoy that is as convincingly terrible as the original.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4fc5d89880a983b655e137d80434250a</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The blossom has gone missing. No, not Blossom the unicorn, the blossom on the trees! The heroes are sent on a quest deep into the heart of the forest, where legend has it you can see a face watching you from the trees. Twinkle doesn?t believe in legends, but when help comes from nowhere as they try and stop the scoundrel that is stealing the blossom, she is forced to reconsider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2f8d2357ef662dfdfa8453de1222ecd1</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are relieved that the loud, threatening voice they can hear actually belongs to a small slug named Zorgoth, who is armed with a megaphone. However, when Zorgoth uses his Orb of Compression to shrink the heroes down to the size of ants, their relief evaporates. They must now embark on a long and dangerous quest, through their picnic items and beyond, to warn the Council before Zorgoth shrinks the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe50df153eaba594e89a65c54ae953f0c</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes quest to stop Balthazar from turning forest folk into household objects, Herbert realises that he can defeat the wizard?s spell by using the magic tricks he has practiced. Blossom is particularly intrigued by Herbert the Peculiar?s tricks, not to mention his stage name, so when Herbert himself is transformed into a table lamp, it?s Blossom the Very Impressive to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p02b5755668bd5974ec3f672d77162daf</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a pig who has the ability to find food using his snout.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1ce8e7ccc147b0ae527c57d37725d16</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings take part in a safari photo competition on an animal reserve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p87591ace945bfdf453a92c3829fd0bc0</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings are trapped in a ball, and an ostrich sits on it, mistaking it for an egg.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd360edab947bab57be77ecad7762ad6c</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The savannah animals bow down before whoever sits on the throne-shaped boulder.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e3bcdf201997d8e0f31003c453c9d11</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The band get a new trumpet player, with disastrous consequences. Also, the apple dropouts hatch an explosive plan to break free, and superhero Slippery Nana comes to the rescue to save a tomato... sort of! Deep in the back of the fridge, Frankfurter's monster is on the rampage, and Dr Rhu-barb surprises the judges with his white rabbit trick in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9d8cc7f011cc4e57ef694c747ebd22f</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>A mischievous new breed of dragons called Vine Tails steal the Book of Dragons.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31be02cdee0c0389b82f418d2ad9cf2a</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>The girls try to cheer up Celeste, who wants to get expelled so she can go home to see her mother. Meanwhile, Mary-Lou finds herself facing a snail invasion when she takes an art class.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p01f62a429f0c9978d02fb2772f4513ae</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Addie and Audrey?s friendship blossoms as they go door-to-door to spread the word about Juniper?s witches. Maggie starts a secret rebellion, putting her at odds with Elinor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fe90bee762eed019908d0b716da7059</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>An overprotective Heath accuses Grace of sabotage, while Grace and Jonah make a bet to make it on to A-Troupe. Meanwhile, Izzy grapples with keeping Anthony?s secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5b4c76f289d443a95cb05ffbadf7a365</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>With A-Troupe all in on regionals, Pete takes his eyes off the Brawl and auditions for dance captain. Olive looks for a place where she belongs, while Grace dreams of joining A-Troupe.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e554040d8151175d38b78010cb1824d</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Carter, Glen, Zane, and Skye must hide their secret identities from everyone. They are struggling with teamwork, when hot-headed Gormian Bors tries to prove the Scions don?t have what it takes. The Scions finally unite against him but, in so doing, they attract the attention of Graven.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p16497753ab657a2216c622950836aa27</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings use a frog with hypnotising powers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbd74eae5287515b461c9282bcc4d8e8</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
