<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A pirate captain regrets stealing a herd of seasick cows, a Georgian sportsman invents a whole new way of boxing, King Charles II raps about his party lifestyle, and the Georgian army goes to war against a bunch of naughty schoolboys.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e5f4295938a4955551888a20c3e6f03</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>In Ancient Greece, it's time for Spartan High School Musical, a jester breaks bad news to Henry VIII using armpit raspberries, learn how to stay fit with the Caveman Workout, and Roman emperor Nero stars in a (not very) romantic movie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p517e976f5b716aeb138ee3b6166d7897</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Diamond when the guest on a live TV show can?t stop pumping! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes, pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p124aa384cfc9de9b57a6c0777805b147</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Squawkencluck reboots the now 100 per cent reliable Big Head base computer, which immediately locks up everyone in a maximum security prison.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p807580e7b44481f79c8475072cd446ef</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's attempts to boost Penfold's confidence backfire when they lead to a ferocious games monster escaping into the real world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p107003566b41bffd5346594c3f9d54eb</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Brunel, the crazed time-travelling Victorian gentlechimp, is back and determined to change history so that Danger Mouse and Penfold never meet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c7b4ec1cfd4ed38c7cbcb24ef88353f</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang can?t wait for their all-day PE training day with Grizzly Griller and are baffled when their idol makes them learn a range of boring non-sports that only Walter excels at.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13014ffef7cef77e45cb02cd6a8721d2</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and his mates rebel against an outbreak of unfair fun-killing rules that are being imposed on Beanotown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f84e659fa74f9534a219e00043217b3</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and Gnasher accidentally do good deeds for the people of Beanotown. Intrigued by the new sensation of being thanked and appreciated, they go on a 'helping rampage', leaving a wake of mayhem behind them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8a5033f5d7b0f34dcc6198f2e6ce3ea</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert has invented a new contraption to help him fly using an old set of bagpipes. The 'Herbecopter', as Herbert likes to call it, is rather noisy but extremely effective, and Twinkle is unhappy at no longer being the only flying hero. So, when the heroes quest to get Friendlyface?s priceless locket back from a dragon, Twinkle and Herbert become extremely competitive and risk completely failing the quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa955ab16670c700cec4ca1249af0b548</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Blossom accidentally uses a witch?s broom to make sticks for toasting marshmallows, the owner of the broom casts a spell of squeaky voices on all the heroes. The spell will be lifted once the heroes have returned with new broomstick branches. A simple enough quest, think the heroes, until they realise that a witch?s broom can only be made from the branches of the Really Spooky Tree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe37511be85e501039449287ddef18d2b</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find an ice block that holds a frozen prehistoric animal.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p88eb6bc20f2eb8deabb1e06234837eb7</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a container filled with metal survival food flasks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0287b9b09672b2fe39abe8f7f107f3fa</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings attempt to take back a chocolate egg from a group of penguins.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb634cea656ce1728d93bd2b352b1369c</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom and the riders must rescue Plowhorn from Sledkin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e214da0219881d6a5448804eb882fcc</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom and Jun struggle to get ingredients for Gronckle Iron to help stop the World Serpent.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f7df1a4bb45514bfa2c325522f5670d</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>With Astra suspended, Hannah makes the impossible decision to leave. Can her friends convince her to stay.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc3693098adcc48114cd1a677f363492</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe buzzes with excitement, ready to perform for the biggest opportunity of their lives. But their excitement is cut short when Summer fails to show up. Piper and Amy's friendship is tested when Piper catches Amy stirring up the past.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e510cbf698c170dcf3569c951412dac</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>It?s the season finale, and the Vipers could get promoted! However, Aoife is headhunted for county trials - can she do both and make it to the big final against arch-rivals the Comets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf75da12a774401b907e62f945fb6549e</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:05PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Tasked with letting go of items that might be holding them back, Lily struggles to shred Matt Furnish?s love letters, and Claire can?t sell her beloved merch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c8c057f5b92b690440da8b3d67e808a</image>
    <start>06:05PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>When Miss Marmaduke?s love of sushi leads to firing all the teachers, Lily, Claire, Jin and Mr Malone join forces with the kids to get their jobs back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b9515de0bf5e11b5e51007faabc9d74</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
