<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to Suriname, a country with more forest than anywhere else on earth. He kayaks upriver in search of some deadly critters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae61be0573c4be4246d27fa124cbcdc0</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 7-9 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about the journey of a river, in this case the Nile, as well as hydropower and dams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82b7581f7039e84791f08f09a1505bbd</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The brothers learn all about different types of cosy animal dens. Bird expert Nadeem helps Cam build a bird box, and Aaron reveals why the Asiatic lion is most endangered.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcc2bea3a0b9396f6a346a5fc0fae598f</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Fashion fun as students are challenged to design and model outfits for a school show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a8b5ed563b79e0b055cb6e86b7ee169</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Art Ninja</title>
    <desc>Ricky starts to receive countless gifts from a mystery superfan whilst coincidentally items begin to disappear from his flat. Gavin is instructed to keep watch, though he's a little distracted. Meanwhile, Ricky makes a shiny selfie in homage to Gustav Klimt, an octopus using a candle and a squirty flower! With his flat half empty, can Ricky finally recover his stuff and uncover his mystery fan.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd06cc3d022cb8d7985eddf08b59cd88c</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Get ready for incredible experiments and mind-bending puzzles to impress your friends. Owain and Tilly are here to explore epic science tricks to try at home and showcase brand new technology innovations from around the world! In this episode, discover why a boomerang always comes back, search for forensic evidence to catch a cake thief, hitch a ride in a car with no driver, and see a ball defy gravity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea0387dd16800881de2d72e86b241d24</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Wouldn't it be cool to be able to walk through walls? From turning into a gas to quantum trickery, we discover why it wouldn't be quite as useful as you'd like.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0e230fa2ad1567230d5610a5e88a4cf3</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Chop, chop, it's the Horrible Histories' Terrible Tudors Special, with everything you need to know about history's most famous family. Featuring a never-before-seen sketch with the murderous Medicis, hilarious outtakes, and a special one-off written by a CBBC competition winner - it's your one-stop Tudor shop.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4990fa93a56a86c7058a3f4015bff7d5</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Zoe from Oxfordshire is mad about science and dreams of becoming a scientist one day. She loves to carry out messy, noisy experiments, but her dad works night shifts, which means she has to be quiet while he sleeps. She desperately wants her own space where she can pursue her passions and make a mess whenever she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1362ca6c17f3b744fcd72eef1ba4224c</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy has double-booked himself and must attend a family party rather than the band?s anniversary celebrations. Moxy plans a daring mission to break him out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12ee72b007386e686b82538b87e65f3e</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>The Go Jetters are visiting the Everglades National Park in Florida, USA. It's an area made up mainly of water with amazing wildlife living there, including alligators! The Go Jetters are working with a local park ranger to put up signs warning people not to eat food near the water as it might attract the alligators. Meanwhile, Grandmaster Glitch is also at the Everglades enjoying a holiday with his Grimbots. He decides to stop and have a picnic by the water, which brings the alligators dangerously close to him and a boat full of tourists. It's down to the Go Jetters and the park ranger to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96ceda2bd6dcf2f9fa0f8b790460efd1</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Big Lizard wants to have a go with Dad's new drone, but first he has to prove that he can go a whole day without breaking something precious. Good luck, Big Lizard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p850b309749660e2b38b39d00c45b2933</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. Whether it's a perilous voyage to the bottom of the sea or the piratey pursuit of a giant squid, the Octonauts leap into action. The Octonauts are exploring Antarctica when Shellington discovers strange microscopic creatures living under the ice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p242d7c633b4f9fd6586900df211d6a72</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When secret information is leaked from HQ, all eyes fall on Colonel K. Is it possible he is a traitor, or is there something suspicious about his moustache.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db875e58f17940935f6776c5bb499c3</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>While Zoe helps Doug with his homework project about Alaska, Simon and Jess take Waffle and Evie to the shops to buy new school shoes. But Waffle's attempts to help end up causing chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ea5a4f370ad0cb1ad9431c914904fb6</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>The Tato Team are playing beach volleyball. But when Evil Pea's parents, Mummy Pea and Daddy Pea, pay her a visit, they are disappointed to learn that she doesn't rule the supermarket. They vow to help their daughter defeat Supertato once and for all. After cornering him with three freezy hoses and freezing his super sidekicks, it looks like Evil Pea might finally be victorious. But when she is distracted, Supertato and the veggies use their beach volleyball to block the attack and the plan backfires... freezing her parents instead.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81357dbe11e26974b460a16c167532f7</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang take on the power of WilburCorp to stop Walter?s new line of collectable toys ruining the Beanotown environment with all its wasteful plastic packaging.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c44a8d584dd7a07558e7563e65f62b0</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Rubi?s dance machine gets accidentally muddled up with Crusty the Robot Pie?s coding. Dennis and Gnasher have to dance on it all day in perfect sync, or Crusty?s entire persona will be wiped forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc196d03c4998053896105cc5f5c04bc8</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>It?s been ages since their last quest, and the heroes are losing their edge, so Mr Friendlyface invents a strange and terrible monster that he says is stomping through the forest causing havoc, and sends the heroes on a fake quest to get rid of it. Friendlyface soon comes to regret his trickery when, with the heroes out of the way, the goblins decide to take over the forest for their jam jamboree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd73f5a342e51bd6aa4e1226b5b388fb</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After the battery dies on her laser shoe, special agent Gloria Hope calls on the Ninjas to help her find a new one and foil criminal mastermind Pam D'Terre.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10d3013b50db1457cc92c2ac34d58fdc</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Drama series. Sasha can stay at the Dumping Ground as long as she obeys the rules. All is fine until her naughty little brother Dexter arrives.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2db44f3427b4b413392bea3cf77b9535</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Ariana comes to a realisation as she fights her way through the Dance Captain Battle Royale, and the international twists are far from over.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc4c1a50126c1fa172d0b05da89038e4e</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A celebration of some of history?s greatest females, including Spartan Queen Gorgo terrorising Historical Love Island, supergroup The Tudor Queens, and the original Wonder Women.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p582ac5e48494296f4adc6415c654b2b8</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>There?s a new tripe hound in Beanotown, and Gnasher falls head over paws in love with her. Bertie is looking after the visiting dog, Ginger, and is determined to keep her away from riff-raff like Gnasher.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c6935906c9fad8f02b717eec4e4caaa</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>An order mix-up leads to a delivery of hyperactive tentacles at Bash Street School. However, no-one wants the job of looking after the pesky things, and attempts to duck out of the tentacle-care duties lead to chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd04f790a2a06b0b64f43ec40406c119c</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron releases a new strain of elephant flu. Can DM and Penfold find the cure before everyone is turned into a snotty elephant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51f8cb9515674180a911e9981fe74ee0</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After some playful gnomes take her phone, a mum and her son ask the Ninjas for help. However, a game of magical tag ensues when the gnomes also take the Ninjas' delivery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e6614daa2f8b7a97e30b3497c60c300</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a tree with chocolate spread sap.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3585c633baec4c2b027d134bc532043b</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse is tested on his experiment to create the perfect family and is sure he will fail! However, his siblings convince him to hire actors to play perfect versions of themselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p74d538ded050c20a33665d7e2f080fec</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest until a heroic one comes along. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Odd Squad and Villains work together to stop a giant robot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ecb8fd587aedc874bc91e06bf8e589a</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents accidentally lose someone in headquarters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pffe16f8607e9b7c534d70c45b0848532</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth and Leshawna try to outdo each other with fake injuries to gain more attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe635ab159f06f65d1cb8af629461d176</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Gold Record.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6bb881e9b26f09372f21fa4936589205</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>A visit to Naranja Academy results in answers, and new questions, about Terapagos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pecf6b702814f4d246f300391aff711a4</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>There?s a brand new slide at school, and Pickle really wants to try it out. However, things get complicated when Pickle's mood magic causes Mia and Mr Ludcomb?s hair to grow uncontrollably.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fdd46f4b3717baf8071605b9e07bf96</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. When Kate asks Emily to hold dance evaluations for placements in the group dance, Emily decides to put Michelle in the back row, which causes waves amongst the dancers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa3145037e37ecb44a9edb7f99a35d148</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find an ultra-modern glowing cabin they can use for their party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1b288d68d121be98f9d5b947e9b4735f</image>
    <start>06:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
