<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After the battery dies on her laser shoe, special agent Gloria Hope calls on the Ninjas to help her find a new one and foil criminal mastermind Pam D'Terre.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10d3013b50db1457cc92c2ac34d58fdc</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When the Farmer accidentally drills a hole in a waterpipe while putting up a new shelf, Bitzer frantically tries to stop the leak from soaking the living room and prevent the Farmer?s precious teapots from sliding off the shelf.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d0dd9504a3c0f105eb983ecfaee021d</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a magic stick that functions as a Yummy divining rod.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p16fa51bb776109875ebe265c75d998d8</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy is afraid of being honest in case he hurts other people's feelings and finds himself doing things he doesn?t like just to keep others happy. Mouse and Cheese encourage him to be totally honest, only to find that Boy?s total honesty can be rather blunt. Can the gang rein him in before Boy alienates the entire town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p266389173e1520b4e65cb4c48680fe55</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are on a quest to find the vault containing the Amulet of Answers and protect it at all costs. But the Riddlemaster is back, and he manages to trap them in his castle, tricking Herbert into handing the Amulet of Answers over to him. Now he has all the answers to every question ever asked, and the heroes must find a way to outwit him - even though he knows what they are going to do next.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe25fa88d8b5c74373b8dbfb32088efca</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When an unlucky coin is accidentally released into the public, the agents must retrieve it before the world ends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e794a83b3d2c55eec5e8e9ab3734047</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When a new room opens up in headquarters, all the agents want a piece.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p48d81a5a15782933c7172775a48d0f89</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Izzy wants to play a superhero game but has difficulty persuading her friends to join in.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70d5282f53657d0ee3c0c5e0137de88b</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Simplificator.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2db79bb10b78cc075f41d666ec980654</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs bowl into space with DIY alien skittles, Emma Stothard weaves a wicker dog, and Kiell Smith-Bynoe draws a ghost so spooked, it?s nearly see-through.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe84a9fb444c89c3b7b8033f116add9f6</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Matron arrives with Nancy, her young ward, and Gwen tells her to ask Matron to stay, which annoys Matron. Nancy joins the third formers as they search for the missing time capsule.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p49ad384923660547da1815e89ea7bbfb</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>No longer dance captain, Anthony finds following orders difficult. Jett and Ariana try to be friends again, while Heath?s history with Daisy complicates things with Pascale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfba3f0a5c1730f35b314ede0c813a92f</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Abby and Shini go head-to-head in a powerchair football challenge! Using specially designed powerchairs as part of four-a-side teams, who will come out on top.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe198144b1c57887ed93fb809b7488166</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
