<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>When a Pok? Ball factory goes on the fritz, Orla steps up to the challenge of fixing it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p032492f3a2e0fa674f97c48211b5688d</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A fidget spinner, lightbulb, microwave and mobile phone are among the items getting the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p210dbecc36328fd83055bfe68045fa40</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Can a fish really be responsible for wrecking Dolos's boat, sinking the Aronnax and almost destroying the Rover? Fontaine believes so - and it's invaded Jeffrey's home on the Aronnax. How can she get rid of it and its bad luck.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b5182cf6e46b31672a4346297be0552</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>An order mix-up leads to a delivery of hyperactive tentacles at Bash Street School. However, no-one wants the job of looking after the pesky things, and attempts to duck out of the tentacle-care duties lead to chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd04f790a2a06b0b64f43ec40406c119c</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The world is in jeopardy and the only thing that can save it is a 1,000ft Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7dcc9c255cb548ada924dfbdc51cc0cf</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When a scientist borrows the Ninjas? powers and takes her pet bird on a trip around the world, the powerless trio struggle to run their delivery business.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcb61f203895a48a888727a6ff8e9999a</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Set on a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. But Shaun's insatiable curiosity often leads him into the unlikeliest adventures. A pesky goat is tethered in the sheep's field, and threatens to eat all their grass.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14a3da180a2a70e76d1dbb99bb1662bd</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a jar of jelly that gets stuck in a high-up spot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p20fc70ddc4e0f10bae41278fc0610631</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Doozie Smoothies want to find a face to advertise their new range, Cheese is keen to enter the photo competition, with Dog?s help as photographer. However, when an embarrassing photo of Cheese is chosen for the promotion, Cheese hatches a plan to get her hands on it before it's unveiled, even if it means dashing Dog's hopes of success.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pab56a269bec690a3d02591f39f6fdc06</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle uses her excellent pocket beast card skills when on a quest to rescue the missing Council of Happiness from Grackle the Giant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c52df7e45b3a76f78f6ac5a5d573bb1</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad is haunted by a ghost.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf0052df934f22523e5b7eb4e5673e7d2</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Owen and new recruit Ozlyn wait out a storm while transporting a creature. Curriculum: Measurement - Capacity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pffe634bacbb854317f13c699b7c5ac6a</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>The class camping trip turns into a treasure hunt, while Harold looks to trap a Bigfoot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4317ddecad9de25b04544978ce824b51</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Dark Humour.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1f4f3fb53f5ffdd9b7a531ae68e99de2</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Terapagos uses its power to purify Laqua, but a new threat waits in the shadows.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p713b70e7b7b46fb1d26e93585eb9164c</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>It?s racing time! Pro gamer Yammy guides the teams to the finish line as they give it their all in Sonic Forces - but who will cross the finish line first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf3a03776fe179e9f199dd2567517b169</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>With A-Troupe all in on regionals, Pete takes his eyes off the Brawl and auditions for dance captain. Olive looks for a place where she belongs, while Grace dreams of joining A-Troupe.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe85665761583635fbb3c4dd760674a7e</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Abby attempts a dog agility course with pet expert Chloe and her super spaniel support dog.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p757915a20a78561a38313ac6478e8832</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>05 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Can Shaun prevent the delivery of new spectacles to the Farmer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p45d098086d9307c2c55b7df88802fb4e</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold are in a training simulation when one of DM's flying kicks damages the holodeck with catastrophic consequences. They wake to find they have been in a three-year dream, that they aren't secret agents and work in IT instead, and the Danger Agency has been a figment of their imaginations! Whilst Penfold and Squawk quickly settle into a life of menial office work, DM struggles to accept life as Dane G Mouse.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2be9862d6d9621fc75eda5af2c518c22</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Mrs Creecher confiscates Dennis's rare sour sweetie, the Tongue Destroyer! Dennis is desperate to get the sweet back and takes his friends on an adventure to the school's Confiscatorium, a secret place where all confiscated goods are hidden, in the depths of Bash Street School.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59345ded18b2ac0ee7e8394444da7b49</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Girl is failing science class, so Mouse offers to help her learn. However, Girl decides it will be easier to borrow one of his inventions and cheat instead. Everything is going to plan until the borrowed invention goes wrong and causes a scientific calamity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p387204adcf2e93aa73aa4d915551c7ae</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd1570ee64e92d258d857f9cd3ffc9cb</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings try to destroy the statues of Grizzy, but he will not let them ruin his art.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1a9dc775f45d98b8dbb235bb72079f8a</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A container full of Yummy? What a dream for Grizzy and the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p73a561ce9a6c25c6c43ad3d39368d7fa</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>A mysterious villain named The Shadow takes control of the Mobile Unit van.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc253562c1542252d0b7ada9912d2ff43</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Trapped inside Que's video game diary, Pierce's day just got graphic! One level up, Charlie is held captive as his goblin dungeon master dreams of an extra life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf8140fba55cc3325c78799347a116f5b</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Whilst on a quest to return the Icicle of Destiny, Trevor topples into a cavern of tiny mushrooms who treat him like a king.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6587ed590db6ffbdbc38b906cd7ccb3a</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Pop sensation Zoe Now (Nadine Coyle) is coming to officially open Pottsfield leisure centre?s new reception. Joy tasks Danny and Mick with looking after the star guest but get in a tangle with the opening ribbon. Zoe Now arrives but Danny?s attempts at hospitality leave her without a voice - minutes before she?s due to sing. With the aid of a cap and wig from lost property, lots of smoke and a backing track, Danny reckons nobody will spot the difference if he takes her place. Mick plays Zoe?s hit song over the PA for Danny to mime to, but he gets too in the moment and accidentally skips the music tracks. After Danny initially busks it to save the day, they are found out. But Mick surprises the crowd with a fantastic acoustic rendition of the Zoe Now track which Zoe is very impressed with.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51b62c2e7ef6e44545ab7f8302a8db8b</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>Dragons, dinos and divas! The Kwapongs craft fire-breathers, Romesh Ranganathan draws a rapping T-rex, and Bristles dives into the bold, brilliant world of Frida Kahlo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35625862ebe527b01a7c825cbdc1577a</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings love sesame nougat, but Grizzy also adores this treat and steals their box.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p64a57734b6a24b062d71ddbece2023c7</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir meet heroes from a parallel world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe51709fe483e07b288d104ee7c76dce7</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Mrs Armitage on Wheels</title>
    <desc>A tale from Quentin Blake's Box of Treasures. Inventor extraordinaire Mrs Armitage and faithful dog Breakspear love adventurous hobbies like skydiving until an accident dents Mrs Armitage?s confidence. Recovered, she plans a short cycling trip, but keeps putting it off adapting her bike with horns, a tool kit, and even a sail! The ?land yacht? eventually launches, but a further accident leaves Mrs Armitage doubly nervous. Luckily, her Uncle Cosmo comes to the rescue gifting Mrs Armitage his old car and getting her finally back on the road.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c4f701d200c61799b15b87de59d749b</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play pirates on a beached boat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6daa38c7457a858d5904930fb10cd1a</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:45AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Electro at a fake fashion photoshoot when her fabulous, precious dress is ruined. Meanwhile, the other Gladiators are up to mischief behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd1bbc15f7e13b3dc2f66637f66d3cf9d</image>
    <start>10:45AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>While Lystra and Hendrick attend their first school parents? evening, Pickle, Mia and Roland become trapped in Pickle?s house, and her magic makes the floor turn to lava.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbbed6ec3c37cde1beb51843963bcbe75</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>RADI8 have a new leader: an influencer hand-picked by Sandra and her algorithm. However, in order to make room, someone is going to be cut from the group.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf1dbfe713c7346731f8ef2848c5b601d</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>As tempers flare after the latest revelation, Coach Byrne puts the whole team into detention. Mason contemplates giving up football altogether.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p227a50771aebbd00d76465eaf3f7ae1a</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>Steve is on a mission to find the weirdest dinosaur ever. He kick-starts with Gigantoraptor, an eight-metre-tall giant that laid the biggest eggs in history. Then, courtesy of a monster truck crash, he meets the miniscule Magyarosaurus. But that's not freaky enough, so finally he focuses on a dinosaur that head-butted its rivals to death - something Steve's hoping to replicate with the mother of all robots. Weird.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34c2716d3f5cc916edb9a15cdbe5391e</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>The band are guests on Zoe Ball?s radio show, but accidentally shut down the BBC. They have to take over and present all the shows in order to keep the BBC on air.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21f155873da85609f75dc8ebb5162576</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Star of socials Rhia gets set for sabotage following a race of teeny v tiny as Callum sets the lads The Big Tiny Bike Challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p214ab0f2bc9e7cc7ed539af5e42e4f4f</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Tracker finds trapped creatures in an underground tunnel after falling into a sinkhole.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p413494b05c8a4dde413fa83ab52365d2</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Whilst Dad searches for a faulty wire, Cosima and Big Lizard play tag in the ship and accidentally break Big Lizard's bath bed! Where will he sleep now? And where's that pesky wire.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27b20bb3866865593fa592da4ecbf022</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Baron Greenback brews a plot to steal every beverage on the planet and mix them all together, making an undrinkable, disgusting sludge. By depriving the population of their much-needed drinks break he'll cause worldwide exhaustion. Danger Mouse seems unfazed, but without his cherished tea Penfold wilts on their rescue mission. Can Danger Mouse thwart the baron's thirsty plot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf917845bd542156a5514c0aea46c08e</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Gnasher accidentally gulps down Dennis's permission slip for the school trip! There's only one thing for it - they need Prof von Screwtop to use his shrink ray to shrink them down to bite-size humans so they can travel on a sausage into Gnasher's tummy and find the slip! Easy! Well, it would be if it wasn't for the tiny alien empress Miasma living in there.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82572549a9fa117a10188f4698254b42</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert is really proud of the plants he has grown ready for a visit from The Complete Gnome Gardener magazine. However, when a Wind Dragon flies through the forest destroying all his hard work, Herbert turns to desperate measures ? a barrowful of Stinkweasel?s stinkiest compost! Now, the whole forest is at risk of being overwhelmed by the smell, and the heroes must quest to get rid of it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6fbe790ae4282b14265104a8bedddd57</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>In this heart-pounding documentary, two boys from different backgrounds come together through the traditional Pakistani sport of neza bazi (tent pegging). Charging into the competition, Jaleel and Subhaan face an exciting and challenging journey - is winning the most important thing, or is it about connecting with their heritage and forging new friendships? Set against the backdrop of fast-paced action, their shared passion for the sport takes them beyond the physical challenge as they discover the deeper significance of cultural identity and the power of friendship. With the crowd cheering, hooves pounding the ground and horses adorned in vibrant colours, Me, My Horse and My Spear explores not only the thrill of competition but the enduring ties between tradition, friendship and self-discovery. Will Jaleel and Subhaan come to realise that true victory lies in more than just a trophy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b4759234c8132828da5025141b0c3f8</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Strange things are happening aboard the Brave Olivine - could a Pok?mon be the cause.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcdaebdddcf742da93e0a6dbc9fd365e3</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A light switch, a fortune cookie, traffic lights and a bottle are among the items getting the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0cfcc8a9be40b62d2c554c3e78add16a</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>The Rover is swallowed by a huge, supposedly extinct prehistoric shark - a megalodon! Will and Fontaine manage to cling to its gills just inside its mouth. Kaiko and Ant frantically try to free them - they can't hold on forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbadd143fd9077f74f3c7f4b7e665b8ee</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>On the first day of a new school year, Dennis and the gang imagine all the things that might be new and unfamiliar at Bash Street School. By the time they reach the front gates, they are all expecting the worst.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3faada4acf7db9d5c697dcdb4bf0045a</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When secret information is leaked from HQ, all eyes fall on Colonel K. Is it possible he is a traitor, or is there something suspicious about his moustache.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db875e58f17940935f6776c5bb499c3</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>To win the annual Golden Wand contest, Merlina summons the Ninjas to find her an amazing magic trick to impress the judges. But the final winner takes everyone by surprise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p24416808631b7fb8497c6fb022cb8ebe</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life with sheepdog Bitzer. The aroma of the Farmer's takeaway inspires Shaun to go on a mission to a local pizzeria.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7fb6ddee45f4479ff66669b92fa76ed7</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings play a game: it's the Lemmings Knights v the Bear Magician.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0ed9e82e3ba0d61d2f02762acf46458c</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Cheese realizes she hasn't done half of what her idol, Posh, has accomplished, she tries to catch up by imitating everything Posh does - but things go very wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc478b59547dd91ec7b9473b9c1062784</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Forest inspectors pay the forest a visit to check its super-happy status. Friendlyface sends the heroes on outlandish quests to guarantee results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf423a5126c7145dec4e840079fa076e4</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Otis and Olympia stop werewolf Olaf from turning back into a boy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pad08afc73b96e3560d6cab85228c21be</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Otis struggles with his new high-tech agent?s jacket.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9878b8435735e7a646f5da8225e6c791</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen takes over the job of caring for the class hamster and learns he is not so cute.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70a72456e7a1a1ca3936bacce3cb457b</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>What if Monarch kept having second chances.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7bc6a86860d5b11f6661830281b583ad</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Chairwoman Geeta challenges Liko, Roy and Dot to a battle to test their strength.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb092d64f1c82be0c88bc62bc1854c663</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Guided by pro gamer Slogo, the teams serve up an epic game of Switch Sports Volleyball. Who will score more points and earn a place in the final.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4c8a2cbbcded1ecb10dffaf13a215681</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>No longer dance captain, Anthony finds following orders difficult. Jett and Ariana try to be friends again, while Heath?s history with Daisy complicates things with Pascale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6fe3d3df235a0aa0979d15b7a930a0bf</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Abby and Shini go head-to-head racing hovercrafts ? find out who flies across land and water to victory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa91afd351d98a63e1d6dc927ce9f3855</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>06 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Can Shaun help reunite Goz, a newly hatched gosling, with his mum and dad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d4d2f9fd76beb1476802caee2d126c9</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse faces the Queen of Weevils in a fearful Halloween special.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ff6788cafa5778e2972fb67508deb9d</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis must escape detention and Bash Street School to make the Beanotown Brawny Bean Race before Walter wins it! With the help of a note placed in his desk, he must sneak past Mrs Creecher and make a run for it - unless the mysterious note-giver stops him first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9167fe1b5f9cceb7d9f064d5b1a19a74</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Mouse accidentally saves Cheese's life from a toppling tree, a grateful Cheese becomes determined to thank him by doing everything she can for him. But Cheese is soon bothering Mouse all the time and her endless caring is becoming too much, causing Boy and Girl to hatch a plan to even things out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9109e873e859d6effa3c5f7efeb97401</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c16021af4e67354dba130b42704d364</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>After the Yeti's house is destroyed, the Lemmings are quick to point the finger at Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p08d177e86e46cf42f4ecb3cb64daa9c2</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy decides to adopt a coconut.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa46da99ab8403e36a8d474b0b8fb95b6</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit must convince Soundcheck to get back together again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7ad4dea8ce20820906d494a47026e96f</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>It's major treble when a flushed singing monster gets stuck in the toilet. Charlie starts to fret and tries to keep it low-key before it can harm anyone.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd151ad4fa7c45b694c6562245b59539b</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert takes his failed cooling hat invention along on a quest, using it to save the day after being faced with the Riddlemaster?s jibes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa71b4703dab60fe05f881ddc78ac43d6</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Joy wants to open a luxury spa centre at Pottsfield, and Danny?s done every single job on the list, correction, on one side of the list! With influential vlogger Luke Cutforth coming to be the spa?s first guest, Danny and Mick have to race to put together a luxury spa treatment from whatever they can find - not to mention finding a world class Swedish massage expert... Mick.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb1afa6a8e27c9b519f51ce1d59943fd2</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>Family portraits get personal! The Kwapongs try a clever painting hack, Tom Allen draws a super fancy unicorn, and Maisie Matilda paints a mini masterpiece on the edge of a book.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f120992cce42bd242375db26a42d6ec</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a mysterious stone, endowing them with the mastery of Shaolin Kung Fu.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe7690cdab092fb9368ec4408ae3dd01a</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Famous Five</title>
    <desc>As the summer comes to an end, George sets in motion a final adventure to protect a circus magician from an unscrupulous doctor who wishes to make use of his powers in the clinic.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p876f6dc5e82e8eef09862fd0ac749fa1</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a school of crabs that live in an underwater city.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc70e9e8acaa52af511ac5db7db9185bc</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle?s magic accidentally makes Mr Ludcomb fall in love with Miss Hill, and he tries increasingly desperate ways to win her heart. But Mia wants it stopped before it gets out of hand.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13b837e092a0ac16cf10e3e9ffe1f91d</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>RADI8 struggle to secure approval to debut after a member gets cut, and Hannah teams up with an unlikely partner to get Sandra out of OME.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf09aacfc3c009700494c73be7a7282f0</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>It?s the last match of the season, and everyone?s future is on the line. Can Hawx United cause an upset against Foxborough? Who will be cut and who will be saved.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1a43e485d56ecf7acb6dce9e1dc1358</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>Steve discovers just what it takes to be a terror from the skies, and believe us, it's a wild ride! He starts by strapping himself into one of Britain's fastest wind tunnels, where he goes head-to-head against the Microraptor. Then he goes green - literally - as he hitches a ride in a stunt plane. Finally, he unleashes the big guns as he takes on the biggest flying animal in history - Hatzegoptyrex - and meets another epic blast from the past.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5fc6dafc7937094a5b8f6276fc966a5e</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>When Professor Quantum invents a machine that creates instant Rockstar talent, who better to call than the Odd Socks? Whiff spots an opportunity to take a short cut to stardom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbeb2d8f1e15081ab775172baed6f03df</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Socials stars Shauni and Jake help Callum challenge Adam and Joe to face their fears! The question is, who will be the GOAT and impress Callum the most.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1a400f85c748d999de15cf79008d02be</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Ranger Marsh recounts Shellington's journey to reunite a monitor lizard with his siblings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p475ddd35a6243fde25d02413dda600c1</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>During a hoverboard race, Dad's new super-powered hoverboard malfunctions, so Cosima and Big Lizard throw the race to rescue him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1699994e05f37e862faa1cc48c831c94</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>A mishap on a mission leaves Danger Mouse confused - why is Penfold not talking to him? It might be because today is Penfold's birthday and he hasn't remembered it again! Squawk sprays DM with her experimental empathy gas in the hope that he will find it easier to care about other people. The newly empathetic DM is a changed mouse! One who seems to think breaking the Baron out of prison is a great idea.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa906b53f7371fff74d44e2194a58bf1b</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface's first sleepover in the den is troubled by spooky tales of a frightening Fangtom and Walter turning up with a demolition gang determined to flatten the den.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p87cc33fd0a8665db870b7564252cc82f</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes aren?t really meant to do quests without Mr Friendlyface?s express permission. But when they come across a cute little squirrel queen, and she begs for their help, they find her impossible to resist. All they have to do is quest to the Tree of Certain Doom and pass his challenges. But the squirrel queen is not who she appears to be, and the heroes have to quickly un-quest their quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc66ead86a1798e4f31033a6bf01a29a</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>Alfie started riding motorbikes when he was just four-years-old. Fast forward six years, and he is now competing in a drag racing championship and attempting to break land speed records. Diagnosed with ADHD and Autism at the age of eight, Alfie discovered a unique outlet for his energy and a source of focus on the race track. The sport captured his attention in a way nothing else had and also introduced him to fellow competitor, and now best friend, Jack. As Alfie gears up for the racing season, he must deal with the challenge of mastering a brand new, more powerful motorbike that he hopes will propel him to higher speeds. However, with increased power, come fresh challenges. The new season also brings an opportunity to set a land speed record, another milestone on Alfie?s journey towards his ultimate dream - becoming the fastest boy in the world. Adding to the pressure, Alfie's racing idol Bubba Myers - the world?s fastest man on one wheel - is making the trip from the United States to watch his record-breaking attempt. With best friend Jack hot on his heels, and his world record attempt looming ever closer, will Alfie master his new wheels in time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb5801a1b015df8479a45da7388df2b2c</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Searching for Lapras, the Rising Volt Tacklers investigate an odd white mist over the sea.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd0e80ce060ee91d91313fe50a33ad51b</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A football, a biscuit, a sofa bed and a pair of shoes are among the items getting the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf1786c5e1632112d437a33a96c3312d</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>The Nektons try to identify a unique life form. They've never seen it, they've only heard its sound: 'Bloop'. Just as Ant discovers its true nature, a huge underwater mining machine threatens to destroy it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7f925b40ef2392892bdc9046135840f5</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The kids of Beanotown decide that they can run the town far better than the grown-ups. However, they discover it isn?t nearly as easy or fun as they had hoped.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa15e18ace150b21c21fc62dda6a4fddb</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Shortly after Danger Mouse's biggest fan comes to visit, members of the team start to disappear.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p802a8ae5995df356a97d1d477738819a</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When their dear friend and very first customer, Bonnie, orders a tent, the Ninjas travel down memory lane as they recount their first meeting and first ever delivery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p50fdbe3b6bccc0a45a6517dbaaf7bb5c</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. On a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. When a bull wanders into the sheep's field, Shaun discovers that it is a bad idea to make him see red. But then the naughty pigs pour some red paint into the sheep dip.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd7fa9021bbe5f9d4a4cc2900a118dbf8</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy's sample of Yummy is mysteriously crushed - but who is the culprit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p93597cfcd6284d4eff680bc3ccf8bda1</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Adeline quits due to artistic differences, Cheese is hired as director of the annual town founders' play. The family is happy to help, but Cheese soon turns super-bossy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf5ca9b0faffa444d3e13954c24269e75</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface?s hat has been stolen by a Big Ole Worm, and the heroes must quest to get it back. As they trail the worm through the Prickly Desert, Trevor accidentally spikes himself all over on a cactus. But all is not lost ? now that he is covered in sharp spikes, Trevor realises that he has a unique superpower, and when the time comes to confront the Big Ole Worm, it?s Spiky Trevor to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d893098488de351f2861251077cc5bc</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Odd Squad builds an exact replica of the villain?s vault to intercept a jetpack.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p49fb3592e61265209a5d9d350dd16e70</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia tries to win back a stolen gadget on a villain game show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb69a979896a239aad4b2ee7aff59854b</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan tricks Beth into believing she broke his battery-powered bike.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa608c0317cbcbf41f823628dae40d0b4</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Riposte Prime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p46c6550b324a83053b88341b3ace3e0c</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>A descent into the Great Crater of Paldea reveals wonders and Pok?mon beyond imagination.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa54626811e3033cb1efd809d9e52c53b</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Pro gamer Jelly guides the teams in an exhilarating WRC race. Who will cross the finish line first in this nail-biting battle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e54710fa1fe949763698fba45a0ba38</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Keeping Team Brawl?s secret leaves Ariana torn. Michelle and Eldon take a look back at their past as Anthony avoids confronting his present.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p53e3f6af7ef3bf04ac1208a8601ad694</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Abby and Shini go head-to-head in a powerchair football challenge! Using specially designed powerchairs as part of four-a-side teams, who will come out on top.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe198144b1c57887ed93fb809b7488166</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The farm is used as a location for a historical drama, but Mowermouth eats the film.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb22d9607023c096be1ef2f8521f1ad2a</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Danger agents go undercover disguised as a family to find out why the world?s villains are heading to one holiday camp, Sidneyland. When Baron Greenback shows up, the team are convinced he?s up to no good, but can?t find any evidence of wrongdoing. When Penfold enters Squawk and DM in a dance competition they discover the prize is the fabled Helmet of Power, an ultimate invention bent on destruction.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b5ce7408b56f7960eb3b2cde7d508f8</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis's ultimate hero, Grizzly Griller, plans on trekking to the source of the River Beano, broadcasting the treacherous path on live TV. Dennis introduces him to his pet hamster Galahad - only to discover they are his biggest fear! Grizzly is so afraid that Dennis must disguise himself as his hero and go in his place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8740f186fd542531c6393457aada6f7e</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Dog decides to show the family that he can be as tough as the wolves they are watching on TV. He joins a gang of street dogs and soon becomes leader of the pack. Meanwhile, the rest of the kids worry when Dog doesn?t come home and go out looking for him. However, they find that he is now too cool to be part of the 'old' family - until he is forced to make a choice between loyalty to the pack and loyalty to his best friend Boy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80906893d3cfdb5661c71eda227eba55</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7901fd319112513941ee458bf31ff69e</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy pretends to have a twisted ankle so that the Lemmings have to take care of him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p778c943244c038dd40892ba970e83fd6</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings set up a mini-fair, but Grizzy steals the Lemmings' tickets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdda6dfb8ff413c76388fa30a994e25d9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit must convince Soundcheck to get back together again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb9fe93e52121c824e091c6c0d138adb6</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Charlie wrestles with being just a chore boy when Que hosts a monster hunter tournament. Entering in disguise, he is ready to lay the smackdown after a pretentious pre-teen participant mocks Pierce.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9505f4a5a731c1ec5990928067fb6a55</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle is unhappy with how easy questing has become since Cral the Eagle joined the heroes, offending the eagle just when they need him the most.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ac8fa176bea27e14bcc365246b3ae79</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Lance is a ping pong whizz, he always aces the annual Pottsfield Ping Pong competition. This year Danny?s determined to teach him a thing or two and has stayed up all night watching online tutorials. Now he can?t keep his eyes open long enough to play! Lance smells victory, Mick smells trouble. Mick is determined to find Danny somewhere to get a nap. However, with Joy on the prowl and Lance making things difficult it looks like Danny may never lift that trophy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p794ef896234e11d37436fc31d1481e91</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs take flight with stained-glass wings, Jill Scott MBE draws a footballing big cat, and Bristles gives the juicy lowdown on artist Giuseppe Arcimboldo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3df0fbebb2280bb7ac68e32c6cd4ccac</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A peace missionary panda tries to calm down Grizzy and the Lemmings during a fight.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef857e1433114a38274dcf38670f76c6</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Captain Barnacles and Peso become lost in a dangerous maze of underwater caves while helping a baby octopus get home, and the rest of the Octonauts must rescue them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e1fa8298ada6d9f4d0a9bbc9b20dd0c</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>It seems an epic battle took place in the cabin, and Grizzy is missing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f4173f642ff3256664f7a4cf0a08f74</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Diamond prank Comet at a fake Christmas calendar photoshoot. The other Gladiators have sneaky fun pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5cd8bf081d5ab1bc368bae668e80dd2d</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle wants to win first prize at her school's sports day. However, she gets paired with Roland, who refuses to take part, and her magic accidentally makes him super strong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8594fcb13a3ba08d43e7d627d93cd4f</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>Ken is back, and it seems like everything is back to normal. However, when a famous photographer arrives to take pre-debut photos, the trainees realise they still have issues to work out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p25bb505ccc302d4d5e28e4c83cb31d06</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Andrew?s guilt about Bobby puts a strain on his friendship with Christina. As new players join Hawx in controversial circumstances, Coach Byrne considers his future.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80f3d3edabd4420d8dbcb0f7e79e87a4</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>Steve travels to new depths as he discovers just what it takes to be an aquatic terror. His quest sees him rocket though the water in spectacular style - just like an Opthalmosaurus. Then he heads to his very own Jurassic park to chomp through chain with the power of Sarcosuchus. Finally, the fear factor gets cranked to the max as Steve dives into the murky unknown in the hunt for the infamous predator x.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0246428309dd5e3bc890619f87dce67c</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Jackie needs help getting her horse to jump. However, Hugh is no ordinary horse ? he's a pantomime horse! It?s when the band discover that Hugh loves dancing that they save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbcc938140d2c5b9a2f14e938d192c5a7</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Little bro Callum challenges Adam and Joe to bring out their inner sloths in order to avoid facing a forfeit on the Wheel of Doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3e4ac01bb9021818eb7a55a4f25ff05c</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Periwinkle strays during a Bialowieza Forest mission and discovers a rare European Bison.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5cfcadb351b0d4704df34ba5d5a139ba</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad and Cosima both think they're the best at pranking. Their prank war quickly spirals out of control, until Big Lizard finally reveals Proxima's real pranking champion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea0f60cf71247ea3d276941d6971e477</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's over-reliance on gadgets prompts Colonel K to send his top agent on a tech-free nature retreat. Unbeknownst to Danger Mouse, Greenback has the same plans for his daughter, Delilah, whose social media obsession has also spiralled out of control. Back at HQ Penfold is tasked with protecting the entire world from the threat of super-villainy. Stripped off his gadgets, DM struggles to adapt to life in the wilderness and, when a talking pine cone called Conni begins to offer him survival tips, he begins to question his own sanity. Soon enough, Delilah catches wind of DM's presence and she plots to destroy him as a means of getting back into her Dad's good books.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p75c10893273f4622c94d4cf5fb696d17</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The class dig up a mysterious time capsule which sets them off on a race to find hidden treasure before Walter or a greed-crazed Paul the Potato can find it first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p659edd59775ca7523bb64a0d16d30e47</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The blossom has gone missing. No, not Blossom the unicorn, the blossom on the trees! The heroes are sent on a quest deep into the heart of the forest, where legend has it you can see a face watching you from the trees. Twinkle doesn?t believe in legends, but when help comes from nowhere as they try and stop the scoundrel that is stealing the blossom, she is forced to reconsider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2f8d2357ef662dfdfa8453de1222ecd1</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>Having found fame around the world as a young child, talented teen drummer Nandi Bushell sets out on a new musical path.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p72a61a393180e6e77e7017d8203cad5a</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko comes up with a plan for confronting Lapras of the Six Heroes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p492011ee27c5adfb7d000b0355f1123c</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>A weird glowing fish has lured every fish in the area to its bioluminescence. When Kaiko and Will also fall under its spell, Ant and Fontaine must rescue their parents - while wearing blindfolds against the hypnotic glow.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p61cdb386fec3ad084876177dea337b41</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Fed up with Dennis pulling the wool over Mrs Creecher's eyes, Walter orchestrates a robot to take over Class 3C - with disastrous results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p09cd14a7c66d70b97a06114b327de9ed</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The heroes find themselves fighting for their lives on an alien world in Quark's latest money-spinning sports event.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a349849bdee1e607399cc7c77be8b24</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Felix asks the Ninjas for a superpower so that he can meet Mega Powerful Man. However, when villainous Lance traps every superhero, the Ninjas and Felix must step in and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81c0111f0dd84eb090eb31b4ef54b492</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. Shaun finds the farmer's old record player on the dump and organises a rave in the barn, but trouble looms when the naughty pigs gatecrash the party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d85e8a5e8a7604eacfba23dddab4e8d</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The cabin comes to life and wants to return to Canada without Grizzy or the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd3bf809eba7aa4ce014113e511d0efb6</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Gramps tells the kids about a heavenly clearing in the woods, and they decide to make it their hang-out spot for the summer. However, the Smith twins find out about it too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1b4ca7a59f2228a8a82b61b74bf242b1</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The forest has run out of bath sponges and is becoming very stinky. Their latest order never arrived, and so the heroes must quest under the sea to Merhaven to collect them. However, Hoofius, whose singing stinks worse than his armpits, decides to enter the annual Merhaven Song Contest and accidentally causes a simple quest to collect bath sponges to turn into something much more perilous.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ed5d646aa33c0f016a4f842cc22d80c</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Agent Olympia is not happy when an agent with the same name shows up at headquarters. Curriculum: Measuring temperature.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3dc5e187c321f7b4f6f77226abb9c3ea</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Ms O tells Olympia and Otis a story about a famous villain duo. Curriculum: Adding, subtracting and multiplying by zero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf57f18551a75efc65bc912f7566e48af</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef almost ruins National Hotdog Day when he forgets to book the Hot-Diggity-Doggity Dog.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa0aac1dd1681a527aae9c418a5fe84d4</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face an invisible enemy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa159bd9b067167936a1a52cfe1fdcccb</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>The Rising Volt Tacklers locate Entei of the Six Heroes, but something seems off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8596d2d582588aa0f3912eab1985f024</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>The winning teams return to the arena to take on Mario Kart in the Grand Final. Who will win the competition and claim the Game on Grandparents trophy and GOAT title.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc965b4b97374457007445f0dd4a65bf1</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Pete tries to juggle both the Brawl and regionals, but it may be too much. Ethan discovers a huge secret within A-Troupe, and Olive is suspicious of Ariana and Grace?s friendship.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1b7576d62429f4032216d555f0bfb517</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Abby takes on a wheelchair motocross challenge ? can she perform the tricks and stunts taught to her by world champion, Tomas Woods.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54135eb056632874cbaba8a329c5925c</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The Farmer opens a petting zoo but loses control of the customers. Can Shaun restore order.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p98cb08547b6cab15d2f88c4e8b2a223b</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When a sudden urge to fly the Mark IV hits, Penfold leads a confused Danger Mouse to a farm, from which he claims to feel an unexplained magnetic pull. An entranced Penfold is met by a shadowy figure - Granny Penfold! Penfold recounts his childhood years on Granny?s farm, where he was trained in the ancient martial art of Farm Fu; a farming based martial art. Granny needs Penfold?s help to retrieve the sacred Fung Farm Book of Farm Fu, which has fallen into the hands of her enemies, causing farm animals to turn evil and rise up against their owners.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5bc9fb86a9c9d89de3a6896036c3a7d9</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface steals Professor Von Screwtop's Pastry-based Intelligent Espionage unit (PIE) after forming a strong bond with the pie-shaped robot. Pieface is dismayed when Walter steals it from him to protect his dad from the embarrassing footage the PIE's memory chip holds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4db578615381ab592eeaeea97d895804</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The family have been telling their deepest, darkest secrets to Cat for years. But when Cat finds one of Mouse?s inventions that gives her intelligence and speech, she threatens to tell all their secrets if they don't do everything she asks. The kids must decide between living under their feline pharaoh's thumb or confessing their secrets to each other.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfed16d83f85eb7f2591ee30d5e8a513b</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p61dd694df56fdab7c28daaacef9942b6</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play marbles, and it's driving Grizzy crazy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6da67b82a65bfa51ab80ff34f6cbd6a4</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy exchanges his indifferent fish with the Lemmings' affectionate and lively fish.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p07e8c90f4bc95e6cc138af9db789ccd7</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit is called to Odd Squad?s top-secret security facility.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pce45058c1f25d13694109f555e8b4a3b</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Helsing should never have trusted the gang with his mind swap ray. Now, Charlie is a kettle, Pierce is a phone, and Snorp has stolen his body.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4049d564b490860df3677dc6ab0d2388</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>An angry Swampclops follows the heroes back from their quest for a giant raspberry, so Hoofius must abandon his chances of winning the bake-off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3dcc908834fa89d31657019c7b692113</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Danny and Mick?s dad Clive has turned up with his latest in a long line of ?sure-fire? money making schemes: washing customers? cars in the car park while they use the leisure centre. The boys are happy to help and are soon scrubbing away, but when Joy finds out and demands a free wash, the boys clean her beloved old banger so hard it falls to bits. Don?t worry lads, Clive knows how to fix this? or at least replace one problem with a much bigger problem. Yeah, thanks dad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cf1ec3aa72fe269d49ee1c868538607</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs build 'Kwembley', their DIY table football pitch, Mandy Barker wows turning plastic waste into art, and comedian Aisling Bea draws a puffin with a potato waffle problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1500fcc3c13870d2b9e03edb99166eb0</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings create a shadow puppet show where seven papercut lemmings confront a bear.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc86af08c9c02f6ba215273b5a0f148b3</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: Sun and Moon</title>
    <desc>When Ash Ketchum oversleeps on his tenth birthday, he ends up with a stubborn Pikachu instead of the first partner Pok?mon he wanted! Together with new friends Verity and Sorrel, Ash must journey across the land to return the Rainbow Wing to the Legendary Pok?mon Ho-Oh. However, they must face off with arrogant Trainer Cross and the mysterious Mythical Pok?mon Marshadow. Will they succeed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcc3c89cf3bdb0c6aa17ba489732e14f6</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Tubes</title>
    <desc>Olympia shows viewers how to solve an odd problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd96c9fb1a748407ad7e7f561bbc8cdd9</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Swumpy sneaks into school, and Pickle accidentally makes him super clever so that she comes top in her test! This backfires when she has to represent the school in a maths competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9907bc19c58d6741f49861caa644601d</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>Ken assigns everyone the task of filming a promo to introduce themselves to the world, but it brings up unexpected connections and jealousies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p496de0671a31835b94228fcc25875a55</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>New girl Leah helps Christina with her nerves, but will a talent show derail their friendship? A new welfare officer at Hawx pushes Coach Byrne out of his comfort zone too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb0246254a7a8987821c13b46adf316d</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>Steve's on a mission to find dinosaurs that have something a little special... fearsome killers, with incredible abilities! Get ready for a sensory sensation! His quest sees him race in the dark like a troodon and track prey from miles away taking tips from the daspletosaurus, and finally he gets his hands on a real-life caiman to show how their pressure pits are just like that of the spinosaurus. Strap yourself in for a sensory overload.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6201883edcbd2ef25e7761ad149708e</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>The band turn detective and go in search of Rosie?s lucky flying disc which she needs for a competition. While cracking the case, they discover a surprising secret about Whiff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd466b430d7261385636385604b35fe4</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Adam and Joe take to the streets to become living statues in Callum?s latest challenge - but who will be the best man standing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae94f7750320dd3374c20dbb2662af9d</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>A storm carries sharks into a swamp so the Octonauts must help all the creatures coexist.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pca63cb1cc42fdbf159b0303cc05620d1</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Cosima takes over Dad's mission to film a unique underwater plant. But his special camera proves harder to operate than she'd thought, and Big Lizard keeps getting distracted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p978b38140949d563c78029d0cfe54f3e</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Snowman is hired as Danger Mouse's new sidekick, leaving Penfold without a job.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb9a8b62eb1f051a7a86e10437f9214c</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Dennis and the gang think they have caused Ralf to lose his job, they're determined to make his last day at Bash Street School totally blam by setting up the greatest prank Ralf's ever known.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3d939c9462f01933b550eae67571eb8</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are relieved that the loud, threatening voice they can hear actually belongs to a small slug named Zorgoth, who is armed with a megaphone. However, when Zorgoth uses his Orb of Compression to shrink the heroes down to the size of ants, their relief evaporates. They must now embark on a long and dangerous quest, through their picnic items and beyond, to warn the Council before Zorgoth shrinks the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe50df153eaba594e89a65c54ae953f0c</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>Jack is just 13 years old, but he is already one of the best young darts players in the world. As the British youth darts champion, he has his sights set on an even bigger title: world champion. Jack travels to Gibraltar for the World Junior Open, where he will compete both in the singles and as part of the England squad. However, the road to victory won?t be easy, as Jack has previously lost a world final against Luke Littler, who has since gone on to become professional world champion at just 17. Can Jack turn the tables and bring home the gold? We follow Jack as he trains, competes and faces off against his biggest rivals, including his England teammate Archie, currently ranked number one in the world. With fast-paced action, nail-biting matches and the pressure of playing for his country, we follow the highs and lows of Jack?s road to the top.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p78959b3cdf19b2ba7a972b96f195fadb</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Amethio challenges the black Rayquaza, and Terapagos displays some of its true power.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p362de3d9335cc2d2ba79ff8660f6238a</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>While fighting over Viking treasure, the Nektons take over the Dark Orca. But the pirates in turn take over the Aronnax. Neither side is happy about strangers in their homes, but neither side is willing to back down.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p182d1acdf3f80be57cabbfbb24b20c7e</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A bungled attempt at a stunt leads to Dennis accidentally becoming an internet star and Beanotown celebrity! But his moment of fame is short and Dennis is soon replaced by Walter's cat, who can play the piano. Dennis has to stage the best stunt yet to gain back his audience.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2448826bf08a8b69aefa3652e97decf5</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>In order to stop a deranged Victorian time-travelling chimp from uninventing the world, Danger Mouse and Penfold must arrive in the past just before the nick of time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb89086a78e1589c68cd9ddbc5eb06285</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas must use their imagination when Anna orders a new toy as a birthday present for her father - a toymaker who's already invented every toy imaginable.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb22bbd3bc21c3ae9f1950c247833d48</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. The flock think they are in for fun when a kite blows into their field.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef5d96d96f8e8c29656c5a6cab5c2c7c</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a box filled with fortune cookies close to the Great Wall of China.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pba2796334e942468921c463b1c433065</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The gang want to win theme park tickets that are up for grabs in a robot fighting contest. They ask to use Mouse?s unbeatable robot, but he prefers to help them build their own.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pafe052db79735499dff691fceca1bb7c</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Only wood elves have ever defeated the mighty Eye of Vernon hat, so when the Riddlemaster wears the eye to take over the forest, the heroes quest to Wood Elf Wood to get help. However, Twinkle really doesn?t want to, as wood elves are so stuck up! Struggling to contain her irritation with their high-and-mighty ways, Twinkle still manages to offend them, and the heroes wonder how they will ever save the forest now.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32df456943a31359aa3e76648f081c8f</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia and Otis are tasked with calling a truce between feuding guests. Curriculum: Using a Venn Diagram, 3D shapes: spheres and cubes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a7cc9c25316a9316d40d4a87c98e2f3</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Ms O leaves headquarters in the hands of an unlikely crew. Curriculum: Spatial Sense: Mapping, Position, Location and Direction.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd794773fd1ca66f3bb6c8d6344136323</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef brokers a truce with lice by selecting three kids to 'host' them on their heads.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p300a4c3a34f447193e6a22be19fcab31</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug faces Argos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9dd5da959e11c2622285ca2b471cc2ec</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>The Rising Volt Tacklers finally get a rematch with the Black Rayquaza.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p76a6cd10b0dd4098d3f8b997309657ba</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Top Minecraft and Mario Kart tips to help you turn your grandparent into a gaming legend. Plus Jelly, Yammy and Slogo face off in the ultimate Minecraft build showdown! Who will be crowned the Pro Gamer Champion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pefa6da1af07a4d5e59f2a20d30b7e1d1</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>As the regionals qualifier clashes with the Brawl?s, A-Troupe struggle under the weight of all the secrets they have kept from each other.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe113b7e440701120dd4668cb899cf7d1</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Joel tries Kite Foiling with Olympic Gold medallist Ellie Aldridge ? can he navigate a board across the waves using the wind power of a kite.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7cfd6fd223c9ab06eead334bd48901a4</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. Shirley the sheep has put on weight, so Shaun helps her get in shape with a rigorous exercise regime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62965f8ec13c5343b9a20d521aff8707</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse and the Baron are forced to team up in order to defeat a cheese-obsessed villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc640fda27059d028e627a20d12c99338</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Mayor Wilbur passes a law to increase healthy eating in Beanotown, replacing all foods with peas...of the mushy variety! The gang must avoid the people of Beanotown who are rapidly turning into Zompeas after eating the green mush. Dennis uses the only ordinary peas in town to sabotage Wilbur's mush-making factory and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41d58d1465e51eb4de1792f354b29a85</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Boy and Girl start receiving lavish gifts addressed to ?two great kids?, Mouse thinks it must be a mistake. He and Dog set out to investigate whether these presents are meant for someone else, but the other kids don't like that idea at all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p83183b454813d61ba000f321722fff50</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p98f168df5f29f37ae0a42de84dfafe1c</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>When Charlie ignores the rules of Pierce's magical board game, the living pieces escape, creating a dicey situation that the gang must roll with.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a09de134fc0b8e65bb5078672a8bec2</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad is haunted by a ghost.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf0052df934f22523e5b7eb4e5673e7d2</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert is really proud of the plants he has grown ready for a visit from The Complete Gnome Gardener magazine. However, when a Wind Dragon flies through the forest destroying all his hard work, Herbert turns to desperate measures ? a barrowful of Stinkweasel?s stinkiest compost! Now, the whole forest is at risk of being overwhelmed by the smell, and the heroes must quest to get rid of it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6fbe790ae4282b14265104a8bedddd57</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Learn how the heroes became Ladybug and Cat Noir.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13756d1dd4ab40bb9be92476adfabee1</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Marinette refuses to become Ladybug, but Paris needs her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb927ed3d5e60f64acbd5dc7b1b44ebf</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Joined by Perrin, the Rising Volt Tacklers set out to find Kleavor on Tengu Mountain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d673cc286577b672f953048a7f66c0a</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a silkworm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb2a4455efc0d2ba913ad4e4083bbf47b</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings use all the electricity for their phones - now Grizzy can?t watch TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p465df138cba7e7ae123993705a66a905</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings catch a grasshopper that can give you whatever your heart desires.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e0fd7c58b3a252cdfc561d821057d41</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The siblings try to break their annoying habits for the sake of family peace. At first they offer each other support, but then one-by-one they start to give up. Only Boy and Girl keep going, but can they make it to the end of 24 hours.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf01ab48424de754588783a2e22e48b0b</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>A dog show is coming up, and cool prizes are given to the winning dog and its trainer. Cheese, Girl and Mouse all have great ideas for how to train Dog for the grand finale. And if Dog picks one of their finales, that sibling gets to be the trainer who shares in the prize! Boy also wants to help but gets shunned for having a less impressive idea on how to win. The contest arrives, but Dog is torn when it comes to his finale. Whose idea does he choose? Can Boy jump in with his 'unimpressive' idea and help save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbdaeec7627628d03ca2742675670ed96</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After her siblings accidentally insult her dreams of being a pop star, Cheese is bonked on the head and starts to believe she's a huge celebrity! Mouse says they all must play along, because if they ruin the illusion then there's a chance Cheese could go bonkers. Cheese turns into a diva, making outrageous demands from her siblings, and soon enough they're sick of it. But when they learn she was duping them all along, they set out to teach her a lesson..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4540d9337e6bd866504e38a486ddadec</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen has his superball confiscated, so the gang set off to retrieve it from Chef?s office.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p73436548f2765fadaa07495786f981bd</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Jude befriends a chicken with an attitude when an unusual petting zoo visits the school.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6564b7f9b1833bcbeba99b1e6168d336</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Online potato sensation Spudman is joined by Joe-bot as he tries to program this malfunctioning robot to serve baked potatoes, and Adam B-bot gets to work in an ice cream shop.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ff06053d24e3c937fdcc22f2c716252</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Challenges, celebrities, makes and adventures with the Blue Peter team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c2dad280d7a573302baf70e15a69a2e</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:25AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs build 'Kwembley', their DIY table football pitch, Mandy Barker wows turning plastic waste into art, and comedian Aisling Bea draws a puffin with a potato waffle problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1500fcc3c13870d2b9e03edb99166eb0</image>
    <start>11:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Elijah and Sue go head to head with Finley and Graham as they compete for the chance to make it to the Grand Final and become ultimate Game on Grandparents champion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f52fbedfee0801094153a91aa6b57df</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. When people in town can no longer count down, Olive and Otto must uncover who is causing the problem and why.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd79a2406943b710052f6477ad3ae2c2</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. When several of Oscar's robots made in his own image become lost in town, Olive and Otto must help him find them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfba44b98c725830596050a280ce1966a</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Alien zombies, space monks, a demon clown, an evil knight and a world record attempt -it's just another day at Cranmede Academy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a4f6570cbeeb3d53adb000b54c1d578</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle wants to win first prize at her school's sports day. However, she gets paired with Roland, who refuses to take part, and her magic accidentally makes him super strong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8594fcb13a3ba08d43e7d627d93cd4f</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>You?re making bogies in your nose all the time. To show this, Dr Xand uses the Ouchcam to give us an exclusive close-up of one of his freshly picked beauties, before he and Dr Chris use a supersized nose to make gloopy snot into something more crusty. We?ve got a Top 5 countdown of the Longest Longy Long Things Ever, including the mind-blowingly long, longest-ever burp. Gladiator Dynamite is back making sure Dr Dan and Dr Raph play by the rules as they go toe-to-toe in a body battle ? it?s all fun and games until the loser has to get into the ice bath! We get a chance to follow Dr Ronx through the whole of their hospital shift in Doctors on Duty. Emilia has cut her lip at school and goes to the emergency department in Liverpool, and Jake is in hospital in Edinburgh after injuring his neck when a pal picked him up and accidentally dropped him on his head.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe812a9e18f268a5aa8b7b0ce8266c308</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Dr Big Brain has an electrical short circuit, Marie Curie is wowed by a rocket man, some of the great women of science are celebrated, and 200 monks get electrocuted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21daa97d981587de14f8ff3ad8bddf40</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>When Ken suggests that Hannah tries living a day in the life of a trainee, she quickly struggles to find her footing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p528bd48683e536eac40e921ac19bef05</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>It?s the last match of the season, and everyone?s future is on the line. Can Hawx United cause an upset against Foxborough? Who will be cut and who will be saved.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1a43e485d56ecf7acb6dce9e1dc1358</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef takes the kids on a trip to a museum, and Duncan goes on a mission to scare Courtney.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc72751ce3c887c4b03b0417d2a8bca7d</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan convinces Owen to start misbehaving to show him how much fun their timeouts can be.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p64cdbe54e04dd37f4adbf42b4a490149</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Bridgette gets the hiccups for the first time and tries desperately to get rid of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb93d6040b77fd2f1a2b5d7d46d15ace1</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron and Penfold are stranded on a desert island. In the skies above, there is a race to snatch Brunel's All Encompassing Remote Control.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa7b8e966b5c6c306f3a119bdf3118798</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Colonel K disappears on a free holiday, Danger Mouse pulls rank and assumes the mantle of caretaker colonel. However, the role is much less exciting than he anticipated, as world-saving missions make way for endless paperwork. Meanwhile, K's freebie spa retreat happens to be a diversion tactic in Greenback's latest plot to take over the world, with the baron banking on the Danger Agency falling apart without its figurehead and the world descending into disarray.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paef6868cdecdac98504d06f4fc8a956a</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Envious at Danger Mouse's ever-growing medal collection, Penfold questions whether he will ever be deemed special enough to receive a prize of his own. Seconds later, a knock at the door reveals a holographic Quark, who anoints Penfold as 'the chosen one' in a suspiciously automated message that culminates in an overawed Penfold receiving his very own magic wand. Penfold's joy is short-lived however - as he and DM step outside of HQ to find that the streets of are London teeming with hundreds of wannabe wizards, all brandishing identical wands. After discovering that the wands are mass-produced shavings from Merlin's legendary staff, the pair set out to stop Quark's latest money-making scheme by reuniting the staff with its rightful owner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p323dc2e8e64fccd5de7990c027816ff5</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the siblings try to make an awesome Christmas surprise for their parents, things go wrong every step of the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pce5c4f9b0f49d66f108cb37d0a045fdf</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Gramps comes to stay, the kids tell him the story of how Mum and Dad almost didn?t get married. When the kids first met each other, neither family could get used to the other?s funny ways and just didn?t get along. They fought so much that the wedding planner quit! Will the six kids figure out a way to be a family, or will Mum and Dad be forced to call off their wedding.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8835247f164916b34101aa26f1a0da50</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>In this second part of the flashback story of Mum and Dad?s wedding, the kids realize how unhappy they were apart, but they can't see how to fix things. Then a bird-based emergency sees both groups of kids leap into action to work together and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e535fd2fee7b3b090c7ca871cc213c7</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a magic stick that functions as a Yummy divining rod.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcee1931a27a2dfd300dfe45402832d2b</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a jewel that gives them total control over the fireflies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p441f9d3dc8cbcbd950cad86aa8c0bc2f</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes aren?t really meant to do quests without Mr Friendlyface?s express permission. But when they come across a cute little squirrel queen, and she begs for their help, they find her impossible to resist. All they have to do is quest to the Tree of Certain Doom and pass his challenges. But the squirrel queen is not who she appears to be, and the heroes have to quickly un-quest their quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc66ead86a1798e4f31033a6bf01a29a</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The blossom has gone missing. No, not Blossom the unicorn, the blossom on the trees! The heroes are sent on a quest deep into the heart of the forest, where legend has it you can see a face watching you from the trees. Twinkle doesn?t believe in legends, but when help comes from nowhere as they try and stop the scoundrel that is stealing the blossom, she is forced to reconsider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2f8d2357ef662dfdfa8453de1222ecd1</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are relieved that the loud, threatening voice they can hear actually belongs to a small slug named Zorgoth, who is armed with a megaphone. However, when Zorgoth uses his Orb of Compression to shrink the heroes down to the size of ants, their relief evaporates. They must now embark on a long and dangerous quest, through their picnic items and beyond, to warn the Council before Zorgoth shrinks the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe50df153eaba594e89a65c54ae953f0c</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Blink takes over a huge beach cleaning drone, and Grandpa and Mansour unite to tackle it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c7b711065be5e3e02e19304ccd08631</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Mansour, Obaid and Salem fall out with Shamma during a VR game, and Blink takes advantage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b5c36c82cb1d483084df97d9f3aaee1</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>One member from each team must spend the day balancing on a pole under the hot sun, and with no food in their tummy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34bd78ea1bfc532d7fc78ae8e9422045</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gremlins: Secrets of the Mogwai</title>
    <desc>Sam, Elle and Gizmo's nerves are tested as they follow Grandpa's map.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b6733dc58cc2df194e355a8116e17d9</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>10 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
