<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When two different pieces of flat-pack furniture are delivered to the Farmer and Bitzer, confusion ensues as they start to mix up the pieces. Shaun and the flock are forced to give them a lesson in following instructions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6faba19999bdaf0067c3c03224597602</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's film star status is threatened by a toilet uprising. An epic battle on the streets of Tokyo between Danger Mouse and Dr Loocifer! Oh, wait - it's just a scene being filmed for Danger Mouse: The Movie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa699c08bac85f3f5f4670350bfb26834</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis leads the gang on the baffling trail of a mysterious Beanotown secret society.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbe40fbbd57946697982b8c481f8009a4</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Tired of feeling like a loser, Mouse decides to play dirty to win Mazes and Monsters against his siblings, even if it means it takes away the fun of the game for everyone.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31e7b05f8c9cd8564e6f3bbd8fdd2f3c</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef7706296379c6989a37da832a8336b6</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a silkworm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb2a4455efc0d2ba913ad4e4083bbf47b</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings use all the electricity for their phones - now Grizzy can?t watch TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p465df138cba7e7ae123993705a66a905</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf326fb9ddf1e4b8189998894cdaba294</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Forest inspectors pay the forest a visit to check its super-happy status. Friendlyface sends the heroes on outlandish quests to guarantee results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf423a5126c7145dec4e840079fa076e4</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: Black and White</title>
    <desc>When Ash, Iris and Cilan enter a battle competition in Eindoak Town, they meet and befriend mythical Pok?mon Victini. However, disaster strikes when misguided wanderer Damon seizes Victini for his own plans! Can Ash prove himself a hero and earn the help of the legendary Reshiram to rescue Victini and save Eindoak Town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb04e230c9d82712b43bc1c387cab9a1</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A totally wicked song about gravity, a T-rex going to see a doctor, vampires on holiday, and Sir Isaac Newton riding a rollercoaster - welcome to the bizarre world of Horrible Science.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p225ef60f63c5a1f6aa9ee4f55650c08d</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall and his long-suffering crew return for more deadly encounters with animals hoping to earn a place on his hallowed Deadly 60 list. Steve Backshall travels to Indonesia in search of three very different reptiles to add to his list of 60 deadly predators. He and his crew have a nerve-racking close encounter when they are chased by a group of ravenous, three-metre-long komodo dragons, the world's largest venomous lizards! Steve also demonstrates the incredible gliding technique of a tiny flying lizard and heads out on a nocturnal hunt for the beautiful but lethal green pit viper.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p746766f2cf7cf0ebb0da2b993dcd49a9</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Things get explosive when Dr Chris and Dr Xand look at how spots are made, plus an incredible emergency service at work in Australia: the Flying Doctors.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b4c137dff0cf46b799270e7eb64b46d</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>In this episode, we meet nine-year-old twin sisters Kiki and Queenie. We also follow U11 boys Teddy and Miles in their biggest tournament of the year.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32db01aaffdf41be1b2b695848d338ff</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Predators</title>
    <desc>Steve uncovers the secrets of sharks, the world?s most infamous predators. From the ocean?s most graceful killers to the biggest shark to have ever existed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3bf81cc8d942b29ddd4732aa40bb593d</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It's a big day at Pottsfield Leisure Centre - there is a new boss in town. Sharon Granger means business and wants to create an advert to bring in more customers and make her mark. She tasks Danny and Mick to make an advert showing the best bits of the leisure centre... what could possibly go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7bb2d3421a49fd3a99f24a2c68077b06</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy?s sister Ruby wants to meet her hero, superstar vlogger Fay Moss, so Andy and the Band risk missing their next gig by racing off to help out. Staging a fake fashion photoshoot by posing as flashy designers, they attempt to bag some time with Fay by distracting her security guard! Cousin Mac?s new auto-tuner invention is put to good use, but after an epic diva tantrum, will Fay live up to all of Ruby expectations.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fd9ca307fd295ae771597804d126e27</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum is a Little Bro in control! He?s pitting his Big Bro Adam against best mate Joe to see who will win a series of funny, gungy and gross challenges and who will take on a forfeit from the Wheel Of Doom in this epic competition. Callum may be Little Bro, but he?s in control, so Adam and Joe need to impress him! Adam and Joe wake up to discover Callum has made their arms grow extra long overnight. How will they walk the dog, make brekky and ? most importantly ? style their trademark locks with really long limbs? Once Callum decides who?s taking the win, it?s onto the Biggest Splash Challenge. Who can plunge into gunge and create a splash that will impress Little Bro Callum so much he excuses them from the Wheel of Doom?s rank forfeit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p08b0fb7e9af46654217afa6d613eef93</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Warm temperatures wake up some hibernating dormice, and the Octonauts must protect them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f9fc506aadd9217d7128a831e93a53b</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When a meteorite splashes into the sea, Dad and Cosima cause problems by claiming it in the name of science, against the wishes of the sea creatures.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e6f70978ad1d72f2b5eca2f74a72900</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The baron's true love threatens to bring Danger Mouse to his knees.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfcaae47453a9f3c1541b759fb60634cb</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis gets into a fluffy mess when he runs into Von Screwtop's hadron collider with the professor's pet hamster, Galahad. To stop Dennis from completely changing into a hamster, the gang must sneak him into Wilbur's lab to use his reverse hadron collider and change him back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80dfb84ec4b3edb443b7d8d57691f72a</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle uses her excellent pocket beast card skills when on a quest to rescue the missing Council of Happiness from Grackle the Giant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c52df7e45b3a76f78f6ac5a5d573bb1</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Could farts power a rocket? If you ask a question like that to Dr Chris and Dr Xand, you know they will want to investigate ? and if they can, they will blast off an actual rocket too! We welcome Gladiator Dynamite to Team Ouch! Her job is to referee Dr Dan and Dr Raph as they pit their bodies against each other in Dan vs Raph: Body Battles. Today, it?s a muscle they are testing: the triceps. Will it be Dr Dan or Dr Raph who ends up in the ice bath as a loser?s forfeit? One thing is for sure, Dynamite?s decision is final! Doctors Chris, Xand and Ronx are Ouch and About giving answers to kids? medical questions, with Margot asking why people have asthma. In Australia, the Flying Doctors fly Jack and his mum to hospital in New South Wales for a check-up following Jack's bone marrow transplant. Back in the emergency department in the UK, Logan has hurt his knee after tripping and landing on a log, and Harshali has a pink bead stuck up her nose! Ouch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94a8d6fd6580fb7b64d941699a3b2c35</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko has gone missing, so Dot calls on a celebrity connection for help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42b9dc2a58d4c4bf9c7737c0bee2bb85</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a box filled with fortune cookies close to the Great Wall of China.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pba2796334e942468921c463b1c433065</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Animated series. A dragon-hunting expedition leads Ant to find an ancient scroll that holds clues to an amazing mystery. But his family are trapped by the dragon and only Ant and Jeffrey can save them! And Jeffrey's a fish.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p046066e525d9f961e471343dff55474b</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Rubi?s dance machine gets accidentally muddled up with Crusty the Robot Pie?s coding. Dennis and Gnasher have to dance on it all day in perfect sync, or Crusty?s entire persona will be wiped forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc196d03c4998053896105cc5f5c04bc8</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Danger agents go undercover disguised as a family to find out why the world?s villains are heading to one holiday camp, Sidneyland. When Baron Greenback shows up, the team are convinced he?s up to no good, but can?t find any evidence of wrongdoing. When Penfold enters Squawk and DM in a dance competition they discover the prize is the fabled Helmet of Power, an ultimate invention bent on destruction.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b5ce7408b56f7960eb3b2cde7d508f8</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A panicked factory owner asks the Ninjas for help to produce Xian Ye's action figure, but Konpeki's obsession with the soccer star makes it difficult to complete the task.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc2a8751c3ff7bce191db43b611b67043</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>While proudly testing his new doorbell camera, the Farmer realises he has locked himself out. Bitzer must help his boss get back into the farmhouse while simultaneously making sure he doesn?t spot Timmy and Shaun with a runaway kite.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1852ca2377930b34605a83021e353269</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy creates a new Yummy-based recipe: Choco-noodles.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa1a04431661ac2aeb668f346bbb87773</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy gets his dream job at the collectibles store, but when a family of screeching birds makes the store entrance their home, the customers stay away. It's Boy's job to move the birds, but Girl discovers they?re endangered and have to stay. If Boy can't get rid of the birds he'll be fired! But what's more important - his job or the birds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d56a7d28e8f920ef9622a88ac8f08de</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle is unhappy with how easy questing has become since Cral the Eagle joined the heroes, offending the eagle just when they need him the most.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ac8fa176bea27e14bcc365246b3ae79</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents celebrate an important milestone in their partnership.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd46cd88fb1d62102eb10a1553a7f2a21</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents try to determine what kind of creature will hatch from an egg.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p666d2606ef1cdfced44b7267472cdd42</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Bridgette gets the hiccups for the first time and tries desperately to get rid of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb93d6040b77fd2f1a2b5d7d46d15ace1</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug faces Ephemeral.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p87a8e11efb1bf3f77b72b0639f913ebe</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Encounters at the Crystal Pool lead to battles, new friends and discoveries about the past.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc2a45dc842a88d407ec72f3a10d1f00a</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Jo causes chaos when she tells Celeste?s mother that Celeste doesn?t want to return home. Meanwhile, Nancy, June and Felicity are excited to discover that Fred knows about the time capsule.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p149f709f8f1effdeb4864ef7580c7e41</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Tensions run high in A-troupe when Finn's mistake leads them to rework their routine hours before they are set to perform. Nick is forced to make a difficult decision that results in Piper paying for Finn?s mistake, which puts their relationship on shaky ground.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa3867ca29b3b243f4cf7d75f97e6686e</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>This time on Shark Bites, Steve Backshall meets the snappiest shark in our seas. The lemon shark scours the sandy seabed for food, but how does it get a good grip on hidden prey? Steve heads to the Bahamas in the Caribbean to dive with these feisty sharks. He heads down on his dive with a time slice rig to film the lemon shark's bite in three dimensions before heading into his shark lab to analyse it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p04dcbbb89007c2c46f0efdd0bd78d96e</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>An all-night gaming session turns the Farmer and Bitzer into sleep-deprived zombies the next day. Shaun takes the chance to change Bitzer?s checklist to suit himself, but he manages to miss the final item: shearing time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3f60727be2d84e2a3113f71146047e4</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The last thing DM would normally want to do is play a boring board game, but when one arrives in the post, it releases knockout gas and he's surprised to wake up in the town of Greenback. Jeopardy Mouse, Hazard Mouse and Danger Cash have also been snatched and are equally clueless why until a dragon attacks the group and a net drops from the sky at an opportune moment. Our guys realise they have been shrunk to chess-piece size by Ian the Danger Fan and are now pawns in his real-life board game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p89d3a3ac086dc94904568d6e0040f283</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Walter and Dennis go head to head in a sponsored silence. Being quiet doesn?t come naturally to either of them, as they struggle to make it through a chaotic school day and keep schtumm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f774701f77fb51f6357283a8b30f9ef</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>K-Jam and Girl have plans for the best day ever! However, when Cheese shoves herself in and takes over, she jeopardizes all of their plans.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea51e2ba2bb2d7cc4061772d9eb901bf</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdaae4e47abbdf082c5b760b7064f088c</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings catch a grasshopper that can give you whatever your heart desires.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e0fd7c58b3a252cdfc561d821057d41</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings use magic Chinese lanterns for sound and light shows.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc5e5b2b6e0498ea0f97679ba5f75b9a4</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9219a4ed6990cdd4d9ec30d5d0a40f34</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Whilst on a quest to return the Icicle of Destiny, Trevor topples into a cavern of tiny mushrooms who treat him like a king.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6587ed590db6ffbdbc38b906cd7ccb3a</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step Live - The Movie</title>
    <desc>In 2015, the cast of The Next Step began an eight-week, sold-out, coast-to-coast tour across Canada. For the fortunate fans who had tickets to those sold-out performances it was a chance to see their favourite dancers in person. But what would it be like to have the best seat in the house and a backstage pass.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a7be2cfa2b60931aea75cedee8e07c4</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Apollo prank Dynamite, turning her into a singing banana! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99a45e9399b5fa5991e3b3eb060bfd42</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Big Danny and Big Manny find science shocking, Da Vinci does a sound experiment, Newton rides again, Queen Vic shows off, and Dr Big Brain doesn?t see the attraction of electromagnets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8dd0beb4fb74ad45650014dd91335b55</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>In the medieval Ethiopian city of Harar, Steve Backshall has a unique and potentially lethal encounter with a pack of spotted hyenas. Capable of tearing their prey apart with super-strong jaws and thick muscular bodies, here they are hand-fed, allowing Steve the encounter of a lifetime with this normally unapproachable predator. Heading out of the town and up into the mountains, Steve meets the rarest wolf on earth and discovers why a grass-munching monkey, the gelada baboon, has a set of teeth that would make a vampire jealous.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ccc0f8bd2221f4b916e83c059ef6ad8</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Find out how fast your nerves work in a snotty experiment that sees Dr Xand blow a fuse, and the Cupboard of Everything is time travelling to a very smelly Victorian street.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p155f6685236c638b082ef5a70126b243</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>We meet Gavers, who has always had a tough battle against much bigger kids his own age, and four academy players watch the first team in action.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf231f55c7a2154610aff5d8541b2f372</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Predators</title>
    <desc>Steve gets chased down a mountain by a peregrine falcon and high-dives like a gannet off a cliff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e9a0bcc8dd8fc674a9469ad978a2ca6</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Footballing legend Chris Kamara is coming to the leisure centre to unveil a statue that has been made of him. All Mick has to do is make sure no-one sees it before he arrives and protect it at all costs. This should be an easy task, but with Danny close by and with a football in toe, nothing is as simple as it seems.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2abc192b35f3a247810fd29f11c216d</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Odd Sock Kaylim has a holiday headache - his family need to go on holiday, but their car is stuck. Andy and the Band?s plan to help is truly out of this world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13ad311e03b90fad3357ad6fa4c2bbca</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum is a Little Bro in control! He?s made a series of funny, gungy and gross challenges for his Big Bro Adam and best mate Joe to see who?s the best and who loses, having to take on a forfeit from the Wheel of Doom. When a slime baby shows up at their front door, Adam and Joe suddenly take on daddy duties. But how do you comfort a slime baby, teach it to speak or take it for a walk without spilling the slime? And once that?s over, Callum challenges them to become life-sized toys and hunt around their house for epic accessories. Who?ll race back to their toy box first, Adam or Joe? These daddy-os are about to find out in this head-to-head epic battle to determine who?s the CEO and who?s taking a spin on the Wheel of Doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf309fbf017e2b95f5612f22d43948e02</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts find some lost eggs in a nest off the coast and search for the mother.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a30845f680c10250d61a4a3675340bc</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad needs some training to pass his astronaut fitness test. Cosima and Big Lizard put him through his paces! When Rex gets into trouble, Dad?s hard work finally pays off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb80434f85462029178993348008abe14</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse makes short work of Burt Badboy and his newly acquired band of fanatical feline followers, the group's leader Mandy and her cult of cats immediately trade in their colourful mohican hairstyles for eyepatches and become Danger Mouse worshippers. At first Danger Mouse is having too much fun to take notice of Penfold's warnings about his new-found cult status, but even he is forced to act when the cats follow his example a little too literally and live life a little too dangerously. Danger Mouse's attempt to disown the cats goes down like a lead balloon, and they use mouse-fu skills and a superpowered amulet stolen from Tutenkamoo to show their idol the error of his ways. Danger Mouse battles the frenzied feline onslaught and saves HQ from becoming a giant scratching post. However, this only reaffirms the idea that he is the chosen one in the minds of Mandy and the cult of cats. Danger Mouse realises that the only solution is to find a new obsession for the cats.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cecc13bc26e14071dc1ed1bb687eebf</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis discovers that Ralf the janitor is the legendary Prankmaster General and is told he could become his successor. Walter won't let this happen and challenges him to a prank battle to win Ralf's book of pranking - the infamous Prankypedia.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fdd220cddb6e710107b2fa25d30a3c1</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Forest inspectors pay the forest a visit to check its super-happy status. Friendlyface sends the heroes on outlandish quests to guarantee results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf423a5126c7145dec4e840079fa076e4</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel and Shini are in Wales for a close-up encounter feeding crocodiles, they take some tiny turtles for a health check, and we show you how to make a wildlife-inspired pencil pot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p019a331ee6029e35e0d98e4784665965</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Officially a trainer, Dot teams up with Quaxly to help take back Liko?s stolen pendant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9bc5f0c03e7ee5f9277fd5d43ed70bb</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings love sesame nougat, but Grizzy also adores this treat and steals their box.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p64a57734b6a24b062d71ddbece2023c7</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Dark Orca pirates attack! They believe the Nektons have a rare treasure aboard their sub. To escape, Kaiko must guide the Aronnax through an erupting, undersea volcano! But can the sub survive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd520f862f6cabfeabbb19014b13d8dae</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A patch of wet cement, a boy and a dog itching to put their prints into it and a policeman determined not to let that happen. Can Dennis and Gnasher muddle Sergeant Slipper long enough before the cement sets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3cbcc2b42f737a35aae5268e19aff3be</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When a sudden urge to fly the Mark IV hits, Penfold leads a confused Danger Mouse to a farm, from which he claims to feel an unexplained magnetic pull. An entranced Penfold is met by a shadowy figure - Granny Penfold! Penfold recounts his childhood years on Granny?s farm, where he was trained in the ancient martial art of Farm Fu; a farming based martial art. Granny needs Penfold?s help to retrieve the sacred Fung Farm Book of Farm Fu, which has fallen into the hands of her enemies, causing farm animals to turn evil and rise up against their owners.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5bc9fb86a9c9d89de3a6896036c3a7d9</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When her superhero suit gets shrunk in the wash, Mega Hero Girl summons the Ninjas to find her a new one so that she can save a planet from an incoming asteroid.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p43b73bae7cd910ec88e39265c681b614</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The Farmer has taken up beekeeping and is loving all the honey produced by the hive. However, when he discards his protective suit, the swarm move in, bringing it to life! Soon, the ?Bee-Man? is bossing Bitzer around.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc354936294dc8908b721c1100ac957a3</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a temple dedicated to an ancestral brioche.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10643fca7fc86640614edef9f8a31551</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>A photographer is coming to take snaps of Girl's latest cosplay creation. She needs the others' help building it and agrees to do a series of favours for them in return. However, chaos breaks out when sneaky Girl starts secretly trading off these favours among the gang themselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf228ff0628556fe4a73703f510b527c0</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>An angry Swampclops follows the heroes back from their quest for a giant raspberry, so Hoofius must abandon his chances of winning the bake-off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3dcc908834fa89d31657019c7b692113</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents discover things are very different at Odd Squad at night.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ad839cbad7983f6045b82d4f1e49e23</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Coach O determines which agents get to visit the unicorns in Cloud Town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6b3eaa6706b91bbaeafb6f921efe4c4a</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan is determined to stop the musical duo Bananas &amp; Cheese from coming to the daycare.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd71f329b98ff41291c47ec44f0ca6020</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug teams up with a new ally to face Kuro Neko.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd7e0499bb764c15c8928a6ba2b526fb6</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Joined by Perrin, the Rising Volt Tacklers set out to find Kleavor on Tengu Mountain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d673cc286577b672f953048a7f66c0a</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Alicia and Darrell are trapped in the cellar after Alicia receives some bad news. Can finding the time capsule help them? Meanwhile, Irene feels pressured by her musical ambitions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p821f0a71198bd3e77b921a92fca3d471</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe preps for their dance, but an unexpected twist throws a massive wrench in their performance. As A-Troupe?s future rests on an unexpected dancer?s shoulders, a crisis of confidence threatens to sink the routine. Finn begs Piper to forgive him, but his apology falls on deaf ears, leaving Finn to hope that a grand gesture will earn Piper?s forgiveness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/padb8e2056fdea237ecf7616642f203e7</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Bitzer is horrified when the Farmer scribbles all over his map showing the location of his buried bone, fearing he will never rediscover his treasure. The flock are on hand to help him search, even if their methods are unorthodox.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde8c349f04c3c64ef16ec18f49455bce</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's addiction to challenges threatens the world. Quark tricks Danger Mouse into transporting a ticking time bomb back to Earth. This device threatens to turn the entire world into gold within hours. Quark's face print is the key to deactivating the bomb, and while dragging the extra-mouthed extraterrestrial across space wouldn't usually pose much of a problem to DM, Quark aims to see his plan through by exploiting his captor's recently diagnosed 'Compulsive Challenge Disorder'. With the HQ in sight and minutes to spare, DM's 'CCD' takes hold at the worst possible moment, and he abandons the mission in order to battle an army of bounty hunters. Can DM come to his senses and channel his affliction into saving his friends and stop the planet from turning into a huge gold bauble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a0eba2335e392bf6d0c015b6b6474e7</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang find out that JJ has a set of pre-match good luck rituals. In the run-up to an important Blamjitsu event, Walter deviously throws bad luck omens into JJ?s path, threatening her chances of success.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3c30a8458c845f0ca547fee6492f559c</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the siblings grow jealous of Boy and Girl going to school, Mouse offers to become their homeschool teacher. Too bad Dog, Cat and Cheese aren't exactly model students.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p39a58e7a11468918cb9bc3976121f470</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p93b72ba69f78b07158fba10bbacdbe2f</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings lay hands on an ancient console, and Grizzy is transported into the game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31177e19b22b7b6fd1c283788e89e3f8</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a mask that terrifies anyone who looks at it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1940c1b33ce8f0692bb0dbf611d37b6</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Agents Opal and Omar uncover the location of a legendary odd artifact.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb1a1fbc6396eb897cd452bcd1881ce6e</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface?s hat has been stolen by a Big Ole Worm, and the heroes must quest to get it back. As they trail the worm through the Prickly Desert, Trevor accidentally spikes himself all over on a cactus. But all is not lost ? now that he is covered in sharp spikes, Trevor realises that he has a unique superpower, and when the time comes to confront the Big Ole Worm, it?s Spiky Trevor to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d893098488de351f2861251077cc5bc</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad: The Movie</title>
    <desc>When a group of adults run Odd Squad out of business, the agents are forced to become regular kids again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p940d89c545bc8e46b3a2423109556bb4</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Forest inspectors pay the forest a visit to check its super-happy status. Friendlyface sends the heroes on outlandish quests to guarantee results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf423a5126c7145dec4e840079fa076e4</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Phantom prank Fire at a kids' birthday party! The rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3eb6afc7027c8bfed2f443d8a7e7d70e</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Mary Ploppins soothes those digestive ills, Dr Big Brain tries banana power, and Einstein reacts to Tim Peake. Fred Sirieix guest stars.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p817374987312a170e9ec24db4169edd8</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve is on his home turf, scouring land, sea and air for some of the deadliest critters that the UK has to offer. First, he heads for the seas off the coast of Plymouth in search of monsters from the deep. And he's not disappointed! In the bowels of a wreck he comes face to face with a giant conger eel, one of the most feared predators in the ocean. Back on land he meets a double deadly killer, the dragonfly. As adults they are amazing aerial assassins, but they lead a double life. Before they emerge as elegant winged beauties, the larvae are terrors of the underwater world, impaling their unsuspecting prey with their alien-like double-hinged jaws. Finally, with the aid of a giant vertical wind tunnel, Steve tries to hover like a kestrel, one of the prettiest but fiercest falcons.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1d02bab5172ffb5e99de911caf4ce278</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Dr Xand?s in a spin to show why dizziness occurs, the Flying Doctors help a baby in Australia, and Dr Raph takes an icy dip as he meets a Brilliant Body who swims in the Arctic.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfa8d6a2c88990591bbff4458ce36b12c</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>In this episode, the focus is on U13s goalie Keanu, who is in remission from leukaemia and back to his best. We also meet 14-year-old midfield dynamo Libby.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc51c937c7a46f3fc15cced1c4e773c36</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Predators</title>
    <desc>Steve meets a punching shrimp, the world?s heaviest eagle, and comes face to face with a wolf.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c12ada4bfab9e8a1185753c67f2b1b1</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Talented artist Satchel has been painting a big mural at Pottsfield which is ready to be unveiled and photographed by the local paper. However, Danny isn't happy with how he has been painted and decides to make a few 'small' changes that leave the mural unrecognisable, just as the photographer arrives.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe8cac76d7ffc3fe7eb897f71085c8b53</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Odd Sock Alana needs help with her disobedient French poodle, Monty. Andy and the Band try to train the pup, but their canine class is decidedly dog-eared.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p726f95a615984e09bec9ff3231108f40</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum's pitting his Big Bro Adam against best mate Joe in this hilarious competition made up of funny, gross and gungy challenges. Who'll take the win and who will take a spin on the Wheel of Doom? It?s all up to Callum so they?ll need to impress him! When Joe and Adam open their front doors to find a 20m high crane outside, they know Little Bro Callum?s up to something! He?s challenged them to an epic Big Drop contest? with mum?s vase and their own phones. Which precious items will survive the drop, and how can watermelon and a gunge pool protect them? Once that?s sorted, it?s onto building gigantic hats with everyday objects in a bid to avoid Callum?s forfeit Wheel of Doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1d2866a7b019052f7a902d701a630fde</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>A storm in Vietnam floods a cave, trapping Ryla, Kwazii, Shellington - and a tiger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc316ac2439c36f849fb58b31ea2e85e4</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When the buggy gets a flat tyre, Dad, Cosima and Big Lizard are stranded. Big Lizard?s playful nature helps reveal a creative solution to their problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa03aeaf60b6464ad7052d257c7def1d0</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold receive a crash course in the customs of America's oldest holiday when they cover for Jeopardy Mouse as she takes time off for Thanksgiving. After barely escaping from the war zone of a Black Friday sale, they find themselves back at Jeopardy's apartment. DM prepares to tuck into the plentiful Thanksgiving spread when Hissteria and Ham Hands rise out of the dishes. They announce their newly formed coalition and joint plans to vanquish America. DM sticks to his stand-in duties and refuses Jeopardy's help as he and Penfold follow Hissteria and Ham Hands' trail. They find the villainous pair hijacking the Thanksgiving Day parade - launching a gas attack from the air that will turn everything in sight to stuffing. With holiday-saving solutions at a premium, Penfold convinces a reluctant DM to call Jeopardy for help. Jeopardy assures DM that doing things with friends is what Thanksgiving is all about as they set about taking Ham Hands and Hissteria down. They distract them long enough to cut them loose along with the rest of the gas-filled balloons.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5362698311ba343ffe4571fba7fb7bc3</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Mayor Wilbur passes a law to increase healthy eating in Beanotown, replacing all foods with peas...of the mushy variety! The gang must avoid the people of Beanotown who are rapidly turning into Zompeas after eating the green mush. Dennis uses the only ordinary peas in town to sabotage Wilbur's mush-making factory and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41d58d1465e51eb4de1792f354b29a85</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes wake up on Snow Day morning, there isn?t a snowflake in sight! The heroes must quest to free the Snow Dragon and save Snow Day for all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70e545bcacb2d124e1fd8b0469e27b2a</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>To investigate why tummy rumbles are so loud when you?re hungry, the doctors call in the supersized stomach of Mega Xand! When Dr Chris and Dr Xand count down the Top 5 Bizarre-est Body Parts You Never Knew You Had, you will discover that the mysterious palmaris longus is so bizarre that you might not have it at all! The big question in Ouchology is whether it will be Dr Chris, Dr Xand or Dr Ronx who gets snotted by their kid quizmasters. If the doctors can put all the organs in the right place on their own bodies, they could win enough points to avoid the snot - but someone has to come last! Elsewhere, for Investigation Ouch!, Dr Chris finds out why real doctors are doing fake operations on fake organs inside fake patients in Nottingham. At the emergency department in Edinburgh, Alice has hurt her head and arm by accidentally running into a fence. And when Finlay arrives with burns on his forearms, the medics think it might have something to do with parsnips.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe8147477dc78b233d22fec7bfd20d4eb</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Fuecoco and Wattrel aren?t getting along, so Roy sets up some teamwork training.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p91959b198f9e9173c47496978c3efb96</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a mysterious stone, endowing them with the mastery of Shaolin Kung Fu.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe7690cdab092fb9368ec4408ae3dd01a</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Animated series. A new artificial intelligence running the sub stops the Nektons from saving a kayaker because it's too dangerous. When the Nektons try to shut her down, she takes over completely! Can Ant outwit AIMY and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p55e9ed8259c3111253b702e319a7bb8e</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Dennis thinks Gnasher has trashed a valuable piece of hideous art, the gang try desperately to cover up the damage and produce a decoy that is as convincingly terrible as the original.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4fc5d89880a983b655e137d80434250a</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Clip show. The Danger Agency realises that a lack of accounting has left them bankrupt. Whilst the bailiffs are in collecting goods from HQ the team decide to hold a telethon, asking people to phone in and donate to order their favourite clips to be played. Their target is a whopping ten million pounds! Can they reach their target in time? And what clip is DM trying to hide.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p85c2dc0931075bbc11c3f53b5253b881</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas bring superstar Jean Pascal to the aid of a princess who orders a talented musician to help in calming her difficult dragon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcf7f65ee4caa33a4d5430d34dd5b581b</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun steps in a can of red paint, and his resulting red hoof makes him a style icon on the farm. Before long, the rest of the flock try their own new looks and soon steal the limelight. As the outfits become more and more outrageous, Shaun wonders if less might sometimes be more.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5311608370a06605a09997e8b42e43c8</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>An AI accidentally connects to Grizzy?s stuffed teddy bear, which comes to life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde01d3fb2c717f9ad8f439d98c2db79a</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The annual town-wide Hide &amp; Seek contest is here! The family always hides together, but Girl points out that Boy stinks at hiding and is bound to make them lose. Nobody else minds, but Ace Hider Girl decides to go it alone, leaving her family at the mercy of the relentless seeker, Wanda! Will Girl realize the error of her ways and lead her family to victory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa62483ec1128c5362231112f093a148d</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When tasked with the simple quest of building a flat-packed wardrobe, the heroes fail to read the instructions and are whirled into a wonky world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb7deb542b557edde37b8d10af30afbd6</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When a virus that turns people into cakes spreads through headquarters, the agents try to contain the outbreak.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4a329d5a37f8993e68969187c33427d3</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents compete to win Agents of the Month.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p61bc6e6ceb89a982bef9ccf1d8d95e64</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>In order to earn her final Girl Campers badge, Courtney must win Gwen's friendship.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa5a28eb9c675a1197f3cf39c1f63fea2</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and her superheroes face Penalteam.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p60a263686440410e7668a161b78caeec</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko, Roy and Dot finally find Kleavor of the Six Heroes - and it wants to battle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p73e5b5f7499b291235e01e0a835bf146</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Home Sweet Rome</title>
    <desc>Lucy starts school in Rome, and her new pop star stepmum wants her to call her 'mum'.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a21fd9f65fa6df2e440c7c104cfce6f</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe faces stiff competition in a final performance but are left shocked when they discover a staggering revelation from a former teammate. TNS makes a decision about their final performance that alters their dance careers forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p183799364a06bb04831d86b4a3fdf4d4</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
