<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Dot struggles to accept Iono?s plan to livestream their upcoming Tera training battle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p014c9110d60c3bc1d1b56b7f8061a747</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>The Real Mutants assemble, people are drinking vomit and electrocuting themselves for science, and the earth and moon have an earworm about the solar system.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdad153ab81fb68e8962c09f25134220e</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle wants to win first prize at her school's sports day. However, she gets paired with Roland, who refuses to take part, and her magic accidentally makes him super strong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8594fcb13a3ba08d43e7d627d93cd4f</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>It?s time to get messy with Splatoon! Guided by pro-gamer Yammy, the teams face off in an ink-filled showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27987bbc67e39e72b95f53ed0527afce</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Max and Harvey host the Queasy Spa quiz, where the bros face some nauseating treatments! And can they pilot their own water jet packs in the Ultimate Memory Test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0c7b3f50db472fef03c655a2f172fd2</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>It's the Go Jetters as you've never seen them before as they take part in a disco-dazzling around the world gameshow! Foz and Xui are on Team Go Jetter and Grandmaster Glitch and Kyan are on Team Glitch as they go head to head to see who will win. Ubercorn and Lars are the quizmasters asking the questions in this ultimate geographic quiz.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e1ad3f96a0f0ee1325282cb82e5c7b8</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Rex is missing, but Dad, Cosima and Big Lizard need him to save them from a giant slug.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd05492cf93c8626bd0f248b5750c1ac2</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>After Shellington crashes the Gup-D, he and Kwazii team up with a moray eel and grouper fish to pick up the pieces.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41340382f293c134be10b4c47b8c0433</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>A sales rep visits. Despite Pancake?s doubts, he convinces the Piris to buy extra flippers. The penguins discover that their purchases are duds but find a clever new use for them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd938df44aed41395e3b7baced04b4f5d</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Evil Pea tricks Supertato and the Veggies, who fall into the deli counter and come face to face with the Turnip of Terror. They escape with help from the not-so-scary Turnip.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5b23548801878640fe9e039d4f88b171</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Jeopardy Mouse wins the Agent of the Month competition, Danger Mouse and Penfold are forced to travel to New York for a lesson and to take on the criminal organisation known as Hydrant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9bea4a009f4a743a746eef2582c505df</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Torn between practising Blamjitsu with the yeti and helping the Dinmakers write a new school song, JJ tries to combine the two by bringing the yeti along to band practice disguised as a very hairy roadie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p24c0df8168b5b4a7d7561917cb6a22bb</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang enter Pieface into a comedy contest to make him realise how brilliantly funny he is. Determined to win the crown, Walter uses the latest WilburCorp gadget on the unsuspecting audience to sway the vote.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p29814aa4fcf9e0c65fb33e57634a057d</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are relieved that the loud, threatening voice they can hear actually belongs to a small slug named Zorgoth, who is armed with a megaphone. However, when Zorgoth uses his Orb of Compression to shrink the heroes down to the size of ants, their relief evaporates. They must now embark on a long and dangerous quest, through their picnic items and beyond, to warn the Council before Zorgoth shrinks the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe50df153eaba594e89a65c54ae953f0c</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Keen to join a race with her classmates, a cavegirl orders a tame T-rex from the Ninjas. But they must work together with her teacher to train the unruly dinosaur.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd34d7bee5af1cf2dfe9ae7b94e254c8f</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Tee gets a taste of what life outside care might be like when she goes for her first college interview. But sparks fly between her and Carmen when neither of their days go according to plan.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p356f8c29dd68dd843d4083e84c1ca47d</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Alex Scott joins Rattus for a sport-themed special. Mary Queen of Scots goes grief-golfing, the H2 Freestylers take on a whole village, and sports-mad Henry VIII sings Get Sweaty.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c51af73f227c5f0d489a2caccb3374f</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Big Brain has a chemical catastrophe, Sir Isaac Newton rides a coaster again, with shocking results, Loofah is after a murderer, and Dr Henry VIII on call.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peee6d9a3675c97b17d21716f58b7d6ed</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Walter?s pampered cat Clawdia persuades her way into the gang, and only Gnasher can tell that she has a hidden agenda to oust him from Dennis?s life forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9693aec238af05d59c74a5ee6a6fbdaa</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold receive a crash course in the customs of America's oldest holiday when they cover for Jeopardy Mouse as she takes time off for Thanksgiving. After barely escaping from the war zone of a Black Friday sale, they find themselves back at Jeopardy's apartment. DM prepares to tuck into the plentiful Thanksgiving spread when Hissteria and Ham Hands rise out of the dishes. They announce their newly formed coalition and joint plans to vanquish America. DM sticks to his stand-in duties and refuses Jeopardy's help as he and Penfold follow Hissteria and Ham Hands' trail. They find the villainous pair hijacking the Thanksgiving Day parade - launching a gas attack from the air that will turn everything in sight to stuffing. With holiday-saving solutions at a premium, Penfold convinces a reluctant DM to call Jeopardy for help. Jeopardy assures DM that doing things with friends is what Thanksgiving is all about as they set about taking Ham Hands and Hissteria down. They distract them long enough to cut them loose along with the rest of the gas-filled balloons.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5362698311ba343ffe4571fba7fb7bc3</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A Perfumer asks the Ninjas to help him create a new and original scent for the Queen by finding the rarest flower in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf8aaecab844d9164013726aaa9448c22</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy decides to adopt a coconut.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa46da99ab8403e36a8d474b0b8fb95b6</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Lady Burlington's precious jewels are stolen, the kids believe that Cat was the unwitting thief and didn't know that she was stealing. They try to put things right by returning the valuables and teaching Cat the error of her ways. However, with Lady Burlington?s security guard searching for the burglar, the kids find their task way trickier than anticipated.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf59c8d2dec2daca258b148dd3d1f8a36</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Only wood elves have ever defeated the mighty Eye of Vernon hat, so when the Riddlemaster wears the eye to take over the forest, the heroes quest to Wood Elf Wood to get help. However, Twinkle really doesn?t want to, as wood elves are so stuck up! Struggling to contain her irritation with their high-and-mighty ways, Twinkle still manages to offend them, and the heroes wonder how they will ever save the forest now.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32df456943a31359aa3e76648f081c8f</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit is accidentally locked out of their van.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc5361551d360b5d5bb5a18f72d7c2b91</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit returns to the Museum of Natural Odd to battle a stone warrior.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p16753239ad5a1e4323bd66a480c2ddc0</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan tricks Beth into believing she broke his battery-powered bike.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa608c0317cbcbf41f823628dae40d0b4</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Truth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pab7f72eb688c7ddc39d4b020ba71096c</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Back on the Brave Olivine, Liko, Roy and Dot receive an unexpected challenge to battle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc610269f8f8b3a6cfce6acc923f40f3</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Dr Big Brain has an electrical short circuit, Marie Curie is wowed by a rocket man, some of the great women of science are celebrated, and 200 monks get electrocuted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21daa97d981587de14f8ff3ad8bddf40</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. Riley tries to make amends with her sister, but it doesn't go exactly as planned. Eldon struggles with the feelings he has for both Michelle and Emily.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03bb486c2a4c3e2c3e18364c14d663b5</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. Superhero Slippy Nana sort of saves a peach from a terrifying ordeal, Count Grape-ula strikes an unsuspecting victim, the maki and iso ambush a suspicious nigiri in a ninja sushi attack, deep in the back of the mouldy fridge, Frankfurter's monster comes to life, and the conjoined cherries attempt to start a band in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9748f75b43daf711134cae9dde0e143</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>30 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>While proudly testing his new doorbell camera, the Farmer realises he has locked himself out. Bitzer must help his boss get back into the farmhouse while simultaneously making sure he doesn?t spot Timmy and Shaun with a runaway kite.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1852ca2377930b34605a83021e353269</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When the Baron speeds up the rotation of Earth using windmills, Danger Mouse and Penfold age 300 years and must take on their nemesis as very, very, very old men.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b0704c5d4df92b6473d98abf4e56522</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Paul the Potato is love-struck by the poster girl potato advertising WilburCorp?s new line of super-posh chips. The gang stage a daring potato rescue in the WilburCorp factory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p509b952fbaf1e149740c52cc753d1901</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids are horrified to discover that their favourite spot, Paradise Grove, has been polluted by the Bobblehead Factory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6882b5b7d4db65749a3ea59239b8c602</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35c7f6db494c51224bfb0604e3a1a64c</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings are victims of inexplicable thefts.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6cb0a6d9bc2e4befe360258ebf89619e</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings use a frog with hypnotising powers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbd74eae5287515b461c9282bcc4d8e8</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Special agents from the Big O's office threaten to shut down Odd Squad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peac60c353b30408f095960017890b648</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Witch, who was trapped in a Merhaven clam shell while pinching a pearl, grants Blossom a single wish to thank her for releasing her and saving her life. Blossom excitedly chooses a mermaid?s tail to improve her swimming. However, when the Merqueen complains that her pearl is missing, and the heroes have to quest to get it back, Blossom soon realises how tricky a mermaid?s tail can become on land.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5de1c5363e6236bc3067ca23bed0355e</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Wallace &amp; Gromit: Vengeance Most Fowl</title>
    <desc>Wallace invents a 'smart gnome' that has a mind of its own - or does it? It falls to Gromit to take on the dastardly Feathers McGraw once more... or Wallace may never invent again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe6a84154d3eef931a54961a23d434a29</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:50AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Trevor is extremely proud of being the clever one in the gang and thinks that his smart mouth is his superpower. However, his friends feel that sometimes his jokes go too far - and they are right to be concerned! When Mr Friendlyface sends the heroes on a quest to prevent Toothgrinder the Ogre from messing up the village green, it?s Trevor?s smart mouth that puts all the heroes in danger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc10a55045431109408268b6cc99aaf5</image>
    <start>09:50AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Alix?s brother - aka Pharaoh.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1513e0d42073d47fd549ecf4f28bc05e</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Dot creates a plan for her Tera training aptitude test against Iono - but will it work.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p29d0f0fcb80808c46ffd306e4bb9cedd</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Rapping science teacher Matt Green becomes the first human being ever to visit Quark when he joins Pipette on her home planet to help host this special episode about Earth and space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc7de445b1ca12b41b36ae36d7c7a831a</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Swumpy sneaks into school, and Pickle accidentally makes him super clever so that she comes top in her test! This backfires when she has to represent the school in a maths competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9907bc19c58d6741f49861caa644601d</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Guided by pro-gamer Jelly, the teams gear up for an exhilarating race in Mario Kart. Who will master the art of power-ups and cross the finish line first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p57ace613b3eb966afb3655d0e166e3ba</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Adam and Joe are joined by their dogs to help them in the kitchen! What could go wrong? The fluffy sous chefs get to work on baking Callum?s dog Bailey a doggy treat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67c4553efcdb7e3501f85dfc88999f22</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>The Go Jetters have travelled to Horsetail Fall in the Yosemite National Park. It's a 300m-high waterfall made of melted snow. Once a year the setting sun lights up the water, making it glow like fire for just a few special minutes. This is called Firefall, and if there isn't enough water from the melting snow, Firefall doesn't happen. Unfortunately, Grandmaster Glitch has built a snow princess at the top of the fall and is using an ice machine to stop her melting. When the Go Jetters arrive to watch Firefall, they see that there is no water falling down! Can the team save snowy Princess Glorinda and Firefall.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p02e39eea712ef99a78393dc19ad9aab9</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When Dad's Lizard Translator malfunctions, Cosima is carried away by a giant beetle! Cosima and Big Lizard realise they don't need to speak the same language to be best friends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3cf532313614dbb34458c3f5f17ecaa</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>While diving down to the Midnight Zone, the Octonauts are attacked by bomber worms, and are enlisted to rescue an injured member of their troop.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8b8bbc6d7ad280ba6fb492602a88ac57</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>Nugget?s new fitness device sparks a craze on the berg. Running, skating and jumping, the Piris battle it out to score the most points, with a surprise winner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p90b12026134d5d01d6aca430bd974aed</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Supertato?s dancing is too powerful and destructive, but when he has to face Evil Pea in a dance-off to save his trapped friends, he soon realises his moves can save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd0834c26d34ce60bbc7a5b6b1145ef6d</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Penfold's addiction to social media helps the Baron turn all of Danger Mouse's secrets against him in a plot to deflate the planet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6f7ce120fee94baea61d80208ee3e590</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Walter?s pampered cat Clawdia persuades her way into the gang, and only Gnasher can tell that she has a hidden agenda to oust him from Dennis?s life forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9693aec238af05d59c74a5ee6a6fbdaa</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Doctor Pfooflepfeffer?s first act as head of governors is to turn Bash Street School into a boarding school. However, the pupils devise a series of daring attempts to escape.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfae0f6b0a2a73c82608043234539dd59</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes quest to stop Balthazar from turning forest folk into household objects, Herbert realises that he can defeat the wizard?s spell by using the magic tricks he has practiced. Blossom is particularly intrigued by Herbert the Peculiar?s tricks, not to mention his stage name, so when Herbert himself is transformed into a table lamp, it?s Blossom the Very Impressive to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p02b5755668bd5974ec3f672d77162daf</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A girl orders a beatboxing teacher after seeing a professional beatboxer in the park. However, the Ninjas must first figure out what beatboxing is.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a76925cb0e22cbb4f1bf4ee102b5b24</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Unsure of where she fits in, Sasha's glad when an old friend seems to show an interest in her. But does he really have her best interests at heart.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5f6336991ae7fec01c394769e2f5e4e</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>In honour of Father?s Day, Horrible Histories takes a look at some of history?s daftest dads, featuring Henry VIII, Charles Dickens, William the Conqueror and Joseph Stalin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p71d72dc6ad8c3988b11d1c2f66c426a2</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A special guide to working scientifically, whether that involves drinking black vomit, measuring people?s farts, or firing arrows into their bum.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p353c0c51ff7efe9e6d78587b0b2209b1</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis was up most of the night and can barely stay awake. Gnasher and the gang work hard to help steer dozing Dennis through the day, when all he wants to do is continue to dream about battling Zombie-Spiders.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0cde7e1c096f93579aa55afb03c8a28</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Professor Squawkencluck's seriousizer is nabbed by Pompom, the fun-and laughter-hating president of the clown planet of Bozoria.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb09fa38911603cbb359cbf590ed6e3e8</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When a genie gives the Ninjas three wishes in exchange for payment of his order, they each wish to swap roles. However, they quickly realise that they preferred it just the way it was.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p37b6fcf9d25e1e7b2cc1c7808b3750a4</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy pretends to have a twisted ankle so that the Lemmings have to take care of him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p778c943244c038dd40892ba970e83fd6</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids are asked to watch their neighbour's pet hamster and are given strict instructions not to let it out of its cage. However, Mouse doesn't believe any animal should live in a cage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p28f3c819160e656641eaee19a23624e6</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes have found the Wishing Trident, which will help them on their quest to prevent the summoning of the legendary two-headed dragon, Iceburn. The problem is, Blossom has used one wish by mistake, and Herbert has accidentally used a second one. Now the heroes are left to defeat the dragon using only one wish, a never-ending ice cream cone (with sprinkles) and a giant spicy sausage hat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf940465ee4740a280d4541c1e5c9723d</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Opal and Orla head to the Valley of Odd to solve as much oddness as possible.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa5fd055d6f3e1fc11ba7c2cfb2bfa352</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Darrell, Felicity and friends are back with more mysteries, pranks and adventures.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd10d69fa6c5aebe0862260126bb7cd8d</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel goes behind the scenes at Radio 1?s Big Weekend in Liverpool and meets some of the incredible acts performing. We catch up with the stars of Lilo and Stitch and find out how the dinos were created for the new series of Walking with Dinosaurs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p783dade0a08464af8a42e28b5d06bd43</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Marinette must travel through time to save the future.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pead05736541917f542e9fba818cb3879</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:15PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A weird and wonderful look at how gravity, magnetism and friction impact everything. With Fred Sirieix.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94fd45c10fe71cfd50c37b15a03b378a</image>
    <start>06:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:40PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>When Mansour loses Sara?s pet rabbit, Blink causes havoc with lookalike robot rabbits.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4188cceb795ded19b383d5f480c083d2</image>
    <start>06:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>Toast soldiers take to the skies in their toast-rack helicopter, Maki and Iso ambush a suspicious Nigiri in a ninja sushi attack, intrepid star bar attempts an ambitious trip to the moon, Frankfurter's monster comes to life in the back of the mouldy fridge and Stunt Tomato amazes the judges with a death-defying magic trick.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc4fa2dcdd91d3aae2ea1617ead3cc67</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Despite warnings, the sheep have gobbled up the birthday cake Bitzer has baked for the Farmer. Realising the kitchen cupboards are bare, Shaun and the flock must try and source ingredients for a new one from around the farm before Bitzer realises. The result is certainly a surprise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52cad13186b4964b457432c0b79519b7</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Only Danger Mouse can save the world from chaos when the Baron stops the world spinning with a plague of traffic lights.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb74677422bfaddaf06495faaf5c7c649</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Determined to prove he can accomplish a task without getting distracted, Dennis takes on the simple job of bringing the class register to the school office. He instantly distracts himself on an epic scale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb20653e5b67a5132f1ebf7148c402cbf</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids audition for a movie that's shooting in town, and a reluctant Cat lands the role as lead alien. However, Cat would rather just go to the circus.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p796b12621c8125783afd7d121c86b2d5</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8db81c6d44ee67c82d91fb097c7177bf</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When their dear friend and very first customer, Bonnie, orders a tent, the Ninjas travel down memory lane as they recount their first meeting and first ever delivery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p50fdbe3b6bccc0a45a6517dbaaf7bb5c</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents bring someone with an odd problem back to headquarters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03a2f1563cb1b025b7340bc27a3233c4</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Forest inspectors pay the forest a visit to check its super-happy status. Friendlyface sends the heroes on outlandish quests to guarantee results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf423a5126c7145dec4e840079fa076e4</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Glaciator again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p197ca86139737c989bdc2523a81096dc</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:55AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>The kwamis make a choice that will transform Paris.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa2a84e7c78f78346ee77adf4e2e53b73</image>
    <start>08:55AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: XY</title>
    <desc>As our heroes head to Coumarine City, they find two brothers with a lesson to learn.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p056bfbdd2589dec4c5aa30a8f9ebceb7</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Electro at a fake fashion photoshoot when her fabulous, precious dress is ruined. Meanwhile, the other Gladiators are up to mischief behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd1bbc15f7e13b3dc2f66637f66d3cf9d</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings turn into crab rescuers, but soon the house is full of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p20c34fe3859cc08a69a508d203bb7b27</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play pirates on a beached boat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6daa38c7457a858d5904930fb10cd1a</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Cheese accidentally begins writing her new fantasy novel inside Boy's diary, Boy is inspired to live out the life of the novel's great hero! By applying the story to his life, Boy is soon one of the cool kids, making Girl jealous. When she sees Cheese's novel-writing is the cause, Girl helps her write the next chapter to take Boy down a peg or two.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62fb1ea3b82ef516c198dd565a53c8b0</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the boys and girls get sick of having to share the bathroom, they split it into two! The girls' side becomes one big party with no rules, but on the boys' side Dog makes many rules! Boy and Mouse hate it, but they don't want to hurt Dog's feelings. Girl tries to lure them over to the girls' side with all the things they love to play with. Eventually Boy and Mouse sneak over to the girls' side to join in the fun - until Dog confronts them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ef23b470a33dca1bbcf9dae735dcd3c</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When the last page of the story-time book is lost, Gwen steps in to create the ending.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11fb197af7d8998c4056abf304e72828</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth shares her slime recipe with her friends, and together they create a goo monster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p456343ae47a574c8929254e0297f6774</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>It?s time to go undercover and discover who makes the best spy. Laser mazes, gadgets and creative camouflage - only one spy will take the win.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcb96a4a004f310e8e63c7f291a09ebd9</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy is determined to make the Odd Socks into ?proper? teachers, but the band?s unique methods lead to chaos. Can they turn it around before the school day ends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8112d8a5b097c024da3a23604243c06c</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel goes behind the scenes at Radio 1?s Big Weekend in Liverpool and meets some of the incredible acts performing. We catch up with the stars of Lilo and Stitch and find out how the dinos were created for the new series of Walking with Dinosaurs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p783dade0a08464af8a42e28b5d06bd43</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Odd Squad UK is celebrating its jubilee, but the party can?t get started until Orli locates the missing Ozzi, who has a bad case of the Saturdays.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0cc0452f982d60aa0d1416a766bc13f0</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Ozzie is torn between helping his replacement, Opie, on her first day manning the Odd Squad Department of Help desk, and an important mission with Orli and Onom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f5d4ee2f0a077b41ef6c23d2798bc0d</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>There?s a brand new slide at school, and Pickle really wants to try it out. However, things get complicated when Pickle's mood magic causes Mia and Mr Ludcomb?s hair to grow uncontrollably.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fdd46f4b3717baf8071605b9e07bf96</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle wants to become school ambassador. When she accidentally clones herself, she thinks the second Pickle will help her win the day. Unfortunately, they soon fall out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21c352b54ad359875557e19af629a4b8</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>There is public confusion when King Charles II bans coffee shops, a seasick chicken ruins a Roman sea battle, mighty Egyptian pharaoh Ramesses II meets some smelly peasants on Historical Wife Swap and a cave-dwelling Stone Age couple try to buy their first house.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcc63a02b5e86d609f850abb3006bb2e9</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Mary Ploppins soothes those digestive ills, Dr Big Brain tries banana power, and Einstein reacts to Tim Peake. Fred Sirieix guest stars.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p817374987312a170e9ec24db4169edd8</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>Aoife is determined to get the Vipers a new kit - will her crazy fundraising plans work out well or horribly backfire.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6b1fe250b3bddf5df95cc448aa9b7a95</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Andrew feels out of his depth in the unforgiving environment of the academy. Can he rise above Alex?s taunts and find a way to turn his fortunes around.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41a9cb5e5a01253a1d48ff80911e6bc6</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef tries to trick the kids into making his mother gifts after he forgets Mother's Day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb83be820d725d3dca24249aa7e59fa8</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Harold is determined to keep everyone safe on the class camping trip by catching Bigfoot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p941d3fc9842083f030dbb05ab461f301</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>The class camping trip turns into a treasure hunt, while Harold looks to trap a Bigfoot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4317ddecad9de25b04544978ce824b51</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Jeopardy Mouse wins the Agent of the Month competition, Danger Mouse and Penfold are forced to travel to New York for a lesson and to take on the criminal organisation known as Hydrant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9bea4a009f4a743a746eef2582c505df</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Penfold's addiction to social media helps the Baron turn all of Danger Mouse's secrets against him in a plot to deflate the planet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6f7ce120fee94baea61d80208ee3e590</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse has to face his only fear when Penfold accidentally awakens a gigantic World Wide Spider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfdab1c9194bfa295bffcbe93ab6fe774</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Suddenly feeling too old to be collecting toys, Boy gives up his bobbleheads and decides to do the things that grown-ups do instead. The others desperately try to turn Boy back into his slightly more interesting self by taking him to meet the owner of the world's biggest collection of bobble heads, where Boy must choose between what he thinks is cool and what he loves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p53eae7f2ec93d84dbfefaf2b4a97f238</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse is tested on his experiment to create the perfect family and is sure he will fail! However, his siblings convince him to hire actors to play perfect versions of themselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p74d538ded050c20a33665d7e2f080fec</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When one of Mouse?s inventions accidentally sticks Cat?s discarded fur to Boy?s face, his new 'beard' suddenly makes him the most popular kid in school! Seeing her chance to stop her enemy Lila Bird from becoming class president, Girl convinces Boy to run for president too. It looks like Boy might win, until another accident causes Cat?s whole body to get stuck to his face. Can he win the election with such a strange new beard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p914a4dbe62695432e7ae7da249569069</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>It's time for the racket game, where big scores mean big prizes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb4876fa452c0f93c5471f450963b20c9</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings organised a mega-party, leading to the cabin being invaded by bats.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p017dac7b4c386b657d1c3d9999e8170c</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings activate the air conditioner's AI, causing it to fall in love with the fridge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42dd0368414c1fcd0af910a94e7b785f</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes set out on a quest to find out who is draining colour from the forest and muster all their positivity to save it from greyness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3d4f995b8c3040f9e2b17fe57dfa29f</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Forest inspectors pay the forest a visit to check its super-happy status. Friendlyface sends the heroes on outlandish quests to guarantee results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf423a5126c7145dec4e840079fa076e4</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Much to Trevor?s irritation, a rare phoenix woodpecker takes a liking to him - so he demands an immediate quest to return the bird to its real home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd460f05ee8f6efe98ada93b746aa74d</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Mansour traps Blink, but chaos erupts on Mars when alien patterns appear on the planet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p04244a9d89c09b8964ce12222136caed</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:05PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Tarek runs for class president, and Blink backs him to spoil Mansour?s chances of winning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef670360698c46a4f8648058a8a7fd1a</image>
    <start>06:05PM</start>
    <finish>06:20PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>Chris welcomes 16 new campers back to the original island and divides them into two teams who will face off in a blindfolded challenge that?s sure to cause pain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2ad36220f0bad5a9618d7b21aba47371</image>
    <start>06:20PM</start>
    <finish>06:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Electro at a fake fashion photoshoot when her fabulous, precious dress is ruined. Meanwhile, the other Gladiators are up to mischief behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd1bbc15f7e13b3dc2f66637f66d3cf9d</image>
    <start>06:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>01 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
