<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: Gift of the Night Fury</title>
    <desc>Festive animated short featuring characters from How to Train Your Dragon. Hiccup and his friends are preparing for Snoggletog, the Viking equivalent of Christmas, when all of the dragons suddenly fly away and leave Berk. All, that is, except for Toothless, who cannot fly unaided. Hiccup has a solution for Toothless, but will the dragons return to Berk? Featuring the voices of Jay Baruchel, Gerard Butler and America Ferrera.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1a50b1b524f797da08ef2e7f67ef9476</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A weird and wonderful look at how gravity, magnetism and friction impact everything. With Fred Sirieix.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94fd45c10fe71cfd50c37b15a03b378a</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. Michelle decides to change the line positions, but Emily and Stephanie are not happy about it. Emily confesses a secret to Eldon that brings them a little closer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa22439632e1e3aa19a89d4961d676dbb</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The thrill-seeking eggs take up bungee jumping, the potato racers whizz around, and Mr Strawberry serenades Mrs Strawberry. Fearless Pete Parsnip comes face to face with a terrifying hairy spider, and Slippery Nana comes a cropper impressing the judges in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9af765987c32160992a5512af85bce81</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
