<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis can?t get Grizzly?s new animal training method to work on a wilful Gnasher. However, when they realise that Gnasher can use the method to get humans to obey him instead, they exploit this new power to the max.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p965cb1910091f1f086e689ad9c5309e4</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse must fight his own urge to be awesome to stop the world turning into a gigantic intergalactic tourist attraction. Attempting to prove his theory that what the world always needs is a hero, Danger Mouse fights off what appears to be an alien invasion of Earth - but his inflated ego soon becomes the real intergalactic threat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d43d2ca6490ff7c844b2a28644f5408</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A trainee witch asks the Ninjas to find her a cat so she can pass her magic exam. However, getting the easily frightened kitten to participate proves to be a challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4057a11885fce1ebd8e72996ee149c8e</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. On a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. But Shaun's insatiable curiosity often leads him into the unlikeliest adventures. When the Farmer takes Timmy's favourite sheep dolly, the little lamb won't stop crying. So Shaun rallies the flock to get it back from Pidsley, the farm cat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p980c4dc12b84d9a7a61ee4e79fbaa5f1</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings are fighting over a crown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38da76867021476c0c21a33b4ec809f9</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Girl hears that Lila secretly thinks she is great and tries to get her to admit it. But how far does she have to go for Lila to declare Girl?s greatness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd3c2f9785ccbb5395bfd668c471bc2a</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The tired heroes must quest to find out and stop whatever is making the loud wailing noise that has kept the residents of the forest up all night.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe737598843036feb34240aa725c51adc</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When Ms O leaves to conduct a super-secret mission, the agents compete to figure out who is in charge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p869126efa5973de5da9e29546dc380d7</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Otis and Olympia are stuck with a new robot partner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf79ba2a92eacf194943621245c0db54</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan and Leshawna try to take advantage of Izzy's love for the game of Simon Says.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6aaf405756a724290c20cdc97d40c5e9</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>The kwamis? choice is transforming Paris.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67bc963b830482a39833a67eae184781</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>The Rising Volt Tacklers and the Explorers battle over the fate of Laqua.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5cb0995236fa925e4cab08fc13f2b545</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>It?s time to go head-to-head in Super Smash Bros! Guided by pro gamer Slogo, the teams face off in an epic showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p467af63634bc9b5fbc3b0e35787e6d64</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Jett tries to find her place in A-Troupe but is feeling left out. Ethan reminisces about his time in Paris, while Adele looks to a new opportunity abroad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pff1e14bffa83ddee79bbc84502624ffd</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>This time on Shark Bites, Steve Backshall meets the snappiest shark in our seas. The lemon shark scours the sandy seabed for food, but how does it get a good grip on hidden prey? Steve heads to the Bahamas in the Caribbean to dive with these feisty sharks. He heads down on his dive with a time slice rig to film the lemon shark's bite in three dimensions before heading into his shark lab to analyse it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p04dcbbb89007c2c46f0efdd0bd78d96e</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>31 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The flock try to see off a pair of fly-tippers who have been filling the pond with rubbish.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5b0813a1af94649b88ef237ea77ea0b1</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's over-reliance on gadgets prompts Colonel K to send his top agent on a tech-free nature retreat. Unbeknownst to Danger Mouse, Greenback has the same plans for his daughter, Delilah, whose social media obsession has also spiralled out of control. Back at HQ Penfold is tasked with protecting the entire world from the threat of super-villainy. Stripped off his gadgets, DM struggles to adapt to life in the wilderness and, when a talking pine cone called Conni begins to offer him survival tips, he begins to question his own sanity. Soon enough, Delilah catches wind of DM's presence and she plots to destroy him as a means of getting back into her Dad's good books.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p75c10893273f4622c94d4cf5fb696d17</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Fed up with Dennis pulling the wool over Mrs Creecher's eyes, Walter orchestrates a robot to take over Class 3C - with disastrous results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p09cd14a7c66d70b97a06114b327de9ed</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The Girls and the Boys compete to get to the top of Bear Mountain, using very different styles of camping. But when the legendary bear appears, they have to team up to survive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb67492964d5542c23a8c00dc0f1fb470</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea45382aabc09d74e0c04015c9c9437f</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings get into super-fast snowmobiles and launch into a race.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2c13dfaf56c97e2cf1d0f61b1bb4812</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings and Grizzy clash over a choco granita recipe.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6446e0ff6f4768dcfa1bea1d272638b9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Omar finds himself stuck in a mysterious void.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8640329be2a7868dd1655f1f2f21a601</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Watch the mud (and food) fly as sheep take on pigs in the fight to end all fights.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p58526dc6683d56458587390dfeba0dbc</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Helsing tasks the gang with finding a magical genie lamp, thinking that they won't give it a polish. Now, Charlie is famous, Pierce is a CEO and Que has legs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p91ee48925752b847214b40962f3ce830</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>The winning teams return to the arena to take on Mario Kart in the Grand Final. Who will win the competition and claim the Game on Grandparents trophy and GOAT title.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc965b4b97374457007445f0dd4a65bf1</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Pete tries to juggle both the Brawl and regionals, but it may be too much. Ethan discovers a huge secret within A-Troupe, and Olive is suspicious of Ariana and Grace?s friendship.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1b7576d62429f4032216d555f0bfb517</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts embark on the biggest adventure ever! The crew is caught off guard by a volcanic eruption in the Pacific, but this single emergency soon turns into a global disaster when eruptions are triggered all across the Ring of Fire ? a chain of hundreds of land and undersea volcanoes encircling the Pacific Ocean. As the Octonauts scramble to rise to the challenge of their multipronged rescue mission, Tweak has one last trick up her sleeve: the Gup-Z ? a giant, untested new mecha Gup that will take the whole crew to operate.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p968ddc3ab074bbb0dc7e211eb77c2b5c</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings turn into crab rescuers, but soon the house is full of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p20c34fe3859cc08a69a508d203bb7b27</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Bionic ends up dressed as a rabbit when Nitro pranks him at a fake photoshoot, and the rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes as they prank the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf7d7f9299d05e5c92784905daf4991d</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle enters the local dog show with her pet, Swumpy the warthoffle. When Roland cheats, Pickle?s magic makes Mr Ludcomb behave like a dog. In the chaos, someone steals the trophy..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p79a65fbb9344caa706f0c5d89982e20b</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Jo causes chaos when she tells Celeste?s mother that Celeste doesn?t want to return home. Meanwhile, Nancy, June and Felicity are excited to discover that Fred knows about the time capsule.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p149f709f8f1effdeb4864ef7580c7e41</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Coach Byrne?s controversial new tactics throw the team into disarray, rousing Bobby's suspicions. Is he really trying to improve them, or is there something more sinister going on.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2e9a87fa2fbe261ba573ac3798d71a29</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>Steve is going large as he focuses on the biggest animals to have ever walked the earth. In his dino den, he starts by meeting the Argentinosaurus - an animal so large that even its poo was deadly! But if you thought that was the biggest ever dinosaur, then think again. With stunning graphics and epic stunts, featuring a piano smash, a fire hose hose-down and the most powerful heart in the animal kingdom, Steve crowns his king of all beasts.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc4d8bb991c22c2b0112aebfdd2156fb5</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Rio has lost his air guitar and his confidence. The band travel through space to take him home to Planet Rock to see the Godfather of Rock, who will help him get them back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a24d8d454ad4b5f337d26d47e518be1</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Adam and Joe become busy bees for a gunge-fuelled challenge ? who will collect the most nectar and win Callum?s ultimate respect.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1bcc08b0a5bc2e62651b6a15b1544e1a</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Paani seeks refuge in a grouse's burrow during a snowstorm but then gets trapped.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf3a9f367597927d1585a29f64e161314</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Big Lizard isn't happy in his skin! Cosima tries everything to stop him scratching until she realises that's exactly what he needs to do. He's shedding his skin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc6c6abf47d547f20cf001458e36522a7</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Penfold takes a trip inside Danger Mouse's body to save him from a deadly aversion to his own heroism.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ce6cb7f273c50dec13b586f423e47c3</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It's the famous Beanotown Freewheeler Derby! During practice, the gang realize Walter's go-kart is especially speedy. Worried that Walter will beat his record, Dennis creates a lighter, faster kart but loses control and injures himself. It is up to Rubi's wheelchair know-how and Dennis' super-speedy karting skills to win the race.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc06c659e58bbb60506adaf46f42db5f7</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Gnome Crystal Mine has ground to a halt, leaving the forest with no crystals, no power supply and melting ice lollies! The heroes are tasked with a quest to find out what has happened and to fix it. It turns out that a slimy beast named Smarg has made the mine her home. But with Hoofius?s fear of gunk getting the better of him, evicting the slippery Smarg is not going to be easy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p858de20cb9333a64f647c54c77975ddd</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>The world is not always built for kids like 13-year-old Eleanor - who has a visual impairment - but she wants to change that. Follow her trailblazing challenge to audio describe a live show at the National Theatre ? usually done by sighted people. While juggling her own journey to gain independence, Eleanor must prove to herself and her parents that she is ready to take her next big steps.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c71f370ef9bb5166d740331b73f6fd5</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>A visit to the Wild Area turns into a curry-making adventure for the Rising Volt Tacklers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc3ee687857fc44c3ca640d412d19f8eb</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Proteus, leader of the mysterious Guardians, traps the Aronnax in a magnetic field and kidnaps Ant, believing he is the key to finding Lemuria. Ant thinks Proteus is crazy. He tries to escape to save his family.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf161682262b2ca69586146afeb04a158</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis is mega-excited to trial a pair of hi-tech Smarty Pants - underpants with all the capabilities of a smartphone. However, whenever he and the gang test the pants, Walter is always one step ahead of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa4f51a6964d88c18d4f4da9b7679e7c5</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. When the Baron rearranges the countries of the world, Danger Mouse reluctantly joins forces with his American counterpart Jeopardy Mouse and takes New Zealand for a spin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p360a767bfafedebd93220d5ac0d52736</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>While fulfilling customer orders, the Ninjas realise that a spy has been following them to help a copycat Ninja delivery service steal their business.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfa1f6025e5cc54d907f1d54131f3c3d8</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Animation about the adventures of Shaun the Sheep. Shaun's attempts to get his hands on some apples from a tree overhanging the naughty pigs' yard cause trouble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p00ac34d3b58ad11095e49aa35082a70e</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>After touching a mysterious tooth, a lemming turns into a were-lemming.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa5eb91ad6825bc4f46c8da62199c9e14</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids start upcycling broken items for people in town. However, things go wrong when Cheese focuses on making things look cool rather than fixing them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p312e51f7f0e662ce5893155a54dc2dd3</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes are faced with the Goblin King moving into the Big Birch, they decide to invent a quest that will soon have him running back home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9987df26df4a4713222e9b576a9111f2</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Agents compete against rival Odd Squad agents to solve an odd problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e0f6430aadd878214936f5dfa5c7be5</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Otis and Olympia investigate why people in town are stuck in slow motion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcea725021fcaffbb3d36283dd3eda6a0</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Chef tries to trick the kids into making his mother gifts after he forgets Mother's Day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb83be820d725d3dca24249aa7e59fa8</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face an elusive villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde8c939cb2856a527ae4925122886276</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>After 100 years, the secrets of Laqua finally come to light.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0360f783a139b692684e52faf1554e8</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>It?s time for Samba de Amigo! Two teams, guided by pro gamer Jelly, dance their way to victory. Which team will make it through.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd396aad57d1fcef8daf0cf8248e0f686</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>As Adele says goodbye to The Next Step, she tries to mend fences with Olive. Things get complicated between Heath and Pascale as Anthony deals with Adele leaving.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12094601243ee9d32365dcaf717213be</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall meets a shark that is a master of teamwork - the blacktip shark. The blacktip isn't the largest shark in its territory, so it adopts a sensible solution to survive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fa985555bdb05d543b4994edb96b627</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>01 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Can Bitzer and Shaun ensure that the regular dance competition is run fairly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p53b5d63a64ac2ffbb47c2e68a7be3d1a</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Snowman is hired as Danger Mouse's new sidekick, leaving Penfold without a job.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb9a8b62eb1f051a7a86e10437f9214c</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A bungled attempt at a stunt leads to Dennis accidentally becoming an internet star and Beanotown celebrity! But his moment of fame is short and Dennis is soon replaced by Walter's cat, who can play the piano. Dennis has to stage the best stunt yet to gain back his audience.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2448826bf08a8b69aefa3652e97decf5</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Girl enters a cosplay costume contest to win a trophy and meet her favourite TV star, but needs somebody to wear the back end of her enormous costume. Boy is horrified at dressing as the character?s bum, but he doesn't want to let his sister down. Can he put aside his embarrassment to help Girl win the competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p39a709d325b91d9a6c575a2c63275204</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1568e51e62cb059402d58560eef577c8</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy discovers a special lamp that can compact organic elements.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a53737e98d0f3674c4501f7700dd884</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The extraordinary animals from a tablet game come to life after the device explodes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3a27aae2aea7f6befb2d2839f29139f</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Omar catches a case of Clown-i-tosis.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2283ada004226e79a3bce16222be74e8</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Buckle up for a turbocharged, F1-style road race with Bitzer! Who will make it to pole position.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6729e7e7bf9fa8e5983973ed96f4ea38</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>The gang find Helsing's monster phone book and prank call Frank, the world?s scariest monster. The gang must prepare the house when a furious Frank seeks his revenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf82a4655b1e582d10ff2733ea238236</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Top Minecraft and Mario Kart tips to help you turn your grandparent into a gaming legend. Plus Jelly, Yammy and Slogo face off in the ultimate Minecraft build showdown! Who will be crowned the Pro Gamer Champion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pefa6da1af07a4d5e59f2a20d30b7e1d1</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>As the regionals qualifier clashes with the Brawl?s, A-Troupe struggle under the weight of all the secrets they have kept from each other.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe113b7e440701120dd4668cb899cf7d1</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: Sun and Moon</title>
    <desc>Danger looms in Fula City, and Ash, Pikachu and their new friends fight to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13ac5aeb187a72a1754a4ce305f83080</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>The Hairy Egg is ready to hatch and Pickle is keeping it safe. There is widespread panic when it disappears and Pickle's parents forget who they are. Time is running out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd96d374a3fba1543af24430fa482c95</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Alicia and Darrell are trapped in the cellar after Alicia receives some bad news. Can finding the time capsule help them? Meanwhile, Irene feels pressured by her musical ambitions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p821f0a71198bd3e77b921a92fca3d471</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>As the players embrace their new positions, Christina helps Andrew train to be a striker. However, an anonymous message leaves her facing an impossible decision.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1444817816479a2ec3ae0de4e77894e9</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Dinosaurs with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>The Jurassic was home to the most vicious and violent predators the world has ever seen. To survive, herbivores had to fight back. Steve Backshall goes on a mission to track down the deadliest of all dinosaur defenders. He meets the armoured tank that is Nodosaurus, tests whether an Iguanodon really has what it takes to beat a T rex and thanks to some mega-engineering, unleashes an Ankylosaurus tail-swinging robot that goes on the rampage and then some.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa74001bc6d9ed961b4966d78cb139ae4</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Whiff says he needs help so Mac invents Robo Whiff ? a super efficient robot roadie. Things soon start to go wrong, however, as Whiff?s pushy robotic twin starts to take over the band.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa36b9e262eca9bf4e78ff33c7cbae2ea</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum inflicts terror and temptation on Adam and Joe to see who can impress him the most and be the 'last to leave the circle'.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2e94d65ceb7459c6e25e6e58c77d47f9</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>When a herd of elephants is trapped in a cave, the Octonauts have to get them out quickly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5967b9ccf4a487d20b60ec323ae9e33f</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad gets a severe case of Proximan hiccups. Big Lizard and Cosima do their best to help, but their attempt to scare Dad goes wrong when a real 'monster' turns up.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ddd5626eeb3a49f1e8f652d03cfb731</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The danger agents are at Squawk's super-secret Wild West testing facility, home to a society of Penbots, robots who have a rather familiar face. Squawk is sure she has improved upon Penfold and made the perfect robotic sidekick for Danger Mouse, Tenfold. But Tenfold malfunctions and transforms into the ruthless Meanfold, determined to destroy anyone who is not quite perfect.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe9b5368e847ec4ab98ee821a340abf34</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>There's a werewolf-type creature on the prowl and suspicion falls on Gnasher. Dennis has to prove his best pal's innocence as the full moon shines down on Beanotown..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7bd095aa830e7aad546c21dc4103e322</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is acting very strangely indeed. He refuses to stamp any of Admin Bunny?s documents, keeps getting distracted by butterflies, and seems oddly happy! The heroes are extremely suspicious and decide that someone must have swapped him with a doppelganger. Now they must quest to find out where the real Friendlyface is and get him back before the forest descends into total chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde2e0b6ed02cd81a52a1b5ae1f9bd3e8</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>BSL campaigner Daniel Jillings is on a mission to get the whole world signing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38ec132c061cdbe2988ed862f3c9d580</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>When Roy?s Ancient Pok? Ball is stolen, the Rising Volt Tacklers track down the thief.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3864166ebfef7253126247bfd45d4887</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Devil Daniels, Monster Hunter thinks he's hunting a siren - a mythical creature whose song lures sailors to their doom. The Nektons discover it's actually a rare whale with a unique voice and race to save it from destruction.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe7e7537110283e7f51a0d040d5f9b3a7</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>There?s a new tripe hound in Beanotown, and Gnasher falls head over paws in love with her. Bertie is looking after the visiting dog, Ginger, and is determined to keep her away from riff-raff like Gnasher.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c6935906c9fad8f02b717eec4e4caaa</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When an old enemy returns, Colonel K must come out of retirement to save the world from an outbreak of rudeness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2e371392bd76d59ab61f378473f577e</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Desperate for peace and quiet, an alien leader orders an entertainer to take care of his planet's creatures. However, things nearly go wrong when Konpeki brings a giant cake.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5456763dfebacd2f3cd1490329ffc3f2</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. The farmer takes up oil painting and is determined to paint a masterpiece. However, when his back is turned, Shaun and the flock decide to have a go.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc89d02e974c9b5e67593bb2e1caa4026</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy uses a hen to protect some Yummy jars from the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa5b246dbc4d33b694533bc526f36adb0</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Gramps gets an offer to leave town for a whole year to go on an adventurous trek, but the kids would miss him and try to convince him to stay.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5134396fb773f24cd21838f62de9d1cd</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>While questing to keep her hero safe on her long journey, superfan Blossom fusses and frets too much, making things awkward.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe6ab2dbb5103b7a559efd71238dac7b</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Odd Squad and Villains work together to stop a giant robot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ecb8fd587aedc874bc91e06bf8e589a</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents accidentally lose someone in headquarters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pffe16f8607e9b7c534d70c45b0848532</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Harold is determined to keep everyone safe on the class camping trip by catching Bigfoot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p941d3fc9842083f030dbb05ab461f301</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Gold Record.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6bb881e9b26f09372f21fa4936589205</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko and friends show their strength in a battle against Gibeon and the White Zygarde.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa2fabd223c5b2eca9263dd72bfe5b5f4</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>It?s colour and mayhem as pro gamer Yammy guides the teams through Fall Guys. But who will prevail in these chaotic battles.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pad97a9358569518c0c0dd366f313b299</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>An overprotective Heath accuses Grace of sabotage, while Grace and Jonah make a bet to make it on to A-Troupe. Meanwhile, Izzy grapples with keeping Anthony?s secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p98b58fbdb69531c7dbfb68abe1998543</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Gladiators? stars Apollo and Electro surprise children in a Salford school when they lead a PE lesson with a difference.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd9807d54b258071ad8fa7ee08110d3f1</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>02 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
