<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>4 O'Clock Club</title>
    <desc>Bell's staff training session is ruined by Chester's disastrous fire safety inspection. Meanwhile, Owen and Evan sneak into school to avert a disaster of their own.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1102411937b3ce4af286187460aad743</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Danny and Mick are waiting in reception for a package to be delivered. While they wait, they reminisce about the hilarious things they have been through together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p46a3512a1ae3c201f64bd175fa11669d</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It?s Danny and Mick?s first day at the new leisure centre, and they are surprised to be greeted by their old boss Joy. She wastes no time in making sure they stay out of trouble by getting them to dust the sports hall ceiling. How can such a simple task go so wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6187a5321578c00a0603c2ff008d8789</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Max and Harvey host the Queasy Spa quiz, where the bros face some nauseating treatments! And can they pilot their own water jet packs in the Ultimate Memory Test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0c7b3f50db472fef03c655a2f172fd2</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>Looking to help protect the planet, Cam, Tyler and Aaron take inspiration from the zoo?s animal eco-heroes, including pygmy marmosets, Amur tigers and orangutans.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe74b7e32ca68358013cf2fa1dead5e7b</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Naturalist Steve Backshall heads to the Bahamas in order to get up close and personal with a whole bunch of sharks. There are plenty of shark species to choose from and Steve has his work cut out deciding which ones are worthy of a place on his Deadly 60 list. Hooking up with shark scientists helps him decide and gives him an opportunity to release some baby sharks into the wild, and he learns how to hypnotise them with his bare hands. Getting mobbed by hungry reef sharks and swimming with a four-metre tiger shark are all in a day's work for Steve and the team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9349cfce16e0015173b853597176fe6b</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>A helicopter trip over the vast expanse of Brazil's northern savannah helps adventurer Steve Backshall find his next contender for the Deadly 60. He is in search of the elusive giant anteater, but can he get close enough to film one for his list? A chance encounter with a tough little owl with an ingenious way of catching its supper captures Steve's attention and the rainforest lives up to its name as a very wet team ventures out at night looking for some of the world's deadliest bugs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62a22e4c0f29e059eb199874aea74982</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Find out how fast your nerves work in a snotty experiment that sees Dr Xand blow a fuse, and the Cupboard of Everything is time travelling to a very smelly Victorian street.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p155f6685236c638b082ef5a70126b243</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Including an annoying French prankster from the Middle Ages, bizarre Aztec food on Historical MasterChef, what happens when Queen Elizabeth I needs the toilet, and how not to impress a woman in Victorian times.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p536197083060eeb5509b64ea9b1043f0</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Some medieval knights discover the most disgusting way to attack a castle, the Saxons demonstrate the stupidest way to lose a battle, a Georgian goes shopping in a modern pet shop, and the kings and queens of England demonstrate how to remember them all - through the power of song.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6d0fd4365a2744c2c39cf41273d17e63</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Electro at a fake fashion photoshoot when her fabulous, precious dress is ruined. Meanwhile, the other Gladiators are up to mischief behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd1bbc15f7e13b3dc2f66637f66d3cf9d</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Cute kittens are infiltrating positions of authority all around the world. Are they the feline equivalent of the illuminati, or do they just want to make napping compulsory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9f4b865a30bb897fdb78127e21f8077</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse goes undercover as the fifth member of Quark's mega-popular boy band, discovering his inner performer and a musical plot to destroy the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p77a97761345f53edbf51556bc28c35eb</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse must battle Quark again, but this time in the weirdest and most dangerous of places: Penfold's dreams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef370659f818656714ea292bc7ca5e2e</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis leads the gang on the baffling trail of a mysterious Beanotown secret society.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbe40fbbd57946697982b8c481f8009a4</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Walter and Dennis go head to head in a sponsored silence. Being quiet doesn?t come naturally to either of them, as they struggle to make it through a chaotic school day and keep schtumm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f774701f77fb51f6357283a8b30f9ef</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang find out that JJ has a set of pre-match good luck rituals. In the run-up to an important Blamjitsu event, Walter deviously throws bad luck omens into JJ?s path, threatening her chances of success.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3c30a8458c845f0ca547fee6492f559c</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Witch, who was trapped in a Merhaven clam shell while pinching a pearl, grants Blossom a single wish to thank her for releasing her and saving her life. Blossom excitedly chooses a mermaid?s tail to improve her swimming. However, when the Merqueen complains that her pearl is missing, and the heroes have to quest to get it back, Blossom soon realises how tricky a mermaid?s tail can become on land.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5de1c5363e6236bc3067ca23bed0355e</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are on a quest to find the vault containing the Amulet of Answers and protect it at all costs. But the Riddlemaster is back, and he manages to trap them in his castle, tricking Herbert into handing the Amulet of Answers over to him. Now he has all the answers to every question ever asked, and the heroes must find a way to outwit him - even though he knows what they are going to do next.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe25fa88d8b5c74373b8dbfb32088efca</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes discover that their latest quest - delivering 30 birthday balloons to Mr Friendlyface?s cousin - isn?t as easy as they expected.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10c7fd9b3be98e5feec3cbead7efdc69</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a magical djembe that possesses whoever listens to it through the demon of dance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80ca80a7640d6c97370cbe76034ce69d</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>In the midst of a heatwave, Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over the fridge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa972752e707eb996f7a33d53ae54e9e5</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a mask that can control dreams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc98e754619fbce788aed0f57aa420690</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy watches TV, while the Lemmings want to dance. TV v music - the sonic war has begun.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p109f3debefb996fbde2e14eed1d526c0</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced madcap, stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The potato racers are driving each other round the bend, the DIY doughnuts attempt to fix the bathroom, the cavemen mushrooms come face to face with some big, hairy mammoth pots, fearless Pete Parsnip takes on a ferocious foe, and Slippery Nana takes on a pizza-cutting unicycle in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc75a0813855bf2fc00f9eb5e7b778651</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom and the Riders must work together to rescue Eugene from a dragon?s nest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc467185a7cc7a0405c3a8a6a7a34f905</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Irene offers to help Ron with his band, who are playing that afternoon, forgetting she has to take an important music exam. Meanwhile, Felicity and June find clues to the missing time capsule.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7244e2997a67495eda0c16ca981f82a7</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>A trip to the big city leads to a shocking discovery about Maggie?s disappearance, and Nina and Keedie build a shaky truce while party shopping.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb6421909aa03af91feccab45bb170d8c</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>No longer dance captain, Anthony finds following orders difficult. Jett and Ariana try to be friends again, while Heath?s history with Daisy complicates things with Pascale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6fe3d3df235a0aa0979d15b7a930a0bf</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Keeping Team Brawl?s secret leaves Ariana torn. Michelle and Eldon take a look back at their past as Anthony avoids confronting his present.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p53e3f6af7ef3bf04ac1208a8601ad694</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Graven dispatches two of his generals to Earth to claim the Shard of the Soul of Gorm, forcing the Scions to accelerate their training and protect the artifact. However, with the Scions mired in personal problems, the Gormiti must help them discover their inner strengths on, and off, the battlefield.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f86d004a612bbcbb6bcf03d783df57e</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds a compass that indicates the direction of one's own desires.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf8a424f541389746fb3b18354fe81b45</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>An out-of-shape Farmer is encouraged to get fit using an improvised exercise bike.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2bcdad5eb5939559349ac3168491441</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse inherits the ancient but sprightly MK3 car after the beloved MK4 gets jammed-up. But Penfold is suspicious when the MK3 is determined to have DM all to himself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paafdc13fd551ca2258f2e20f604f4d55</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s Pieface?s turn to look after the class hamster, Space Captain Harrison McScruff-Butt. His own self doubt and Walter?s resolve to sabotage him lead to a rescue mission to free Scruff-Butt from Walter?s mansion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p030b103e478730d5108a53c51e2b4099</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the boys and girls get sick of having to share the bathroom, they split it into two! The girls' side becomes one big party with no rules, but on the boys' side Dog makes many rules! Boy and Mouse hate it, but they don't want to hurt Dog's feelings. Girl tries to lure them over to the girls' side with all the things they love to play with. Eventually Boy and Mouse sneak over to the girls' side to join in the fun - until Dog confronts them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ef23b470a33dca1bbcf9dae735dcd3c</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52093f4fc97c71b54b830256f4c2aa42</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The cabin comes to life and wants to return to Canada without Grizzy or the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd3bf809eba7aa4ce014113e511d0efb6</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>While falling, Grizzy performs a series of acrobatics that amazes the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p941b78c23a09776a0ea01141c7222e36</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Omar and Oswald search for the perfect gifts for Orla?s 500th birthday.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pddc3735175da55b667a8dd31e211c24d</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Watch the mud (and food) fly as sheep take on pigs in the fight to end all fights.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p58526dc6683d56458587390dfeba0dbc</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Something wicca this way comes when Witchy is released early, trading a bottle in the archive room for a new broom with a view and leaving Pierce disenchanted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5badf274218ccc4f3bcba74374228182</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Pro gamer Jelly guides the teams through the speedy world of Sonic Superstars. Who will race through the course and cross the finish line first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c5b667c20c88c120e93b9d6710dc734</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe?s latest victory is cut short after an Absolute Dance rules change shakes things up. Now, winning regionals isn?t just about their reputation. It's also about saving the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7103b075fe967418318c8e3e24cdd05d</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: Black and White</title>
    <desc>A vast Pok?mon habitat amid the hustle and bustle of the big city seems like the perfect new home for a group of five Genesect. The arrival of these mythical Pok?mon quickly becomes a problem, though, as their nest threatens the city?s power supply and they keep attacking anyone who approaches it. On top of that, they have attracted the attention of the legendary Pok?mon Mewtwo, who sympathizes with them because its own origins also involve human tampering. Their leader, a red Genesect, doesn?t trust Mewtwo, and their confrontation quickly rages out of control! Can Ash and his friends stop these two powerful Pok?mon before they destroy the city.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdba3419dfa18d08b2ea84574987c588a</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play marbles, and it's driving Grizzy crazy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6da67b82a65bfa51ab80ff34f6cbd6a4</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Diamond when the guest on a live TV show can?t stop pumping! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes, pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p124aa384cfc9de9b57a6c0777805b147</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle Storm and her parents flee the magical land of Kleftania and end up on Earth, where everything is strange and confusing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8be65ec0a511423024da890d9e1df73f</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Darrell?s final year starts with a fierce argument with Gwen, but she knows they need to work together. Meanwhile, French student Celeste joins the Third and plays a prank on the teachers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5f56dd0f62ae77c0e4472811ae4950e</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Young footballers Christina and Andrew dream of making it into Hawx United Academy. The odds are stacked against them - until Jamie Johnson decides to get involved.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p640fb876577b356d8527df9590bd90cf</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to Suriname, a country with more forest than anywhere else on earth. He kayaks upriver in search of some deadly critters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae61be0573c4be4246d27fa124cbcdc0</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Odd Sock Georgia can?t get her PE kit from a strange lost property cupboard at school, so Andy and the Band take on a daring and delicate operation to retrieve it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb9d30541d6a2b81eabad2a368e392c8</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Little Bro Callum sets Adam and Joe another epic quest: become a king, build the best cardboard castle, and defend your kingdom against the destructive dragon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p378c2ff8e857aa5d5929292f3eeac3c4</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>A honey badger claims a watering hole, so Kwazii challenges her to a digging contest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7757ef7eefe587e166c20e0c5d9f23bc</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When Dad runs out of marmalade, Big Lizard shows Cosima a plant that's growing Proximan oranges. The leaves turn out to be giant bugs, who aren't happy about sharing their fruit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p85d68fe5a114ec11ba06667d09c34f99</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>A late-night scary movie makes Penfold extra jittery, forcing Danger Mouse to make his sidekick sit out the latest mission to stop the Baron from flooding the entire world. When his search for Greenback proves fruitless, things go from bad to worse when Danger Mouse realises that the Baron has headed to the planet's only 100 per cent waterproof building and Penfold's current location - Danger HQ.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p409d62d6c8428e64f9af154a3cc6c776</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface's all-time hero, Cherry Bakewell, is coming to Beanotown to judge the annual bake-off. Pieface wants to make the best pie ever and win the competition, but when Dennis discovers Pieface has never actually baked a pie before, he does everything he can to ensure a win, with pie-splattering results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0410786c047c999e04107f9e22bc39f3</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are excited to visit Whizzpop?s Pop-Up Bakery and taste his magical cakes, but they are shocked to find that the protein bars have shouty raisins in them, the custard tarts are rock hard, and the floating sponges keep floating away! Trevor quests to solve the mystery, but having accidentally fallen into Whizzpop?s invisibility flour, how on earth will he get everyone?s attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe2faf77b85cf0b2852c9a1177edf9ab5</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Gladiator Dynamite is back to make sure things don?t get too explosive when Dr Dan and Dr Raph get into a Body Battle in a planktastic challenge to test their core muscles. On the basketball court, we meet Joel Henry, our Brilliant Bodies slam-dunk champion, to find out how he jumps so much higher than Dr Chris. It?s game on in the lab when Dr Xand becomes Saliva Man and Dr Chris tries everything he knows to overcome his superpowers as the doctors show us what spit is for. In an amazing Bodytricks, six kids surprise themselves by lifting Dr Ronx off a chair using only two fingers! And in the emergency department in Edinburgh, we follow the treatment of Niamh, who has broken her elbow doing a back handspring at gymnastics, and Adhya, who took a whack on the thumb during a hockey match. Ouch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p08db54266af2514592094cbe1c2c13cd</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>After rescuing a wild Hatenna, Liko contemplates her own feelings and makes a new friend.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pff951c4649af6afe59446542efe9f731</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Sketchy Comedy</title>
    <desc>A bunch of bananas, a door handle, a fridge and a tortilla are among the items get the Sketchy treatment.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb38bf8d208dac138f723a8719cab4286</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Nektons meet online superstar Devil Daniels, who will stop at nothing to reach the fame that he seeks - but can the Nektons protect a creature that he has his sights on in particular.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf77d7e9636f2bbe54a5b35b9750ee6d6</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Gnasher is practically immobile inside a full-body cast. When he goes missing, Dennis and the gang race all over Beanotown to find him, always one step behind the helpless hound.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd55d2e54635de7190d8ef7a9ff7d0bd0</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse is forced to choose between dedication to duty and friendship when he battles the Baron in his underwater Toadlantis base.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0e99707170c40698f2e2e60ec597982e</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A nightwatchman at a museum is baffled when an Egyptian exhibition keeps moving around, so he asks the Ninjas to deliver a detective who can solve the mystery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb73d44474f0cb29f7895a3f396cd28bd</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Bitzer is horrified when the Farmer scribbles all over his map showing the location of his buried bone, fearing he will never rediscover his treasure. The flock are on hand to help him search, even if their methods are unorthodox.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde8c349f04c3c64ef16ec18f49455bce</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds a giant home cinema screen.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p57083d29e406f3a34c2e18fb2182864b</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When a horrible smell ruins everyone's day at the beach, Cheese mistakenly believes she is growing stinky and is too embarrassed to go out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa104c1d0f02f523766fc02546729ae21</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes and the Council of Happiness swap jobs, and when the council fail in their quest, the whole forest is at risk of being flooded by Stinkystuff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a544a2a926fb3c68c7a21626bc95543</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents bring someone with an odd problem back to headquarters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03a2f1563cb1b025b7340bc27a3233c4</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. It's villain report card day at Odd Squad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9dae7f88c4e057d5a1eacff1e5e09570</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth sets out to get rid of all their old toys, hoping Chef will buy the new toy she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65f80c82e11fb083e3d726fe80ab11f0</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>The heroes face a jubilating villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f73dc0af7a7a65511dc1d3a5c051b5c</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Chairwoman Geeta challenges Liko, Roy and Dot to a battle to test their strength.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9c4ff1cec6ec6ad912e1a36b842dfc84</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Home Sweet Rome</title>
    <desc>Lucy meets Francesca?s parents and learns more about her family. Kyla teams up with Jimmy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p83abe12205850a2611be7419414ba29f</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Brawl pits Ariana and Michelle against each other as Lucien shakes up regionals rehearsals. Meanwhile, Izzy tries to overcome their dance captain doubts.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42174bc16570e4662a26b95b81208e65</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Life on the farm becomes a hive of athletic activity as Shaun and friends stage their very own sporting extravaganza. In heroic style Shaun, Bitzer and friends compete for victory whenever the Farmer's back is turned. A vigorous table tennis match sends Shaun around the world in his attempts to return the ball to his opponent.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe0e17bb9eb837650f0d88cf3d7324be2</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>22 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
