<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Following a long journey, the Rising Volt Tacklers finally reach Laqua.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf896e931f045c1a61db1bc8914edea28</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Carter, Glen, Zane, and Skye must hide their secret identities from everyone. They are struggling with teamwork, when hot-headed Gormian Bors tries to prove the Scions don?t have what it takes. The Scions finally unite against him but, in so doing, they attract the attention of Graven.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p16497753ab657a2216c622950836aa27</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Daisy?s return makes things more difficult for Heath. Eldon and Michelle consider parting ways as an injured Pete feels left out of the Brawl.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6b5147c4642565487a47814ae7a8a27</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Challenges, celebrities, makes and adventures with the Blue Peter team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc735eec2b4419f24733980858c0b519e</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun tricks Bitzer into thinking he is unwell so that he can stay in the barn playing video games all day. However, before long, the other sheep are also pulling sickies, and Bitzer is starting to get suspicious. The threat of nasty medicine has everyone out of bed in a flash.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p859bcc0ba6d00ac73d3e8310a33597fe</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Penfold?s countless hours spent playing Giraffe Warriors pay off when he gets the highest score of all time. Before he can celebrate and convince Danger Mouse that a video game win is a real life win, the pair are whisked off to the planet which inspired the game, where Penfold is asked to defend it from an alien invasion! With DM sidelined Penfold must take up the mantle of the last giraffe warrior, a hero destined to save the planet from peril.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35cdb4911478918f91bc396dfce97610</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Mayor Wilbur passes a law to increase healthy eating in Beanotown, replacing all foods with peas...of the mushy variety! The gang must avoid the people of Beanotown who are rapidly turning into Zompeas after eating the green mush. Dennis uses the only ordinary peas in town to sabotage Wilbur's mush-making factory and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41d58d1465e51eb4de1792f354b29a85</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy is ecstatic to go on a tour of the bobbleheads factory, but the rest of the kids are bored and cross because the brochure lied. So they secretly make a one-of-a-kind bobblehead just for Boy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p44f8a7d0d8aaa45c1497e17e869fdbd3</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc2bac1c6fa7306ba7023b70176aa056c</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy wants to watch TV, but the Lemmings prefer to have fun playing music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb81dcd41f9b8627f90482e8dfa7df1a</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A rocket carries the cabin into space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c78219ad43711cd65fcc2202b9c6992</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit reports to the New York City Odd Squad to help with a big problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31393a6794de6f2a223001931d92464f</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Helsing's new floating security orb goes from BFF to frenemy when it ejects everyone onto the lawn and takes over Helsing's house! The gang must find a way in to give it the hard reboot it deserves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe5b06a4040ad9140beb3e833422e307f</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes find treasure as they bid to save Merhaven from an angry seaweed. Blossom is delighted with her bath bomb treasure, but rather than use it, she insists on bringing it along on the watery quest to save it for a special occasion. But as the angry seaweed nears Merhaven, Blossom realises she must finally sacrifice her treasure to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4cabd4631ea30373511762999c2b1fe4</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Naomi has asked for a raise, Joy?s advised her to take some time off to think about it, which is why Danny and Mick are in charge of the cafe. They?ve just about got the hang of it when a new automated smoothie maker arrives. The machine is supposed to make life easier, but that?s not how Danny and Mick see it. Soon smoothies are flying, and everyone is left with egg on their face. And strawberry. And a bit of banana?.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b4c9cf8f021ccd65862af8d996b9857</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs get noisy with homemade instruments, Aowen Jin paints UV art that glows, and Emily Steel - aka Gladiator Dynamite - flexes her muscles by drawing a weightlifting alpaca.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d00237a732b167e672df30111b12313</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings build an airborne craft made of Chinese umbrellas to steal the TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p20ddcb21d4ba305bb4c6980243857e09</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Great Barrier Reef, the world's largest structure of living organisms at 1,400 miles long, is home to the most diverse population of undersea life on the planet, and it's under attack! In an epic story torn from the headlines, the Octonauts embark on their largest, most complex rescue mission ever - saving the Great Barrier Reef and all the creatures that live there from an invasion of coral-hungry crown-of-thorns starfish. The Octonauts meet a tiny coral polyp looking to find a home on the very same reef where the Octonauts are deploying their new medical base, the Gup-W, and the Gup-P, a specialised first responder emergency vehicle. To save the reef and their new polyp friend, the Octonauts must combine forces with a diverse crew of zapping, splatting and claw-snapping reef creatures to fend off the spiky, coral-munching starfish.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c0dc458f6e97f617eb92df8b75313fa</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Angel Pavement</title>
    <desc>A tale from Quentin Blake's Box of Treasures. Corky and Loopy are two ordinary girls who happen to also be secret angels! With the aid of a magic pencil that can draw in the air, they go on 'angel patrol;, amazing people in their town with beautiful art and rescuing the odd animal. When they meet street artist Sid, they decide to help him take part in a local drawing competition by lending him the special pencil. Sid creates incredible drawings in the sky and brings joy and wonder to all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8427157182cecb41fc8f48d23a6b9123</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Apollo prank Dynamite, turning her into a singing banana! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99a45e9399b5fa5991e3b3eb060bfd42</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Can underdog Cranmede take on the mighty reigning champions Gorsforth at the Interschool Country Dance Championships? And can Tam overcome her dance demons in time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1485a447b6247106aa11cbbdb4498d5d</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>With Astra suspended, Hannah makes the impossible decision to leave. Can her friends convince her to stay.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc3693098adcc48114cd1a677f363492</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Skilful trialist Jay unsettles the other Hawx players and challenges Alex?s authority. Coach Byrne makes a difficult decision, and someone?s going to get cut? But who.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac68d2bda1346c66ea1477637fdfb6a2</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Mission Shark</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall is on a mission to create a new generation of shark saviours, but first he needs to find his team. In this episode, Steve takes 12 young UK hopefuls to boot camp with the challenge of choosing just six from the group. To earn their ticket to swim with sharks in a designated Shark Sanctuary in the Bahamas, the 12 have to complete a series of challenges, including swimming, a clifftop leap into water and a demanding abseil. With a weekend of training completed, who will Steve pick to be in his team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc258d9fd2ae84df2b435fa201e01761a</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Young Ben wants to win the Oddpool sandcastle competition. The band head to the beach, and Rio meets a sea genie who gives everyone a big surprise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7f84fa8da7522537bc61f7822db88abf</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Little bro Callum sends Adam and Joe to the seaside to see who can build the greatest sandcastle in a bid to avoid the wheel of doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa1e581c0b2edb0a8f4e62471b0976dfb</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>When birds cause trouble aboard the Octoray, Tweak uses her Octowatch to help with repairs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p36119280da16de9ca6a67955e506c3b9</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Finding an earth probe makes Dad homesick. When Big Lizard accidentally destroys it, Cosima knows what to do. She recreates the contents - Proxima-style.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe44fe6c98a91e76a5ce34a8afbff4b5</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Danger agents go undercover disguised as a family to find out why the world?s villains are heading to one holiday camp, Sidneyland. When Baron Greenback shows up, the team are convinced he?s up to no good, but can?t find any evidence of wrongdoing. When Penfold enters Squawk and DM in a dance competition they discover the prize is the fabled Helmet of Power, an ultimate invention bent on destruction.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b5ce7408b56f7960eb3b2cde7d508f8</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A snake bite causes Grizzly Griller to forget all his survival know-how, so it's down to his greatest fan Dennis to help him re-learn his survival skills and help them all make it safely back to Beanotown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d701f1ef35c0ede4ea972cfc0c218a6</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes discover that their latest quest - delivering 30 birthday balloons to Mr Friendlyface?s cousin - isn?t as easy as they expected.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10c7fd9b3be98e5feec3cbead7efdc69</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>As Adele says goodbye to The Next Step, she tries to mend fences with Olive. Things get complicated between Heath and Pascale as Anthony deals with Adele leaving.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12094601243ee9d32365dcaf717213be</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Fuecoco does its best to quell a group of angry wild Pok?mon with song and dance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p68fd577f4044d5539cdffb1037e8155c</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Taffy</title>
    <desc>Mrs Muchmore is chosen to represent April in the country club?s calendar. Fuffernin will be there in a few hours to take the best picture possible, and everyone has to be dressed in green, from bow to toe.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfb9308b349661db62565e480e8890f10</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Trying to rescue Jess Gorman in an underwater cave proves dangerous for Ant and Fontaine until a manatee comes to their aid. But is it too late.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb62124f1023aacdda64a83825676306e</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis's ultimate hero, Grizzly Griller, plans on trekking to the source of the River Beano, broadcasting the treacherous path on live TV. Dennis introduces him to his pet hamster Galahad - only to discover they are his biggest fear! Grizzly is so afraid that Dennis must disguise himself as his hero and go in his place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8740f186fd542531c6393457aada6f7e</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Count Duckula is back, and he is determined to take over the world, one terrible TV show at a time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p78f9f0a97c4d271042d27c59788eb11c</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Two sisters arguing over tidying up their house end up with a bigger problem when the Ninjas deliver two cleaning robots from the future who are planning a robotic rebellion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7db05f3ffc7255bc464cfe0eb0754b3c</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Set on a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. Shaun finds a camera which some ramblers have dropped and sets about taking snapshots of the flock. Bitzer is soon on the trail of the missing camera.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbfdf487e61bc85086eaec74349686a06</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings create a shadow puppet show where seven papercut lemmings confront a bear.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc86af08c9c02f6ba215273b5a0f148b3</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>K-Jam is moving into the neighbourhood and staying with the family for a while. However, Girl gets insecure and thinks that her awesome best friend is trying to take her place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbace25267391c527963e66f359240ab</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia discovers a secret about her partner. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs, data analysis and collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p487861630ae6473048dde909b125dabf</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olympia discovers a secret about her partner. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs, data analysis and collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p200888983017e30e8e27c57e31798c5b</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan sees an opportunity for a break from daycare when an angry skunk hunts down Chef.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p369231ecc447b57e864ac5d90b077f18</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face a revolutionary enemy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe794b82c94b5da3fc969d1d75fc5d92</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>The Rising Volt Tacklers and the Explorers battle over the fate of Laqua.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5cb0995236fa925e4cab08fc13f2b545</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Graven dispatches two of his generals to Earth to claim the Shard of the Soul of Gorm, forcing the Scions to accelerate their training and protect the artifact. However, with the Scions mired in personal problems, the Gormiti must help them discover their inner strengths on, and off, the battlefield.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f86d004a612bbcbb6bcf03d783df57e</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupers begin to switch over to Team Brawl, but when Olive and Eldon figure out a way back into regionals, Anthony and Ethan have their loyalties tested.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdfbe47178e58aaec452002ff1f8d03b8</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Does Joel have what it takes to pass the Royal Marines Commando Endurance course?! Squeezing through tunnels and getting soaked in water obstacles, followed by a gruelling run back to base, all against the clock.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3b4138df05292645a07b18a2fa96ced</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When a meteor shower is forecast to pass over Mossy Bottom, Bitzer really wants to see the shooting stars. However, he keeps getting distracted by the flock?s curiosity and the Farmer?s late-night picnic.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paed19956be0ae4e13e120b77e3af55ba</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold are introduced to Squawk?s latest invention ? a warp drive device that will transport HQ anywhere in the universe at a moment?s notice. Squawk?s demonstration seems to go without a hitch - that is until the gang notice an exact duplicate of the HQ across the road, with identical duplicates of the Danger Team inside. When the duplicate Big Head is activated and starts causing mayhem the two DMs join forces to try and stop her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf0691a04cfdc488c1f2a7e7040389e29</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Walter attempts to ruin The Dinmakers' chance of reaching fame. He will stop at nothing - even wearing a frock and pretending to be a fan called Wanda who loves Dennis in order to break up the band.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p185b9baa4b788b368de5e75e2d93003b</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>On a dark and stormy night, the kids tell a scary story about local legend Big Bad Ben! Mouse says he doesn't exist, but when a dark figure arrives at the house, they all believe it's Big Bad Ben - even Mouse! Who is this stranger in the storm? Can they work together to protect themselves? And, hang on, didn?t Cheese order pizza.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p79c9e0907c61ad532b85e1c481150b77</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf7bf21699d68cd6b40a859dbc3c2fa34</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>It's time for the racket game, where big scores mean big prizes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb4876fa452c0f93c5471f450963b20c9</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings adopt a cute insect that eats wood. And what's made of wood? The cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pff351cedb37a51b39f803f5886026822</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>An agent-in-training visits the Mobile Unit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p79d20441d3969ddc950988a6b3ed567c</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Trying to train Snorp is a complete catastrophe for the gang, leaving Charlie and Que 'feline' frustrated. As word spreads that he may become an 'outside pet', Snorp's enemies are coming for him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10c08a5cb66c677da06ea14a8b448809</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes go on a quest to get Hoofius?s Toby Jug back from the depths of the Riddling Ruins and are faced with a series of puzzles and traps to solve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67fad6fb2cc188991a416f8965659da7</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>All the Pottsfield Leisure Centre staff are raising money for Comic Relief. Danny and Lance, as always, turn it into a competition to see which of them can raise the most money! But between Danny?s disastrously defective charity calendar, and Mick?s frankly frightening fancy dress, the brothers only succeed in driving the totaliser lower than when they started. It?s going to take everybody putting aside their rivalries and working together as a team to turn this situation around. That, and a lot of soggy sponges.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6558aa7ce6fe7f9bca9a21e48a31ec28</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>08:55AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs set sail with homemade pirate ships, Sophie Ryder sculpts a huge Minotaur, and Harry Hill draws himself being chased by a very big, very blue cat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p950470bcf5000eb12035d467de5b8256</image>
    <start>08:55AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The mood of a raccoon becomes contagious to all those around him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7a5dd8a643af87b46b15270f98dd64c9</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: XY</title>
    <desc>A power unbound, a battle of legends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p322713452f73834fcb5c8c0ed070b808</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Phantom prank Fire at a kids' birthday party! The rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3eb6afc7027c8bfed2f443d8a7e7d70e</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>It?s Superhero Day, but not everyone chooses to embrace their unique superpower. Luca turns super villain, Claire shuns her superfan and Mr Malone makes a super-awkward gaff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6ca084bd2034a10047f1308f2941fd49</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>X-Key are gearing up for their TV appearance, unaware of the traitor in their midst, and, after a shocking revelation, Astra must do everything they can to pull off the impossible.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0ec84c76f3c30275a965add2f7f1b6ae</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Strange goings-on at Hawx Academy make the players worry the place is haunted. Jay struggles to settle in, while Alex is taunted by Hawx rivals Foxborough.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc4dac4e4d2b9c6a5707aa5ed62250768</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Mission Shark</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall has chosen his UK team of six to travel with him to Bimini in the Bahamas, where they learn how to scuba dive and become the next generation of shark saviours. The mission begins as soon as they land, and they have just two weeks to complete four training dives, but first it?s time to meet four local Bahamian children who are also joining Steve?s team. On board the dive boat, they encounter their first shark species ? the Caribbean reef shark ? a deadly predator engineered for hunting underwater. Then it?s off to the dive location to start the first series of tests. Some of the team take to diving with ease and soon pass the preliminary stage of their training. For others, it is a much harder challenge, with the tasks proving too much at their first attempt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4a212c329026bccbe3710eb188b9fae6</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>TV Stars Sam and Mark prank the Odd Socks, and there is an even bigger surprise when the lads start giving out awards for the best bits from the series - who will be the winners.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0afc03afb5404fcb89a061ba7b5bfa0c</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Online greeter extraordinaire Troy Hawke helps Callum challenge Adam and Joe to be the most complimentary to passers-by.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/ped8c9f4d688bddfc27d20814bdbcea8d</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>When Kwazii and Calico Jack get stranded on an island, the Octonauts must search for them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p711b28f057f24edc9450ca884c6ba142</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>It's been one year since Cosima crash landed on Proxima, but no-one else has remembered this anniversary! Can a perfect picnic jolt their memories.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52ef4f7288ee99b772ad68e542eb05a9</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When a sudden urge to fly the Mark IV hits, Penfold leads a confused Danger Mouse to a farm, from which he claims to feel an unexplained magnetic pull. An entranced Penfold is met by a shadowy figure - Granny Penfold! Penfold recounts his childhood years on Granny?s farm, where he was trained in the ancient martial art of Farm Fu; a farming based martial art. Granny needs Penfold?s help to retrieve the sacred Fung Farm Book of Farm Fu, which has fallen into the hands of her enemies, causing farm animals to turn evil and rise up against their owners.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5bc9fb86a9c9d89de3a6896036c3a7d9</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang train Bertie in the art of standing up to people so he can rebel against Walter's bossiness - but they train him too well and he becomes a dangerous rebel without a clue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ee81567708d80e99b9f35e4a420add2</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Whilst on a quest to return the Icicle of Destiny, Trevor topples into a cavern of tiny mushrooms who treat him like a king.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6587ed590db6ffbdbc38b906cd7ccb3a</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>An overprotective Heath accuses Grace of sabotage, while Grace and Jonah make a bet to make it on to A-Troupe. Meanwhile, Izzy grapples with keeping Anthony?s secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p98b58fbdb69531c7dbfb68abe1998543</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko, Mollie and their Pok?mon set out to save a Tandemaus pair separated by a storm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p941d680c0b29788ee2b02f98f587c4cd</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Taffy</title>
    <desc>Every time Bentley steals Taffy?s bow, Taffy seems to find another one from nowhere. Bentley tries to find the source of his supply so that he can destroy it and finally expose Taffy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc15dd1ec0725169209f3264096c5a87c</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>The Aronnax and Alpheus?s sub are trapped within a giant jellyfish! They?ve been eaten and the jellyfish won?t let food out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p916c85101eb07165f67a52271108d625</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface steals Professor Von Screwtop's Pastry-based Intelligent Espionage unit (PIE) after forming a strong bond with the pie-shaped robot. Pieface is dismayed when Walter steals it from him to protect his dad from the embarrassing footage the PIE's memory chip holds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4db578615381ab592eeaeea97d895804</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's plan to hold a surprise party for Professor Squawkencluck is undone when the Baron releases killer birthday presents into the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p142b27e7bb29436619c5a233aa8b58ec</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A fairy-tale princess being pestered by an annoying prince orders a new dragon from the Ninjas, who return with the most ferocious monster of them all - a T-Rex.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70302567796da86615c59a39a8a223b9</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. A circus sets up in a nearby field, and a spellbound Timmy wanders off to investigate. Can Shaun rescue him before the farmer notices he's gone.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a12f4a74e3e01355e1a8d436e474630</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy relaxes in the massage chair, but the electricity supply stops in the log cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8b95b3a4287e28006124b3827736c563</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the kids think that Mom may be pregnant, they set out to prove they will be great babysitters. Along the way, they learn that it's much harder to do it alone than it is together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb5bb5a7b40090762af8e629842f8f3e8</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are excited to visit Whizzpop?s Pop-Up Bakery and taste his magical cakes, but they are shocked to find that the protein bars have shouty raisins in them, the custard tarts are rock hard, and the floating sponges keep floating away! Trevor quests to solve the mystery, but having accidentally fallen into Whizzpop?s invisibility flour, how on earth will he get everyone?s attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe2faf77b85cf0b2852c9a1177edf9ab5</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf326fb9ddf1e4b8189998894cdaba294</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9219a4ed6990cdd4d9ec30d5d0a40f34</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Challenges, celebrities, makes and adventures with the Blue Peter team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4762ad46eff5636ad504a235887f92a3</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir unknowingly face Queen Mayor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ddd267d48b17366fafe68beb1bbb05b</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>After 100 years, the secrets of Laqua finally come to light.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0360f783a139b692684e52faf1554e8</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Just as the Scions start coming into their own, harnessing their potential as a team, all their hard-won progress comes to a halt when they attempt the ultimate Scion ability: Fusion. The unexpected outcome endangers both Carter and Myridell while giving Graven another strategic advantage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80370a7258c8348a620257f43a263566</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:20PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Kenzie helps Pete make a difficult decision. The Brawl?s love theme gets in the way of Heath and Daisy fixing their friendship, and Michelle turns to Eldon for Brawl advice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p78694b47d4acdfcbe0bbffab1b09836a</image>
    <start>06:20PM</start>
    <finish>06:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: Legend of the Boneknapper Dragon</title>
    <desc>Animated short. When Gobber's house burns down, the old Viking is convinced that his nemesis, the legendary Boneknapper dragon, is responsible. Bent on revenge, Gobber resolves to hunt it down once and for all, despite the fact that no one believes the dragon exists. Regardless, Hiccup and the gang decide to accompany him for his own good. On the sea voyage, Gobber tells the story of his rivalry with the beast, which gets sillier with each episode. When the gang find themselves shipwrecked on the suspected island of the beast, they finally learn the truth about the dragon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc74aefee6d25de383371feb7631f2a1</image>
    <start>06:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
