<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ricky Wilson's Art Jam</title>
    <desc>Radio 1 DJ Nick ?Grimmy? Grimshaw visits the Art Jam studio to show Ricky three items that mean the world to him - a colourful Keith Haring print, a picture of a Paris bridge wrapped in gold fabric and a special Damien Hirst album cover. While chatting to Ricky, Nick shares amazing stories about being a DJ, the celebrities he has met, his lifelong love of art and his two beloved dogs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1579fad2ba6a5d51ffb91860c1ec4f41</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Dr Chris gets a soaking in the lab, and picking a shade of purple leaves people gobsmacked in Mindbenders. And who will get snotted in Ouchology.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p95faf39f896abbd5631cae724bd51278</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Enter the fun world of a football-mad family, where life is never quiet, and meet para-footballer Ellie as she travels to the Women's Euros.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p597618fd7dc87d9159a7b18fce5597e7</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Best in the World</title>
    <desc>Best in the World is the entertainment clip show that invites CBBC viewers to playalong at home with Guinness World Records. We showcase the greatest and wackiest record breakers in hilarious guessing games - can you forecast the winner, solve what just happened or guess how many times they need do the thing they need to do? Competitive mug carrying? Golf club chucking? We?ve got both! Sit down and enjoy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb74f02e4003b29f35d49c4abe50e42bd</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Nine Minute Ninja</title>
    <desc>There's a party mood in the flat as the Grand Master makes a joke juice bottle from jelly and Ricky has a sweet trick for drawing a celebratory cake. There's also a party game inspired by LS Lowry.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/ped247b94263e93077d15b3932e9ab164</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>An Incan kid has the worst birthday ever, a Roman farmer meets a door-to-door poo salesman, and King George IV embarks on a solo musical career.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa2c1304b7416a9da50aaf00217adcfef</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Goalkeeper and football fan Tristan had to take a break from playing with his local team due to illness. He wants a den to help him recover and to store all his football memorabilia.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd3ab6cc8075b80c38ce9f444d55923be</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum inflicts terror and temptation on Adam and Joe to see who can impress him the most and be the 'last to leave the circle'.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2e94d65ceb7459c6e25e6e58c77d47f9</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>Lars sees a mysterious creature near the Academy jungle and rushes to tell the others. Ubercorn explains that new species are discovered all the time, so this could be something that no one has seen before. He also tells them that new species are often named after the person who finds them. Excited by the prospect of lending their name to this mysterious creature, the Go Jetters, Grandmaster Glitch and Tala head out on a jungle expedition - but something seems to be watching them from the treetops..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe9dce97ec543c0aeb9fb58ae5b52674b</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Big Lizard frustrates Dad by stealing a strange plant from the ship. A disaster is averted when Big Lizard persuades Dad that there's more to this plant than meets the eye - and nose..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14ca5ecf6caf025ddb70672d85186143</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>An unknown weta's distress call forces the Octonauts to do some detective work.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p118d34fe78affbde68885fb52c143607</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Piripenguins</title>
    <desc>A sales rep visits. Despite Pancake?s doubts, he convinces the Piris to buy extra flippers. The penguins discover that their purchases are duds but find a clever new use for them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd938df44aed41395e3b7baced04b4f5d</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Carrot is starring in her own circus and thinks that Supertato is trying to steal her limelight. She soon realises that Supertato is trying to rescue her from Evil Pea?s meddling.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p724fa84cd8d908ca771b9ce1c28d3ad3</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Jeopardy Mouse are on a mission in space - will they work together as a team? In the midst of an interstellar team-up, a bickering Danger Mouse and Jeopardy Mouse crash-land on a desolate planet. While Penfold, Squawkencluck and King Kong Brunel search for a way to bring the pair back to Earth, the stubborn pair split up in their new surroundings. DM and Jeopardy Mouse are brought back together when they're captured by a horde of Fly People - the planet isn't deserted after all! The Fly People's hatred of DM is explained when our hero is reunited with Lionel the huge World Wide Spider, who he accidentally sent to the planet of the flies. Lionel's fondness for snacking on the local population has landed him a place on the menu - he's going to be fed to the terrifying pit-dwelling 'Beast', and now DM and Jeopardy are going to be eaten too! Will DM and JM finally resolve to cooperate to get out of this perilous position.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6d72d4eed999a80d4b929f9cf71a337</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface steals Professor Von Screwtop's Pastry-based Intelligent Espionage unit (PIE) after forming a strong bond with the pie-shaped robot. Pieface is dismayed when Walter steals it from him to protect his dad from the embarrassing footage the PIE's memory chip holds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4db578615381ab592eeaeea97d895804</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Mrs Creecher uses the school's allotment to hold Class 3C's 'Biggest Veg' competition. Determined to outshine Walter, Dennis will do anything to grow the biggest veg. Little does he know that JJ's gran's special potion, when mixed with Walter's dad's V-V plant food, will transform their plants into giant living, walking, groaning veggies. They turn to Paul the Potato to help them 'smoothie' out the situation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f43826a07b6a52478a605bf5876bb34</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>While questing to keep her hero safe on her long journey, superfan Blossom fusses and frets too much, making things awkward.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe6ab2dbb5103b7a559efd71238dac7b</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas battle a hungry space blob as they try to fulfill an order for a flag for astronaut Lewis Weaklegs to plant on the moon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa72aa11d357947a4eb9393e0f89a1c2e</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>From terrifying Spartan mums to hidden Victorian mums, via Queen Victoria and Cleopatra, Horrible Histories looks at some of history?s most monstrous mothers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6f21dc87d6f7778d064b717e1ff32e0</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Britain's greatest sailor, Admiral Nelson, turns out to be horribly seasick, and two doctors from the Middle Ages argue over how to treat a patient. Plus, discover the many uses for an Incan llama, and the World War Two Girls sing about girl power on the Home Front.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p183c52c86f4ce6bcb7a4de76b7e0a5b9</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Terrible Tudors King Henry VIII and his daughter Queen Elizabeth I bicker about who was the best ruler. Henry had a mechanical dragon kite, but Liz had a flushing toilet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1f7d56aaa1b1dc8f4857651e70d84f9c</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse faces the Queen of Weevils in a fearful Halloween special.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ff6788cafa5778e2972fb67508deb9d</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>In order to secure the highest star rating for her restaurant, Chef Topsee turns to the Ninjas to find a giant egg for critic Jean-Pierre Point D'orgure.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34ad50ac5670ffe0903db420b45f5e91</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When a meteor shower is forecast to pass over Mossy Bottom, Bitzer really wants to see the shooting stars. However, he keeps getting distracted by the flock?s curiosity and the Farmer?s late-night picnic.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paed19956be0ae4e13e120b77e3af55ba</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a hidden mechanism on the Great Wall of China.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e9b40eecda303f7fa1885c29e9016b1</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the kids wonder about what they?ll be when they grow up, Mouse?s enhanced online career quiz leads Boy to think he is destined to be an astronaut, with Girl thinking she will end up a boring safety inspector. Both struggle to embrace their fates - but Mouse?s science can?t be wrong, can it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4905b446520109c731d611286b667d14</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert takes his failed cooling hat invention along on a quest, using it to save the day after being faced with the Riddlemaster?s jibes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa71b4703dab60fe05f881ddc78ac43d6</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents struggle to catch an odd creature.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peec9bd5ed02d81eb8de81e85a8c1524e</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan convinces Owen to start misbehaving to show him how much fun their timeouts can be.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p64cdbe54e04dd37f4adbf42b4a490149</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel and Shini are in Wales for a close-up encounter feeding crocodiles, they take some tiny turtles for a health check, and we show you how to make a wildlife-inspired pencil pot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p019a331ee6029e35e0d98e4784665965</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Apollo prank Dynamite, turning her into a singing banana! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99a45e9399b5fa5991e3b3eb060bfd42</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs make a bug jungle, Chris Howarth makes sand art waves, and Rob Biddulph shows how to draw a furry monster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p37672a63f7ec87e89f34fc36ae95bc34</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Tracy Beaker Returns</title>
    <desc>Drama set in a children's home. Carmen and Lily plan on manipulating Mike into letting Shadow stay at the Dumping Ground with Lily when she has respite care the following week. The girls arrive back at the DG to find Jody, a wild, screaming girl who is refusing to have a bath. Carmen is told Jody has to share with her. She and Lily go to Sapphire who refuses to move in with Elektra so that Jody can have her room, and Mike then tells Lily that now things are fine with her dad, she won't need respite care anymore anyway. Tired of her hyperactive antics, Elektra locks Jody in the toy cupboard. Jody breaks free, tips a plant over Elektra's head and disappears. Tracy and Mike find her at her wreck of a family home. Her mum and brothers, who have a criminal court case pending, have left. Jody is distraught. Mike and Tracy take her back to the Dumping Ground. An upset Lily tells Carmen how she needs a break from her dad, not the other way around. She makes Carmen promise not to say anything for fear of the authorities taking her away from her dad again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p22cf55229d91124f237d1c041675af11</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>As the regionals qualifier clashes with the Brawl?s, A-Troupe struggle under the weight of all the secrets they have kept from each other.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe9d1cb97d31ebc00d15259e3a3812cd0</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>A new season at Hawx Academy brings new faces, new challenges and old rivalries.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e471a642d1c44ef35c378fd85b704e5</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>05 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>With the Farmer and Bitzer out at the Golden Tractor Awards, the flock take the chance to enjoy all the mod cons of the house ? until they overload the power, plunging the house into total darkness. When the Farmer returns, the flock must escape the house without getting caught.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd7b31aa1a58ad1739e5097ed867b02f7</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Has Danger Mouse finally met his match? An evil version of the hero escapes from a parallel dimension and joins forces with Baron Greenback.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa755ac1daa2a711230c9321971439bf6</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Fed up with Dennis pulling the wool over Mrs Creecher's eyes, Walter orchestrates a robot to take over Class 3C - with disastrous results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p09cd14a7c66d70b97a06114b327de9ed</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Much to the kids' horror, Gramps starts spending a lot of time with mean Miss Molly! The gang do whatever it takes to keep the two apart.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc164d1eb50b7b3d1b3041fdb1b4540e9</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03b2f37b79d69229267b6bd168a309fe</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When a sheriff tries to clean up her town and kick out Stinky Dan McGrubb, she orders a cleaning squad from the Ninjas.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p89c17e4e6513e3724ff82bd6ae7f658a</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents go to Negative Town to track a villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf0b27bf2348114cf4d41fd712d8d4748</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes and the Council of Happiness swap jobs, and when the council fail in their quest, the whole forest is at risk of being flooded by Stinkystuff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a544a2a926fb3c68c7a21626bc95543</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir unknowingly face Queen Mayor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ddd267d48b17366fafe68beb1bbb05b</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Marinette discovers a secret that nothing could have prepared her for.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1192cd55e9e8d08cfb95b2742664a03</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>As Tera training comes to an end, Liko and Roy face off in battle at Naranja Academy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1f418d89c413c1cbd616bb137f01723b</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy wants to watch TV, but the Lemmings want to have fun playing music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb81dcd41f9b8627f90482e8dfa7df1a</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play with a baby ostrich that Grizzy found outside.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9b02f3095f1dc487cda4763f743454b5</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings are throwing a big birthday party, but Grizzy is not in the mood.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3db4fa9889189f0cc9220e9804405d6</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Mouse accidentally saves Cheese's life from a toppling tree, a grateful Cheese becomes determined to thank him by doing everything she can for him. But Cheese is soon bothering Mouse all the time and her endless caring is becoming too much, causing Boy and Girl to hatch a plan to even things out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9109e873e859d6effa3c5f7efeb97401</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Dog decides to show the family that he can be as tough as the wolves they are watching on TV. He joins a gang of street dogs and soon becomes leader of the pack. Meanwhile, the rest of the kids worry when Dog doesn?t come home and go out looking for him. However, they find that he is now too cool to be part of the 'old' family - until he is forced to make a choice between loyalty to the pack and loyalty to his best friend Boy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80906893d3cfdb5661c71eda227eba55</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The family have been telling their deepest, darkest secrets to Cat for years. But when Cat finds one of Mouse?s inventions that gives her intelligence and speech, she threatens to tell all their secrets if they don't do everything she asks. The kids must decide between living under their feline pharaoh's thumb or confessing their secrets to each other.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfed16d83f85eb7f2591ee30d5e8a513b</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen takes over the job of caring for the class hamster and learns he is not so cute.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70a72456e7a1a1ca3936bacce3cb457b</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan tricks Beth into believing she broke his battery-powered bike.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa608c0317cbcbf41f823628dae40d0b4</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Who is the froggiest frog? It?s time to find out as Adam and Joe spend the day as one! Featuring a disgusting diet, loudest ribbit and an obstacle course - only one frog can win.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f55dfa77aa8e40fcce40c3ec44de082</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs make a bug jungle, Chris Howarth makes sand art waves, and Rob Biddulph shows how to draw a furry monster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p37672a63f7ec87e89f34fc36ae95bc34</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel and Shini are in Wales for a close-up encounter feeding crocodiles, they take some tiny turtles for a health check, and we show you how to make a wildlife-inspired pencil pot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p019a331ee6029e35e0d98e4784665965</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. When odd things start happening to the Bears basketball team, Olive and Otto must set things straight before the big game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc6ee320d065f69e421ccb20835a0d128</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigate strange events. Olive and Otto must work out how and why things are disappearing around town when all Otto wants to do is listen to a song by his favourite band.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfb70c017c537e025bc6b666a09bced7e</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Spooky Files</title>
    <desc>It?s high school graduation for Derek and Billie, but the biggest, baddest Spooky ever has just come through the portal.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4545443d89b3256c6841c67339c9b061</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Spooky Files</title>
    <desc>With Big Bad holding their Spooky friends captive, the Spooky crew must dig mega deep if they have any hope of stopping Big Bad before it?s too late.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8614184bef18f4cfcad464ea3539d0a4</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Could farts power a rocket? If you ask a question like that to Dr Chris and Dr Xand, you know they will want to investigate ? and if they can, they will blast off an actual rocket too! We welcome Gladiator Dynamite to Team Ouch! Her job is to referee Dr Dan and Dr Raph as they pit their bodies against each other in Dan vs Raph: Body Battles. Today, it?s a muscle they are testing: the triceps. Will it be Dr Dan or Dr Raph who ends up in the ice bath as a loser?s forfeit? One thing is for sure, Dynamite?s decision is final! Doctors Chris, Xand and Ronx are Ouch and About giving answers to kids? medical questions, with Margot asking why people have asthma. In Australia, the Flying Doctors fly Jack and his mum to hospital in New South Wales for a check-up following Jack's bone marrow transplant. Back in the emergency department in the UK, Logan has hurt his knee after tripping and landing on a log, and Harshali has a pink bead stuck up her nose! Ouch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94a8d6fd6580fb7b64d941699a3b2c35</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Fred Sirieix stars in Scientific First Dates, Marie Curie reacts to space, and the dinosaurs get an unwelcome musical meteor visitor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2a33358dcb8b4090c89b64ab78a468a</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>It?s the inter-school tournament, and the Vipers might just win. Jessica is determined to spoil everything, and Aoife must use all her detective powers to keep the team together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p146b239f847b5c78963ab9a0c9716863</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Coach Byrne?s controversial new tactics throw the team into disarray, rousing Bobby's suspicions. Is he really trying to improve them, or is there something more sinister going on.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2e9a87fa2fbe261ba573ac3798d71a29</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan, Leshawna and Jude vie for corner pieces of Izzy's birthday cake. Who will get one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe2e1748a1a2ebd9e384f8c9c0e17c0dd</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When Owen gets cheated out of a much-wanted ice cream, the kids unite to right the wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0e0faa507faa293dac67782cacaa6f8</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Noah tries to rescue the chocolates Owen forgot outside before something else steals them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe990410924ceb1db2243b7a84a432d8e</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse goes undercover as the fifth member of Quark's mega-popular boy band, discovering his inner performer and a musical plot to destroy the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p77a97761345f53edbf51556bc28c35eb</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse must battle Quark again, but this time in the weirdest and most dangerous of places: Penfold's dreams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef370659f818656714ea292bc7ca5e2e</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron steals DM's confidence and gives it to his shy daughter, Delilah Von Greenback, creating a dangerous criminal mastermind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5df627a084f7c486593e10df1725c85c</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Lila has a brand new vlog that goes viral in school. Girl doesn?t like seeing her nasty rival have such success and so begins filming her own vlog about her family?s real life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb005c8f7adebe43c3bec3815c239134b</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy's nose makes a weird whistling sound when he is asleep, which is no big deal until it is captured on video and goes viral - but is this new-found popularity a good thing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p764082128262bead290081aac7b0c3b0</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>With the rest of the gang sick with colds, Mouse builds his own personal transparent bubble to keep himself healthy. But soon the others get also their bubbles to enjoy their own space, even if they're not sick anymore.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peac044daa2577ce7a3c237afbdaf0f7b</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings organise a mega-party, leading to the cabin being invaded by bats.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p017dac7b4c386b657d1c3d9999e8170c</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy creates a new Yummy-based recipe: Choco-noodles.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa1a04431661ac2aeb668f346bbb87773</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The tired heroes must quest to find out and stop whatever is making the loud wailing noise that has kept the residents of the forest up all night.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe737598843036feb34240aa725c51adc</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Stinkweasel drops a rain of yukkiness onto the forest, the Fairy Squad, with their excellent flying skills, decide they are the ones for the job. However, Hoofius insists this should be their quest, even if he does hate ick! And when the Fairy Squad get their wings gunked and are unable to fly, the heroes can resume their quest to end Stinkweasel?s reign of stinky nonsense - no flying required.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d85af1ed37a16cec54b2e5a529e9bbc</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert has invented a new contraption to help him fly using an old set of bagpipes. The 'Herbecopter', as Herbert likes to call it, is rather noisy but extremely effective, and Twinkle is unhappy at no longer being the only flying hero. So, when the heroes quest to get Friendlyface?s priceless locket back from a dragon, Twinkle and Herbert become extremely competitive and risk completely failing the quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa955ab16670c700cec4ca1249af0b548</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Mansour offers Blink a way out of a virus trap for a truce, but Blink double-crosses him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe5a2fb6f90efd3d451621c5109e7769c</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Mansour races against time to stop Blink from taking over the quantum computer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ea7ae1f94a52a3a7ccc157b47ed3f3b</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>The teams take part in a competition to catapult a fellow team member! The first team to reach 10,000 points wins. The losing team, as always, will be sending someone home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9e9b870dd71313b0ee3dec7dd9cbcdbc</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gremlins: Secrets of the Mogwai</title>
    <desc>Gizmo is torn from his home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd40eb8fa652490a2110561353a55a29d</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>06 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>After the Farmer manages to drive his tractor into a mud patch, Shaun, Bitzer and the flock try to rescue it from the quagmire. Before long, however, the stranded vehicle sinks far beyond their reach.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p48863823b752a00185efd1d51b78cf84</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold become reluctant parents when it appears the Baron has wiped his own memory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3e99b351aa4afb22052be158681eea93</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A bungled attempt at a stunt leads to Dennis accidentally becoming an internet star and Beanotown celebrity! But his moment of fame is short and Dennis is soon replaced by Walter's cat, who can play the piano. Dennis has to stage the best stunt yet to gain back his audience.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2448826bf08a8b69aefa3652e97decf5</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy and Dog are working on their comedy act for a talent show. Unfortunately, nobody finds them funny, until they find a runaway parrot who laughs hysterically at them 24\/7.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2259d11d9d558996d9cc83f1858fc6df</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p68c5c8a1a630ffea4c657390d12fcd52</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A frantic bride needs a romantic ice sculpture to appease her nervous groom, so the Ninjas travel to the north pole to deliver a wedding day she will never forget.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4244299fed08c9f23c9ffa18cc4ee1d7</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Oona must pass her lab director's test or risk getting kicked off Odd Squad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c632c88aa80e16ae46ae71103168455</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Blossom accidentally uses a witch?s broom to make sticks for toasting marshmallows, the owner of the broom casts a spell of squeaky voices on all the heroes. The spell will be lifted once the heroes have returned with new broomstick branches. A simple enough quest, think the heroes, until they realise that a witch?s broom can only be made from the branches of the Really Spooky Tree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe37511be85e501039449287ddef18d2b</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Is it the final day for Monarch, Ladybug and Cat Noir.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0feae8ff909b51ad39cc8a4e6a14e549</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:55AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy notices that the Lemmings have laid hands on a pirate cannon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf7d718e20f9db9f57661911a80b230c3</image>
    <start>08:55AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel and Shini are in Wales for a close-up encounter feeding crocodiles, they take some tiny turtles for a health check, and we show you how to make a wildlife-inspired pencil pot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p019a331ee6029e35e0d98e4784665965</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>Family portraits get personal! The Kwapongs try a clever painting hack, Tom Allen draws a super fancy unicorn, and Maisie Matilda paints a mini masterpiece on the edge of a book.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f120992cce42bd242375db26a42d6ec</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>4 O'Clock Club</title>
    <desc>Darnesh has to eat a jar of pickled eggs before the sell-by date expires. And Eli sees the girl of his dreams but makes the mistake of involving Fleur and Eleesha in his love life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4cb06066fd4d4ff95d5f47794f4fcef9</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Sharon's boss, Mrs Harris, has come to the leisure centre to make sure that things are running smoothly. She thinks she can run it better herself and so fires a distraught Sharon. However, it is not as easy as it looks, and Danny and Mick make sure Mrs Harris' boss, Dame Frost, fires her and brings Sharon back to get things back under control.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc48c42de1ac92aebec5fbb26b4b82158</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:25AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It?s the Invention of the Year awards, and everyone at the leisure centre has ideas they are hoping to pitch. Business mogul Jacqui Williams turns up to judge and isn?t impressed with what she sees. Danny?s invention of a chair that does everything might turn her head, however.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p949257162198c4c08b4d5a5b10a2ad15</image>
    <start>10:25AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>It?s time to go undercover and discover who makes the best spy. Laser mazes, gadgets and creative camouflage - only one spy will take the win.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcb96a4a004f310e8e63c7f291a09ebd9</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>Explore the fantastic features of the zoo?s most weirdly wonderful animals. Hufflepuff the hedgehog tenrec enjoys a dust bath, and Jua the serval puts her radar ears to the test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p344eb5eb52a29be737e8f913c56f6f63</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>The action shifts to Steve's home turf as the Deadly 60 team scour the UK in search of its lethal beauties. Terry Nutkins lends a helping hand in spotting otters and tells Steve the story of how he lost two fingers to one of these creatures. A bit of pond-dipping reveals a whole host of the nasties ready to bite, maim and generally eat each other, and Steve gets a chance to meet with the biggest spider in the UK. Then it's off for a high-speed chase as Steve plays pigeon for the afternoon and nearly loses his head whilst being hunted by the fastest animal on the planet, the truly incredible peregrine falcon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p560e22ac583728731db26b4262e81024</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Adventurer Steve Backshall and the Deadly 60 team pack their cold weather gear and head north to Alaska. They battle for days and nights in the freezing conditions of the frozen tundra, hoping to find polar bears to add to the list. They are rewarded with a rare sighting of a wolverine and some cheeky Arctic foxes. Steve has heard of a place where thousands of bald eagles arrive every year to feed on the spawning salmon. Keen to see them first-hand, he heads up one of the freezing rivers to get a closer look. Alaska is also home to the grizzly bear, and Steve won't be going home until he has seen one and added it to his list.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p17105a235161339bb136198006171642</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Dr Chris gets a soaking in the lab, and picking a shade of purple leaves people gobsmacked in Mindbenders. And who will get snotted in Ouchology.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p95faf39f896abbd5631cae724bd51278</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Some Vikings attack a monastery but cannot remember why, a peasant gets a posh makeover on Georgian Fashion Fix, Crimewatch BC tries to solve the murder of Julius Caesar. And prepare to be confused by the Egyptian Hieroglyphics song.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9c67fa2886ed9e757320a8ac9580b915</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>The Stuarts are confused by the newly discovered drink of tea, a Viking funeral ends in a massive fight, a child evacuated in the Blitz thinks farm animals are monsters, and some cowboys sing about life in the Wild West.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p485abd05cbc8943ffd1061c1a0968cbd</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Hammer with a hysterical, historical Gladiator mix-up in a magazine interview, and the other Gladiators have sneaky backstage fun at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3ce3b2d65e95acafb7130f4d3f3b0897</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Princess is back and erases all weekdays so she can play at the weekend forever. Danger Mouse must ruin everyone's lives by fixing the problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51b2ee65ff2e3f266a9013ffa3688df9</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse is responsible for Professor Squawkencluck losing her job his clumsy attempts to get her back help the Baron steal half the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3bb8928291651f97c9f27761acb6a515</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Our dynamic duo take on a shoddy army of knock-offs when alien Quark's latest money-making scheme is to create cheap copies of Danger Mouse and Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc3534acab020f64bb5ca220b64ae15c1</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Professor von Screwtop gets mistaken for the new kid in school and joins Class 3C for the day. Rubi is so embarrassed at her dad?s antics that she resorts to pranking to get him into trouble and out of the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p060c373a4ae75d174dc60fc03089f42e</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>JJ applies for an elite sporting school. However, not realising it's miles away from Beanotown, he needs to do badly in the sporting assessment to get out of it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p25f8c727ad716ff6332cb203cd3afeab</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang take on the power of WilburCorp to stop Walter?s new line of collectable toys ruining the Beanotown environment with all its wasteful plastic packaging.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c44a8d584dd7a07558e7563e65f62b0</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface is particularly tetchy this morning. He is packing for a skiing trip, but a dragon has pinched his golden fleece, and he urgently needs the heroes to quest it back ? how else will he stay warm and cosy on the slopes? However, when the heroes accidentally agree to let his niece Trixie tag along with them, they fear that her clumsiness and lack of hero skills will ruin everything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c3ff87984db3abc93407af293a6fe99</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert is really proud of the plants he has grown ready for a visit from The Complete Gnome Gardener magazine. However, when a Wind Dragon flies through the forest destroying all his hard work, Herbert turns to desperate measures ? a barrowful of Stinkweasel?s stinkiest compost! Now, the whole forest is at risk of being overwhelmed by the smell, and the heroes must quest to get rid of it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6fbe790ae4282b14265104a8bedddd57</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes aren?t really meant to do quests without Mr Friendlyface?s express permission. But when they come across a cute little squirrel queen, and she begs for their help, they find her impossible to resist. All they have to do is quest to the Tree of Certain Doom and pass his challenges. But the squirrel queen is not who she appears to be, and the heroes have to quickly un-quest their quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc66ead86a1798e4f31033a6bf01a29a</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A Lemming finds a mysterious mask that endows him with the power of telekinesis.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peecc469e064293cb3826d2ecd69c6307</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy chases after the Lemmings and the jar of Yummy in their remote-controlled car.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p92aff3c434c1be5d19dc5f8fd5c7244c</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings take possession of a magic sceptre that has the ability to shrink objects.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p777d66872fcd3672633acf25cf19f79b</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy swipes the peanut reserves of the elephant playing with the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54036a52fcc54e05e7dec7e09578175a</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom tries to convince Olivia that the Hidden World is safe for them to explore.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3c0c8f7cb15ed3c4c9e79ed4d228b6cf</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Alicia falls out with Darrell and the other sixth formers when she edits the school newsletter. Meanwhile, Jo and Susan get into trouble with Mr Parker over his new typewriter.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf872c930eba29ef318fd0cec2941516a</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Addie bravely presents her memorial idea to the old-fashioned village council, and in 16th-century Juniper, Maggie stands up to a fearsome witch hunter.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5828bf783af72e843efe5408d9913843</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Jett tries to find her place in A-Troupe but is feeling left out. Ethan reminisces about his time in Paris, while Adele looks to a new opportunity abroad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9315e88d52382d5866e8352363827dd3</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>As Adele says goodbye to The Next Step, she tries to mend fences with Olive. Things get complicated between Heath and Pascale as Anthony deals with Adele leaving.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6b1be36aa0e94cecaeba7f3f1ecfc8f4</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>The new Scions begin their training by bonding with their four Gormiti, the spirit warriors who empower and guide them. However, Myridell surprises the Scions with a trip to Gorm, where the teens must pass their first test - defending the Temple of Gorm from Graven?s vicious Skavs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3c720ec31a4d049f2df422ba713218ba</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings are victims of inexplicable thefts.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6cb0a6d9bc2e4befe360258ebf89619e</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When two different pieces of flat-pack furniture are delivered to the Farmer and Bitzer, confusion ensues as they start to mix up the pieces. Shaun and the flock are forced to give them a lesson in following instructions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6faba19999bdaf0067c3c03224597602</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's film star status is threatened by a toilet uprising. An epic battle on the streets of Tokyo between Danger Mouse and Dr Loocifer! Oh, wait - it's just a scene being filmed for Danger Mouse: The Movie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa699c08bac85f3f5f4670350bfb26834</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis leads the gang on the baffling trail of a mysterious Beanotown secret society.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbe40fbbd57946697982b8c481f8009a4</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Tired of feeling like a loser, Mouse decides to play dirty to win Mazes and Monsters against his siblings, even if it means it takes away the fun of the game for everyone.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31e7b05f8c9cd8564e6f3bbd8fdd2f3c</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef7706296379c6989a37da832a8336b6</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a silkworm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb2a4455efc0d2ba913ad4e4083bbf47b</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings use all the electricity for their phones - now Grizzy can?t watch TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p465df138cba7e7ae123993705a66a905</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf326fb9ddf1e4b8189998894cdaba294</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Forest inspectors pay the forest a visit to check its super-happy status. Friendlyface sends the heroes on outlandish quests to guarantee results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf423a5126c7145dec4e840079fa076e4</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: Black and White</title>
    <desc>When Ash, Iris and Cilan enter a battle competition in Eindoak Town, they meet and befriend mythical Pok?mon Victini. However, disaster strikes when misguided wanderer Damon seizes Victini for his own plans! Can Ash prove himself a hero and earn the help of the legendary Reshiram to rescue Victini and save Eindoak Town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb04e230c9d82712b43bc1c387cab9a1</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>A totally wicked song about gravity, a T-rex going to see a doctor, vampires on holiday, and Sir Isaac Newton riding a rollercoaster - welcome to the bizarre world of Horrible Science.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p225ef60f63c5a1f6aa9ee4f55650c08d</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall and his long-suffering crew return for more deadly encounters with animals hoping to earn a place on his hallowed Deadly 60 list. Steve Backshall travels to Indonesia in search of three very different reptiles to add to his list of 60 deadly predators. He and his crew have a nerve-racking close encounter when they are chased by a group of ravenous, three-metre-long komodo dragons, the world's largest venomous lizards! Steve also demonstrates the incredible gliding technique of a tiny flying lizard and heads out on a nocturnal hunt for the beautiful but lethal green pit viper.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p746766f2cf7cf0ebb0da2b993dcd49a9</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Things get explosive when Dr Chris and Dr Xand look at how spots are made, plus an incredible emergency service at work in Australia: the Flying Doctors.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b4c137dff0cf46b799270e7eb64b46d</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>In this episode, we meet nine-year-old twin sisters Kiki and Queenie. We also follow U11 boys Teddy and Miles in their biggest tournament of the year.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32db01aaffdf41be1b2b695848d338ff</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Predators</title>
    <desc>Steve uncovers the secrets of sharks, the world?s most infamous predators. From the ocean?s most graceful killers to the biggest shark to have ever existed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3bf81cc8d942b29ddd4732aa40bb593d</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It's a big day at Pottsfield Leisure Centre - there is a new boss in town. Sharon Granger means business and wants to create an advert to bring in more customers and make her mark. She tasks Danny and Mick to make an advert showing the best bits of the leisure centre... what could possibly go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7bb2d3421a49fd3a99f24a2c68077b06</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy?s sister Ruby wants to meet her hero, superstar vlogger Fay Moss, so Andy and the Band risk missing their next gig by racing off to help out. Staging a fake fashion photoshoot by posing as flashy designers, they attempt to bag some time with Fay by distracting her security guard! Cousin Mac?s new auto-tuner invention is put to good use, but after an epic diva tantrum, will Fay live up to all of Ruby expectations.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fd9ca307fd295ae771597804d126e27</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum is a Little Bro in control! He?s pitting his Big Bro Adam against best mate Joe to see who will win a series of funny, gungy and gross challenges and who will take on a forfeit from the Wheel Of Doom in this epic competition. Callum may be Little Bro, but he?s in control, so Adam and Joe need to impress him! Adam and Joe wake up to discover Callum has made their arms grow extra long overnight. How will they walk the dog, make brekky and ? most importantly ? style their trademark locks with really long limbs? Once Callum decides who?s taking the win, it?s onto the Biggest Splash Challenge. Who can plunge into gunge and create a splash that will impress Little Bro Callum so much he excuses them from the Wheel of Doom?s rank forfeit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p08b0fb7e9af46654217afa6d613eef93</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Warm temperatures wake up some hibernating dormice, and the Octonauts must protect them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f9fc506aadd9217d7128a831e93a53b</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When a meteorite splashes into the sea, Dad and Cosima cause problems by claiming it in the name of science, against the wishes of the sea creatures.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e6f70978ad1d72f2b5eca2f74a72900</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The baron's true love threatens to bring Danger Mouse to his knees.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfcaae47453a9f3c1541b759fb60634cb</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis gets into a fluffy mess when he runs into Von Screwtop's hadron collider with the professor's pet hamster, Galahad. To stop Dennis from completely changing into a hamster, the gang must sneak him into Wilbur's lab to use his reverse hadron collider and change him back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80dfb84ec4b3edb443b7d8d57691f72a</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle uses her excellent pocket beast card skills when on a quest to rescue the missing Council of Happiness from Grackle the Giant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c52df7e45b3a76f78f6ac5a5d573bb1</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Could farts power a rocket? If you ask a question like that to Dr Chris and Dr Xand, you know they will want to investigate ? and if they can, they will blast off an actual rocket too! We welcome Gladiator Dynamite to Team Ouch! Her job is to referee Dr Dan and Dr Raph as they pit their bodies against each other in Dan vs Raph: Body Battles. Today, it?s a muscle they are testing: the triceps. Will it be Dr Dan or Dr Raph who ends up in the ice bath as a loser?s forfeit? One thing is for sure, Dynamite?s decision is final! Doctors Chris, Xand and Ronx are Ouch and About giving answers to kids? medical questions, with Margot asking why people have asthma. In Australia, the Flying Doctors fly Jack and his mum to hospital in New South Wales for a check-up following Jack's bone marrow transplant. Back in the emergency department in the UK, Logan has hurt his knee after tripping and landing on a log, and Harshali has a pink bead stuck up her nose! Ouch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94a8d6fd6580fb7b64d941699a3b2c35</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko has gone missing, so Dot calls on a celebrity connection for help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42b9dc2a58d4c4bf9c7737c0bee2bb85</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a box filled with fortune cookies close to the Great Wall of China.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pba2796334e942468921c463b1c433065</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Animated series. A dragon-hunting expedition leads Ant to find an ancient scroll that holds clues to an amazing mystery. But his family are trapped by the dragon and only Ant and Jeffrey can save them! And Jeffrey's a fish.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p046066e525d9f961e471343dff55474b</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Rubi?s dance machine gets accidentally muddled up with Crusty the Robot Pie?s coding. Dennis and Gnasher have to dance on it all day in perfect sync, or Crusty?s entire persona will be wiped forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc196d03c4998053896105cc5f5c04bc8</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Danger agents go undercover disguised as a family to find out why the world?s villains are heading to one holiday camp, Sidneyland. When Baron Greenback shows up, the team are convinced he?s up to no good, but can?t find any evidence of wrongdoing. When Penfold enters Squawk and DM in a dance competition they discover the prize is the fabled Helmet of Power, an ultimate invention bent on destruction.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b5ce7408b56f7960eb3b2cde7d508f8</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A panicked factory owner asks the Ninjas for help to produce Xian Ye's action figure, but Konpeki's obsession with the soccer star makes it difficult to complete the task.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc2a8751c3ff7bce191db43b611b67043</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>While proudly testing his new doorbell camera, the Farmer realises he has locked himself out. Bitzer must help his boss get back into the farmhouse while simultaneously making sure he doesn?t spot Timmy and Shaun with a runaway kite.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1852ca2377930b34605a83021e353269</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy creates a new Yummy-based recipe: Choco-noodles.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa1a04431661ac2aeb668f346bbb87773</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy gets his dream job at the collectibles store, but when a family of screeching birds makes the store entrance their home, the customers stay away. It's Boy's job to move the birds, but Girl discovers they?re endangered and have to stay. If Boy can't get rid of the birds he'll be fired! But what's more important - his job or the birds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d56a7d28e8f920ef9622a88ac8f08de</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle is unhappy with how easy questing has become since Cral the Eagle joined the heroes, offending the eagle just when they need him the most.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9ac8fa176bea27e14bcc365246b3ae79</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents celebrate an important milestone in their partnership.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd46cd88fb1d62102eb10a1553a7f2a21</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents try to determine what kind of creature will hatch from an egg.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p666d2606ef1cdfced44b7267472cdd42</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Bridgette gets the hiccups for the first time and tries desperately to get rid of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb93d6040b77fd2f1a2b5d7d46d15ace1</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug faces Ephemeral.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p87a8e11efb1bf3f77b72b0639f913ebe</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Encounters at the Crystal Pool lead to battles, new friends and discoveries about the past.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc2a45dc842a88d407ec72f3a10d1f00a</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Jo causes chaos when she tells Celeste?s mother that Celeste doesn?t want to return home. Meanwhile, Nancy, June and Felicity are excited to discover that Fred knows about the time capsule.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p149f709f8f1effdeb4864ef7580c7e41</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Tensions run high in A-troupe when Finn's mistake leads them to rework their routine hours before they are set to perform. Nick is forced to make a difficult decision that results in Piper paying for Finn?s mistake, which puts their relationship on shaky ground.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa3867ca29b3b243f4cf7d75f97e6686e</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>This time on Shark Bites, Steve Backshall meets the snappiest shark in our seas. The lemon shark scours the sandy seabed for food, but how does it get a good grip on hidden prey? Steve heads to the Bahamas in the Caribbean to dive with these feisty sharks. He heads down on his dive with a time slice rig to film the lemon shark's bite in three dimensions before heading into his shark lab to analyse it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p04dcbbb89007c2c46f0efdd0bd78d96e</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>An all-night gaming session turns the Farmer and Bitzer into sleep-deprived zombies the next day. Shaun takes the chance to change Bitzer?s checklist to suit himself, but he manages to miss the final item: shearing time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3f60727be2d84e2a3113f71146047e4</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The last thing DM would normally want to do is play a boring board game, but when one arrives in the post, it releases knockout gas and he's surprised to wake up in the town of Greenback. Jeopardy Mouse, Hazard Mouse and Danger Cash have also been snatched and are equally clueless why until a dragon attacks the group and a net drops from the sky at an opportune moment. Our guys realise they have been shrunk to chess-piece size by Ian the Danger Fan and are now pawns in his real-life board game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p89d3a3ac086dc94904568d6e0040f283</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Walter and Dennis go head to head in a sponsored silence. Being quiet doesn?t come naturally to either of them, as they struggle to make it through a chaotic school day and keep schtumm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f774701f77fb51f6357283a8b30f9ef</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>K-Jam and Girl have plans for the best day ever! However, when Cheese shoves herself in and takes over, she jeopardizes all of their plans.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea51e2ba2bb2d7cc4061772d9eb901bf</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdaae4e47abbdf082c5b760b7064f088c</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings catch a grasshopper that can give you whatever your heart desires.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e0fd7c58b3a252cdfc561d821057d41</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings use magic Chinese lanterns for sound and light shows.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc5e5b2b6e0498ea0f97679ba5f75b9a4</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9219a4ed6990cdd4d9ec30d5d0a40f34</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Whilst on a quest to return the Icicle of Destiny, Trevor topples into a cavern of tiny mushrooms who treat him like a king.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6587ed590db6ffbdbc38b906cd7ccb3a</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step Live - The Movie</title>
    <desc>In 2015, the cast of The Next Step began an eight-week, sold-out, coast-to-coast tour across Canada. For the fortunate fans who had tickets to those sold-out performances it was a chance to see their favourite dancers in person. But what would it be like to have the best seat in the house and a backstage pass.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a7be2cfa2b60931aea75cedee8e07c4</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Apollo prank Dynamite, turning her into a singing banana! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99a45e9399b5fa5991e3b3eb060bfd42</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Big Danny and Big Manny find science shocking, Da Vinci does a sound experiment, Newton rides again, Queen Vic shows off, and Dr Big Brain doesn?t see the attraction of electromagnets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8dd0beb4fb74ad45650014dd91335b55</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>In the medieval Ethiopian city of Harar, Steve Backshall has a unique and potentially lethal encounter with a pack of spotted hyenas. Capable of tearing their prey apart with super-strong jaws and thick muscular bodies, here they are hand-fed, allowing Steve the encounter of a lifetime with this normally unapproachable predator. Heading out of the town and up into the mountains, Steve meets the rarest wolf on earth and discovers why a grass-munching monkey, the gelada baboon, has a set of teeth that would make a vampire jealous.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ccc0f8bd2221f4b916e83c059ef6ad8</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Find out how fast your nerves work in a snotty experiment that sees Dr Xand blow a fuse, and the Cupboard of Everything is time travelling to a very smelly Victorian street.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p155f6685236c638b082ef5a70126b243</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>We meet Gavers, who has always had a tough battle against much bigger kids his own age, and four academy players watch the first team in action.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf231f55c7a2154610aff5d8541b2f372</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Predators</title>
    <desc>Steve gets chased down a mountain by a peregrine falcon and high-dives like a gannet off a cliff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e9a0bcc8dd8fc674a9469ad978a2ca6</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Footballing legend Chris Kamara is coming to the leisure centre to unveil a statue that has been made of him. All Mick has to do is make sure no-one sees it before he arrives and protect it at all costs. This should be an easy task, but with Danny close by and with a football in toe, nothing is as simple as it seems.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2abc192b35f3a247810fd29f11c216d</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Odd Sock Kaylim has a holiday headache - his family need to go on holiday, but their car is stuck. Andy and the Band?s plan to help is truly out of this world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13ad311e03b90fad3357ad6fa4c2bbca</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum is a Little Bro in control! He?s made a series of funny, gungy and gross challenges for his Big Bro Adam and best mate Joe to see who?s the best and who loses, having to take on a forfeit from the Wheel of Doom. When a slime baby shows up at their front door, Adam and Joe suddenly take on daddy duties. But how do you comfort a slime baby, teach it to speak or take it for a walk without spilling the slime? And once that?s over, Callum challenges them to become life-sized toys and hunt around their house for epic accessories. Who?ll race back to their toy box first, Adam or Joe? These daddy-os are about to find out in this head-to-head epic battle to determine who?s the CEO and who?s taking a spin on the Wheel of Doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf309fbf017e2b95f5612f22d43948e02</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts find some lost eggs in a nest off the coast and search for the mother.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a30845f680c10250d61a4a3675340bc</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad needs some training to pass his astronaut fitness test. Cosima and Big Lizard put him through his paces! When Rex gets into trouble, Dad?s hard work finally pays off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb80434f85462029178993348008abe14</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse makes short work of Burt Badboy and his newly acquired band of fanatical feline followers, the group's leader Mandy and her cult of cats immediately trade in their colourful mohican hairstyles for eyepatches and become Danger Mouse worshippers. At first Danger Mouse is having too much fun to take notice of Penfold's warnings about his new-found cult status, but even he is forced to act when the cats follow his example a little too literally and live life a little too dangerously. Danger Mouse's attempt to disown the cats goes down like a lead balloon, and they use mouse-fu skills and a superpowered amulet stolen from Tutenkamoo to show their idol the error of his ways. Danger Mouse battles the frenzied feline onslaught and saves HQ from becoming a giant scratching post. However, this only reaffirms the idea that he is the chosen one in the minds of Mandy and the cult of cats. Danger Mouse realises that the only solution is to find a new obsession for the cats.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cecc13bc26e14071dc1ed1bb687eebf</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis discovers that Ralf the janitor is the legendary Prankmaster General and is told he could become his successor. Walter won't let this happen and challenges him to a prank battle to win Ralf's book of pranking - the infamous Prankypedia.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fdd220cddb6e710107b2fa25d30a3c1</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Forest inspectors pay the forest a visit to check its super-happy status. Friendlyface sends the heroes on outlandish quests to guarantee results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf423a5126c7145dec4e840079fa076e4</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel and Shini are in Wales for a close-up encounter feeding crocodiles, they take some tiny turtles for a health check, and we show you how to make a wildlife-inspired pencil pot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p019a331ee6029e35e0d98e4784665965</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Officially a trainer, Dot teams up with Quaxly to help take back Liko?s stolen pendant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9bc5f0c03e7ee5f9277fd5d43ed70bb</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings love sesame nougat, but Grizzy also adores this treat and steals their box.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p64a57734b6a24b062d71ddbece2023c7</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Dark Orca pirates attack! They believe the Nektons have a rare treasure aboard their sub. To escape, Kaiko must guide the Aronnax through an erupting, undersea volcano! But can the sub survive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd520f862f6cabfeabbb19014b13d8dae</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>A patch of wet cement, a boy and a dog itching to put their prints into it and a policeman determined not to let that happen. Can Dennis and Gnasher muddle Sergeant Slipper long enough before the cement sets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3cbcc2b42f737a35aae5268e19aff3be</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When a sudden urge to fly the Mark IV hits, Penfold leads a confused Danger Mouse to a farm, from which he claims to feel an unexplained magnetic pull. An entranced Penfold is met by a shadowy figure - Granny Penfold! Penfold recounts his childhood years on Granny?s farm, where he was trained in the ancient martial art of Farm Fu; a farming based martial art. Granny needs Penfold?s help to retrieve the sacred Fung Farm Book of Farm Fu, which has fallen into the hands of her enemies, causing farm animals to turn evil and rise up against their owners.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5bc9fb86a9c9d89de3a6896036c3a7d9</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When her superhero suit gets shrunk in the wash, Mega Hero Girl summons the Ninjas to find her a new one so that she can save a planet from an incoming asteroid.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p43b73bae7cd910ec88e39265c681b614</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The Farmer has taken up beekeeping and is loving all the honey produced by the hive. However, when he discards his protective suit, the swarm move in, bringing it to life! Soon, the ?Bee-Man? is bossing Bitzer around.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc354936294dc8908b721c1100ac957a3</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a temple dedicated to an ancestral brioche.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10643fca7fc86640614edef9f8a31551</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>A photographer is coming to take snaps of Girl's latest cosplay creation. She needs the others' help building it and agrees to do a series of favours for them in return. However, chaos breaks out when sneaky Girl starts secretly trading off these favours among the gang themselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf228ff0628556fe4a73703f510b527c0</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>An angry Swampclops follows the heroes back from their quest for a giant raspberry, so Hoofius must abandon his chances of winning the bake-off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3dcc908834fa89d31657019c7b692113</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents discover things are very different at Odd Squad at night.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ad839cbad7983f6045b82d4f1e49e23</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Coach O determines which agents get to visit the unicorns in Cloud Town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6b3eaa6706b91bbaeafb6f921efe4c4a</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan is determined to stop the musical duo Bananas &amp; Cheese from coming to the daycare.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd71f329b98ff41291c47ec44f0ca6020</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug teams up with a new ally to face Kuro Neko.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd7e0499bb764c15c8928a6ba2b526fb6</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Joined by Perrin, the Rising Volt Tacklers set out to find Kleavor on Tengu Mountain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d673cc286577b672f953048a7f66c0a</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Alicia and Darrell are trapped in the cellar after Alicia receives some bad news. Can finding the time capsule help them? Meanwhile, Irene feels pressured by her musical ambitions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p821f0a71198bd3e77b921a92fca3d471</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe preps for their dance, but an unexpected twist throws a massive wrench in their performance. As A-Troupe?s future rests on an unexpected dancer?s shoulders, a crisis of confidence threatens to sink the routine. Finn begs Piper to forgive him, but his apology falls on deaf ears, leaving Finn to hope that a grand gesture will earn Piper?s forgiveness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/padb8e2056fdea237ecf7616642f203e7</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Bitzer is horrified when the Farmer scribbles all over his map showing the location of his buried bone, fearing he will never rediscover his treasure. The flock are on hand to help him search, even if their methods are unorthodox.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde8c349f04c3c64ef16ec18f49455bce</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's addiction to challenges threatens the world. Quark tricks Danger Mouse into transporting a ticking time bomb back to Earth. This device threatens to turn the entire world into gold within hours. Quark's face print is the key to deactivating the bomb, and while dragging the extra-mouthed extraterrestrial across space wouldn't usually pose much of a problem to DM, Quark aims to see his plan through by exploiting his captor's recently diagnosed 'Compulsive Challenge Disorder'. With the HQ in sight and minutes to spare, DM's 'CCD' takes hold at the worst possible moment, and he abandons the mission in order to battle an army of bounty hunters. Can DM come to his senses and channel his affliction into saving his friends and stop the planet from turning into a huge gold bauble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a0eba2335e392bf6d0c015b6b6474e7</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang find out that JJ has a set of pre-match good luck rituals. In the run-up to an important Blamjitsu event, Walter deviously throws bad luck omens into JJ?s path, threatening her chances of success.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3c30a8458c845f0ca547fee6492f559c</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the siblings grow jealous of Boy and Girl going to school, Mouse offers to become their homeschool teacher. Too bad Dog, Cat and Cheese aren't exactly model students.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p39a58e7a11468918cb9bc3976121f470</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p93b72ba69f78b07158fba10bbacdbe2f</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings lay hands on an ancient console, and Grizzy is transported into the game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31177e19b22b7b6fd1c283788e89e3f8</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a mask that terrifies anyone who looks at it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1940c1b33ce8f0692bb0dbf611d37b6</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Agents Opal and Omar uncover the location of a legendary odd artifact.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb1a1fbc6396eb897cd452bcd1881ce6e</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface?s hat has been stolen by a Big Ole Worm, and the heroes must quest to get it back. As they trail the worm through the Prickly Desert, Trevor accidentally spikes himself all over on a cactus. But all is not lost ? now that he is covered in sharp spikes, Trevor realises that he has a unique superpower, and when the time comes to confront the Big Ole Worm, it?s Spiky Trevor to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d893098488de351f2861251077cc5bc</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad: The Movie</title>
    <desc>When a group of adults run Odd Squad out of business, the agents are forced to become regular kids again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p940d89c545bc8e46b3a2423109556bb4</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Forest inspectors pay the forest a visit to check its super-happy status. Friendlyface sends the heroes on outlandish quests to guarantee results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf423a5126c7145dec4e840079fa076e4</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Phantom prank Fire at a kids' birthday party! The rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3eb6afc7027c8bfed2f443d8a7e7d70e</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Mary Ploppins soothes those digestive ills, Dr Big Brain tries banana power, and Einstein reacts to Tim Peake. Fred Sirieix guest stars.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p817374987312a170e9ec24db4169edd8</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve is on his home turf, scouring land, sea and air for some of the deadliest critters that the UK has to offer. First, he heads for the seas off the coast of Plymouth in search of monsters from the deep. And he's not disappointed! In the bowels of a wreck he comes face to face with a giant conger eel, one of the most feared predators in the ocean. Back on land he meets a double deadly killer, the dragonfly. As adults they are amazing aerial assassins, but they lead a double life. Before they emerge as elegant winged beauties, the larvae are terrors of the underwater world, impaling their unsuspecting prey with their alien-like double-hinged jaws. Finally, with the aid of a giant vertical wind tunnel, Steve tries to hover like a kestrel, one of the prettiest but fiercest falcons.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1d02bab5172ffb5e99de911caf4ce278</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Dr Xand?s in a spin to show why dizziness occurs, the Flying Doctors help a baby in Australia, and Dr Raph takes an icy dip as he meets a Brilliant Body who swims in the Arctic.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfa8d6a2c88990591bbff4458ce36b12c</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>In this episode, the focus is on U13s goalie Keanu, who is in remission from leukaemia and back to his best. We also meet 14-year-old midfield dynamo Libby.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc51c937c7a46f3fc15cced1c4e773c36</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Predators</title>
    <desc>Steve meets a punching shrimp, the world?s heaviest eagle, and comes face to face with a wolf.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5c12ada4bfab9e8a1185753c67f2b1b1</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Talented artist Satchel has been painting a big mural at Pottsfield which is ready to be unveiled and photographed by the local paper. However, Danny isn't happy with how he has been painted and decides to make a few 'small' changes that leave the mural unrecognisable, just as the photographer arrives.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe8cac76d7ffc3fe7eb897f71085c8b53</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Odd Sock Alana needs help with her disobedient French poodle, Monty. Andy and the Band try to train the pup, but their canine class is decidedly dog-eared.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p726f95a615984e09bec9ff3231108f40</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum's pitting his Big Bro Adam against best mate Joe in this hilarious competition made up of funny, gross and gungy challenges. Who'll take the win and who will take a spin on the Wheel of Doom? It?s all up to Callum so they?ll need to impress him! When Joe and Adam open their front doors to find a 20m high crane outside, they know Little Bro Callum?s up to something! He?s challenged them to an epic Big Drop contest? with mum?s vase and their own phones. Which precious items will survive the drop, and how can watermelon and a gunge pool protect them? Once that?s sorted, it?s onto building gigantic hats with everyday objects in a bid to avoid Callum?s forfeit Wheel of Doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1d2866a7b019052f7a902d701a630fde</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>A storm in Vietnam floods a cave, trapping Ryla, Kwazii, Shellington - and a tiger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc316ac2439c36f849fb58b31ea2e85e4</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When the buggy gets a flat tyre, Dad, Cosima and Big Lizard are stranded. Big Lizard?s playful nature helps reveal a creative solution to their problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa03aeaf60b6464ad7052d257c7def1d0</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold receive a crash course in the customs of America's oldest holiday when they cover for Jeopardy Mouse as she takes time off for Thanksgiving. After barely escaping from the war zone of a Black Friday sale, they find themselves back at Jeopardy's apartment. DM prepares to tuck into the plentiful Thanksgiving spread when Hissteria and Ham Hands rise out of the dishes. They announce their newly formed coalition and joint plans to vanquish America. DM sticks to his stand-in duties and refuses Jeopardy's help as he and Penfold follow Hissteria and Ham Hands' trail. They find the villainous pair hijacking the Thanksgiving Day parade - launching a gas attack from the air that will turn everything in sight to stuffing. With holiday-saving solutions at a premium, Penfold convinces a reluctant DM to call Jeopardy for help. Jeopardy assures DM that doing things with friends is what Thanksgiving is all about as they set about taking Ham Hands and Hissteria down. They distract them long enough to cut them loose along with the rest of the gas-filled balloons.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5362698311ba343ffe4571fba7fb7bc3</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Mayor Wilbur passes a law to increase healthy eating in Beanotown, replacing all foods with peas...of the mushy variety! The gang must avoid the people of Beanotown who are rapidly turning into Zompeas after eating the green mush. Dennis uses the only ordinary peas in town to sabotage Wilbur's mush-making factory and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41d58d1465e51eb4de1792f354b29a85</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes wake up on Snow Day morning, there isn?t a snowflake in sight! The heroes must quest to free the Snow Dragon and save Snow Day for all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70e545bcacb2d124e1fd8b0469e27b2a</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>To investigate why tummy rumbles are so loud when you?re hungry, the doctors call in the supersized stomach of Mega Xand! When Dr Chris and Dr Xand count down the Top 5 Bizarre-est Body Parts You Never Knew You Had, you will discover that the mysterious palmaris longus is so bizarre that you might not have it at all! The big question in Ouchology is whether it will be Dr Chris, Dr Xand or Dr Ronx who gets snotted by their kid quizmasters. If the doctors can put all the organs in the right place on their own bodies, they could win enough points to avoid the snot - but someone has to come last! Elsewhere, for Investigation Ouch!, Dr Chris finds out why real doctors are doing fake operations on fake organs inside fake patients in Nottingham. At the emergency department in Edinburgh, Alice has hurt her head and arm by accidentally running into a fence. And when Finlay arrives with burns on his forearms, the medics think it might have something to do with parsnips.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe8147477dc78b233d22fec7bfd20d4eb</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Fuecoco and Wattrel aren?t getting along, so Roy sets up some teamwork training.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p91959b198f9e9173c47496978c3efb96</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a mysterious stone, endowing them with the mastery of Shaolin Kung Fu.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe7690cdab092fb9368ec4408ae3dd01a</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>Animated series. A new artificial intelligence running the sub stops the Nektons from saving a kayaker because it's too dangerous. When the Nektons try to shut her down, she takes over completely! Can Ant outwit AIMY and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p55e9ed8259c3111253b702e319a7bb8e</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Dennis thinks Gnasher has trashed a valuable piece of hideous art, the gang try desperately to cover up the damage and produce a decoy that is as convincingly terrible as the original.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4fc5d89880a983b655e137d80434250a</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Clip show. The Danger Agency realises that a lack of accounting has left them bankrupt. Whilst the bailiffs are in collecting goods from HQ the team decide to hold a telethon, asking people to phone in and donate to order their favourite clips to be played. Their target is a whopping ten million pounds! Can they reach their target in time? And what clip is DM trying to hide.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p85c2dc0931075bbc11c3f53b5253b881</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas bring superstar Jean Pascal to the aid of a princess who orders a talented musician to help in calming her difficult dragon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcf7f65ee4caa33a4d5430d34dd5b581b</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun steps in a can of red paint, and his resulting red hoof makes him a style icon on the farm. Before long, the rest of the flock try their own new looks and soon steal the limelight. As the outfits become more and more outrageous, Shaun wonders if less might sometimes be more.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5311608370a06605a09997e8b42e43c8</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>An AI accidentally connects to Grizzy?s stuffed teddy bear, which comes to life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde01d3fb2c717f9ad8f439d98c2db79a</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The annual town-wide Hide &amp; Seek contest is here! The family always hides together, but Girl points out that Boy stinks at hiding and is bound to make them lose. Nobody else minds, but Ace Hider Girl decides to go it alone, leaving her family at the mercy of the relentless seeker, Wanda! Will Girl realize the error of her ways and lead her family to victory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa62483ec1128c5362231112f093a148d</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When tasked with the simple quest of building a flat-packed wardrobe, the heroes fail to read the instructions and are whirled into a wonky world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb7deb542b557edde37b8d10af30afbd6</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When a virus that turns people into cakes spreads through headquarters, the agents try to contain the outbreak.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4a329d5a37f8993e68969187c33427d3</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents compete to win Agents of the Month.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p61bc6e6ceb89a982bef9ccf1d8d95e64</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>In order to earn her final Girl Campers badge, Courtney must win Gwen's friendship.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa5a28eb9c675a1197f3cf39c1f63fea2</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and her superheroes face Penalteam.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p60a263686440410e7668a161b78caeec</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko, Roy and Dot finally find Kleavor of the Six Heroes - and it wants to battle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p73e5b5f7499b291235e01e0a835bf146</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Home Sweet Rome</title>
    <desc>Lucy starts school in Rome, and her new pop star stepmum wants her to call her 'mum'.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a21fd9f65fa6df2e440c7c104cfce6f</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe faces stiff competition in a final performance but are left shocked when they discover a staggering revelation from a former teammate. TNS makes a decision about their final performance that alters their dance careers forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p183799364a06bb04831d86b4a3fdf4d4</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>10 July 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
