<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>In this episode, find out how to control a balloon, witness gravity roll an object uphill, discover the world?s blackest paint, and meet someone who can see 100 million colours.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p595debd333a65e2933757654ae415ac6</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 11:40AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 11:55AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. Superhero Slippy Nana sort of saves a peach from a terrifying ordeal, Count Grape-ula strikes an unsuspecting victim, the maki and iso ambush a suspicious nigiri in a ninja sushi attack, deep in the back of the mouldy fridge, Frankfurter's monster comes to life, and the conjoined cherries attempt to start a band in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9748f75b43daf711134cae9dde0e143</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 11:55AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 12:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A look at the deadliest dynasties and how they came to, and then held on to, power. Witness Aggrippina's deadly recipes for success and Napoleon's needy sister, how the Lancastrians and the Yorkists came together (ish) for Love Day, how to stage a Russian coup, and how our royal family, the Windsors, came to change their family name to something a little 'less German'.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a18e7747aa740017c4913b5d3d9412e</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 12:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 12:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>History buff Hector from Wigan is a huge fan of William Shakespeare. He needs a space of his own where he can store all his history books, write plays and enjoy his hero?s works.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56419dd18492f3b2b04d21c575ea2426</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 12:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 01:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>With Andy?s mum getting injured, Ruby needs a new doubles partner for a tennis tournament. Mac faces his fears to unearth a secret tennis talent and take to the court once again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p76fa4297d0a825447b4f2bb6b8f69558</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 01:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 01:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>At the Go Jet Academy, Ubercorn has found an old map that leads to the GO Dome of the Ancients. This mysterious dome was built by the first ever Go Jetters and has been lost for hundreds of years. With Foz at the helm with his expert map-reading skills, the Go Jetters take to the Truckster to follow the map and find the ancient dome. But Grandmaster Glitch, being sneaky as usual, takes a photo of the Go Jetters' map and tries to find the dome himself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9455e3818cdc28f07b347c8e68183841</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 01:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 01:25PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Ammon gets spooked by a tiny insect, but overcomes her fear to rescue Cosima and Big Lizard from the rapids.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd693c844fa14f83a47177387cbb407b3</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 01:25PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 01:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Only Danger Mouse can save the world from chaos when the Baron stops the world spinning with a plague of traffic lights.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb74677422bfaddaf06495faaf5c7c649</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 01:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 01:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse must fight his own urge to be awesome to stop the world turning into a gigantic intergalactic tourist attraction. Attempting to prove his theory that what the world always needs is a hero, Danger Mouse fights off what appears to be an alien invasion of Earth - but his inflated ego soon becomes the real intergalactic threat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d43d2ca6490ff7c844b2a28644f5408</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 01:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 01:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>Simon is taking Jess out for a birthday dinner, so Gramps is on babysitting duty. He's brought along Mr Willow's dogs, Trevor and Violet, for the evening. They look just like Waffle, and during a game of hide-and-sing the dogs all hide next door, causing confusion and chaos for poor Mrs Hobbs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p699e3885dfa1b3a90b791ff56ec60171</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 01:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 02:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>It?s Merry Sprouty Day, and everyone is waiting for Sprouty Claus, who is bringing presents to all the good fruit and veggies. However, Evil Pea has an evil plan - to steal the presents for herself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p02376648809bf3bca99de61b046627db</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 02:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 02:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Deep in the caverns below Beanotown town hall, a mysterious species of over-sized hamsters may or may not exist, so may or may not be at risk of being hunted down and turned into fluffy slippers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbd0702cc5afebf8a17005c88036a955a</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 02:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 02:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Miss Mistry and Mrs Creecher clash over the best way to teach Class 3C about butterflies. The gang just want to get through the lesson so they can get out of school in time for a Grizzly Griller Wildlife Event.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f724fc607801733f58ba35ac017e5a6</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 02:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 02:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Only wood elves have ever defeated the mighty Eye of Vernon hat, so when the Riddlemaster wears the eye to take over the forest, the heroes quest to Wood Elf Wood to get help. However, Twinkle really doesn?t want to, as wood elves are so stuck up! Struggling to contain her irritation with their high-and-mighty ways, Twinkle still manages to offend them, and the heroes wonder how they will ever save the forest now.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32df456943a31359aa3e76648f081c8f</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 02:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 02:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A school girl orders a wish-granting vase so she doesn't have to go to school, but the Ninjas must face a series of tests set by the vase's guardian in order to get it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6b01e1206010854040758ec2d81ae7d</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 02:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 03:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Drama series. Ryan gets an unexpected text from Harry - it seems that things are going wrong in Harry's foster placement, and it falls to Ryan to rescue him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa19e6a2ebf8920ed1a7b453d1e5ad752</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 03:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 03:35PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories goes pear-shaped in an explorers special, meeting Christopher Columbus as he tries to teach a class that the world is indeed shaped like a pear. On the strict instructions of Emperor Nero, some hapless Roman centurions are quite literally stuck in the mud, searching for the source of the Nile. And intrepid Arctic explorer Peter Freuchen has to dig his way out of the snow with a frozen poo. From the Vikings' first small steps on American soil to humankind's first giant leaps on the moon, join Horrible Histories on this epic adventure.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9b6145f014cdd5e65d8cddeaf428dd46</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 03:35PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 04:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A special show featuring some of history?s greatest firsts, including the first ever library, Olympic Games, people on the moon and rat roller-skating on TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe595a876ef9e17bc0b058bb214d6279</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 04:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 04:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Miss Mistry arranges to tag along with Dennis and the gang after school, in an attempt to enhance her teaching skills and prevent school governor Pfooflepfeffer from banning her beloved teaching magazine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7390c9ba105b7ed1875a12a98670c204</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 04:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 04:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse goes undercover as the fifth member of Quark's mega-popular boy band, discovering his inner performer and a musical plot to destroy the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p77a97761345f53edbf51556bc28c35eb</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 04:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 05:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas are delighted to be reunited with their old nanny when she calls on their delivery service. Together they reminisce about the day they discovered their powers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p694693e8839c1b91925731ad9b2cef3a</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 05:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 05:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings organise a dance contest, where the first prize is a jar of YUMMY.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2965ff6b516bd699e323a4cefaef7512</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 05:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 05:20PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After her siblings accidentally insult her dreams of being a pop star, Cheese is bonked on the head and starts to believe she's a huge celebrity! Mouse says they all must play along, because if they ruin the illusion then there's a chance Cheese could go bonkers. Cheese turns into a diva, making outrageous demands from her siblings, and soon enough they're sick of it. But when they learn she was duping them all along, they set out to teach her a lesson..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4540d9337e6bd866504e38a486ddadec</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 05:20PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Stinkweasel drops a rain of yukkiness onto the forest, the Fairy Squad, with their excellent flying skills, decide they are the ones for the job. However, Hoofius insists this should be their quest, even if he does hate ick! And when the Fairy Squad get their wings gunked and are unable to fly, the heroes can resume their quest to end Stinkweasel?s reign of stinky nonsense - no flying required.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d85af1ed37a16cec54b2e5a529e9bbc</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 05:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Oona tells the story of when she switched bodies with a fly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p22925506da8094ca8edb1d14348f8800</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 05:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 05:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When Ms O leaves to conduct a super-secret mission, the agents compete to figure out who is in charge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p869126efa5973de5da9e29546dc380d7</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 05:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 06:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen is excited to have a new snowsuit but annoys his friends when he puts it to the test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdac2b4a6b032dffb5c7d92b6dcf774df</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 06:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 06:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>The kwamis? choice is transforming Paris.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67bc963b830482a39833a67eae184781</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 06:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 06:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Friede visits his former workplace to look for clues about the mystery behind Terapagos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c3dda388bac2abac98c77251721d451</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 06:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 07:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle wants to win first prize at her school's sports day. However, she gets paired with Roland, who refuses to take part, and her magic accidentally makes him super strong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8594fcb13a3ba08d43e7d627d93cd4f</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 07:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 07:25PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. The Next Step Dance Studio holds auditions for the ten dancers in A-Troupe that could take the studio to regionals later in the year. With the arrival of an amazing new dancer, no performer's spot is guaranteed.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p614827c6649ab8cb730cb83905be7444</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 07:25PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>02 May 2025 07:50PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy discovers a special lamp that can compact organic elements.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db012894fcac6a72802b96de04dbf13</image>
    <start>02 May 2025 07:50PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 06:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 06:30AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 08:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The farmer is trying to impress his new date by cooking her a romantic dinner. Unfortunately, the farmer can't cook and Bitzer is a useless maitre d'. Can Shaun and the flock save the day when they take over the catering behind the scenes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p00f857a42afb3e6f4a167aa40ab36094</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 08:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 08:10AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>In order to stop a deranged Victorian time-travelling chimp from uninventing the world, Danger Mouse and Penfold must arrive in the past just before the nick of time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb89086a78e1589c68cd9ddbc5eb06285</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 08:10AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 08:20AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Gnasher becomes the star of an action movie, playing Grizzly's on-screen sidekick. But filming keeps him and Dennis apart, leaving Dennis feeling lonely. Could Dennis and Gnasher really become Grizzly and Gnasher.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf69b7bfa9708ece3ec2df8941e20525f</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 08:20AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 08:35AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids are excited about attending spy camp! However, their trainer is a bit of a dud, and the siblings are disappointed not to learn anything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p098a1bcf2cc8f81eee03999d57daf28a</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 08:35AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 08:45AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbe566e9cb927a31905e0c8c379d2dfda</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 08:45AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 08:55AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A Lemming finds a mysterious mask that endows him with the power of telekinesis.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peecc469e064293cb3826d2ecd69c6307</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 08:55AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 09:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy chases after the Lemmings and the jar of Yummy in their remote-controlled car.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p92aff3c434c1be5d19dc5f8fd5c7244c</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 09:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 09:10AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Ms O gets kicked out of her office due to odd infestations.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80724e8b7f321877bdcd9ced9537becb</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 09:10AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 09:20AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom draws the short cheese straw and, rather than join her friends on a picnic, she has to take a magic wand to the recycling centre. Faced with a long queue and a rumbly tummy, Blossom decides that life is too short for recycling - with disastrous consequences. The heroes must skip their picnic and go on a quest to save the forest from the magical mess Blossom has gotten them into.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38db6a019d90d683a5c507a27c6477df</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 09:20AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 09:35AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve goes in search of the deadliest cats in Africa in the carnivore capital of Zambia. He gets up close to the rulers of the Savannah - the lions and leopards.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcb8030afcc5bc05bed71d47079401638</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 09:35AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 10:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about cities, the countryside, and join our bus tour of the UK.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p29a4735a9adbbb421b2435f938356635</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 10:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 10:25AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>Looking to help protect the planet, Cam, Tyler and Aaron take inspiration from the zoo?s animal eco-heroes, including pygmy marmosets, Amur tigers and orangutans.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe74b7e32ca68358013cf2fa1dead5e7b</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 10:25AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 10:45AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Two students put their best feet forward as they audition to dance at school. For Year 8 Harvey its his big dream. And how the sound of gongs can help some of the students de-stress.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa1629cc473d2addc7d647ddfb10841c3</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 10:45AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 11:10AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Art Ninja</title>
    <desc>Ricky's nan has bought him some driving lessons because she thinks he's too old to ride a skateboard. Unfortunately Ricky's not keen and despite the best efforts of his friends and family he won't budge out of neutral. The art is still full-throttle though, with a self-propelling car and a human moped animation, and when they get to the driving centre, Ricky makes epic 3D art with traffic cones that will definitely pass the test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p380cfd5853a6b55901dffe70bb8bf93e</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 11:10AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 11:40AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>In this episode, find out how to make ice in an instant, give the classic paper plane a makeover, test reaction times with a numbers brain teaser and explore the eco-friendly future of homes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11cc5ec9095b062e9fa14eec97454823</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 11:40AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 11:55AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>Toast soldiers take to the skies in their toast-rack helicopter, Maki and Iso ambush a suspicious Nigiri in a ninja sushi attack, intrepid star bar attempts an ambitious trip to the moon, Frankfurter's monster comes to life in the back of the mouldy fridge and Stunt Tomato amazes the judges with a death-defying magic trick.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc4fa2dcdd91d3aae2ea1617ead3cc67</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 11:55AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 12:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories presents a collection of some of history's finest songs, as Rattus attempts to put together his own festival (the delightfully named Glastonsmelly). From singing poos to tuneful Warlords, there's something for all musical tastes, and Rattus has somehow also roped Brad from The Vamps in to help him out, although rather than playing live on the main stage, Brad's role seems to be more about unblocking the toilets just behind it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p97fc0c68a8cc6ce158f83c3adf1cf960</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 12:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 12:25PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Angel from London is an aspiring tap dancer who has nowhere to practise her moves. She is always scuffing her mum?s floors and annoying her brother with the noise. She needs a tip-top tap dance space where she can train properly, store her costumes and display her medals.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa65b8dd6e224d29f6d3a9d0a6cc891e4</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 12:25PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 12:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Attempting to become young again, Whiff accidentally turns the Odd Socks into babies! With Whiff as their babysitter, how will the baby-faced band do an interview and play a gig.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd14a034b0e534d441e226129c8a7bd4c</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 12:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 01:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>Grandmaster Glitch's Grimbots really need some cuddles, so it's down to Glitch to find them a new teddy bear! Glitch knows that bears live in Ontario in Canada, so he heads there to try and find a nice cuddly bear. Meanwhile, the Go Jetters are also in Canada competing in the Ontario lumberjack championships.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe8b43f74c61ec32e68288774ff32b591</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 01:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 01:25PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Big Lizard and Cosima undertake an exciting night-time mission rehoming a friendly slug that's taken residence in Cosima's bedroom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p43e358e4c47eb11a7979b8644394126c</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 01:25PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 01:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. When the Baron rearranges the countries of the world, Danger Mouse reluctantly joins forces with his American counterpart Jeopardy Mouse and takes New Zealand for a spin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p360a767bfafedebd93220d5ac0d52736</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 01:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 01:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When an old enemy returns, Colonel K must come out of retirement to save the world from an outbreak of rudeness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2e371392bd76d59ab61f378473f577e</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 01:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 01:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>Waffle learns that the summer holidays will soon be over and Evie will be going to school. Determined not to be left alone, Waffle hatches a plan to keep the family at home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcd26ff17cf3207ab517200b58ea54168</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 01:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 02:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>It's Merry Sprouty Day, but Evil Pea jumps onto Sprouty Claus's train and steals all the presents for herself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac7c6b855314c72b282c1b9d4de26f3a</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 02:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 02:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface is secretly doing underpants laundry chores for Walter, hoping to help Dennis save up some cash. He urges the gang to audition for a replacement Pieface to make up for his mysterious absence.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0ced6f09c8a135c0107ac2cf9c4bc6b</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 02:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 02:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Olive surprises herself and everyone around her by actually becoming a good cook, Dr Pfooflepfeffer tries to cash in by turning the school canteen into an exclusive and super-expensive dining experience.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdee355ef68772da8fcf20dd134fad956</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 02:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 02:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes have found the Wishing Trident, which will help them on their quest to prevent the summoning of the legendary two-headed dragon, Iceburn. The problem is, Blossom has used one wish by mistake, and Herbert has accidentally used a second one. Now the heroes are left to defeat the dragon using only one wish, a never-ending ice cream cone (with sprinkles) and a giant spicy sausage hat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf940465ee4740a280d4541c1e5c9723d</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 02:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 02:50PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A witch orders a mango to finish off her monster soup. However, when Konpeki greedily gobbles up the soup, Kiro and the witch must take on a daring rescue mission.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11f12531c4146a9d46ec97a0b0025fe5</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 02:50PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 03:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Drama series. Johnny has to face down his fear to protect his family when his violent stepfather gets out of prison.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p15f1201905177d4ba57f3ae15ba44e39</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 03:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 03:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories pays tribute to Formidable Florence Nightingale, The Lady with the Lamp (just don't let Florence hear you calling her that!) The programme charts how Florence revolutionised medicine and the treatment of the sick during the Crimean War, but also how she also unwittingly sparked the public's desire for trinkets and tat featuring her image. Elsewhere, there's the bizarre practice of Victorian war tourism (tea, cake and carnage), a look at some Embarrassing Victorian Bodies, and a visit to Mary Seacole's British Hotel.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b6032e9e63619e0a9b8ccd2332fc235</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 03:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 04:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Protests about inequality or environmental damage are common today, but how have people protested in the past? Emmeline Pankhurst is our guide through this history of protest, from Cato the Younger?s talkative protest in ancient Rome to the cheese riots of 18th-century Nottingham. Also, how will the Luddites cope with the newfangled technology of a video call.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa4ea23a82ebb60f9e87f00e708ba6aba</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 04:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 04:20PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s Pieface?s turn to look after the class hamster, Space Captain Harrison McScruff-Butt. His own self doubt and Walter?s resolve to sabotage him lead to a rescue mission to free Scruff-Butt from Walter?s mansion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p030b103e478730d5108a53c51e2b4099</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 04:20PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 04:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang convince Mrs Creecher that Monday is actually Sunday in the hope of extending their weekend.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9b0399bee9f8bf2e99c10b04c972e7fe</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 04:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 04:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse must battle Quark again, but this time in the weirdest and most dangerous of places: Penfold's dreams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef370659f818656714ea292bc7ca5e2e</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 04:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 04:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Two gnomes entrust the Ninjas to find them cloth so that they can make trousers for a giant and his upcoming dance competition. However, finding a giant-sized piece of cloth proves to be more difficult than they thought.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21ff23841c7005414f98171a0b5a05fb</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 04:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 05:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A block containing Grizzy and the Lemmings' ancestors cracks during their fight.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paab6bbb0e446ab132a7752a6e81c4f9e</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 05:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 05:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Boy, Girl and Cheese learn that their animal siblings have a tough time going through life with their unwieldy tails, they want to understand what it's like. So Mouse builds them mechanical tails to wear, and the three soon learn just how hard it is to do simple tasks. However, they come to master their tails well enough to attend the Curling Tail festival, where all tailed animals celebrate themselves. But when the kids turn their tails to full power to fit in better, they go haywire! They're now in danger of ruining the festival and being discovered as frauds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p017af7c6567e02c660ba97f085ca58db</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 05:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert has invented a new contraption to help him fly using an old set of bagpipes. The 'Herbecopter', as Herbert likes to call it, is rather noisy but extremely effective, and Twinkle is unhappy at no longer being the only flying hero. So, when the heroes quest to get Friendlyface?s priceless locket back from a dragon, Twinkle and Herbert become extremely competitive and risk completely failing the quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa955ab16670c700cec4ca1249af0b548</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 05:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Otis and Olympia are stuck with a new robot partner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf79ba2a92eacf194943621245c0db54</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 05:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 05:50PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan stages a small coup to oust Courtney as their new official class fire officer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p36154bf09ccd9ec599297aaf44b3a88a</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 05:50PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 06:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel takes a trip to Tokyo to go behind the scenes at the world-famous Pok?mon studios. He also tries sumo wrestling, visits a robot caf?, takes on the ultimate snack challenge and attempts to make sushi. Plus, find out how to freshen up your lunch box Pikachu style.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8a2908e9ff4fe5c4295858ed6fba81ac</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 06:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 06:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds a sceptre that covers anything it touches in gold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd43331ff073897731dc5a23ef100236f</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 06:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 06:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko, Roy and Dot are back at Naranja Academy in time to battle the Elite Four.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a5a23be5f55cb9ffc635519197cefd9</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 06:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 07:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Swumpy sneaks into school, and Pickle accidentally makes him super clever so that she comes top in her test! This backfires when she has to represent the school in a maths competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9907bc19c58d6741f49861caa644601d</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 07:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 07:25PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. The members of A-Troupe are chosen and one of the best dancers doesn't make the cut. Emily's position as dance captain is threatened when another dancer is also invited to audition for the position.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5b1d01d29d1c74486534162def20b600</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 07:25PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>03 May 2025 07:50PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The extraordinary animals from a tablet game come to life after the device explodes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3a27aae2aea7f6befb2d2839f29139f</image>
    <start>03 May 2025 07:50PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 06:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 06:30AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 08:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun and Bitzer work together to track down a nut-stealing culprit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4c55caa6a4f618eb17f93b1b87f322e6</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 08:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 08:10AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse is forced to choose between dedication to duty and friendship when he battles the Baron in his underwater Toadlantis base.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0e99707170c40698f2e2e60ec597982e</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 08:10AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 08:20AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang find out that JJ has a set of pre-match good luck rituals. In the run-up to an important Blamjitsu event, Walter deviously throws bad luck omens into JJ?s path, threatening her chances of success.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3c30a8458c845f0ca547fee6492f559c</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 08:20AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 08:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids hold a yard sale but can?t bear giving away their childhood possessions, so they try to pull off a heist to retrieve it all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p425c14d0b2db2fc8fd10ee4ad711c371</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 08:30AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 08:45AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p613cc126c45dfadcd4fa7ad405839413</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 08:45AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 08:50AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Twin sisters ask the Ninjas to help them find them another flying rug to replace the one that they ripped, but it's Konpeki?s pet snails who save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p118baf0490ac38ef40eebdb7e358d718</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 08:50AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 09:05AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. When Ms O gets trapped in a mirror, an opposite Ms O enters the real world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b48182adb66613b0fc536f363f44734</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 09:05AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 09:15AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are lured away by a cloaked figure to compete for the title of Quester of the Year, leaving the forest with no-one to protect its scones.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p26e2fcb5c6b4f009308c94a8aaa4a124</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 09:15AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 09:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face agent Roger - aka Rogercop.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p15e39a2a896d235591996531b9052c11</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 09:30AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 09:50AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Myl?ne - aka Horrificator.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe5adb556e7e067e1606f1775d205f689</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 09:50AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 10:15AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon: XY</title>
    <desc>The final day of the summer camp, with entry into the hall of fame for the winning team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e40edb65eafb20b7aa71532d139000b</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 10:15AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 10:35AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Fury prank Cyclone, who thinks she is filming an animal-themed exercise video dressed as a turtle. The other Gladiators have fun pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14568fca763cea3c2d50d63ef4e99370</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 10:35AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 10:50AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play marbles, and it's driving Grizzy crazy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6da67b82a65bfa51ab80ff34f6cbd6a4</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 10:50AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 11:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy exchanges his indifferent fish with the Lemmings' affectionate and lively fish.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p07e8c90f4bc95e6cc138af9db789ccd7</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 11:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 11:05AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Dog and Cat enjoy a collar-free lifestyle, until an animal-control officer thinks they are strays! Together, they must escape the only place worse than the vet - the pound.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p66b1230c6754e619942b53f531c1c413</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 11:05AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 11:20AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After Mouse underestimates Cat, she figures out how to make his time machine work. After getting stranded in prehistoric times, they have to figure out how to get back home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6acd0d4f1e391e9107c90e276ca84339</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 11:20AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 11:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Courtney challenges Owen and Jude to be the next social media star, with little success.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6ccccb2b9a1b1595dc58abdcbfafd582</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 11:30AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 11:40AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth and Leshawna try to outdo each other with fake injuries to gain more attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe635ab159f06f65d1cb8af629461d176</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 11:40AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 11:50AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Adam and Joe become busy bees for a gunge-fuelled challenge ? who will collect the most nectar and win Callum?s ultimate respect.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1bcc08b0a5bc2e62651b6a15b1544e1a</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 11:50AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 12:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Attempting to shake things up in the school, Andy introduces Swapsies Day. However, when Emerald calls asking for a song to be recorded that day, Andy?s idea backfires dramatically.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p66b08333c40ad36d74888b14f94f2706</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 12:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 12:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel takes a trip to Tokyo to go behind the scenes at the world-famous Pok?mon studios. He also tries sumo wrestling, visits a robot caf?, takes on the ultimate snack challenge and attempts to make sushi. Plus, find out how to freshen up your lunch box Pikachu style.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8a2908e9ff4fe5c4295858ed6fba81ac</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 12:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 12:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When a museum has square objects stolen and two villains obsessed with triangles are seemingly involved, Orli and Ozzie investigate how the villains can be related to the crime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7ad21f144964ec3ff28fb79cca4f8db2</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 12:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 01:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Villain Miss Information is using graphs to spread falsehoods about Odd Squad, which is leading to the public not trusting them. Can Captain O get the public back on side.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81bd195210835185fd3d564b62fdc1a6</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 01:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 01:20PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>With mum away with Jim, Clanger persuades Conor and Aoife to throw a party. Aoife's attempts to impress Jamie backfire when she is tricked by Jessica and pranked by Clanger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd50c8946fd281f833fb6db7516d6f363</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 01:20PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 01:50PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>It?s the season finale, and the Vipers could get promoted! However, Aoife is headhunted for county trials - can she do both and make it to the big final against arch-rivals the Comets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf75da12a774401b907e62f945fb6549e</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 01:50PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 02:20PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Famous monk St Augustine struggles to introduce Christianity to Saxon England, Stuart diarist Samuel Pepys annoys the smartest men in Britain, we witness a daring escape from the Tower of London, and Joan of Arc's story is quite an unusual one for a teenage girl.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8857d6dba2ac878a4eb82709c7fecf4b</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 02:20PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 02:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>With Astra suspended, Hannah makes the impossible decision to leave. Can her friends convince her to stay.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc3693098adcc48114cd1a677f363492</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 02:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 03:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Martha?s mum is back and as unimpressed as ever! Miss Marmaduke foolishly entrusts the others to help prove that Cranmede is an exceptional school.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31d161f9fa4e8c287d35a2f5e27a34f6</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 03:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 03:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Keira wonders if all her dreams could come true as her parents decide they want to foster Chelsey. Phoenix returns to the DG with a secret, and Brodie needs to confess his true feelings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe70902add08c31cec78c6b71fd4e7b7</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 03:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 04:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth sets out to get rid of all their old toys, hoping Chef will buy the new toy she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65f80c82e11fb083e3d726fe80ab11f0</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 04:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 04:20PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When the last page of the story-time book is lost, Gwen steps in to create the ending.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11fb197af7d8998c4056abf304e72828</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 04:20PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 04:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth shares her slime recipe with her friends, and together they create a goo monster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p456343ae47a574c8929254e0297f6774</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 04:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 04:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse's uncontrollable laughter annoys a race of clown aliens so much that they invade Earth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p71ad5c62d44a3d366830c3351b73c1ce</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 04:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 04:50PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse and the Baron are forced to team up in order to defeat a cheese-obsessed villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc640fda27059d028e627a20d12c99338</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 04:50PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 05:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse has to face his only fear when Penfold accidentally awakens a gigantic World Wide Spider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfdab1c9194bfa295bffcbe93ab6fe774</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 05:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 05:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>A dog show is coming up, and cool prizes are given to the winning dog and its trainer. Cheese, Girl and Mouse all have great ideas for how to train Dog for the grand finale. And if Dog picks one of their finales, that sibling gets to be the trainer who shares in the prize! Boy also wants to help but gets shunned for having a less impressive idea on how to win. The contest arrives, but Dog is torn when it comes to his finale. Whose idea does he choose? Can Boy jump in with his 'unimpressive' idea and help save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbdaeec7627628d03ca2742675670ed96</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 05:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After her siblings accidentally insult her dreams of being a pop star, Cheese is bonked on the head and starts to believe she's a huge celebrity! Mouse says they all must play along, because if they ruin the illusion then there's a chance Cheese could go bonkers. Cheese turns into a diva, making outrageous demands from her siblings, and soon enough they're sick of it. But when they learn she was duping them all along, they set out to teach her a lesson..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4540d9337e6bd866504e38a486ddadec</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 05:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Boy, Girl and Cheese learn that their animal siblings have a tough time going through life with their unwieldy tails, they want to understand what it's like. So Mouse builds them mechanical tails to wear, and the three soon learn just how hard it is to do simple tasks. However, they come to master their tails well enough to attend the Curling Tail festival, where all tailed animals celebrate themselves. But when the kids turn their tails to full power to fit in better, they go haywire! They're now in danger of ruining the festival and being discovered as frauds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p017af7c6567e02c660ba97f085ca58db</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 05:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 05:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy struggles to pick coconuts, but the Lemmings find a magic conch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe790119cb595cbdc802925b6696f6fe0</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 05:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 06:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>It's time for the racket game, where big scores mean big prizes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb4876fa452c0f93c5471f450963b20c9</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 06:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 06:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings adopt a cute insect that eats wood. And what's made of wood? The cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pccf019a4a8ccbb39739735ecabb2e164</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 06:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 06:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Much to Trevor?s irritation, a rare phoenix woodpecker takes a liking to him - so he demands an immediate quest to return the bird to its real home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd460f05ee8f6efe98ada93b746aa74d</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 06:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 06:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle feels she is being taken for granted by the other heroes, so she joins the Fairy Squad when they arrive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa88b9a6c763d7c35c89b5f246f002e9f</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 06:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 06:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The tired heroes must quest to find out and stop whatever is making the loud wailing noise that has kept the residents of the forest up all night.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe737598843036feb34240aa725c51adc</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 06:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 06:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Furry-faced video filters torment Mansour's parents, until Mansour outsmarts Blink.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pec940517943c869d9bc9d688930eaaf3</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 06:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 07:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Blink goes on a rampage, taking over the museum?s robotic Stone Age animal exhibits.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1a868fd59f3fe01ba8243234b5df58c3</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 07:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 07:20PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>Release the hounds! Campers are hunted by a pack of fearsome attack dogs... and one pug.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6b6bb0170f1530fcddc459da67e91a0a</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 07:20PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>04 May 2025 07:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Fury prank Cyclone, who thinks she is filming an animal-themed exercise video dressed as a turtle. The other Gladiators have fun pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14568fca763cea3c2d50d63ef4e99370</image>
    <start>04 May 2025 07:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 06:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 06:30AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 08:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Bitzer misuses a drone when he tries to avoid carrying out work on the farm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcd11eb044caf8f67e02610ba8ec325f6</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 08:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 08:10AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse's attempts at gardening lead to a gigantic Welsh space plant taking over the world and an attack of intergalactic bees. Only Penfold's jam obsession can save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf6aa3114eba7d49e15d1d978b0570ee7</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 08:10AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 08:20AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>While helping Sergeant Slipper prove that he has what it takes to remain Beanotown?s policeman, the gang unknowingly become entangled in Doctor Pfooflepfeffer?s real theft.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc05891fb066c59115954c3de0a3c01f0</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 08:20AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 08:35AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Dog invents a gadget that allows him to play fetch alone, Cheese is convinced it will be a runaway success. However, Mouse is desperate to hold on to his place as family inventor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p826fff1f6187bd89705e85903edac68e</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 08:35AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 08:45AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14e789b8e2ffdf7cd2af5508f2911d6a</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 08:45AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 08:50AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A trainee witch asks the Ninjas to find her a cat so she can pass her magic exam. However, getting the easily frightened kitten to participate proves to be a challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4057a11885fce1ebd8e72996ee149c8e</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 08:50AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 09:05AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents try to resolve a disagreement between Ms O and Oksana.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pec925f8ad8786901c400467620fa98d3</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 09:05AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 09:20AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>To avoid Herbert?s surprise visits via his tunnels in the Big Birch, the other heroes take any quest and must deal with an angry plant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1712e7d54bc565d7f40c59dd3788f999</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 09:20AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 09:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A rocket carries the cabin into space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c78219ad43711cd65fcc2202b9c6992</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 09:30AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 09:40AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Penny Rolling - aka Troublemaker.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb14d5489e1ce5bd456da71f810f8d288</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 09:40AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 10:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel takes a trip to Tokyo to go behind the scenes at the world-famous Pok?mon studios. He also tries sumo wrestling, visits a robot caf?, takes on the ultimate snack challenge and attempts to make sushi. Plus, find out how to freshen up your lunch box Pikachu style.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8a2908e9ff4fe5c4295858ed6fba81ac</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 10:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 10:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Diamond when the guest on a live TV show can?t stop pumping! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes, pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p124aa384cfc9de9b57a6c0777805b147</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 10:30AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 10:45AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>4 O'Clock Club</title>
    <desc>Darnesh discovers his locker is haunted by a hungry ghost with a sweet tooth. Meanwhile Eli and Fleur learn to tango, but the dance of love could spell the end of their friendship.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b68f51d9e5990df2b9cc37ec9ef0374</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 10:45AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 11:15AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Stuff is going missing in the leisure centre. As head of security, Joy tasks Mick with getting to the bottom of it. That means spending a night in the leisure centre all alone, or with Danny - Mick isn?t sure what?s worse. Together the boys vow to keep an eye out and get to the bottom of this mystery once and for all. However, with a sleepwalking Joy prowling the corridors it seems like everyone is going to get more than they bargained for in the morning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa58831c654ceeb548103d5ac60ccb390</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 11:15AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 11:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>There?s a horrible snotty fever going around the leisure centre and it?s catching fast. To make matters worse it?s the day of the gymnastics competition. When the Pottsfield?s team get snotty it looks like their chances of winning anything are gone. However, Danny and Mick won?t let that happen - it?s time to jump into a leotard and show everyone what they?ve got.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11a083854ba0f37e3b866c65b4944455</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 11:30AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 11:40AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Finding themselves lost in the labyrinth backstage, the Odd Socks split up and face a race against time. Can they make it back to the stage in time to start the gig.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5cf095fcbf916f63d9b308580203c0d9</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 11:40AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 11:55AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>After a surprise visit from Blu?s gran reveals that Blu hasn?t told her that he?s in a band, the Odd Socks are forced into pretending that he is a lawyer. Can they keep up the lie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5aa9a6e71c043818970228f17a97e5e9</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 11:55AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 12:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve searches for deadly animals living in the capital of Suriname, from snakes in people's gardens to snail-catching kites and one of the deadliest snakes on earth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe4132eb31df163e9d473abb7ca294ba5</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 12:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 12:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to the Mexican island of Cabo Pulmo, where the people have worked tirelessly to bring their surrounding oceans back to life and make it a marine reserve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf3c3ce794d1e94b9e89b0164a58c3960</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 12:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 01:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>When Dr Chris realises that the horrendous cheesy smell in the lab is coming from Dr Xand?s feet, the race is on to find out why they are so pongy. Is it the feet, the sweat, the trainers?! Turns out it isn?t as simple as you might think! Elsewhere, Dr Dan and Dr Raf square up in Body Battles as they put their quad muscles to the test by trying to squat to lay an egg in a nest. Thankfully, Gladiator Dynamite is there to stop anyone cracking up and make sure that the loser gets in the ice bath. As we count down our Top 5 Silliest Named Body Parts, you can check if you have Greek feet and discover where you can find your ginglymus. In Doctors on Duty, Dr Xand goes to hospital with Maddox, who has an appointment at the cystic fibrosis clinic at the Royal Brompton. Elsewhere, Victoria has slipped and fallen on her arm at school, so she is at the emergency department in Edinburgh, while Sorin has cut his face after colliding with his classmate?s cat ear hairband.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62239a19d50e5c2eb6f68d4f4acdfcba</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 01:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 01:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Queen Victoria lovingly forces several of her children to go on historical first dates, Leopold Mozart retires his 18-year-old daughter aged 18, and the Brontes sing about sisterhood.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p19bcde4b63ea08d0b241ea2f8928180e</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 01:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 02:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>The history of our relationship with animals - Charles Darwin presents Yummy Planet, Elizabeth I?s menagerie has some 'lion trouble', and farting fish almost start a nuclear war.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1d25c8ac16820e5e90b774699e14ed5c</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 02:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 02:35PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Apollo prank Dynamite, turning her into a singing banana! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99a45e9399b5fa5991e3b3eb060bfd42</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 02:35PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 02:50PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Supervillain the Princess is determined to pinkify the world. Only Danger Mouse dressed as a little girl can save us.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd4b094d8f11489f1c0cea6bb5a7853fa</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 02:50PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 03:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. DM must save his reputation and the world when Squawkencluck's artificially intelligent defence supercomputer goes despotically insane.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p86269ad8e9039712e6dbdd1417cba059</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 03:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 03:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse has to face his only fear when Penfold accidentally awakens a gigantic World Wide Spider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfdab1c9194bfa295bffcbe93ab6fe774</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 03:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 03:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface is secretly doing underpants laundry chores for Walter, hoping to help Dennis save up some cash. He urges the gang to audition for a replacement Pieface to make up for his mysterious absence.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0ced6f09c8a135c0107ac2cf9c4bc6b</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 03:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 03:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s time for Gnasher?s annual bath, but the stinky hound will do anything to avoid the tub. Dennis and Gnasher go head to head in a town-wide game of cat and mouse ? or rather, tripe hound and wheelie bathtub.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cd3695300ecc962061ac4a3338675c2</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 03:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 03:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The after-school art club is under threat of imminent demolition. In trying to save the club, the gang end up on the trail of the mysterious undercover urban artist known only as Pranksy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p361a97fdcd2b35beabb23cae8c4b65d6</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 03:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 04:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Hoofius plays his grandfaun?s old magical panpipes, his friends do exactly what he asks them to do - perfect for leading a quest... or so he thinks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbada50b36a9303ac56775c369e7c2be0</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 04:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 04:20PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle feels she is being taken for granted by the other heroes, so she joins the Fairy Squad when they arrive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa88b9a6c763d7c35c89b5f246f002e9f</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 04:20PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 04:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The tired heroes must quest to find out and stop whatever is making the loud wailing noise that has kept the residents of the forest up all night.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe737598843036feb34240aa725c51adc</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 04:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 04:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover tai chi movements that generate balls of energy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1aee63413e5b2f680fc76aa287fd2d18</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 04:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 04:50PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings accidentally set off a mechanism in a tower.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e9cf14341b241a06302d7e7d3dc087a</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 04:50PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 05:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over the last jar of Yummy chocolate spread in the cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38276f1f8a2f9d717e4402bd81ba81b0</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 05:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 05:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom tries to prove Sledkin caused an explosion that injured a dragon in the Hidden World.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5893c8953f72743dceaa0c044872c377</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 05:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>D?Angelo struggles to keep a cool head and find a cure for the victims of an attack.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p727d57c1ee4b53ba2c81f655e4600c30</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 05:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>Ken is back, and it seems like everything is back to normal. However, when a famous photographer arrives to take pre-debut photos, the trainees realise they still have issues to work out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p25bb505ccc302d4d5e28e4c83cb31d06</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 05:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 06:20PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>With a thunderstorm raging outside and rehearsal time running out, Henry struggles to pick up the choreo for a nationals routine. Trying to help Henry, Summer finds their relationship tested. After the lights go out in the studio, Kingston, Ozzy, and Lily discover that someone shut the power off on purpose and everyone at the studio becomes a suspect. Heath and Izzy bond over their survivalist ways, much to Ozzy?s dismay.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa06c7fb87734892d28a257aad6cd1fc5</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 06:20PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 06:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>The Vipers are not getting along, so Aoife blags them onto a team-building weekend. The only thing is that it?s at school, military style and with the boys - what could go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p15dc335e196d0bebf4629f17a317b53c</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 06:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 07:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Alien zombies, space monks, a demon clown, an evil knight and a world record attempt -it's just another day at Cranmede Academy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a4f6570cbeeb3d53adb000b54c1d578</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 07:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>05 May 2025 07:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Diamond when the guest on a live TV show can?t stop pumping! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes, pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p124aa384cfc9de9b57a6c0777805b147</image>
    <start>05 May 2025 07:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 06:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 06:30AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 08:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Can Shaun rescue gluttonous goat Mowermouth before being harvested along with the maize.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdc76309ac0cb46f053b3a317a8e60795</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 08:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 08:10AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When all the other danger agents become supersmart due to a batch of genetically enhanced celery, Danger Mouse might need to find a new job.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd3564fbdb5d3af356c096d2505f6a6f2</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 08:10AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 08:20AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis needs to pull off a magnificent stunt to save the skate park from closure, so Gran gives him the skateboard of the legendary Kendo 360 to help. When the special board goes missing at the worst possible moment, Dennis needs to dig deep and realise that it's the skater and not the board that's important.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54738b714536b205261da7b9c907d809</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 08:20AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 08:35AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The CEO buys Jocko?s old amusement arcade and vows to tear it down. However, Boy loves the arcade and challenges her to an epic video game battle with the fate of the arcade at stake.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p841fc93c4ca27297d05e07073f8d029f</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 08:35AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 08:45AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2f9886b7bcc2633283b4deeef6faf959</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 08:45AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 08:55AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings take possession of a magic sceptre that has the ability to shrink objects.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p777d66872fcd3672633acf25cf19f79b</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 08:55AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 09:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy swipes the peanut reserves of the elephant playing with the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54036a52fcc54e05e7dec7e09578175a</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 09:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 09:10AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56daa2b3ab5c528d73d6bf96351ed71c</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 09:10AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 09:20AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>It?s been ages since their last quest, and the heroes are losing their edge, so Mr Friendlyface invents a strange and terrible monster that he says is stomping through the forest causing havoc, and sends the heroes on a fake quest to get rid of it. Friendlyface soon comes to regret his trickery when, with the heroes out of the way, the goblins decide to take over the forest for their jam jamboree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd73f5a342e51bd6aa4e1226b5b388fb</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 09:20AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 09:35AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to Zambia for the first time, where he hears hippo communication on a whole new level, spots a high-diving croc and meets some incredible sniffer dogs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3986f49991a9204dc06d5907226e9e8c</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 09:35AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 10:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 7-9 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about what humans are doing to the planet, as well as deforestation and plastic pollution.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82b6116374a43a5de5ff9bc8065361a9</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 10:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 10:25AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>Meet the zoo?s powerful animals as Sonika the Asiatic lioness gets a grip in a tug-of-war and Tyler takes on Marion the sulcata tortoise in a contest of strength.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d5c59a0ad274d349b9f50da51aaabe9</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 10:25AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 10:45AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Year 8 get their hands dirty in the school allotment, while Year 7?s green team focus on recycling.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p495d7d05db968f57df7bcf329657566e</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 10:45AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 11:10AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Art Ninja</title>
    <desc>Whilst looking after Gav's cat and Sarah's guinea pig, Ricky gets bitten and suddenly he can hear the pets talking! Not only that, they're gossiping about him. He also has to contend with the Grand Master making a kazoo and artist Joan Miro inspiring him to craft a 3D name sculpture, before heading to the Yorkshire Sculpture Park to make animal art really worth talking about.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0f6d021633bba6dd8752fbac9b9e74a</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 11:10AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 11:35AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Get ready for incredible experiments and mind-bending puzzles to impress your friends. Owain and Tilly are here to explore epic science tricks to try at home and showcase brand new technology innovations from around the world! In this episode, discover a cool coin-catching trick, find out how to make movie magic using the power of perspective, and learn a quick fix for filling that empty ice cream tub.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51d2024e820f4610e85bc3cf5be9a856</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 11:35AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 11:50AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Could you build a slide to the other side of the world? You would need to start in space, use the slippiest slide ever and make sure you have enough supplies before you go down it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c93e4b0e1fc4adb5f1d0842be1d0abe</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 11:50AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 12:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories presents our guide to Ancient Civilisations, featuring new sketches about Alexander the Great's first kiss, Emperor Nero's greatest hits, and how double parking in ancient times could result in being impaled, rather than fined. Also, Swill Gumbitz takes a look at Greek statues, the musical instrument that could make you poo yourself, and the evolution of bottom-wiping.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb061542a1366b2ec92cb4d193a65984</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 12:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 12:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Duncan from Glasgow is passionate about protecting orangutans and wants to raise awareness of their plight within his local community. He wants a den where he can hang out, learn more about his favourite primates and how to help them, and share his passion with friends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf7a107877c2eb098db94fe5f6e374e6a</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 12:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 12:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>After Moxy?s drums go missing, Andy concludes it was their rival band, Sandy and the Same Socks! Getting paranoid, a chase ensues as Andy accuses them of stealing everything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb25b473cf84269836f676090139fbcec</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 12:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 01:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>The Go Jetters travel to Algeria in north Africa to check out the ancient Timgad Ruins. Built by the Romans nearly 2,000 years ago, the city was built as a grid, with all the roads running in straight lines from north to south or from east to west. Meanwhile, Grandmaster Glitch's computer game controller has broken, so he is looking for a new one. When he sees the map of the Timgad Ruins on the ship's big screen, he realises that the grid layout makes it look just like a computer game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p213e7889d0e75493f644dcdba401341b</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 01:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 01:25PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Cosima and Big Lizard find some fascinatingly slippery fruit, but bringing it safely back to the ship is more challenging than they imagined.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f770807e1c9b4adae5c07afc1c11262</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 01:25PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 01:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. Whether it's a perilous voyage to the bottom of the sea or the piratey pursuit of a giant squid, the Octonauts leap into action. When a giant wave hurls creatures from the Amazon river up into the trees, the Octonauts must get them down safely without disturbing the poison dart frogs who live there.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3e12710ed136182630cc11e7be43c741</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 01:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 01:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The world is in jeopardy and the only thing that can save it is a 1,000ft Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7dcc9c255cb548ada924dfbdc51cc0cf</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 01:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 01:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>Miss Berrington, Evie's new school teacher, and teaching assistant Mr O'Donnell have come to meet Evie at home before term starts, and Waffle is under strict instructions to be on his best behaviour. But Waffle is teething, and won't stop chewing everything in sight.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p36588dda5dcc56e67db828b9ab3c85b0</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 01:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 02:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Evil Pea has trapped Supertato and replaced him with an evil robot lookalike called Robotato. She has programmed it to do mean things in order to destroy Supertato's reputation so that she can take over the supermarket. Luckily, Carrot senses something's amiss and eventually figures out what's happened. She frees Supertato just in time for him to stop Robotato from carrying out Pea's meanest command yet: splatting everyone with a giant cream pie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7196de0e9b3b637207465499c7d26c68</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 02:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 02:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Professor von Screwtop gets mistaken for the new kid in school and joins Class 3C for the day. Rubi is so embarrassed at her dad?s antics that she resorts to pranking to get him into trouble and out of the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p060c373a4ae75d174dc60fc03089f42e</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 02:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 02:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>JJ applies for an elite sporting school. However, not realising it's miles away from Beanotown, he needs to do badly in the sporting assessment to get out of it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p25f8c727ad716ff6332cb203cd3afeab</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 02:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 02:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom draws the short cheese straw and, rather than join her friends on a picnic, she has to take a magic wand to the recycling centre. Faced with a long queue and a rumbly tummy, Blossom decides that life is too short for recycling - with disastrous consequences. The heroes must skip their picnic and go on a quest to save the forest from the magical mess Blossom has gotten them into.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38db6a019d90d683a5c507a27c6477df</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 02:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 02:50PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Yin and Yang are missing one brick to finish the Great Wall of China. With the minister quickly approaching to see the completed wall, Yang orders a brick from the Ninjas.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3d4e0f4f517467e77515c8efbc52ce0b</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 02:50PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 03:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Drama series. A new girl called Sasha stops off on her way to a secure home and causes chaos. Can the Dumping Ground handle her bad behaviour.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf47c848d3d6b975d9ed9348f65817f1b</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 03:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 03:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Eldon runs a chaotic group rehearsal, and Izzy learns an important leadership lesson. Meanwhile, Pete and Heath do everything in their power to look like dance captain material.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf7b1387b4b8af7734efce9f15eca26bf</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 03:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 03:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A look at how World War II played out on the home front, featuring Churchill's secret loo, the heroic 'ATA Girls' and German spies being caught out by their delicious sausages.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p34479d246837eb45065d27a320a85e07</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 03:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 04:20PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis can?t get Grizzly?s new animal training method to work on a wilful Gnasher. However, when they realise that Gnasher can use the method to get humans to obey him instead, they exploit this new power to the max.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p965cb1910091f1f086e689ad9c5309e4</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 04:20PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 04:35PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis is mega-excited to trial a pair of hi-tech Smarty Pants - underpants with all the capabilities of a smartphone. However, whenever he and the gang test the pants, Walter is always one step ahead of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa879352069255fc7bf2e01b1a28abf51</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 04:35PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 04:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron steals DM's confidence and gives it to his shy daughter, Delilah Von Greenback, creating a dangerous criminal mastermind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5df627a084f7c486593e10df1725c85c</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 04:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 05:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When Pam D?Terre and her giant rabbit sidekick confiscate all the potatoes in the world, the Ninjas must go on a rescue mission to get them back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5b0ff086652d29157b3522733883604</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 05:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 05:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a strange card game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd8280ea25f4c5c8ac45b8837320db09d</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 05:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 05:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Suddenly feeling too old to be collecting toys, Boy gives up his bobbleheads and decides to do the things that grown-ups do instead. The others desperately try to turn Boy back into his slightly more interesting self by taking him to meet the owner of the world's biggest collection of bobble heads, where Boy must choose between what he thinks is cool and what he loves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p53eae7f2ec93d84dbfefaf2b4a97f238</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 05:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Blossom accidentally uses a witch?s broom to make sticks for toasting marshmallows, the owner of the broom casts a spell of squeaky voices on all the heroes. The spell will be lifted once the heroes have returned with new broomstick branches. A simple enough quest, think the heroes, until they realise that a witch?s broom can only be made from the branches of the Really Spooky Tree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe37511be85e501039449287ddef18d2b</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 05:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Agents compete against rival Odd Squad agents to solve an odd problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e0f6430aadd878214936f5dfa5c7be5</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 05:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 05:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Otis and Olympia investigate why people in town are stuck in slow motion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcea725021fcaffbb3d36283dd3eda6a0</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 05:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 06:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Courtney challenges Owen and Jude to be the next social media star, with little success.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6ccccb2b9a1b1595dc58abdcbfafd582</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 06:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 06:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face an elusive villain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde8c939cb2856a527ae4925122886276</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 06:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 06:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>During a match against Rika of the Elite Four, Liko realises what battling is all about.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb554686e74adacd1687add781341b4df</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 06:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 07:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>When Pickle gets stressed about her birthday party, she unintentionally opens the magical portal to Kleftania, bringing evil Lord Clunkett to Earth and seeking revenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96ec8c1439beecfc1c976f03fff179f6</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 07:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 07:25PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. The A-Troupe is split into two teams to test the leadership skills of the girls competing for the role of dance captain. As the competition for the position heats up, Kate warns the dancers to put their differences aside and focus on teamwork.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae268654408cc0cdd7b7a4f3ea9d31d6</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 07:25PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>06 May 2025 07:50PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings decide to free a spirit and send it to Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf3e17ba97de1e96e38a2afc361b91a20</image>
    <start>06 May 2025 07:50PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 06:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 06:30AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 08:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Shaun tries to ensure that Bitzer won?t be defeated in the box cart Grand Prix again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc87d8de89a68ada2f5856aad2fd1c6c1</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 08:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 08:10AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Has Danger Mouse finally met his match? An evil version of the hero escapes from a parallel dimension and joins forces with Baron Greenback.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa755ac1daa2a711230c9321971439bf6</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 08:10AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 08:20AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Gran's Harley gets impounded, Dennis thinks she's lost her groove and given up on her thrill-seeking ways. In trying to help her, Dennis accidentally becomes Old Man Dennis, and teams up with Gran to prove you're never too old to be a rebel.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p06462bc6c222a8dd4acf59ba9de0a0b7</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 08:20AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 08:35AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>K-Jam is moving into the neighbourhood and staying with the family for a while. However, Girl gets insecure and thinks that her awesome best friend is trying to take her place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbace25267391c527963e66f359240ab</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 08:35AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 08:45AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3b43642c96048138824aaaf58461b0b6</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 08:45AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 08:55AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a pig who has the ability to find food using his snout.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p196b5bca0acf23ff7985ace82777a786</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 08:55AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 09:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings take part in a safari photo competition on an animal reserve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p87591ace945bfdf453a92c3829fd0bc0</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 09:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 09:10AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents try to escape from a time loop.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae025c43ad493f0de739ac8970e53148</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 09:10AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 09:20AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 09:20AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 09:35AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve heads to Suriname, a country with more forest than anywhere else on earth. He kayaks upriver in search of some deadly critters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae61be0573c4be4246d27fa124cbcdc0</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 09:35AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 10:00AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 7-9 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about the journey of a river, in this case the Nile, as well as hydropower and dams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82b7581f7039e84791f08f09a1505bbd</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 10:00AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 10:25AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The brothers learn all about different types of cosy animal dens. Bird expert Nadeem helps Cam build a bird box, and Aaron reveals why the Asiatic lion is most endangered.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcc2bea3a0b9396f6a346a5fc0fae598f</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 10:25AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 10:45AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Fashion fun as students are challenged to design and model outfits for a school show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a8b5ed563b79e0b055cb6e86b7ee169</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 10:45AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 11:10AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Art Ninja</title>
    <desc>Ricky starts to receive countless gifts from a mystery superfan whilst coincidentally items begin to disappear from his flat. Gavin is instructed to keep watch, though he's a little distracted. Meanwhile, Ricky makes a shiny selfie in homage to Gustav Klimt, an octopus using a candle and a squirty flower! With his flat half empty, can Ricky finally recover his stuff and uncover his mystery fan.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd06cc3d022cb8d7985eddf08b59cd88c</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 11:10AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 11:40AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Get ready for incredible experiments and mind-bending puzzles to impress your friends. Owain and Tilly are here to explore epic science tricks to try at home and showcase brand new technology innovations from around the world! In this episode, discover why a boomerang always comes back, search for forensic evidence to catch a cake thief, hitch a ride in a car with no driver, and see a ball defy gravity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea0387dd16800881de2d72e86b241d24</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 11:40AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 11:55AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Wouldn't it be cool to be able to walk through walls? From turning into a gas to quantum trickery, we discover why it wouldn't be quite as useful as you'd like.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0e230fa2ad1567230d5610a5e88a4cf3</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 11:55AM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 12:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Chop, chop, it's the Horrible Histories' Terrible Tudors Special, with everything you need to know about history's most famous family. Featuring a never-before-seen sketch with the murderous Medicis, hilarious outtakes, and a special one-off written by a CBBC competition winner - it's your one-stop Tudor shop.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4990fa93a56a86c7058a3f4015bff7d5</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 12:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 12:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Zoe from Oxfordshire is mad about science and dreams of becoming a scientist one day. She loves to carry out messy, noisy experiments, but her dad works night shifts, which means she has to be quiet while he sleeps. She desperately wants her own space where she can pursue her passions and make a mess whenever she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1362ca6c17f3b744fcd72eef1ba4224c</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 12:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 12:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy has double-booked himself and must attend a family party rather than the band?s anniversary celebrations. Moxy plans a daring mission to break him out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12ee72b007386e686b82538b87e65f3e</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 12:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 01:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Go Jetters</title>
    <desc>The Go Jetters are visiting the Everglades National Park in Florida, USA. It's an area made up mainly of water with amazing wildlife living there, including alligators! The Go Jetters are working with a local park ranger to put up signs warning people not to eat food near the water as it might attract the alligators. Meanwhile, Grandmaster Glitch is also at the Everglades enjoying a holiday with his Grimbots. He decides to stop and have a picnic by the water, which brings the alligators dangerously close to him and a boat full of tourists. It's down to the Go Jetters and the park ranger to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96ceda2bd6dcf2f9fa0f8b790460efd1</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 01:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 01:25PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Big Lizard wants to have a go with Dad's new drone, but first he has to prove that he can go a whole day without breaking something precious. Good luck, Big Lizard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p850b309749660e2b38b39d00c45b2933</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 01:25PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 01:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. Whether it's a perilous voyage to the bottom of the sea or the piratey pursuit of a giant squid, the Octonauts leap into action. The Octonauts are exploring Antarctica when Shellington discovers strange microscopic creatures living under the ice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p242d7c633b4f9fd6586900df211d6a72</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 01:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 01:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When secret information is leaked from HQ, all eyes fall on Colonel K. Is it possible he is a traitor, or is there something suspicious about his moustache.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db875e58f17940935f6776c5bb499c3</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 01:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 01:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Waffle the Wonder Dog</title>
    <desc>While Zoe helps Doug with his homework project about Alaska, Simon and Jess take Waffle and Evie to the shops to buy new school shoes. But Waffle's attempts to help end up causing chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ea5a4f370ad0cb1ad9431c914904fb6</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 01:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 02:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>The Tato Team are playing beach volleyball. But when Evil Pea's parents, Mummy Pea and Daddy Pea, pay her a visit, they are disappointed to learn that she doesn't rule the supermarket. They vow to help their daughter defeat Supertato once and for all. After cornering him with three freezy hoses and freezing his super sidekicks, it looks like Evil Pea might finally be victorious. But when she is distracted, Supertato and the veggies use their beach volleyball to block the attack and the plan backfires... freezing her parents instead.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81357dbe11e26974b460a16c167532f7</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 02:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 02:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang take on the power of WilburCorp to stop Walter?s new line of collectable toys ruining the Beanotown environment with all its wasteful plastic packaging.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c44a8d584dd7a07558e7563e65f62b0</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 02:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 02:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Rubi?s dance machine gets accidentally muddled up with Crusty the Robot Pie?s coding. Dennis and Gnasher have to dance on it all day in perfect sync, or Crusty?s entire persona will be wiped forever.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc196d03c4998053896105cc5f5c04bc8</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 02:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 02:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>It?s been ages since their last quest, and the heroes are losing their edge, so Mr Friendlyface invents a strange and terrible monster that he says is stomping through the forest causing havoc, and sends the heroes on a fake quest to get rid of it. Friendlyface soon comes to regret his trickery when, with the heroes out of the way, the goblins decide to take over the forest for their jam jamboree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd73f5a342e51bd6aa4e1226b5b388fb</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 02:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 02:50PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After the battery dies on her laser shoe, special agent Gloria Hope calls on the Ninjas to help her find a new one and foil criminal mastermind Pam D'Terre.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10d3013b50db1457cc92c2ac34d58fdc</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 02:50PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 03:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Drama series. Sasha can stay at the Dumping Ground as long as she obeys the rules. All is fine until her naughty little brother Dexter arrives.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2db44f3427b4b413392bea3cf77b9535</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 03:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 03:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Ariana comes to a realisation as she fights her way through the Dance Captain Battle Royale, and the international twists are far from over.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc4c1a50126c1fa172d0b05da89038e4e</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 03:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 03:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A celebration of some of history?s greatest females, including Spartan Queen Gorgo terrorising Historical Love Island, supergroup The Tudor Queens, and the original Wonder Women.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p582ac5e48494296f4adc6415c654b2b8</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 03:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 04:25PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>There?s a new tripe hound in Beanotown, and Gnasher falls head over paws in love with her. Bertie is looking after the visiting dog, Ginger, and is determined to keep her away from riff-raff like Gnasher.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2c6935906c9fad8f02b717eec4e4caaa</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 04:25PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 04:35PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>An order mix-up leads to a delivery of hyperactive tentacles at Bash Street School. However, no-one wants the job of looking after the pesky things, and attempts to duck out of the tentacle-care duties lead to chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd04f790a2a06b0b64f43ec40406c119c</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 04:35PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 04:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron releases a new strain of elephant flu. Can DM and Penfold find the cure before everyone is turned into a snotty elephant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51f8cb9515674180a911e9981fe74ee0</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 04:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 05:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>After some playful gnomes take her phone, a mum and her son ask the Ninjas for help. However, a game of magical tag ensues when the gnomes also take the Ninjas' delivery.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e6614daa2f8b7a97e30b3497c60c300</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 05:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 05:10PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a tree with chocolate spread sap.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3585c633baec4c2b027d134bc532043b</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 05:10PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 05:20PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse is tested on his experiment to create the perfect family and is sure he will fail! However, his siblings convince him to hire actors to play perfect versions of themselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p74d538ded050c20a33665d7e2f080fec</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 05:20PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest until a heroic one comes along. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 05:30PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 05:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Odd Squad and Villains work together to stop a giant robot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ecb8fd587aedc874bc91e06bf8e589a</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 05:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 05:55PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. The agents accidentally lose someone in headquarters.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pffe16f8607e9b7c534d70c45b0848532</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 05:55PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 06:05PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth and Leshawna try to outdo each other with fake injuries to gain more attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe635ab159f06f65d1cb8af629461d176</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 06:05PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 06:15PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Gold Record.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6bb881e9b26f09372f21fa4936589205</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 06:15PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 06:40PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>A visit to Naranja Academy results in answers, and new questions, about Terapagos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pecf6b702814f4d246f300391aff711a4</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 06:40PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 07:00PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>There?s a brand new slide at school, and Pickle really wants to try it out. However, things get complicated when Pickle's mood magic causes Mia and Mr Ludcomb?s hair to grow uncontrollably.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fdd46f4b3717baf8071605b9e07bf96</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 07:00PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 07:25PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. When Kate asks Emily to hold dance evaluations for placements in the group dance, Emily decides to put Michelle in the back row, which causes waves amongst the dancers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa3145037e37ecb44a9edb7f99a35d148</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 07:25PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>07 May 2025 07:45PM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find an ultra-modern glowing cabin they can use for their party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1b288d68d121be98f9d5b947e9b4735f</image>
    <start>07 May 2025 07:45PM UTC+02:00</start>
    <finish>08 May 2025 06:30AM UTC+02:00</finish>
  </channel>
</tv>
