<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Strange goings-on at Hawx Academy make the players worry the place is haunted. Jay struggles to settle in, while Alex is taunted by Hawx rivals Foxborough.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc4dac4e4d2b9c6a5707aa5ed62250768</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly Mission Shark</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall has chosen his UK team of six to travel with him to Bimini in the Bahamas, where they learn how to scuba dive and become the next generation of shark saviours. The mission begins as soon as they land, and they have just two weeks to complete four training dives, but first it?s time to meet four local Bahamian children who are also joining Steve?s team. On board the dive boat, they encounter their first shark species ? the Caribbean reef shark ? a deadly predator engineered for hunting underwater. Then it?s off to the dive location to start the first series of tests. Some of the team take to diving with ease and soon pass the preliminary stage of their training. For others, it is a much harder challenge, with the tasks proving too much at their first attempt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4a212c329026bccbe3710eb188b9fae6</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>TV Stars Sam and Mark prank the Odd Socks, and there is an even bigger surprise when the lads start giving out awards for the best bits from the series - who will be the winners.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0afc03afb5404fcb89a061ba7b5bfa0c</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Online greeter extraordinaire Troy Hawke helps Callum challenge Adam and Joe to be the most complimentary to passers-by.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/ped8c9f4d688bddfc27d20814bdbcea8d</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>When Kwazii and Calico Jack get stranded on an island, the Octonauts must search for them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p711b28f057f24edc9450ca884c6ba142</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>It's been one year since Cosima crash landed on Proxima, but no-one else has remembered this anniversary! Can a perfect picnic jolt their memories.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52ef4f7288ee99b772ad68e542eb05a9</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When a sudden urge to fly the Mark IV hits, Penfold leads a confused Danger Mouse to a farm, from which he claims to feel an unexplained magnetic pull. An entranced Penfold is met by a shadowy figure - Granny Penfold! Penfold recounts his childhood years on Granny?s farm, where he was trained in the ancient martial art of Farm Fu; a farming based martial art. Granny needs Penfold?s help to retrieve the sacred Fung Farm Book of Farm Fu, which has fallen into the hands of her enemies, causing farm animals to turn evil and rise up against their owners.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5bc9fb86a9c9d89de3a6896036c3a7d9</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang train Bertie in the art of standing up to people so he can rebel against Walter's bossiness - but they train him too well and he becomes a dangerous rebel without a clue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ee81567708d80e99b9f35e4a420add2</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Whilst on a quest to return the Icicle of Destiny, Trevor topples into a cavern of tiny mushrooms who treat him like a king.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6587ed590db6ffbdbc38b906cd7ccb3a</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>An overprotective Heath accuses Grace of sabotage, while Grace and Jonah make a bet to make it on to A-Troupe. Meanwhile, Izzy grapples with keeping Anthony?s secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p98b58fbdb69531c7dbfb68abe1998543</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko, Mollie and their Pok?mon set out to save a Tandemaus pair separated by a storm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p941d680c0b29788ee2b02f98f587c4cd</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Taffy</title>
    <desc>Every time Bentley steals Taffy?s bow, Taffy seems to find another one from nowhere. Bentley tries to find the source of his supply so that he can destroy it and finally expose Taffy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc15dd1ec0725169209f3264096c5a87c</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Deep</title>
    <desc>The Aronnax and Alpheus?s sub are trapped within a giant jellyfish! They?ve been eaten and the jellyfish won?t let food out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p916c85101eb07165f67a52271108d625</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface steals Professor Von Screwtop's Pastry-based Intelligent Espionage unit (PIE) after forming a strong bond with the pie-shaped robot. Pieface is dismayed when Walter steals it from him to protect his dad from the embarrassing footage the PIE's memory chip holds.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4db578615381ab592eeaeea97d895804</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's plan to hold a surprise party for Professor Squawkencluck is undone when the Baron releases killer birthday presents into the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p142b27e7bb29436619c5a233aa8b58ec</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A fairy-tale princess being pestered by an annoying prince orders a new dragon from the Ninjas, who return with the most ferocious monster of them all - a T-Rex.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70302567796da86615c59a39a8a223b9</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. A circus sets up in a nearby field, and a spellbound Timmy wanders off to investigate. Can Shaun rescue him before the farmer notices he's gone.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a12f4a74e3e01355e1a8d436e474630</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy relaxes in the massage chair, but the electricity supply stops in the log cabin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8b95b3a4287e28006124b3827736c563</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the kids think that Mom may be pregnant, they set out to prove they will be great babysitters. Along the way, they learn that it's much harder to do it alone than it is together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb5bb5a7b40090762af8e629842f8f3e8</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are excited to visit Whizzpop?s Pop-Up Bakery and taste his magical cakes, but they are shocked to find that the protein bars have shouty raisins in them, the custard tarts are rock hard, and the floating sponges keep floating away! Trevor quests to solve the mystery, but having accidentally fallen into Whizzpop?s invisibility flour, how on earth will he get everyone?s attention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe2faf77b85cf0b2852c9a1177edf9ab5</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf326fb9ddf1e4b8189998894cdaba294</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents must come together to battle a common enemy. Curriculum: Charts, line graphs. Data Analysis and Collection.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9219a4ed6990cdd4d9ec30d5d0a40f34</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter Challenges</title>
    <desc>Challenges, celebrities, makes and adventures with the Blue Peter team.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4762ad46eff5636ad504a235887f92a3</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir unknowingly face Queen Mayor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ddd267d48b17366fafe68beb1bbb05b</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>After 100 years, the secrets of Laqua finally come to light.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0360f783a139b692684e52faf1554e8</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gormiti: The New Era</title>
    <desc>Just as the Scions start coming into their own, harnessing their potential as a team, all their hard-won progress comes to a halt when they attempt the ultimate Scion ability: Fusion. The unexpected outcome endangers both Carter and Myridell while giving Graven another strategic advantage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80370a7258c8348a620257f43a263566</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:20PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Kenzie helps Pete make a difficult decision. The Brawl?s love theme gets in the way of Heath and Daisy fixing their friendship, and Michelle turns to Eldon for Brawl advice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p78694b47d4acdfcbe0bbffab1b09836a</image>
    <start>06:20PM</start>
    <finish>06:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: Legend of the Boneknapper Dragon</title>
    <desc>Animated short. When Gobber's house burns down, the old Viking is convinced that his nemesis, the legendary Boneknapper dragon, is responsible. Bent on revenge, Gobber resolves to hunt it down once and for all, despite the fact that no one believes the dragon exists. Regardless, Hiccup and the gang decide to accompany him for his own good. On the sea voyage, Gobber tells the story of his rivalry with the beast, which gets sillier with each episode. When the gang find themselves shipwrecked on the suspected island of the beast, they finally learn the truth about the dragon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc74aefee6d25de383371feb7631f2a1</image>
    <start>06:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 August 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
