<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse must fight his own urge to be awesome to stop the world turning into a gigantic intergalactic tourist attraction. Attempting to prove his theory that what the world always needs is a hero, Danger Mouse fights off what appears to be an alien invasion of Earth - but his inflated ego soon becomes the real intergalactic threat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d43d2ca6490ff7c844b2a28644f5408</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse is responsible for Professor Squawkencluck losing her job his clumsy attempts to get her back help the Baron steal half the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3bb8928291651f97c9f27761acb6a515</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Princess is back and erases all weekdays so she can play at the weekend forever. Danger Mouse must ruin everyone's lives by fixing the problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51b2ee65ff2e3f266a9013ffa3688df9</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse has built a rocket ship, and fame-seeker Cheese and excitable Dog decide they want to be the first ones to land on Mars. It would be way too dangerous to actually send these two into space, so Mouse stages a fake Mars landing with the help of the others. But when our two astronauts capture the 'aliens', everyone ends up stranded far, far away from home. Like, a 15 minute walk at least.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc8b944827db5b6e7e910eec7e6370b36</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When one of Mouse?s inventions accidentally sticks Cat?s discarded fur to Boy?s face, his new 'beard' suddenly makes him the most popular kid in school! Seeing her chance to stop her enemy Lila Bird from becoming class president, Girl convinces Boy to run for president too. It looks like Boy might win, until another accident causes Cat?s whole body to get stuck to his face. Can he win the election with such a strange new beard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p914a4dbe62695432e7ae7da249569069</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Cat decides that she wants to become a superhero, and the other kids decide to help her follow her dream. Girl makes her a cool costume and Mouse creates some superhero gadgets, now all Cat has to do is find somebody to save.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcd18456db7fd3391240cf9c7ebdda66f</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings play with a baby ostrich that Grizzy found outside.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9b02f3095f1dc487cda4763f743454b5</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a futuristic underground site.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0fe3e513d4fe1b37a13702add7b05620</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a magic stick that functions as a Yummy divining rod.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcee1931a27a2dfd300dfe45402832d2b</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The forest has run out of bath sponges and is becoming very stinky. Their latest order never arrived, and so the heroes must quest under the sea to Merhaven to collect them. However, Hoofius, whose singing stinks worse than his armpits, decides to enter the annual Merhaven Song Contest and accidentally causes a simple quest to collect bath sponges to turn into something much more perilous.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ed5d646aa33c0f016a4f842cc22d80c</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Only wood elves have ever defeated the mighty Eye of Vernon hat, so when the Riddlemaster wears the eye to take over the forest, the heroes quest to Wood Elf Wood to get help. However, Twinkle really doesn?t want to, as wood elves are so stuck up! Struggling to contain her irritation with their high-and-mighty ways, Twinkle still manages to offend them, and the heroes wonder how they will ever save the forest now.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32df456943a31359aa3e76648f081c8f</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes have found the Wishing Trident, which will help them on their quest to prevent the summoning of the legendary two-headed dragon, Iceburn. The problem is, Blossom has used one wish by mistake, and Herbert has accidentally used a second one. Now the heroes are left to defeat the dragon using only one wish, a never-ending ice cream cone (with sprinkles) and a giant spicy sausage hat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf940465ee4740a280d4541c1e5c9723d</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Obaid?s game knowledge is key when a surprise alien invasion takes place as part of a space training simulation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2ec6f1ea315897bf3b4589cf0331a7a0</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Blink sabotages Mansour's life in a body swap, and Mansour struggles to warn his friends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p89733bc0008308326a52204e181cd1d4</image>
    <start>06:05PM</start>
    <finish>06:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>Each team has a member placed into a clear glass tank that is locked and slowly filling with water. In order to free them, they must retrieve the codes at the far end of a very dangerous obstacle course.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe57fc7a83f88d07113bb16215f685397</image>
    <start>06:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:40PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Phantom is pranked by Nitro and Steel when he believes he?s in a new Gladiators video game, and the other Gladiators have fun pranking the audience behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p236851b7e42258c7058fe0b17e13f20f</image>
    <start>06:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>The Farmer has taken up beekeeping and is loving all the honey produced by the hive. However, when he discards his protective suit, the swarm move in, bringing it to life! Soon, the ?Bee-Man? is bossing Bitzer around.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc354936294dc8908b721c1100ac957a3</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When secret information is leaked from HQ, all eyes fall on Colonel K. Is it possible he is a traitor, or is there something suspicious about his moustache.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db875e58f17940935f6776c5bb499c3</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis is mega-excited to trial a pair of hi-tech Smarty Pants - underpants with all the capabilities of a smartphone. However, whenever he and the gang test the pants, Walter is always one step ahead of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa879352069255fc7bf2e01b1a28abf51</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids want to impress Gramps by completing the Gauntlet of Greatness carnival attraction that he did when he was their age. However, Dog and Girl just can't seem to beat it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db98e87d457a49378a84e78a275e08d</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8cee247f1481dd765d6e9c711bdc26e0</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:50AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A Viking Captain summons the Ninjas to find him a steady beat to get his oarsmen moving in time and outrun his rival, Captain Bullyson.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc098a56c9c36f47530d4c941bded98ca</image>
    <start>07:50AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Odd Squad investigates strange events. Odd Squad must go undercover to recover a stolen gadget.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6a216ea5a7c37fe7ad03597a9e232f3</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom draws the short cheese straw and, rather than join her friends on a picnic, she has to take a magic wand to the recycling centre. Faced with a long queue and a rumbly tummy, Blossom decides that life is too short for recycling - with disastrous consequences. The heroes must skip their picnic and go on a quest to save the forest from the magical mess Blossom has gotten them into.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38db6a019d90d683a5c507a27c6477df</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Riposte Prime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p46c6550b324a83053b88341b3ace3e0c</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy tries to catch a fish despite the Lemmings kitesurfing and the presence of a shark.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb27ef18ffa8ce9017aca0bcd9ad70c9</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel meets the stars of How to Train Your Dragon, and former Strictly winner and wildlife hero Hamza joins us in the Blue Peter garden. Meanwhile, Abby goes head-to-head in a gaming battle with comedy legend Romesh Ranganathan, and viral magician Arshdeep Soni wows us with his magic.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p60470747b03bf8c2559fe926996b09a3</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>The dragon riders enlist the aid of Carla and Hazel to help them prepare for a mission.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e7e0cdb96bfc30b6052ed4403ea9295</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:50AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>4 O'Clock Club</title>
    <desc>Nero heads to Hollywood to see if he can make his fame and fortune as a singer, dancer, rapper and all-round megastar. However, making it big in the Land of Opportunity is harder than he expected. He ends up living in a basement owned by the Tang Family, being represented by Hollywood?s worst most washed-up agent, and attending a college where he teaches a strand on British History ? a subject he knows nothing about. However, while Nero might not make it big he discovers a different kind of success with the friends and surrogate-family around him. Maybe this American adventure might just work out okay! Meanwhile, Owen and Eli try to make it from the UK to the USA to visit Nero. But a series of mishaps at the airport and on the plane mean their holiday doesn?t go entirely to plan? and they end up stranded in Alaska.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0713e3e9e66bb2181cee4f54b8e1ea7</image>
    <start>09:50AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Danny and Mick have to play Romeo and Juliet after a theatre company leaves them in the lurch - this time with Danny playing Romeo and Mick playing Juliet, the role he was born to play.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2e8c77eb0009ebee9e8dd79aeb5ebf59</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Pottsfield is hosting a cake decorating masterclass with guest judge Mary Croissant, but after she catches Danny insulting her, she leaves in a grump. It's up to Danny to convince the class he's Mary, teach Lance's judo class and have a performance review with Sharon... all at the same time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcdec286656e46168f59700ae7e5c4e91</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Forcing Andy?s mum to take a relaxing day off, the Odd Socks take over her hair salon. However, upon the surprise arrival of some royal customers, will the band be able to cope.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac227533664b5a50bd4a24ce8b89857e</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>With Andy?s mum getting injured, Ruby needs a new doubles partner for a tennis tournament. Mac faces his fears to unearth a secret tennis talent and take to the court once again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p76fa4297d0a825447b4f2bb6b8f69558</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Wildlife expert Steve Backshall meets one of the planet's ultimate killers, the saltwater crocodile, as the Deadly 60 team land in Australia's Northern Territories. A rogue croc is terrorising local fisherman, so it is time to lend the park rangers a hand in catching and relocating this prehistoric monster. Steve heads deep into an abandoned mine on a ghost hunt. He is on the search for ghost bats, awesome creatures with huge fangs, that drop on to their prey out of the night sky. Scary stuff, and a first for the Deadly team as these bats have never been filmed in the wild before.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c282614ee27131e13e9c6b11076c432</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Naturalist Steve Backshall's quest to meet 60 of the deadliest animals on the planet takes him to India. He is on the trail of the saw-scaled viper, said to be the deadliest snake on earth and responsible for 50,000 human deaths each year. It might seem that putting it on the Deadly 60 list is a formality but, in a country famous for enormous snakes, Steve discovers that it has plenty of competition. The sloth bear seems an unlikely candidate for the Deadly 60 until it becomes clear that it has razor sharp claws and an incredibly powerful jaw, attributes that do not go unnoticed by Steve as he gets a little too close to one of them. Steve puts his martial arts skills to good use as he tries praying mantis kung fu in an attempt to get to grips with an insect with one of the fastest strikes around.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5b176c698011246f3b29cd2f92c37c43</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Dr Xand arm wrestles the world?s strongest woman to help find out how muscles grow. And the doctors reveal the Top Five Bizarre Things Your Body Can Do.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p98e68483f61ef6e64531983d60fb2a23</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A pirate captain regrets stealing a herd of seasick cows, a Georgian sportsman invents a whole new way of boxing, King Charles II raps about his party lifestyle, and the Georgian army goes to war against a bunch of naughty schoolboys.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e5f4295938a4955551888a20c3e6f03</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>In Ancient Greece, it's time for Spartan High School Musical, a jester breaks bad news to Henry VIII using armpit raspberries, learn how to stay fit with the Caveman Workout, and Roman emperor Nero stars in a (not very) romantic movie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p517e976f5b716aeb138ee3b6166d7897</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Diamond when the guest on a live TV show can?t stop pumping! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes, pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p124aa384cfc9de9b57a6c0777805b147</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Squawkencluck reboots the now 100 per cent reliable Big Head base computer, which immediately locks up everyone in a maximum security prison.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p807580e7b44481f79c8475072cd446ef</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's attempts to boost Penfold's confidence backfire when they lead to a ferocious games monster escaping into the real world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p107003566b41bffd5346594c3f9d54eb</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Brunel, the crazed time-travelling Victorian gentlechimp, is back and determined to change history so that Danger Mouse and Penfold never meet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c7b4ec1cfd4ed38c7cbcb24ef88353f</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang can?t wait for their all-day PE training day with Grizzly Griller and are baffled when their idol makes them learn a range of boring non-sports that only Walter excels at.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13014ffef7cef77e45cb02cd6a8721d2</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and his mates rebel against an outbreak of unfair fun-killing rules that are being imposed on Beanotown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f84e659fa74f9534a219e00043217b3</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and Gnasher accidentally do good deeds for the people of Beanotown. Intrigued by the new sensation of being thanked and appreciated, they go on a 'helping rampage', leaving a wake of mayhem behind them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8a5033f5d7b0f34dcc6198f2e6ce3ea</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert has invented a new contraption to help him fly using an old set of bagpipes. The 'Herbecopter', as Herbert likes to call it, is rather noisy but extremely effective, and Twinkle is unhappy at no longer being the only flying hero. So, when the heroes quest to get Friendlyface?s priceless locket back from a dragon, Twinkle and Herbert become extremely competitive and risk completely failing the quest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa955ab16670c700cec4ca1249af0b548</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Blossom accidentally uses a witch?s broom to make sticks for toasting marshmallows, the owner of the broom casts a spell of squeaky voices on all the heroes. The spell will be lifted once the heroes have returned with new broomstick branches. A simple enough quest, think the heroes, until they realise that a witch?s broom can only be made from the branches of the Really Spooky Tree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe37511be85e501039449287ddef18d2b</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find an ice block that holds a frozen prehistoric animal.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p88eb6bc20f2eb8deabb1e06234837eb7</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a container filled with metal survival food flasks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0287b9b09672b2fe39abe8f7f107f3fa</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings attempt to take back a chocolate egg from a group of penguins.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb634cea656ce1728d93bd2b352b1369c</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom and the riders must rescue Plowhorn from Sledkin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8e214da0219881d6a5448804eb882fcc</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom and Jun struggle to get ingredients for Gronckle Iron to help stop the World Serpent.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8f7df1a4bb45514bfa2c325522f5670d</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>Gangnam Project</title>
    <desc>With Astra suspended, Hannah makes the impossible decision to leave. Can her friends convince her to stay.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc3693098adcc48114cd1a677f363492</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A-Troupe buzzes with excitement, ready to perform for the biggest opportunity of their lives. But their excitement is cut short when Summer fails to show up. Piper and Amy's friendship is tested when Piper catches Amy stirring up the past.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6e510cbf698c170dcf3569c951412dac</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>It?s the season finale, and the Vipers could get promoted! However, Aoife is headhunted for county trials - can she do both and make it to the big final against arch-rivals the Comets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf75da12a774401b907e62f945fb6549e</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:05PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Tasked with letting go of items that might be holding them back, Lily struggles to shred Matt Furnish?s love letters, and Claire can?t sell her beloved merch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c8c057f5b92b690440da8b3d67e808a</image>
    <start>06:05PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>When Miss Marmaduke?s love of sushi leads to firing all the teachers, Lily, Claire, Jin and Mr Malone join forces with the kids to get their jobs back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b9515de0bf5e11b5e51007faabc9d74</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
