<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Freddie Mercury - The Final Act</title>
    <desc>The extraordinary story of Freddie Mercury's battle with AIDS and the groundbreaking tribute concert Queen staged in his memory after he died.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/74/20/04/742004_p21004489_b_h9_ai_360.jpg</image>
    <start>12:03PM</start>
    <finish>01:34PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>The ABC of</title>
    <desc>David Wenham takes Germaine Greer on a journey through her ABC Archival life. In this rare and open interview, she shows sides of herself viewers will not have seen before.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/73/40/14/734014_p22439269_b_h9_aa_360.jpg</image>
    <start>01:34PM</start>
    <finish>02:04PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>Follows the stories with the latest on the day's events, explaining what's happening and why it matters, with reporters across Australia and around the globe uncovering the facts. Presented by Michael Tetlow.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/78/64/65/786465_p15072796_b_h9_ab_360.jpg</image>
    <start>02:04PM</start>
    <finish>02:19PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>The Business</title>
    <desc>Australia's leading daily business and finance show, bringing you up to date on market moves, economic trends and the forces affecting consumers, employees and business owners big and small. Presented by Kirsten Aiken.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/69/96/806996_p11006778_b_h9_aa_360.jpg</image>
    <start>02:19PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Four Corners</title>
    <desc>Over summer, organised crime cast a terrifying shadow over Australia. The Jewish community in Sydney was left reeling - shaken by a wave of attacks. Now the caravan plot \.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/82/31/808231_p236682_b_h9_aa_360.jpg</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:21PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Media Watch</title>
    <desc>It's the show everybody loves until they're on it. Media Watch returns with a new host. Sitting in the hot seat will be four-time Walkley award-winner Linton Besser, an investigative reporter and former foreign correspondent.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/30/45/803045_p12133986_b_h9_ad_360.jpg</image>
    <start>03:21PM</start>
    <finish>03:38PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Q+A</title>
    <desc>Q+A is in Sydney with the winners, losers and wash-up from the federal election. Can Albanese retain his majority? Will the ranks of Greens and teals grow? Or will Dutton defy the polls and win? We discuss what happens next.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/75/95/65/759565_p11006696_b_h9_ak_360.jpg</image>
    <start>03:38PM</start>
    <finish>04:41PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Grand Designs: The Streets</title>
    <desc>Kevin meets Joanna and Ben, who are channelling all their ingenuity to realise their vision of building an American ranch-style house in a gritty part of Glasgow on a tight budget.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/75/89/45/758945_p16724496_b_h9_ak_360.jpg</image>
    <start>04:41PM</start>
    <finish>05:29PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Long Lost Family</title>
    <desc>Two incredible stories: a mother living with a heart-breaking decision made when she was still a child, to give up her son for adoption; and a woman on a quest to solve a family mystery and find her sisters.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/79/27/89/792789_p8621514_b_h9_aq_360.jpg</image>
    <start>05:29PM</start>
    <finish>06:16PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>rage</title>
    <desc>Australia's longest-running music show is home to the biggest vault of music videos from a diverse range of artists, genres, and eras. They curate the best clips of all-time to entertain for hours.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/67/55/21/675521_p279154_b_h3_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>06:16PM</start>
    <finish>07:29PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Gardening Australia</title>
    <desc>Costa Georgiadis looks at reducing urban heat with trees; Sophie Thomson explores a glorious fig farm; Jerry Coleby-Williams has a compost method for every type of organic waste; Tino Carnevale visits seed saving experts.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/74/79/14/747914_p11986162_b_h9_ae_360.jpg</image>
    <start>07:29PM</start>
    <finish>08:29PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>Sarah Ferguson presents Australia's premier daily current affairs program, delivering agenda-setting public affairs journalism and interviews that hold the powerful to account. Plus political analysis from Laura Tingle.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/77/78/73/777873_p8933541_b_h9_ae_360.jpg</image>
    <start>08:29PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Bridget Brennan and James Glenday bring you the latest on all the news you need to know this morning. Emma Rebellato reports from Vatican City, Charles Brice with news, Catherine Murphy with sport and Nate Byrne with weather.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/01/59/800159_p553013_b_h9_ad_360.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
