<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Media Watch</title>
    <desc>It's the show everybody loves until they're on it. Media Watch returns with a new host. Sitting in the hot seat will be four-time Walkley award-winner Linton Besser, an investigative reporter and former foreign correspondent.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/30/45/803045_p12133986_b_h9_ad_360.jpg</image>
    <start>03:21PM</start>
    <finish>03:38PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Q+A</title>
    <desc>Q+A is in Sydney with the winners, losers and wash-up from the federal election. Can Albanese retain his majority? Will the ranks of Greens and teals grow? Or will Dutton defy the polls and win? We discuss what happens next.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/75/95/65/759565_p11006696_b_h9_ak_360.jpg</image>
    <start>03:38PM</start>
    <finish>04:41PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Grand Designs: The Streets</title>
    <desc>Kevin meets Joanna and Ben, who are channelling all their ingenuity to realise their vision of building an American ranch-style house in a gritty part of Glasgow on a tight budget.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/75/89/45/758945_p16724496_b_h9_ak_360.jpg</image>
    <start>04:41PM</start>
    <finish>05:29PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Long Lost Family</title>
    <desc>Two incredible stories: a mother living with a heart-breaking decision made when she was still a child, to give up her son for adoption; and a woman on a quest to solve a family mystery and find her sisters.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/79/27/89/792789_p8621514_b_h9_aq_360.jpg</image>
    <start>05:29PM</start>
    <finish>06:16PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>rage</title>
    <desc>Australia's longest-running music show is home to the biggest vault of music videos from a diverse range of artists, genres, and eras. They curate the best clips of all-time to entertain for hours.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/67/55/21/675521_p279154_b_h3_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>06:16PM</start>
    <finish>07:29PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Gardening Australia</title>
    <desc>Costa Georgiadis looks at reducing urban heat with trees; Sophie Thomson explores a glorious fig farm; Jerry Coleby-Williams has a compost method for every type of organic waste; Tino Carnevale visits seed saving experts.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/74/79/14/747914_p11986162_b_h9_ae_360.jpg</image>
    <start>07:29PM</start>
    <finish>08:29PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>Sarah Ferguson presents Australia's premier daily current affairs program, delivering agenda-setting public affairs journalism and interviews that hold the powerful to account. Plus political analysis from Laura Tingle.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/77/78/73/777873_p8933541_b_h9_ae_360.jpg</image>
    <start>08:29PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>Bridget Brennan and James Glenday bring you the latest on all the news you need to know this morning. Emma Rebellato reports from Vatican City, Charles Brice with news, Catherine Murphy with sport and Nate Byrne with weather.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/01/59/800159_p553013_b_h9_ad_360.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>06 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
