<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>David Attenborough's Galapagos</title>
    <desc>David Attenborough explores the extraordinary riches of Galapagos, beginning with the story of the birth of the islands and how it became populated with life.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/05/66/800566_p9632605_b_h9_ac_360.jpg</image>
    <start>11:51AM</start>
    <finish>12:42PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Australia's Wild Odyssey</title>
    <desc>Monsoonal flood waters fill the wetlands of the north and run through ephemeral rivers towards Kati Thanda/Lake Eyre, bringing life to the arid interior.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/74/54/82/745482_p23841829_b_h9_aa_360.jpg</image>
    <start>12:42PM</start>
    <finish>01:39PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>ABC Late News</title>
    <desc>Follows the stories with the latest on the day's events, explaining what's happening and why it matters, with reporters across Australia and around the globe uncovering the facts. Presented by Michael Tetlow.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/78/64/65/786465_p15072796_b_h9_ab_360.jpg</image>
    <start>01:39PM</start>
    <finish>01:54PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>The Business</title>
    <desc>Australia's leading daily business and finance show, bringing you up to date on market moves, economic trends and the forces affecting consumers, employees and business owners big and small. Presented by Kirsten Aiken.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/69/96/806996_p11006778_b_h9_aa_360.jpg</image>
    <start>01:54PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Four Corners</title>
    <desc>Bunnings has become one of Australia's most dominant and profitable retailers. Critics say it's a corporate predator systematically picking off independents, shutting down competition and abusing its dominance.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/82/31/808231_p236682_b_h9_aa_360.jpg</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Media Watch</title>
    <desc>It's the show everybody loves until they're on it. Media Watch returns with a new host. Sitting in the hot seat will be four-time Walkley award-winner Linton Besser, an investigative reporter and former foreign correspondent.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/30/45/803045_p12133986_b_h9_ad_360.jpg</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:12PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Q+A</title>
    <desc>Patricia Karvelas leads the conversation as citizens put their questions to local and international politicians and thought leaders. Q+A brings together a range of guests to debate the big issues affecting Australians.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/75/95/65/759565_p11006696_b_h9_ak_360.jpg</image>
    <start>03:12PM</start>
    <finish>04:14PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Grand Designs: The Streets</title>
    <desc>Tom and Lori want to escape the anonymity of London so have decided to self-build at Graven Hill in Oxfordshire giving them access to countryside.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/75/89/45/758945_p16724496_b_h9_ak_360.jpg</image>
    <start>04:14PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Long Lost Family: What Happened Next</title>
    <desc>Revisits the siblings Vanda and Davina as they celebrate sister Debbie's birthday; a catch-up with Chris and Sue, who were searching for the son they had put up for adoption as teenagers.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/74/02/38/740238_p14089477_b_h9_af_360.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:47PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>rage</title>
    <desc>Australia's longest-running music show is home to the biggest vault of music videos from a diverse range of artists, genres, and eras. They curate the best clips of all-time to entertain for hours.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/67/55/21/675521_p279154_b_h3_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>05:47PM</start>
    <finish>06:45PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Parkinson In Australia</title>
    <desc>In 1982, Michael Parkinson spoke with Sir Edmund Hillary and Twiggy.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/73/94/01/739401_p22277208_b_h9_aa_360.jpg</image>
    <start>06:45PM</start>
    <finish>07:31PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Gardening Australia</title>
    <desc>Costa Georgiadis meets an inspiring teenaged gardener; Millie Ross explores a garden designed for wildlife; Jane Edmanson shows how to prepare for winter; Jerry Coleby-Williams meets a couple of young plant collectors.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/74/79/14/747914_p11986162_b_h9_ae_360.jpg</image>
    <start>07:31PM</start>
    <finish>08:29PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>7.30</title>
    <desc>Sarah Ferguson presents Australia's premier daily current affairs program, delivering agenda-setting public affairs journalism and interviews that hold the powerful to account. Plus political analysis from Laura Tingle.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/77/78/73/777873_p8933541_b_h9_ae_360.jpg</image>
    <start>08:29PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>As each day begins get the facts you need to stay informed. Bridget Brennan and James Glenday present the latest news, overnight developments and today's top stories, joined by Emma Rebellato, Catherine Murphy and Nate Byrne.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/01/59/800159_p553013_b_h9_ad_360.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
