<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Compass</title>
    <desc>The continuing war in Gaza has left Jewish and Muslim communities here in Australia traumatised and afraid. Antisemitism and Islamophobia are on the rise. Are conversations and friendship still possible?</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/76/34/29/763429_p11844605_b_h9_aa_360.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>ABC News</title>
    <desc>News from where we live. ABC News NSW brings you the day's top stories, exclusive investigations and original reporting on the issues that matter to you. Presented by Nakari Thorpe.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/78/64/41/786441_p10665080_b_h9_ab_360.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:31AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Spicks and Specks</title>
    <desc>It was twenty years ago that Adam Hills asked Australia to play. Now he is back with Myf Warhurst and Alan Brough for an all-new platinum season of Spicks and Specks.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/81/23/65/812365_p12138173_b_h9_ag_360.jpg</image>
    <start>10:31AM</start>
    <finish>11:03AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Bay of Fires</title>
    <desc>Mystery Bay's year-long experiment with free-range capitalism comes to a jarring halt and Stella is forced to realise that being the new Queen of Mystery Bay isn't all it's cracked up to be.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/75/42/97/754297_p25134723_b_h9_aa_360.jpg</image>
    <start>11:03AM</start>
    <finish>11:56AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Little Disasters</title>
    <desc>A mother rushes her baby to A&amp;E, where her close friend, the Doctor, calls Social Services on her.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/81/25/46/812546_p29649267_b_h9_aa_360.jpg</image>
    <start>11:56AM</start>
    <finish>12:41PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Slim And I</title>
    <desc>A feature documentary that tells the incredible story of that partnership and of the woman who lived beside, rather than behind, the legend. Australia's own \.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:41PM</start>
    <finish>02:29PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Take 5 With Zan Rowe</title>
    <desc>Pop sensation Natalie Imbruglia shares five songs that reflect her story. From overnight worldwide fame with her hit Torn, mental health struggles and the journey back to herself, Natalie is an empowering force.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/78/97/01/789701_p23005904_b_h9_ac_360.jpg</image>
    <start>02:29PM</start>
    <finish>02:59PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>rage</title>
    <desc>Australia's longest-running music show is home to the biggest vault of music videos from a diverse range of artists, genres, and eras. They curate the best clips of all-time to entertain for hours.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/67/55/21/675521_p279154_b_h3_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>02:59PM</start>
    <finish>06:02PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Ask the Doctor</title>
    <desc>In this episode, we're helping you to fight off colds and flu. Dr Sandro reveals which home remedies work and which ones don't. Dr Shalin finds out what the difference is between colds and flu and what we can do to prevent them.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/75/95/47/759547_p14186106_b_h9_al_360.jpg</image>
    <start>06:02PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>The Art Of...</title>
    <desc>We've all experienced heartbreak or the death of a loved one. Namila wonders when it comes to getting over heartbreak is the answer in art? Features Josh Thomas, Emma Donovan and Celeste Mountjoy.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/77/66/78/776678_p27457223_b_h9_ab_360.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:01PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Gardening Australia</title>
    <desc>Jane tours a patchwork of urban bushland; Clarence pots up soft and spiky native plants; Sophie meets a renter growing food with her community; Jerry tours an accessible garden; Millie builds planters out of pipes.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/74/79/14/747914_p11986162_b_h9_ae_360.jpg</image>
    <start>07:01PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>Insiders</title>
    <desc>Australians have had their say at the election and now we have a 48th Federal Parliament. How will a re-elected Anthony Albanese use his mandate? How can Sussan Ley, David Littleproud and Larissa Waters rebuild their parties?</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/70/37/49/703749_p945802_b_h3_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <title>News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>As the day begins get the facts you need to stay informed. James Glenday and Emma Rebellato present the latest news, overnight developments and today's top stories plus Catherine Murphy with sport and Nate Byrne with weather.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/01/59/800159_p553013_b_h9_ad_360.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
