<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Live: Badminton Horse Trials</title>
    <desc>Rishi Persad presents from stunning south Gloucestershire as the Badminton Horse Trials reach their climax with the enthralling show jumping tests. The globally renowned trials take place in the grounds of Badminton House - the seat of the Duke of Beaufort - and feature dressage, cross-country and jumping across several days. In 2024, New Zealand's Caroline Powell was a shock overall winner at the age of 51.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8634683_i_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Live: RFL Challenge Cup</title>
    <desc>Mark Chapman presents as nine-time winners Warrington take on 2023 champions Leigh in the semi-finals of rugby's iconic knockout tournament. The Wolves have been in inconsistent form this season but will attempt to reach Wembley for the second successive campaign, having lost out to all-conquering Wigan in last year's final. The Leopards won the Challenge Cup two years ago for the first time since 1971 and will take confidence from having already beaten Warrington in Super League this season.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/GNLZZGG001YTH6K.jpg</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:15PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Expedition with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>Steve leads a team on a mission to become the first to successfully climb a remote mountain in the Stauning Alps of Greenland. In they process, they must cross a vast river and ski across a glacier.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p17168231_e_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>06:15PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Antiques Roadshow</title>
    <desc>The roadshow pays a final visit to Ebrington Square in Derry/Londonderry, where treasures include a statue from Java, Olympic boxing memorabilia and dazzling jewellery from the 1960s.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p25490305_bd_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Top Gear</title>
    <desc>Jeremy, Richard and James face their greatest challenge to date as all three are sent to Africa and each told to buy a second-hand car costing no more than ?1,500. It must not be a 4x4 and must not be designed in any way to go off-road. Which could be a problem, since their task is then to drive across the wilds of Botswana, negotiating massive salt pans, treacherous rivers and animal reserves.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p2295840_e_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Unforgotten: The Bradford City Fire</title>
    <desc>In 1985, a fire ripped through the wooden stands at Bradford City's Stadium. These are the personal stories of those who lived through that day and who won't let it be forgotten.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/g8_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Brooklyn</title>
    <desc>An Irish immigrant in 1950s New York falls for a tough Italian plumber, but faces temptation from another man when she returns to her homeland for a visit. Eilis finds herself torn between her personal freedom and her family responsibilities.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p11436766_bd_h10_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:15AM</finish>
    <date>11 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Wild Men</title>
    <desc>In a desperate attempt to cure his midlife crisis, Martin has fled his family to live high up in the Norwegian mountains. There, he meets Musa, a hash smuggler, who is injured after a car accident. A series of events, the pair are sent fleeing across the Norwegian mountains, pursued by the police, Musa's rivals and Martin's wife.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p19208639_bd_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>12:15AM</start>
    <finish>01:55AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Question Time</title>
    <desc>Features a studio audience quizzing top politicians on the events of the day. The panel surrounding presenter Fiona Bruce is composed of at least one member of the three major parties.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p279016_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:55AM</start>
    <finish>02:55AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Stacey &amp; Joe</title>
    <desc>Christmas is coming, but before the family can fully get into the festive spirit, Joe and Stacey have to get their work commitments wrapped up. Joe's got a starring role in panto, and Stacey is shooting a TV ad. Friday night dinner is a chance to reconnect with the family before the season properly kicks off with a visit to a Christmas tree farm and the family celebrations, which go off with a bang.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29798531_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:55AM</start>
    <finish>03:55AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Is BBC TWO</title>
    <desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9526881_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:55AM</start>
    <finish>06:40AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Repair Shop</title>
    <desc>To mark the 80th anniversary of VE Day, the team open the barn doors to four very special items, each with an extraordinary wartime story behind them. Horologist Steve Fletcher is honoured to welcome 101-year-old Royal Navy veteran John Holloway.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30078652_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:40AM</start>
    <finish>07:40AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Match of the Day 2</title>
    <desc>Mark Chapman introduces highlights of the day's five Premier League games, featuring champions Liverpool against title rivals Arsenal. For much of the season, the Gunners were the closest challengers to Arne Slot's side before falling away towards the end of this campaign. There are also highlights of the day's other four games, including the battle for European football between Newcastle United and Chelsea.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p262681_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>07:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC News</title>
    <desc>A comprehensive compilation of the latest and the most important news stories, updates and developments from the UK and different parts of the world.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8133775_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Politics Live</title>
    <desc>Jo Coburn invites a panel of guests to share their opinions on the newsmaking stories of the day.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p15870294_bd_h10_ba.jpg</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Impossible</title>
    <desc>Contestants compete across the series, scoring points by answering questions correctly. However, they must avoid the impossible answers, otherwise they will be eliminated from the show until the next day.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p16150055_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Lightning</title>
    <desc>Comedian Zoe Lyons presents the fast quiz with a ?3,000 jackpot. Six plucky contestants compete across six rounds, testing their general knowledge, quick thinking and speedy reactions whilst the ruthless spotlight patrols the studio. The contestants' motivation in each round is simple: stay out of the light and you'll be all right!</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p21763521_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Unbeatable</title>
    <desc>Jason Manford hosts the quiz show where players face a question and pick from a board of six rankable answers. Some answers are good, but only one is unbeatable.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p20018841_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Expedition Volcano</title>
    <desc>Chris Jackson and his fellow geologists head to the Nyamulagira volcano, one of the most active yet least explored volcanoes on the planet. The team travel on a UN helicopter flight at treetop level to avoid being hit by ground fire, before landing as close to the active crater as they can. They then have only a few hours to gain as much data as possible to help predict future eruptions.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p14817420_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Flog It!</title>
    <desc>Among the items are a masonic watch and a much sought-after commemorative mug by Eric Ravilious. Paul also visits the extravagant home of Britain's first prime minister, Robert Walpole.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p12340462_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title>
    <desc>Celebrity contestants Craig Doyle, Baroness Tanni Grey-Thompson, Dr Anne-Marie Imafidon and Leo Reich take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26509147_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Anna Haugh's Big Irish Food Tour</title>
    <desc>Vanessa Feltz wants Anna to check out the culinary delights of east Cork. She sends her to help out with lambing before venturing to Ballycotton Harbour to sample the seafood.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29117654_e_h11_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Grand Tours of Scotland's Rivers</title>
    <desc>This Grand Tour begins in the hills above Glen Clova, on a mountainous plateau known as The Mounth. Following the South Esk downstream, Paul enters Corrie Fee where he scrambles on the cliffs with two botanists, searching for Scotland's rarest plant.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p21066537_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Mastermind</title>
    <desc>Clive Myrie presents the last semi-final of the classic quiz where contenders return to the black chair under the glare of the spotlight and the ticking clock to win a place in the grand final.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p27992005_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Only Connect</title>
    <desc>Victoria Coren Mitchell hosts the quiz where knowledge only gets you so far. Two teams from previous series return, but there's a twist to the format - nearly all the questions are audio only.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p28954382_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>University Challenge</title>
    <desc>It's the grand final. Only two student teams are still standing - which one will lift the series trophy? Amol Rajan asks the questions.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p27991938_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Inside Our Minds</title>
    <desc></desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/g8_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Upstart Crow</title>
    <desc>The day of Will's son Hamnet's Confirmation is approaching and Anne has made sure it's been in Will's diary for months. The only problem is this also turns out to be the night of the first ever London Theatre Awards, and what with Will being the greatest writer of all time, and what with all the other theatre companies in London being closed all year because of the plague Will reckons he may be in with a chance of a prize.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p15978113_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Newsnight</title>
    <desc>Featuring extensive coverage of the day's top national and international news stories, along with explanations about the context and potential aftereffects.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p269693_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:58PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC Weather</title>
    <desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8195754_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:58PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Assisted Dying: The Final Choice</title>
    <desc>Meeting the patients in California and Canada who are planning to end their lives with a lethal medication and talk to the doctors who help them. Exploring how assisted dying has developed since it was introduced in both jurisdictions in 2016.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29911906_i_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:40PM</finish>
    <date>12 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <desc>The five pairs are challenged to race from the island checkpoint of Sanya to the mysterious Shangri-La - a city sitting on the edge of the Tibetan plateau towards the foothills of the Himalayas.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29971750_i_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:10AM</start>
    <finish>03:10AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Is BBC TWO</title>
    <desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9526881_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:10AM</start>
    <finish>06:30AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>The teams shop at a huge antiques centre in the Norfolk port town of King's Lynn with their experts, David Fergus and Caroline Hawley.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8099429_bd_h10_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Bidding Room</title>
    <desc>Nigel Havers presides as five sellers aim for the best price for their items, including an extending dining table, a pair of antique golf clubs, fishing rods, a lamp stand, a teddy bear and butcher's scales.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p28997433_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Secret Genius of Modern Life</title>
    <desc>Hannah Fry uncovers the secrets behind the miraculous technologies of the modern world.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p23291328_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC News</title>
    <desc>A comprehensive compilation of the latest and the most important news stories, updates and developments from the UK and different parts of the world.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8133775_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Politics Live</title>
    <desc>Jo Coburn invites a panel of guests to share their opinions on the newsmaking stories of the day.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p15870294_bd_h10_ba.jpg</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Impossible</title>
    <desc>Contestants compete across the series, scoring points by answering questions correctly. However, they must avoid the impossible answers, otherwise they will be eliminated from the show until the next day.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p16150055_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Lightning</title>
    <desc>Comedian Zoe Lyons presents the electrifyingly fast quiz with a ?3,000 jackpot. Six plucky contestants compete across six rounds testing their general knowledge, quick thinking and speedy reactions whilst our ruthless spotlight patrols the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p21763521_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Unbeatable</title>
    <desc>Jason Manford hosts the quiz show where players face a question and pick from a board of six rankable answers. Some answers are good, but only one is unbeatable.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p19896633_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Lost Land of the Tiger</title>
    <desc>Explorer Steve Backshall and sniffer dog Bruiser hunt for tigers through the undergrowth, Gordon Buchanan drives himself to exhaustion tracking tigers in the undergrowth and George McGavin organises a firefly disco.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8359200_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Flog It!</title>
    <desc>The show comes from Milestones Museum in Basingstoke, which recreates the streets of Hampshire past. Elizabeth Talbot and James Lewis are the experts doing the honours as they find the best antiques and collectibles to take to auction. Meanwhile, Paul Martin meets a modern sculptor who takes nature as his inspiration, carving everything from scorpions to giant spiders.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p12589305_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title>
    <desc>Celebrity contestants Craig Doyle, Baroness Tanni Grey-Thompson, Dr Anne-Marie Imafidon and Leo Reich take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26509154_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Anna Haugh's Big Irish Food Tour</title>
    <desc>Anna visits Belfast for the first time, guided by boxer Carl Frampton. She learns about Veda bread, cooks for tourists learning about the Titanic, and discovers Fifteens.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29117633_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Iolo's River Valleys</title>
    <desc>Iolo Williams explores the Dyfi Valley, from the Ynyslas dunes and the Cors Fochno bog to ospreys at Cors Dyfi and wild beavers near Machynlleth.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30076365_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Nigella: Cook, Eat, Repeat</title>
    <desc>Nigella shares her take on the bhorta, a dish of fried and mashed vegetables favoured in the Indian subcontinent, to which she introduces a very British ingredient.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p19037618_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Mortimer and Whitehouse: Gone Fishing</title>
    <desc>Paul and Bob return to the Peak District. They start by fishing the Wye at Haddon Hall, hoping to catch chub, rainbow trout and wild brown trout, before moving on to the Derwent. As they cast, they recall memories of their first trip.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p25777424_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Jules and Greg's Wild Swim</title>
    <desc>The crystal-clear ocean waters and impressive beaches of Mull and Iona are the backdrop for Jules and Greg's last adventure of the season.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26458928_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>QI XL</title>
    <desc>Sandi Toksvig takes a look at upbringing with Sally Phillips, Josh Pugh, Aaron Simmonds and Alan Davies.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p27136309_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:45PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Hypothetical</title>
    <desc>Ivo Graham, Cariad Lloyd, John Robins and Katherine Ryan are posed increasingly absurd hypothetical situations in the comedy game show hosted by Josh Widdicombe and James Acaster.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p16659540_e_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:45PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Newsnight</title>
    <desc>Featuring extensive coverage of the day's top national and international news stories, along with explanations about the context and potential aftereffects.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p269693_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:58PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC Weather</title>
    <desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8195754_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:58PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Saving Lives in Cardiff</title>
    <desc>Neurosurgery consultant George Eralil has prioritised a patient with trigeminal neuralgia. The orthopaedic department faces higher demand. 50-year-old Chris has a large neuroendocrine tumour in his chest. Its position makes it very hard to remove.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30086801_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:05AM</finish>
    <date>13 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Interior Design Masters</title>
    <desc>The designers head to Allianz Stadium Twickenham, the iconic home of England rugby, to do up hospitality suites. They must create a premium experience for diehard rugby fans by producing a swanky bar for serving pre-match drinks and a stylish dining area for putting on a generous spread. Restaurateur Nisha Katona helps Michelle decide who will win a place in the quarter-final.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30078239_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:05AM</start>
    <finish>01:05AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Antiques Roadshow</title>
    <desc>The roadshow travels to Berlin and Bletchley Park to mark the 80th anniversary of VE Day, featuring interviews with veterans and the stories of those who helped liberate Europe.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30077949_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:05AM</start>
    <finish>02:05AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Dad's Army at the BBC</title>
    <desc>Toby Jones, who played Captain Mainwaring in the 2016 `Dad's Army' film, shares a selection of classic clips that feature everyone's favourite Home Guard platoon in appearances that took them beyond the confines of Walmington-on-Sea.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30076319_i_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:05AM</start>
    <finish>03:05AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Is BBC TWO</title>
    <desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9526881_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:05AM</start>
    <finish>06:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Escape to the Country</title>
    <desc>Having met online and fallen in love just over a year ago, today's couple are calling on the help of Nicki Chapman to find them their very first home together in the East Sussex countryside. To better understand what living in this county is like, Nicki meets up with one of its residents, none other than fellow Escape to the Country presenter Alistair Appleton. Alistair welcomes Nicki to his beautiful, off-grid, 200-year-old former coastguard's cottage, which he calls home.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p28083924_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>While Christina Trevanion chats to a close friend and colleague, two teams shop for bargains at the Three Counties Showground with the help of experts David Harper and Danny Sebastian.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p25339852_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title>
    <desc>Actors Tara Lynne O'Neill and Ian McElhinney pop to the shops of Aberdeenshire in their sporty 1970s MG, impersonating cows en route. They each have a kitty of ?400 and guides in the form of Paul Laidlaw and Natasha Raskin Sharp.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p25826702_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC News</title>
    <desc>A comprehensive compilation of the latest and the most important news stories, updates and developments from the UK and different parts of the world.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8133775_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Politics Live</title>
    <desc>Jo Coburn invites a panel of guests to share their opinions on the newsmaking stories of the day.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p15870294_bd_h10_ba.jpg</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Impossible</title>
    <desc>Contestants compete across the series, scoring points by answering questions correctly. However, they must avoid the impossible answers, otherwise they will be eliminated from the show until the next day.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p16150055_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Lightning</title>
    <desc>Comedian Zoe Lyons presents the electrifyingly fast quiz with a ?3,000 jackpot. Six plucky contestants compete across six rounds testing their general knowledge, quick thinking and speedy reactions whilst our ruthless spotlight patrols the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p21763521_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Unbeatable</title>
    <desc>Jason Manford hosts the quiz show where players face a question and pick from a board of six rankable answers. Some answers are good, but only one is unbeatable.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p20018843_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Lost Land of the Tiger</title>
    <desc>The second part of the wildlife adventure series following an expedition to search for tigers in the Himalayas. The team strike out from base camp to track down tigers throughout Bhutan. Kayaker Steve Backshall heads to the eastern jungles, and is pushed to the absolute limit when he takes on a mighty white-water river.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8300616_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Flog It!</title>
    <desc>The show comes from the RAF Museum at Hendon in London. Antiques experts Anita Manning and Mark Stacey find some real treasures among the bags and boxes to take to auction. There's a photo album of RAF Hendon in the 30s and a rare picture that brings a surprise in the saleroom, and Paul Martin visits an exhibition of First World War flying pioneers.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p12589353_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title>
    <desc>Celebrity contestants Craig Doyle, Baroness Tanni Grey-Thompson, Dr Anne-Marie Imafidon and Leo Reich take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26509164_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Anna Haugh's Big Irish Food Tour</title>
    <desc>Presenter Angela Scanlon invites Anna to explore County Mayo's rugged coast. A visit to Achill Island salt producers is followed by harvesting mussels from the stunning Clew Bay.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29117644_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Great House Revival</title>
    <desc>Hugh Wallace meets people transforming derelict properties into modern homes.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26889105_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:50PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Wild</title>
    <desc>A short film that visits Newborough forest, on the edge of the west coast of Anglesey in North Wales, that is home to one of the biggest raven roosts in Europe.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p314421_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:50PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Celebrity Antiques Road Trip</title>
    <desc>Reality TV star Gemma Collins takes on radio DJ, television presenter and best mate Melvin Odoom in a road trip through their favourite county. They also swank about in the most luxurious of classic motors, a 1964 Rolls Royce Silver Shadow.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26071508_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Saving Lives in Cardiff</title>
    <desc>A child whose hearing has significantly reduced has a life-changing operation to insert cochlear implants, and surgeon Dheeraj uses the 'beating heart' technique to save a father.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29858930_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Live at the Apollo</title>
    <desc>Hosted by the magnificent Suzi Ruffell, who welcomes comedians Alfie Brown and Sikisa to the stage.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p23894463_e_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Newsnight</title>
    <desc>Featuring extensive coverage of the day's top national and international news stories, along with explanations about the context and potential aftereffects.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p269693_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:58PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC Weather</title>
    <desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8195754_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:58PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Unspun World with John Simpson</title>
    <desc>John Simpson brings his expertise to bear on the most important stories. In discussion with the BBC's range of experts across the world, he uses their unique local knowledge to go beyond the headlines to get to the unspun truth about the world.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p21623114_bd_h10_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Inside Our Minds</title>
    <desc>Chris helps a tour guide with ADHD reveal to his parents what's really going on inside his head, and a council worker come to terms with the mixed emotions of a late diagnosis.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30130639_i_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Murder Trial</title>
    <desc>The remains of a body are discovered in an abandoned warehouse in Scotland, but the victim, the motive and cause of death are all unknown. Was it murder? A jury must decide.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p25395873_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Surgeons: At the Edge of Life</title>
    <desc>Consultant hepato-biliary surgeon Rajan Ravindran takes on complex procedures involving the liver, pancreas and gall bladder. Meanwhile, at the Western General Hospital, consultant urological surgeon Alex Laird's patient has a lot to lose.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29482858_i_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:30AM</start>
    <finish>02:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Is BBC TWO</title>
    <desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9526881_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30AM</start>
    <finish>06:15AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Homes Under the Hammer</title>
    <desc>Is a ?10,000 guide price on a flat in Ayrshire too good to be true? Martin sees the light in a South London property. And Tommy's blown away by the views at an East Sussex house.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p402752_bd_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:15AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Bidding Room</title>
    <desc>Nigel Havers welcomes five more sellers to the Bidding Room, where they try to sell items to professional dealers who are on the lookout for interesting pieces, with help from expert Simon Bower. Shirley is first into the room today, hoping to sell a 19th-century music stool she's owned for 20 years. With no room to store it any longer, she's in search of a new owner. But will any of the dealers be playing to the tune of Simon's expert valuation?</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p28997433_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Gardeners' World</title>
    <desc>Gardeners' World comes from the spectacular RHS Malvern Spring Festival in Worcestershire; Adam Frost and Sue Kent explore show gardens bursting with clever ideas and creative planting.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29363313_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC News</title>
    <desc>A comprehensive compilation of the latest and the most important news stories, updates and developments from the UK and different parts of the world.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8133775_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Politics Live</title>
    <desc>Jo Coburn invites a panel of guests to share their opinions on the newsmaking stories of the day.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p15870294_bd_h10_ba.jpg</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Impossible</title>
    <desc>Contestants compete across the series, scoring points by answering questions correctly. However, they must avoid the impossible answers, otherwise they will be eliminated from the show until the next day.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p16150055_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Lightning</title>
    <desc>Comedian Zoe Lyons presents the electrifyingly fast quiz with a ?3,000 jackpot. Six plucky contestants compete across six rounds testing their general knowledge, quick thinking and speedy reactions whilst our ruthless spotlight patrols the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p21763521_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Unbeatable</title>
    <desc>Jason Manford hosts the quiz show where players face a question and pick from a board of six rankable answers. Some answers are good, but only one is unbeatable.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p20018844_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Lost Land of the Tiger</title>
    <desc>Following extraordinary rumours of tigers living in the mountains of Bhutan, the expedition shifts to high altitude. Cameraman Gordon Buchanan captures remarkable footage of a snow leopard cub from over 5,000 metres in the air. Along the Tibetan border, explorer Steve Backshall treks to the mystical Tiger Mountain, where he has a very close encounter with the world's most elusive predator.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8302235_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Flog It!</title>
    <desc>Paul Martin is in Norwich Cathedral in Norfolk with experts Kate Bateman and David Fletcher. Among the choice items are an enamel-topped silver trinket box and a vintage model car. Paul also uncovers the meaning of religious graffiti.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p12064104_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title>
    <desc>Celebrity contestants Craig Doyle, Baroness Tanni Grey-Thompson, Dr Anne-Marie Imafidon and Leo Reich take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26509169_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Anna Haugh's Big Irish Food Tour</title>
    <desc>Anna meets `Derry Girls' actor Ian McElhinney in Portrush. He reminisces about his love of dulse, a local seaweed snack. Anna harvests some before the pair work on a pig farm.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29117656_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Forever Home</title>
    <desc>Helen Skelton and architect Patrick Bradley meet a young couple leaving London to build their dream house, by restoring a heritage cottage in their hometown in rural Wales.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29979422_i_h11_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Digging for Britain</title>
    <desc>Digs in northern Britain reveal a Roman emperor's lost bathhouse, the sunken treasures of medieval pilgrims and a formidable fortress perched on top of a Scottish mountain.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26335381_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Marie-Antoinette</title>
    <desc>Marie Antoinette's dangerous sexual affair with Fersen reignites when they star together in `The Marriage of Figaro', but the production turns out to be a plot to challenge Louis' authority.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29451063_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Detectorists</title>
    <desc>Finally, it is the day of the DMDC's annual rally and Terry is expecting a really big turn-out. But for Andy and Lance, will the day bring heartbreak or triumph?</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p12339782_e_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Newsnight</title>
    <desc>Featuring extensive coverage of the day's top national and international news stories, along with explanations about the context and potential aftereffects.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p269693_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:58PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC Weather</title>
    <desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8195754_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:58PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Unforgotten: The Bradford City Fire</title>
    <desc>In 1985, a fire ripped through the wooden stands at Bradford City's Stadium. These are the personal stories of those who lived through that day and who won't let it be forgotten.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/g8_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Saving Lives in Cardiff</title>
    <desc>Neurosurgery consultant George Eralil has prioritised a patient with trigeminal neuralgia. The orthopaedic department faces higher demand. 50-year-old Chris has a large neuroendocrine tumour in his chest. Its position makes it very hard to remove.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30086801_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Doctor Who</title>
    <desc>In Lagos, the mysterious Barber reigns supreme. The Doctor discovers a world where stories have power, but can he stop the Spider and its deadly web of revenge?</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29667472_bd_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>01:30AM</start>
    <finish>02:20AM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Is BBC TWO</title>
    <desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9526881_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:20AM</start>
    <finish>06:15AM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Homes Under the Hammer</title>
    <desc>The prospect of a stunning barn conversion in West Sussex has Martin excited. In east London, Jacqui can't find enough plug sockets. And Dion's in Cheshire, where a first-time developer hasn't followed the 'Hammer Golden Rules'.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p402752_bd_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:15AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Bidding Room</title>
    <desc>Nigel Havers welcomes five more sellers to the Bidding Room, where they try to sell items to professional dealers who are on the lookout for interesting pieces, with help from expert Simon Bower. First through the doors is auction enthusiast Ginny, with an item she hopes will go far. The 19th century French travel trunk was designed in response to burgeoning rail travel, and the lightweight design paved the way for many similar products.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p28997433_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Chronicles of the Glens</title>
    <desc>It's spring, one of the warmest and sunniest on record and The Glens burst into life. On the farms there is lambing and calving to deal with, ground nesting birds are beginning to breed on the moors, and training has begun for the camogie season. But then The Glens, like the rest of Northern Ireland goes into lockdown, as the Covid-19 virus hits the UK. The programme shows how the natural spring beauty of The Glens provides a sanctuary for the inhabitants.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p19356825_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Jules and Greg's Wild Swim</title>
    <desc>Jules and Greg take the plunge into the Isle of Skye's dramatic rock pools and waterfalls.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26458927_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC News</title>
    <desc>A comprehensive compilation of the latest and the most important news stories, updates and developments from the UK and different parts of the world.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8133775_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Political Thinking with Nick Robinson</title>
    <desc>Nick Robinson has a conversation with, not an interrogation of, the people who shape our political thinking about what shaped theirs.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p14986697_bd_h10_af.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Impossible</title>
    <desc>Contestants compete across the series, scoring points by answering questions correctly. However, they must avoid the impossible answers, otherwise they will be eliminated from the show until the next day.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p16150055_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Lightning</title>
    <desc>Comedian Zoe Lyons presents the electrifyingly fast quiz with a ?3,000 jackpot. Six plucky contestants compete across six rounds testing their general knowledge, quick thinking and speedy reactions whilst our ruthless spotlight patrols the studio.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p21763521_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Hidden Kingdoms</title>
    <desc>In Africa's savannah a baby elephant shrew learns how speed is the secret to survival amongst the largest animals on earth, and in America a young grasshopper mouse confronts the Wild West's deadliest creatures to stake a claim of his own.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p10447118_e_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Flog It!</title>
    <desc>Thomas Plant and Adam Partridge find some fascinating antiques and collectibles at Chiddingstone Castle in Kent. Paul also visits Chartwell House, home of Sir Winston Churchill, to uncover the real man behind the politician.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p11059038_bd_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Live: WA Diamond League Athletics</title>
    <desc>Live coverage as the biggest stars in world athletics descend on Doha for the third Diamond League meeting of 2025. A raft of Olympic champions are due to take part including in the high jump, where reigning gold medallist Hamish Kerr is set to resume his rivalry with former Olympic winner Mutaz Barshim. Elsewhere, Great Britain's 2024 world indoor champion Molly Caudery takes part in the pole vault, facing off against two-time world champion Katie Moon and Canadian record holder Alysha Newman.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8776949_i_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title>
    <desc>Celebrity contestants Craig Doyle, Baroness Tanni Grey-Thompson, Dr Anne-Marie Imafidon and Leo Reich take on a series of quiz rounds selected by the host, quiz legend Richard Osman.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26509180_e_h11_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Beechgrove Garden</title>
    <desc>Calum and George take advantage of the changing season to plant out the onions that Calum started as seeds just before Christmas.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p16781848_bd_h10_af.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Gardeners' World</title>
    <desc>As the days lengthen and the garden bursts into life, Monty is busy planting foxgloves, sowing cosmos for cut flowers and planting out his tomatoes. Carol Klein continues to create planting combinations in borders and pots all year round.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29363313_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Hidden Treasures of the National Trust</title>
    <desc>Beatrix Potter's dolls' house undergoes major renovation at Hill Top, and in Clouds Hill, a mysterious painting belonging to Lawrence of Arabia reveals its secrets.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p24641905_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Red Dwarf</title>
    <desc>Holly allows the ship to drift towards a white hole, with no apparent escape. Rimmer faces the option of sacrificing himself to save the lives of the rest of the crew.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p1187573_e_h11_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Newsnight</title>
    <desc>Featuring extensive coverage of the day's top national and international news stories, along with explanations about the context and potential aftereffects.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p269693_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:58PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC Weather</title>
    <desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8195754_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:58PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Eastern Promises</title>
    <desc>A chain of murder and retribution uncoils when a man who is tied to a London crime family crosses paths with an innocent midwife.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p167936_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:40AM</finish>
    <date>16 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
