<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Saturday Kitchen Best Bites</title>
    <desc>An array of recipes from Vivek Singh, Max Hally, Ravinder Bhogal and Philip Khoury. Meanwhile, Rick Stein and The Hairy Bikers head out and about across the UK and abroad.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8208311_bd_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Farming Life</title>
    <desc>It's early winter and although the weather is getting colder and darker, it's a time of year that brings new life on the farms. In the east of Scotland, Martin's sheds are full of pregnant cows,and there are two expectant mothers he's particularly concerned about. In Central Scotland near Loch Lomond, Anne and Bobby must gather in their remaining sheep from the mountains with very little daylight.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p12634452_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Kelly's Heroes</title>
    <desc>World War II adventure about an American soldier who captures a German officer and discovers that his prisoner knows the whereabouts of $16 million in Nazi gold. Getting the colonel drunk, he finds out where the bullion is - it's lying behind enemy lines. The soldier quickly gathers a crew of military misfits to help him with his unusual and daring robbery.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p524_bd_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Where Eagles Dare</title>
    <desc>World War II espionage thriller scripted by Alistair MacLean from his bestseller. An elite squad of commandos are dispatched to rescue an American general held by the Nazis in a castle fortress in the Bavarian Alps. From the moment they parachute behind enemy lines, however, it becomes apparent that they face not only the might of the German army, but also a traitor in their midst.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p685_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Final Score</title>
    <desc>Jason Mohammad presents all the latest scores, results and reaction from the final day of the Premier League season, including the game between Nottingham Forest and Chelsea.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p235351_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Flog It!</title>
    <desc>The team are at Stockport Town Hall in Greater Manchester, and Paul Martin is joined by experts Mark Stacey and Philip Serrell. Philip spots a pair of charcoal drawings by Northern artist Trevor Grimshaw and Mark spies some gold European coins. Paul also takes time out to visit Manchester Art Gallery to admire the work of Pre-Raphaelite artist Ford Madox Brown.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9837025_e_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Day four highlights from the Test match between England and Zimbabwe.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8163404_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Top Gear</title>
    <desc>In the first of a two-part special, Jeremy Clarkson, Richard Hammond and James May are in Africa with a simple mission - to find the definitive source of the Nile. Over the years many explorers claim to have already done just that, but the `Top Gear' trio believe that they can do better by travelling further and faster than any exploration team in history using only grit, ingenuity and three ageing estate cars.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9788487_e_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Scandinavia with Simon Reeve</title>
    <desc>The second leg of Simon's journey takes him from the stunning fjords of Norway to Iceland - the original land of fire and ice.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30182130_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Later ... with Jools Holland</title>
    <desc>With performances from Franz Ferdinand, Joy Crookes, Billy Nomates, ALT BLK ERA, Cameron Winter and Jackson Dean, and Jools chats to Beverley Knight and Holly Johnson.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p424567_bd_h8_aj.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:45PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Radio 1's Big Weekend</title>
    <desc>Radio 1 brings you an incredible weekend of performances from the biggest names in music.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p23478420_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:45PM</start>
    <finish>11:45PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
