<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Shini meets a `Blue Peter' fan who balances school with life as a farmer.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p342385_bd_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>News magazine keeping young viewers up to date with the latest stories and events happening at home and abroad.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p269697_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>08:55AM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Gardeners' World</title>
    <desc>Monty is busy in the cottage garden. As the roses begin to bloom, he inserts underplanting. Adam Frost goes to a walled garden. Nick Bailey's aims to inspire everyone to transform outdoor spaces. A man turns a barren plot into a wonderful haven.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29363313_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:55AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Tommy Steele Story</title>
    <desc>A rags-to-riches tale of a young merchant seaman called Tommy who discovers a certain way with the guitar.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p5982_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Live: Women's Challenge Cup</title>
    <desc>Tanya Arnold presents live coverage as St Helens and Wigan Warriors do battle for the Women's Challenge Cup at Wembley Stadium. The Wigan-Saints rivalry is one of the most famous in rugby league, but this will be the first time the women's teams have met in a major final. Saints have been the dominant force in an ever-expanding women's game and are aiming to lift the trophy for the fifth consecutive time. However, Wigan are emerging as real contenders.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/GNLZZGG0020LRD9.jpg</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>I Know Where I'm Going!</title>
    <desc>A headstrong girl who intends to marry for money is rescued from her mercenary course of action when she is stranded in a Scottish coastal town for a week. Gradually her heartless ambition to marry a multi-millionaire fades and she falls in love with a young naval officer.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p7739_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Natural World</title>
    <desc>David Attenborough tells the story behind the world's most famous meerkat family, part of the longest running animal behaviour study ever. For meerkats Squirt and Weeny, the study means little, as they are facing up to the challenge of a drought.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p10244055_e_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Flog It!</title>
    <desc>Paul Martin presents from the Old Royal Naval College in Greenwich. Antique expert Philip Serrell discovers a postcard signed by Malcolm Campbell showing him in his boat Bluebird, and Jonathan Pratt gets excited over a collection of fans.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p13871349_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Hidden Treasures of the National Trust</title>
    <desc>The battle to save the homes and treasures left by two Royalist women who refused to submit during the English Civil War - Ham House and Corfe Castle.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30130571_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Jane Austen: Rise of a Genius</title>
    <desc>At 27, Jane Austen stands at a crossroads. After the loss of her father throws the family into turmoil, Jane publishes two successful novels, `Sense and Sensibility' and `Pride and Prejudice'.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30269451_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>07:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Scandinavia with Simon Reeve</title>
    <desc>On the last leg of his Scandinavian journey, Simon uncovers the surprising and sometimes shocking side of Sweden and Denmark, two of the happiest and wealthiest countries on earth.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30182130_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:10PM</start>
    <finish>08:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Dad's Army</title>
    <desc>Mainwaring's motley crew are put in charge of a vital telephone line, but get distracted by a bomb hanging from a telephone cable.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p1065963_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:10PM</start>
    <finish>08:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Billy Joel at the BBC</title>
    <desc>With songs like Uptown Girl, Piano Man and We Didn't Start the Fire, Billy Joel was one of the most successful artists of the 1970s and 80s. This deep dive into his appearances over the decades on the BBC digs up the best moments from the archives, with all the biggest hits and fan favourites from his first UK hit, Just the Way You Are, through to the last big single of his career, The River of Dreams.</desc>
    <image>&quot;},{&quot;intent&quot;:&quot;posterTile&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;&quot;},{&quot;intent&quot;:&quot;titleTreatment&quot;,&quot;url&quot;:&quot;&quot;}],&quot;id&quot;:&quot;crid:~~2F~~2Fgn.tv~~2F30341151~~2FSH058276500000~~2Fspecial,imi:0f8fcf2e030219a3ac648ec5416b164f3e9d85cd&quot;}]</image>
    <start>08:40PM</start>
    <finish>09:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Billy Joel: The 100th -- Live at Madison Square Garden</title>
    <desc>Billy Joel's record-breaking 100th consecutive performance at Madison Square Garden.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26719228_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:55PM</start>
    <finish>11:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Old Grey Whistle Test</title>
    <desc>From 1978, Billy Joel performs songs from his album `The Stranger', including, `Movin' Out (Anthony's Song)', `Just the Way You Are' and `Only the Good Die Young'.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p20685855_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:55PM</start>
    <finish>12:45AM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Purple Rain</title>
    <desc>The Kid comes from a broken Minneapolis home but his talent for music and charisma put him on the road to stardom. This film is a semi-autobiographical account of the rock star formerly known as Prince.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8092_bd_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:45AM</start>
    <finish>02:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Bombing of Pan Am 103</title>
    <desc>The ongoing joint Scottish and FBI investigation closes in on the identity of the 'mystery shopper'. Together, the teams work to uncover the co-conspirators behind the Lockerbie bomb plot. Vital progress is threatened by troubled relations between international agencies. A secret CIA asset could hold the key to revealing the identities of those responsible for the bombing of Pan Am 103.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30290758_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30AM</start>
    <finish>03:25AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Bombing of Pan Am 103</title>
    <desc>Over a decade after the Lockerbie bombing, following much debate and international negotiation, the accused will finally stand trial. The venue will be a purpose-built Scottish court in the Netherlands. Bereaved relatives around the world campaign for access to the trial. Scottish police and the FBI continue to work tirelessly to secure vital witness testimony and deliver meticulously collected forensic evidence. Will the investigators finally secure justice for the victims and their families?</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30290850_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:25AM</start>
    <finish>04:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Is BBC TWO</title>
    <desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9526881_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30AM</start>
    <finish>06:20AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Beechgrove Garden</title>
    <desc>With the arrival of June, Beechgrove enters a time of colour, scent and productivity. Lizzie Schofield explores these features as she revisits the herb garden.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p16781848_bd_h10_af.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Weatherman Walking</title>
    <desc>Weatherman Derek Brockway walks from Ynyslas to Aberystwyth, Cardigan Bay. He explores one of Britain's largest and oldest raised peat bogs, and his route then takes him to a unique railway museum, filled with nostalgia.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p16806944_e_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Landward</title>
    <desc>Dougie is in Skye to find out how crofters are providing a summer home for corncrakes. Meanwhile, Shahbaz sails to Ailsa Craig to see how conservationists are protecting the island's seabird colony.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p770363_bd_h10_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Farming Life</title>
    <desc>It's January and the new year brings with it wild weather. On the Isle of Lewis in the Outer Hebrides on the edge of the Atlantic, ex-barrister-turned-crofter Sandy Granville is surveying the damage to his croft after one of the worst storms on record.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p12634462_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Beautiful Fantastic</title>
    <desc>When Bella Brown, a reclusive young woman is threatened with eviction unless she gives her garden a makeover, she sets to work watched by her scornful and curmudgeonly next-door neighbour, Alfie.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p13435759_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Julius Caesar</title>
    <desc>Twenty three senators of Rome's Republic, including Brutus and Cassius, murder Caesar to prevent his supposed aspirations as King of Rome. They go unpunished until Caesar's former legate, Mark Antony, speaks against them. The conspirators are forced to flee to the East, where they form an army. Antony raises his own army to fight them.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p7132_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Rome's Invisible City</title>
    <desc>Alexander Armstrong, with the help of a team of experts using the latest in 3D scanning technology, explores the hidden underground treasures that made Rome the powerhouse of the ancient world.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p11795077_bd_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Clive Myrie's Italian Roadtrip</title>
    <desc>Clive swerves Tuscany's famous posh villas to head to the mediaeval town of Barga, where over half the locals have Scottish connections. Staying in a mansion that's now a Glaswegian-run B&amp;B, Clive finds out why Italians love a fish supper, finds himself cooking dinner for 14, and joins an expedition to discover the forgotten quartz quarry that helped make Tuscany's capital Florence so beautiful.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p24605733_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <desc>In the penultimate episode, the finish line is in sight for the four remaining teams, who need to reach the seventh checkpoint - Panaji, the tiny capital of India's smallest state, Goa.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29971750_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Amazing Hotels: Life Beyond the Lobby</title>
    <desc>Monica Galetti and Rob Rinder visit Italy to go behind the scenes at Borgo Egnazia, a hotel modelled on Puglia's historical local villages. Monica makes foccaccia for a festival, while Rob meets the exceptional decorating team.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p25587133_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Top Gear</title>
    <desc>Jeremy Clarkson, Richard Hammond and James May set out to boost the British economy by embarking on a trade mission to India. Equipped with three old British cars and a range of uniquely British products, they set off on an epic road trip across one of the world's most fascinating and challenging countries, devotedly promoting Britain with distinctly mixed results.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8981085_e_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Imagine...</title>
    <desc>At the age of 91 Mel Brooks is unstoppable. With his musical `Young Frankenstein' opening to great critical acclaim in London late in 2017, Alan Yentob visits Mel at home in Hollywood, at work and at play. With the aid of BBC archives stretching back decades, together they embark on an unpredictable, irresistible journey through the city of stars, meeting the legendary Carl Reiner along the way.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p15150896_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:15PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Imagine...</title>
    <desc>To mark David Bowie's comeback album and a new exhibition, Alan Yentob looks back at his legendary 1975 documentary, Cracked Actor. The film follows Bowie during the Diamond Dogs tour of 1974. The film has become one of the classic rock documentaries of all time, remaining an enduring influence on generations of Bowie fans.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9866022_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:15PM</start>
    <finish>11:10PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Salman Rushdie: Through a Glass Darkly</title>
    <desc>In 2022, Sir Salman Rushdie was on a stage in Chautauqua, Pennsylvania, when a man emerged from the audience and subjected Rushdie to a 27-second knife attack. In an interview with Alan Yentob, Rushdie talks about the attack's devastating effects.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p27274037_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:15AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Imagine...</title>
    <desc>To celebrate the life of editor and author Diana Athill, who has died at the age at 101, another opportunity to see an Imagine documentary first broadcast in 2010. At the age of 92 Diana Athill was suddenly a celebrity. Her frank and entertaining memoirs, mainly written after the age at which most people retire, charted a life less ordinary.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8167695_e_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:15AM</start>
    <finish>01:15AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Imagine...</title>
    <desc>Playwright Tom Stoppard tells Alan Yentob the extraordinary story of his life and his latest play, `Leopoldstadt', in which he faces up to the pain and loss in his past.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p20568357_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:15AM</start>
    <finish>02:50AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Ella Fitzgerald at Ronnie Scott's</title>
    <desc>Recorded at Ronnie Scott's in London in 1974 and backed by the Tommy Flanagan Quartet, Ella Fitzgerald performs some of her most famous songs, including George Gershwin's `The Man I Love'.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p14116781_i_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:50AM</start>
    <finish>03:35AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Ella Fitzgerald's Other Show</title>
    <desc>Ella Fitzgerald in performance at Ronnie Scott's Jazz Club in 1974.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p27015865_i_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:35AM</start>
    <finish>04:15AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Question Time</title>
    <desc>Features a studio audience quizzing top politicians on the events of the day. The panel surrounding presenter Fiona Bruce is composed of at least one member of the three major parties.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p279016_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:15AM</start>
    <finish>05:15AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Is BBC TWO</title>
    <desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9526881_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:15AM</start>
    <finish>06:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Bargain Hunt</title>
    <desc>The teams are trying to bag the bargains at an antiques centre in Long Marston, Warwickshire. David Harper's reds push for that extra pound discount, while Danny Sebastian's blues lose track of the time! Christina Trevanion heads to nearby Uttoxeter.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30281193_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Garden Rescue</title>
    <desc>Chris and Charlie are in Swindon to transform retired rocker Ann's concrete and weed-ridden garden into a low-maintenance space with nature at its heart. The garden would be somewhere to relax and host friends and family.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30173170_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Springwatch</title>
    <desc>Chris Packham and Michaela Strachan continue the 20th anniversary celebrations at the National Trust's Longshaw Estate in the Peak District. They launch a medley of new nests, and like any good soap opera, the drama has already begun.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30234561_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC News</title>
    <desc>A comprehensive compilation of the latest and the most important news stories, updates and developments from the UK and different parts of the world.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8133775_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Politics Live</title>
    <desc>Jo Coburn invites a panel of guests to share their opinions on the newsmaking stories of the day.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p15870294_bd_h10_ba.jpg</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Live Tennis: WTA Queen's 2025</title>
    <desc>Live coverage from Queen's, where a stellar line-up has gathered to take part in the first women's event at the famous venue for more than half a century. The field includes reigning Wimbledon champion Barbora Krejcikova, along with former winners Petra Kvitova and Elena Rybakina, and four-time Grand Slam champion Naomi Osaka. Home hopes are headed by 2021 US Open champion Emma Raducanu and British number one Katie Boulter. Presented by Isa Guha.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29464626_i_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Live: International Friendly Football</title>
    <desc>Coverage from the latest fixture as preparations continue ahead of the next competitive match.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/GNLZZGG0020LPJ1.jpg</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Richard Osman's House of Games</title>
    <desc>Previous players Michael Buerk, Kate Humble, Glenn Moore and Thanyia Moore take on a series of quiz rounds. A daily winner is declared following a quickfire round at the end of each show, and the scores are tallied across the week.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p26606162_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Springwatch</title>
    <desc>As Springwatch heads into week three, Chris Packham and Michaela Strachan have all the weekend drama from the wildlife cameras at the Longshaw Estate. Iolo Williams lands in Mount Stewart, the final stop of his Northern Irish road trip, where he hopes to catch a glimpse of the elusive pine marten and red squirrels that roam the site. There's also an eye-opening film about peregrine crime in the UK.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30234553_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Jane Austen: Rise of a Genius</title>
    <desc>Determined to secure her financial future, Austen dives back into her writing.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30233677_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Upstart Crow</title>
    <desc>Will is thrilled with his new play, in which a bright and strong-minded young woman is crushed and humiliated into submission by a man, but it doesn't go down well with any of the women in his life.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p14537107_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Newsnight</title>
    <desc>Featuring extensive coverage of the day's top national and international news stories, along with explanations about the context and potential aftereffects.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p269693_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:58PM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>BBC Weather</title>
    <desc>The latest weather forecast.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8195754_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:58PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
