<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Hoofius plays his grandfaun's old magical panpipes, his friends do exactly what he asks them to do, perfect for leading a quest, or so he thinks.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p28414647_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:50AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Grizzy and The Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings are starving for their reserves are depleted and their fishing has been unsuccessful. A truck delivers a crate of edibles to the research station.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p27386793_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Grizzy and The Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The extraordinary animals from a tablet game come to life after the device explodes.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p27385917_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons: The Series</title>
    <desc>It is time for the final exhibition match for the Terastallization Assessment. This match has Liko teaming up with Katy to go against the Elite Four member Rika. Liko wonders how she and Floragato can face off against such a powerful opponent.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29191117_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:15AM</start>
    <finish>07:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Adam and Joe take on a Mesozoic mission when Little Bro Callum challenges them to live as dinosaurs for a day. Find out if they can complete their chores while avoiding the erupting volcano.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p23090650_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:40AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>There is a gooey green mess in the lab as the Doctors explain how bile digests fat, and there's a serious case of snotting in Ouchology. Dr Chris finds out how scientists are making a new vaccine to help the Covid-19 pandemic.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29606614_e_h11_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>The team come face-to-face with a walking T-rex in the studio!</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p342385_bd_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>News magazine keeping young viewers up to date with the latest stories and events happening at home and abroad.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p269697_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Around the World in 80 Gardens</title>
    <desc>At Cape Town's famous Kirstenbosch Botanic Gardens Monty sees the king protea, South Africa's national plant, then in the Drakensberg Mountains he sees some native flora in its natural environment. His favourite garden is a school vegetable patch in Thembisa, one of Johannesburg's townships. Monty is intrigued by how gardening styles have changed here since the Dutch first settled in the 19th century.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p3481873_e_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Life in the Air</title>
    <desc>A look at powered flight, revealing why peregrine falcons can top 200 miles an hour, how a hummingbird is a slave to its own rather manic lifestyle and that the albatross's secret to flying for free is its nose.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p12734294_e_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Interior Design Masters</title>
    <desc>The three semi-finalists prepare and deliver their best performance as they travel to Edinburgh. There, they tackle the challenge of transforming Festival Fringe venues for a place in the final.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29858978_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Anna Haugh's Big Irish Food Tour</title>
    <desc>Comedian Ed Byrne escapes to the Wicklow Mountains with Anna for a hike and a surprise meal. They spot sika deer in Glendalough and visit a farm producing halloumi-style cheese.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29117658_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Cockleshell Heroes</title>
    <desc>Major Stringer needs to assemble a crack squad of British Royal Marines for a highly unusual mission. Though Captain Thompson is extremely sceptical, he dutifully helps his new superior recruit and train the needed men. Their audacious plan involves transporting a small group of soldiers by submarine to the coast of occupied France, where they will kayak along an estuary into a Nazi shipyard and commit sabotage. Chances for success are very small.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p1501_k_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Talking Pictures</title>
    <desc>The story of the Hollywood musical, featuring interviews with stars from the genre's golden age, as well as some of the directors and songwriters who helped create them.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p12065876_e_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Meet Me in St. Louis</title>
    <desc>A young woman eagerly awaits the St Louis Exposition as much as love with the boy next door, only for her father to threaten to uproot them to New York, where promotion beckons.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p1612_bd_h10_ad.jpg</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Race Across the World</title>
    <desc>After journeying through China and Nepal, the teams reach northern India. Ahead of them is a journey of 1,500 kilometres north-west of Varanasi to the fifth checkpoint, McLeod Ganj.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p29971750_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Flog It!</title>
    <desc>Paul Martin presents from the Bowes Museum at Barnard Castle in County Durham. Experts Paul Laidlaw and David Harper pick out some gems to value, including illustrated books by Arthur Rackham and Edmund Dulac, and a carved dog's head.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p12608858_e_h11_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Hidden Treasures of the National Trust</title>
    <desc>In Knole House, a life-size nude statue of 18th-century ballet dancer Giovana Zanerini, is being conserved. At the Lake District farmhouse Townend, a bound volume of 18th-century letters is being conserved using traditional book-binding skills.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p24641905_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Day three highlights from the Test match between England and Zimbabwe.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8163404_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>RHS Chelsea Flower Show</title>
    <desc>Monty Don, Rachel de Thame and Arit Anderson look back at the highlights of their week at the RHS Chelsea Flower Show 2025.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p472416_i_h11_ah.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Liza: A Truly Terrific Absolutely True Story</title>
    <desc>Actress and singer Liza Minnelli confronts a range of personal and professional challenges following the tragic death of her mother, Judy Garland, in 1969.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p28993849_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>New York, New York</title>
    <desc>Martin Scorsese's romantic post-war musical film celebrates the glorious days of New York's big band era and centres on a dedicated musician who finds his devotion torn between his music and his songstress-wife.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p857_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:20AM</finish>
    <date>24 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The Bombing of Pan Am 103</title>
    <desc>21 December 1988. A bomb detonates on board Pan Am flight 103 above Lockerbie. The attack kills 270 people. The Scottish police and FBI must join forces to find the perpetrators.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30181576_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:20AM</start>
    <finish>02:15AM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Is BBC TWO</title>
    <desc>A preview of upcoming programmes from BBC Two.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9526881_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:15AM</start>
    <finish>06:30AM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>The A to Z of TV Gardening</title>
    <desc>Carol Kirkwood visits the Hyacinth National Collection as she takes an alphabetical journey through gardening.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p10382173_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:15AM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Beechgrove Garden</title>
    <desc>Ruth is back in her vertical garden, and while there, she shares handy pest control hints as she and Brian continue the care and maintenance of projects from earlier in the series.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p16781848_bd_h10_af.jpg</image>
    <start>08:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:10AM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Landward</title>
    <desc>Dougie is in Glen Clova to find out how a shooting estate is balancing biodiversity and flood resilience. Meanwhile, Anne joins a team of firefighters learning how to tackle wildfires with fire.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p770363_bd_h10_ae.jpg</image>
    <start>09:10AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Saturday Kitchen Best Bites</title>
    <desc>An array of recipes from Vivek Singh, Max Hally, Ravinder Bhogal and Philip Khoury. Meanwhile, Rick Stein and The Hairy Bikers head out and about across the UK and abroad.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8208311_bd_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>This Farming Life</title>
    <desc>It's early winter and although the weather is getting colder and darker, it's a time of year that brings new life on the farms. In the east of Scotland, Martin's sheds are full of pregnant cows,and there are two expectant mothers he's particularly concerned about. In Central Scotland near Loch Lomond, Anne and Bobby must gather in their remaining sheep from the mountains with very little daylight.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p12634452_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Kelly's Heroes</title>
    <desc>World War II adventure about an American soldier who captures a German officer and discovers that his prisoner knows the whereabouts of $16 million in Nazi gold. Getting the colonel drunk, he finds out where the bullion is - it's lying behind enemy lines. The soldier quickly gathers a crew of military misfits to help him with his unusual and daring robbery.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p524_bd_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Where Eagles Dare</title>
    <desc>World War II espionage thriller scripted by Alistair MacLean from his bestseller. An elite squad of commandos are dispatched to rescue an American general held by the Nazis in a castle fortress in the Bavarian Alps. From the moment they parachute behind enemy lines, however, it becomes apparent that they face not only the might of the German army, but also a traitor in their midst.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p685_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Final Score</title>
    <desc>Jason Mohammad presents all the latest scores, results and reaction from the final day of the Premier League season, including the game between Nottingham Forest and Chelsea.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p235351_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Flog It!</title>
    <desc>The team are at Stockport Town Hall in Greater Manchester, and Paul Martin is joined by experts Mark Stacey and Philip Serrell. Philip spots a pair of charcoal drawings by Northern artist Trevor Grimshaw and Mark spies some gold European coins. Paul also takes time out to visit Manchester Art Gallery to admire the work of Pre-Raphaelite artist Ford Madox Brown.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9837025_e_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Test Cricket</title>
    <desc>Day four highlights from the Test match between England and Zimbabwe.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p8163404_bd_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Top Gear</title>
    <desc>In the first of a two-part special, Jeremy Clarkson, Richard Hammond and James May are in Africa with a simple mission - to find the definitive source of the Nile. Over the years many explorers claim to have already done just that, but the `Top Gear' trio believe that they can do better by travelling further and faster than any exploration team in history using only grit, ingenuity and three ageing estate cars.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p9788487_e_h10_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Scandinavia with Simon Reeve</title>
    <desc>The second leg of Simon's journey takes him from the stunning fjords of Norway to Iceland - the original land of fire and ice.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p30182130_bd_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Later ... with Jools Holland</title>
    <desc>With performances from Franz Ferdinand, Joy Crookes, Billy Nomates, ALT BLK ERA, Cameron Winter and Jackson Dean, and Jools chats to Beverley Knight and Holly Johnson.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p424567_bd_h8_aj.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:45PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <title>Radio 1's Big Weekend</title>
    <desc>Radio 1 brings you an incredible weekend of performances from the biggest names in music.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p23478420_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:45PM</start>
    <finish>11:45PM</finish>
    <date>25 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
