<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU is called to Taos, N.M., when someone targets victims' temporal lobes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team questions the credibility of a former FBI agent's bizarre account.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When Reid and Garcia are abducted by a mass murderer, it's up to the rest of the team to find them; the BAU looks to their past to solve why the two heroes have been targeted.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team tracks a serial killer when remains of numerous victims are found in the walls of an elderly couple's home; the hunt becomes urgent after the BAU learns the killer's specific ritual of when to strike; Rossi reconnects with his ex-wife.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Packages with gruesome contents are delivered to six people in the Washington, D.C.. area; Simmons and Kristy struggle to connect with their son, David, who is suspended from school for aggressive behavior.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Soon after the BAU steps in to help local law enforcement isolate a suspect for a murder, a second person who is related to the first victim is killed under similar circumstances; Prentiss is concerned about Garcia's behavior.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates a spooky local ghost story of the &quot;Tall Man&quot; and the clues it provides when two people go missing in the woods; a third person mysteriously surfaces the following day with limited details as to what happened to her friends.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates four murders along the eastern seaboard; the crimes become personal for Alvez when the team discovers there are ties to his time spent in pursuit of a notorious hit man; Alvez and his girlfriend decide to move in together.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>18 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
