<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>NCIS: New Orleans</title>
    <desc>Wade's son asks Pride for help after being attacked and discovering his girlfriend is missing; Pride must meet with a therapist to discuss his process for solving cases.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p14215555_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a bomb leaves three people dead, the team presses a reluctant informant to gather information from his close friends who are under suspicion; OA and his girlfriend clash over where the informant's rights lie.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When a reporter is kidnapped and held without a ransom demand, the team must dig into her past relationships in order to pin down her assailant's motive; Isobel's relationship comes under fire when the case makes a connection to her boyfriend.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team must track down two assailants who wear animal masks while committing armed robberies; Tiffany and Scola butt heads on whether or not to accept the local NYPD's offer to help in the investigation.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>After a man is killed by an explosive package shipped to his home, the team attempts to capture the sender and intercept his latest deadly parcel; Maggie struggles to trust her younger sister.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>The team rushes to track down two doctors abducted by a desperate father willing to do anything to save his son; Jubal's uncertainty in his family life affects his judgement during the hostage situation.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>FBI</title>
    <desc>When the CEO of a major brokerage firm is killed while surrounded by protesters, the team looks into who had the most to lose from his company's perceived manipulations; Scola's previous Wall Street career and the reasons he left come to light.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p15528073_b_h8_az.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Kovac fears for the worst as he awaits the jury's decision between himself and Curtis Ames (Forest Whitaker); Ray gets jealous when he sees Neela and Gates flirting.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891893_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Abby and Kovac hire a nanny to care for their son; Morris and Sam treat a belligerent patient who seemingly has the flu, but he refuses treatment when they discover his condition is more complicated.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891893_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Abby and Kovac argue about a diagnosis when a woman comes to the ER with signs of spousal abuse; Gates, Abby and Neela must quickly determine a child's ailment when a group of confused homeless kids enters the ER.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891893_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Abby responds to a bus crash; Neela accepts an invitation from Gates; Pratt confides in Dr. Weaver about his brother.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891893_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Dr. Pratt has a hard time coming to terms with his brother's newly-discovered sexual orientation; Kovac spots Curtis Ames (Forest Whitaker) outside his apartment but does not tell Abby.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891893_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Gates betrays the trust of a homeless boy seeking help for his friend; Curtis Ames (Forest Whitaker) gets a restraining order against Kovac; Neela gets the chance to be part of a special holiday miracle.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p7891893_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU is called to Taos, N.M., when someone targets victims' temporal lobes.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team questions the credibility of a former FBI agent's bizarre account.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>When Reid and Garcia are abducted by a mass murderer, it's up to the rest of the team to find them; the BAU looks to their past to solve why the two heroes have been targeted.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The team tracks a serial killer when remains of numerous victims are found in the walls of an elderly couple's home; the hunt becomes urgent after the BAU learns the killer's specific ritual of when to strike; Rossi reconnects with his ex-wife.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Packages with gruesome contents are delivered to six people in the Washington, D.C.. area; Simmons and Kristy struggle to connect with their son, David, who is suspended from school for aggressive behavior.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>Soon after the BAU steps in to help local law enforcement isolate a suspect for a murder, a second person who is related to the first victim is killed under similar circumstances; Prentiss is concerned about Garcia's behavior.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates a spooky local ghost story of the &quot;Tall Man&quot; and the clues it provides when two people go missing in the woods; a third person mysteriously surfaces the following day with limited details as to what happened to her friends.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>PopTV US</name>
    <id>PopTV.us</id>
    <title>Criminal Minds</title>
    <desc>The BAU investigates four murders along the eastern seaboard; the crimes become personal for Alvez when the team discovers there are ties to his time spent in pursuit of a notorious hit man; Alvez and his girlfriend decide to move in together.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p185123_b_h8_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>18 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
