<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A special episode of the historical sketch show, focusing on the great British queen Boudica, starring Lorna Watson from Watson &amp; Oliver. We follow Boudica as she turns against her Roman masters and unleashes her wrecking ball on Colchester, St Albans and London. It is cut-throat Celts versus rotten Romans - it is going to be very gory! Meanwhile, across the world, we meet famous emperors Caligula and Nero dishing out their own unique brand of imperial nastiness. With of course, our host Rattus to guide the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9e7fe25f8295e4becc12075d61b3dbc</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Danny and Mick have to play Romeo and Juliet after a theatre company leaves them in the lurch - this time with Danny playing Romeo and Mick playing Juliet, the role he was born to play.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2e8c77eb0009ebee9e8dd79aeb5ebf59</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Odd Sock Freddie can?t do his homework because of his baby sister constantly screaming the house down, so Andy and the Band perform the ultimate lullaby to rock her to sleep.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb5a8591f2203f900d17b16cb4c6f4fff</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Viper with a fake interview that ends with an unexpected splashdown, but he doesn?t find it funny! The other Gladiators have sneaky behind-the-scenes fun at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d2e22d45141442e761e7181750d3d5d</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated deep sea adventure series. Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. The Octonauts head to the kelp forest to visit Shellington's sister Pearl and her newborn son Periwinkle - only to find the forest endangered by an infestation of kelp-eating urchins.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p18d7efad16b0ef1a34775b2f7f1f39d7</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Whilst Dad searches for a faulty wire, Cosima and Big Lizard play tag in the ship and accidentally break Big Lizard's bath bed! Where will he sleep now? And where's that pesky wire.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27b20bb3866865593fa592da4ecbf022</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>A late-night scary movie makes Penfold extra jittery, forcing Danger Mouse to make his sidekick sit out the latest mission to stop the Baron from flooding the entire world. When his search for Greenback proves fruitless, things go from bad to worse when Danger Mouse realises that the Baron has headed to the planet's only 100 per cent waterproof building and Penfold's current location - Danger HQ.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p409d62d6c8428e64f9af154a3cc6c776</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>In the distant future, the social outcast Derek Mullard watches a video of the world being destroyed by history's biggest villain - Danger Mouse! To make matters worse, Danger Mouse is Derek's ancient ancestor and the reason he's forbidden from marrying his beautiful paramour, Pennyfold. Meanwhile, in the present day, Danger Mouse is in the midst of foiling Quark's latest plot, which involves auctioning off the nice bits of the world and compact crushing the rest. A time-travelling Derek arrives on the scene to confront Danger Mouse and prevent the world's destruction, correcting the course of history in the process.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65fea07e21b46cf4819aacca1edb7291</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes and the Council of Happiness swap jobs, and when the council fail in their quest, the whole forest is at risk of being flooded by Stinkystuff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a544a2a926fb3c68c7a21626bc95543</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>In order to crown a new king, Merlin summons the Ninjas to pull the legendary sword from the stone. After a few tries, they realize the solution is right under their noses.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcbca7621e76f54ad4a7abff2f2b3e1ed</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>Baby pufflings, Northern Lights and midnight sun. - join the puffin patrol as they rescue lost pufflings on a remote Icelandic island.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8290a1e71ee733623351645a5181b999</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Mark and Lauren get the help of experts to design dream dens for children. Nyobi loves to be creative and spends hours working on her art and design projects. However Nyobi needs more room, a proper desk space and better art materials in order to fully 'express herself'! Also, her tendency to splash paint on her bedroom carpet, in their rented accommodation, is causing some problems for Nyobi and her mum.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pebb6213855de6e30c18d340efbe3b648</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced madcap, stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. Musical Melon joins a grape boy band, Fishing Finger catches more than he can handle, terrifying Count Grape-ula strikes, the toast soldiers ambush an unsuspecting victim, and the thrill-seeking eggs give a cracking performance in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc71e6a5d3d73e54275fc070b7449b104</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>New teacher Miss Mistry is taking Class 3C on a trip to Flumes o' Doom theme park. If anyone is a nano-second late, the bus leaves without them. Walter pulls out all the stops to make Dennis late for the bus.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb1a2b6da96c302dbf59dd322ca1e52b3</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes wake up on Snow Day morning, there isn?t a snowflake in sight! The heroes must quest to free the Snow Dragon and save Snow Day for all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70e545bcacb2d124e1fd8b0469e27b2a</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Exhausted by all her superhero work, Cat asks Mr Boots to be her sidekick. However, Cat gets jealous when it turns out that Mr Boots is better at being a superhero than she is.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9664e99f804329b06e4480832387933b</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Dad takes up ventriloquism as a hobby. The kids must find a way to stop Dad from embarrassing himself as he tries to showcase his new talent around town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0d4afab8bdef7962e0063b6984afaff1</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings meet fairies, one of which breathes life into their bagpipes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52ca24e90332e5cc7495b2699e4a3e40</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob vows to clean an entire building.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0abaaf838ac368e9e9c2514e989ca775</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Atticus starts a secret club with Rory, who then invites everyone else to join.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p171101b9e41548ef4156125a7631c4d0</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>In this two-part season finale, the Odd Squad Mobile Unit must stop a group of villains who want to break into Odd Squad Headquarters to steal an ancient artifact. Little do the Agents know, their greatest challenge will come from someone inside.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p07cb59806543777fe989c5ba2dd8cbe7</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Que volunteers Helsing?s house for a sleepover with the popular girls at school - but how long can she keep her weirdness in check.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1a7879d623be5e2f595020aa18fb2b43</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Courtney must go all day without correcting her friends, regardless of what they do wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe12d009fb4b08949cdf975f6bbb47a8</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko and Amethio are trapped in a freezing cave and must work together to escape.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p232df02fd173721149992d8a8414c2d0</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>With Halloween approaching, the Year 7s have been told about the school ghost and set off to hunt for it. Meanwhile, the Anything Goes cast try not to get too spooked by the thought of opening night for their show, and Encore - the most senior dancers at the school - warm up for their next big show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb23418f094c47204647f6ce302d72560</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Charlie and Teri come up with a plan to split up the new Hawxborough U12s team, while Andrew goes in search of redemption.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pff97c2fa18b7f19374af3ce5ef3ae059</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio. Solo and duet competitors are chosen for nationals, where each round is an elimination. Michelle is hurt when Eldon won't do the duet with her. Riley's world comes crashing down when James betrays her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0d4ab3ab369b53109851266d5dbe73bc</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Gladiators? stars Apollo and Electro surprise children in a Salford school when they lead a PE lesson with a difference.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfcd4e5a3bdf2843cec4b8f9fe7289d76</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>17 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. It is a peaceful night at the farm, until Shaun starts to walk in his sleep and the flock cannot resist their natural instinct to follow.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p012e6a9e43043401ef147d944e67d24a</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Envious at Danger Mouse's ever-growing medal collection, Penfold questions whether he will ever be deemed special enough to receive a prize of his own. Seconds later, a knock at the door reveals a holographic Quark, who anoints Penfold as 'the chosen one' in a suspiciously automated message that culminates in an overawed Penfold receiving his very own magic wand. Penfold's joy is short-lived however - as he and DM step outside of HQ to find that the streets of are London teeming with hundreds of wannabe wizards, all brandishing identical wands. After discovering that the wands are mass-produced shavings from Merlin's legendary staff, the pair set out to stop Quark's latest money-making scheme by reuniting the staff with its rightful owner.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p323dc2e8e64fccd5de7990c027816ff5</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes go on a quest to get Hoofius?s Toby Jug back from the depths of the Riddling Ruins and are faced with a series of puzzles and traps to solve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67fad6fb2cc188991a416f8965659da7</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse is proud of helping the siblings solve their problems using ?mouse steps?. In fact, he is so proud that he becomes obsessed with helping Girl solve her mysterious problem too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paabeb3764b1472b22a0f521174d230bb</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4a5a3b7326d9a37b53b890e761f8f1fb</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy watches TV, while the Lemmings want to dance. TV v music - the sonic war has begun.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p109f3debefb996fbde2e14eed1d526c0</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy discovers a large medieval magic trunk that can blend two objects into one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8caea34a9789b51d040cd759f1f9e061</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Sandy builds a ship in a bottle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b40fdad01bebe446e68ec986ca7f4f1</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When a museum has square objects stolen and two villains obsessed with triangles are seemingly involved, Orli and Ozzie investigate how the villains can be related to the crime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7ad21f144964ec3ff28fb79cca4f8db2</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:40AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Que hates seeing Helsing and Monster Head fight and thinks she has the perfect solution - what if Monster Head had a body.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc01dcbe75b40a0cbfa0813d167236d2e</image>
    <start>08:40AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Webbthorpe Leisure Centre has some new, extremely posh toilets that will receive a grand opening by Lady Fol De Rol. Lance is tasked with guarding the new facility so that Danny and Mick don?t ruin the day, but the boys are desperate to try them out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p45195a2d3e2212ef7210a88e67c8ae64</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 9-11 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Poetical devices, understanding poem structure, and writing in the style of Joshua Seigal.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe180b385cc4bbf3bfec6e48914944ffd</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Owain and Tilly discover the secret of turning one bubble into two, find out how to make sound effects with a spring, and use brightly coloured jelly to give your brain a wobble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32b09954dacceae9c9d470f393b422a5</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>As the girls celebrate Chinese New Year, PE teacher Miss Elsley believes netball player Jina could be destined for sporting success. She has arranged a visit from a local scout, but will Jina prove her potential.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1def4e8561c1d0605c3a50d7cd92b047</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs set sail with homemade pirate ships, Sophie Ryder sculpts a huge Minotaur, and Harry Hill draws himself being chased by a very big, very blue cat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p950470bcf5000eb12035d467de5b8256</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The One Zoo Three brothers explore San Diego Zoo Safari Park in the US and come face to face with rhinos, giraffes and the California condor. Tyler is faced with one of the biggest piles of poo he he has ever seen while on the trail of a crash of white rhinos. But this is no ordinary mountain of muck ? Tyler discovers the importance of a rhino loo and what these animals can do with a pile of poo! Meanwhile, Aaron is lucky enough to go behind the scenes at the safari park?s special lab, where he discovers how the latest science is being used to bring back certain species, such as the beautiful Przewalski?s horse, from the brink of extinction, . Cam has a unique opportunity to look at a California condor chick inside an egg and to hand-feed a young lappet-faced vulture, with the help of an unusual puppet. Cute Alert introduces an adorable little beauty who lives up high in the branches ? Som, the Matschie?s tree-kangaroo. And Aaron sticks his neck out to reveal some real wows and wonders about the giraffe ?- but are they fact or fake.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbf1737a2ad0528a80cf8ad2ec5bf2496</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Daisy, eight, has type one diabetes and has an insulin pump attached to her 24 hours a day. This doesn't stop her doing her favourite thing - sewing! When she is not at her sewing club, her sewing machine is out and she is designing and making her own creations... until dinner time that is! She has to pack everything away so the family can eat at the table. Daisy needs a sewing den where she can create fabulous designs in peace.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb2f9b72e31d11e93a7639fdbb8f2488</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius: Monster Builds</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom go head to head with the fiercest forces in nature as they enter the genius world of engineering against floods, wind and earthquakes. They head to the Netherlands to see how one of the world's great coastal defences keeps the sea at bay, find a suitably hair-raising method to put earthquake proofing to the test and tackle gale-force winds in their bid to stormproof their most precious possessions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd8d64b099fd8f9a2b60d693b438f26e3</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A special episode of the historical sketch show about Winston Churchill, starring Jim Howick. We follow Churchill from a young soldier in India during the time of Queen Victoria, through the First World War, to victory in World War II and finally to his retirement in the Swinging Sixties - what a journey! Meanwhile, across the world, we meet the American soldier literally spreading propaganda around the battlefields, and learn about Gandhi's more eccentric side. With, of course, our host Rattus to guide the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p72857cc3d7af97d7b38b6edb302cf228</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Pottsfield is hosting a cake decorating masterclass with guest judge Mary Croissant, but after she catches Danny insulting her, she leaves in a grump. It's up to Danny to convince the class he's Mary, teach Lance's judo class and have a performance review with Sharon... all at the same time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcdec286656e46168f59700ae7e5c4e91</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy loses his voice, throwing the day?s gig into jeopardy. However, the most unexpected person steps forward to take Andy?s place, causing havoc as the band race to get there.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p44a91e7003d71fd1108b4542cfd28892</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Hammer with a hysterical, historical Gladiator mix-up in a magazine interview, and the other Gladiators have sneaky backstage fun at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3ce3b2d65e95acafb7130f4d3f3b0897</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated deep sea adventure series. Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. The Octonauts study a group of baby hammerhead sharks as they hunt on their own for the first time and poke their noses into trouble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d28447b57f4fabd9223004f2edcd00f</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>During a hoverboard race, Dad's new super-powered hoverboard malfunctions, so Cosima and Big Lizard throw the race to rescue him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1699994e05f37e862faa1cc48c831c94</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold accompany Professor Squawkencluck to the Brainiac Symposium - the annual science convention, where King Kong Brunels's latest misfiring invention, the Cow Trainer, reminds his fellow boffins exactly why he is the laughing stock of the scientist community. When King Kong Brunel suggests that the Professor's success is all due to her privileged life as Danger Agency lab technician with scientist parents, an irked Squawk uses Brunel's Cow Trainer to swap bodies with him in order to show that she could be just as successful in his shoes. However, she soon finds that life as King Kong Brunel is as dispiriting as he makes out, as she is laughed out of the symposium when masquerading as her simian adversary. Elsewhere, an opportunistic King Kong Brunel finds himself revelling at playing Squawk, as finds he himself inside her lab having hitched a lift back to HQ with an unwitting Danger Mouse and Penfold. On discovering the truth, Danger Mouse and Penfold have the body- swapper turned on them, as KKB escapes back to the convention with his newly acquired Squawk-shaped credibility, and a new invention so poorly put together that it could end the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10d782c873c5cb440e14211052a06036</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>On seeing his adopted goldfish get busted for stealing top-secret documents, Penfold bewails the fact he has never had a pet of his own to love and cherish. He gets his wish when Danger Mouse and Squawk discover the Baron's plans to brainwash the world's pets into becoming his personal army of slaves, and they hand him the responsibility of babysitting the Baron's own pet Nero, having craftily swapped him with a robotic impersonator as a means of getting to the Baron's mind control device - the Pet Whistle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pda092f5371bdaf387f43f04cace63c4b</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are made to clean the Cave of Mirrors as punishment for frolicking before a quest is complete, and they accidentally release the Party Harpy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf80b921c507ca0e99023f7222f1a27bf</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>With his crew on the verge of a mutiny, a pirate captain and his parrot order a treasure trove to placate them, leading the Ninjas on a trip to the Egyptian pyramids.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2783968984de9058e40b2c416d3deeab</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall tracks cheetahs across Zambia by motorbike, witnessing epic hunting and the challenges faced by this endangered predator.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fceb6dcae8bced48912e9f9f2bd0e93</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Mark and Lauren get the help of experts to design dream dens for children. Ten-year-old Ben can't get enough of his beloved train set! At the moment though, he shares his bedroom with his four-year-old sister, who turns everything into a train wreck! With no space for his ever-expanding track, Ben is desperate for a den in his garden with space for his dream layout to help keep his trains running on time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p84dc4a41f9b44e1844a6b04ee434e0a7</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. On a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. When a bull wanders into the sheep's field, Shaun discovers that it is a bad idea to make him see red. But then the naughty pigs pour some red paint into the sheep dip.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd7fa9021bbe5f9d4a4cc2900a118dbf8</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface is secretly doing underpants laundry chores for Walter, hoping to help Dennis save up some cash. He urges the gang to audition for a replacement Pieface to make up for his mysterious absence.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0ced6f09c8a135c0107ac2cf9c4bc6b</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface?s hat has been stolen by a Big Ole Worm, and the heroes must quest to get it back. As they trail the worm through the Prickly Desert, Trevor accidentally spikes himself all over on a cactus. But all is not lost ? now that he is covered in sharp spikes, Trevor realises that he has a unique superpower, and when the time comes to confront the Big Ole Worm, it?s Spiky Trevor to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d893098488de351f2861251077cc5bc</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After one of Mouse's inventions accidentally hurts Cat, the kids convince Mouse to go to Farmer Joe's Tech Detox camp to learn how to function without technology.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb527f70cbf4d2b03f38af0bbcc0fb214</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After losing a bet, Mouse and Cheese are forced to spend time with Old Lady McGuire. Their annoyance fades when they realise that they have her huge game room all to themselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e72970cccabbbb1de5e1d3ec864c382</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds a magic shepherd's crook, which he uses to direct the sheep according to his desires.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p26bd434e9877c2bf24c794f7b28b75cf</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Plankton tells Patrick he is his conscience.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd810d91a16d5d9a067eb40584a9f970a</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Rory is bewildered and confused when he finds out a Year 6 girl likes him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7a7ad672382dfe39aab5bf596ff480d7</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>In this two-part season finale, the Odd Squad Mobile Unit must stop a group of villains who want to break into Odd Squad Headquarters to steal an ancient artifact. Little do the Agents know, their greatest challenge will come from someone inside.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa37d7850c3ab328b302d7a082b0dccb7</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>The gang are cleaning Helsing?s swamp-like pool. Pierce is scared to get his new watch wet until he meets a mysterious fish monster named Finn.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80503b9fe16dfa7ebc31cfc572f13a6a</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Bro's in Control stars Adam B, Callum B and Joe Tasker go head-to-head against the Blue Peter presenters in three bonkers battles... with an unexpected prank! Shini goes behind the scenes at Heathrow Airport to discover the epic jobs and secret areas you never usually get to see.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ad36727ce459667469b317a4d815882</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>While falling, Grizzy performs a series of acrobatics that amazes the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p941b78c23a09776a0ea01141c7222e36</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>It's fireworks night! There?s a big display at school, and everyone is there. The Encore dancers set up a stall to raise money for costumes and have enough sweets and treats for everyone ? but they need to sell them all. After months of rehearsals, it's finally opening night for Anything Goes - but will the cast hold their nerve and put on an outstanding performance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p781979e7338fd00165b505f892f58308</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>Tiger Lilly, Summer and Charlie are among 22 children sent to a dance boot camp because of their bad behaviour at school. None of them can dance, and they don?t want to be there.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a891727fede7e0cba1a05241b0e8fa6</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Auditions for the small group dance are held amid personal betrayals and misunderstandings. James apologises to Riley but she cannot bring herself to forgive him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p40fbe41c69536cb0e93f3964c462a799</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Joel takes on his scariest challenge yet as he camps in a tent overnight 500ft in the sky! And to get there he must climb and navigate his way through the slate mines of Honister Pass.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf8b3a99b10afdade637733d318be61a1</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>18 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Animation set on a remote rural farm. Shirley drinks Bitzer's fizzy pop and gets a nasty case of hiccups. None of the cures Shaun tries work, until the Farmer takes a bath.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2074c1c5051c1f5b0581cedd73017d6</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Part one of two. Danger Mouse faces his toughest challenge ever as a mysterious super-villain releases all the villains from Arkwright and plots the end of our hero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pad93a9194a1518da9967732539543b76</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Pieface's first sleepover in the den is troubled by spooky tales of a frightening Fangtom and Walter turning up with a demolition gang determined to flatten the den.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p87cc33fd0a8665db870b7564252cc82f</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The CEO buys Jocko?s old amusement arcade and vows to tear it down. However, Boy loves the arcade and challenges her to an epic video game battle with the fate of the arcade at stake.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p841fc93c4ca27297d05e07073f8d029f</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p40c76b7aec5a1ecd2d8418d65636249d</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>When the archive room floods, the gang are up a creek without a paddle. Adrift on a floating bookshelf with a crew of monsters, the gang's paranoia brings their worst fears to light.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdceb065d275c29f12dea936e6db7266c</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Mr Krabs makes Larry the Lobster temporary manager.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd0e22dd97fb97622e2e8e8094bbc594c</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings build an airborne craft made of Chinese umbrellas to steal the TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p20ddcb21d4ba305bb4c6980243857e09</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The mood of a raccoon becomes contagious to all those around him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb75db3c52b9c0dd7e92cf7f5dcb5de7b</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug must face her own grandmother, who has akumatized into Befana.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pab9ac1d792cd4dd77fa0ac2717721c5e</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Saturday Mash-Up! Live</title>
    <desc>Joe and Shereen are joined by stars of The Traitors - and one of them will be slimed! Cast members from CBBC?s Stage Stars share stories about their new series, and Joe and Shereen take on an epic digger challenge! Kidz Bop perform, and there is cartoon fun with SpongeBob Squarepants! Plus comedy from Awful Coffee and a look at one of this month?s biggest gaming releases in Eat Sleep Game Review.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc3b3be1e4ec83df9ee9fa3c13f268d1e</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Bro's in Control stars Adam B, Callum B and Joe Tasker go head-to-head against the Blue Peter presenters in three bonkers battles... with an unexpected prank! Shini goes behind the scenes at Heathrow Airport to discover the epic jobs and secret areas you never usually get to see.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ad36727ce459667469b317a4d815882</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs make a bug jungle, Chris Howarth makes sand art waves, and Rob Biddulph shows how to draw a furry monster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p37672a63f7ec87e89f34fc36ae95bc34</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>The teams show off their skills on the pitch with FC 24, guided by pro-gamer Slogo. Who will come out on top in this nail-biting showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p24348b85f48eac4fca8fa188a402032c</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Olive and Otto help Ms O host a lunch for some very important but easily offended guests.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6fba4b8962fc601a5f83570d84e362cc</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>In order to save humanity, Olive and Otto must locate a treasure chest that Oscar buried.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd60cd193aa3d5bad27d77f946e36395d</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Spooky Files</title>
    <desc>When the crew find a Spooky that makes people sneeze out the truth, they struggle to keep their Spooky mission a secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc45d001ff2fab254d5e1954b3be6092b</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>Pickle?s parents go to their first earth party, leaving Mia?s annoying sister Tina to babysit her. However, nothing is keeping Pickle from joining the fun.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fc6ce48faf420800eeea339154a0235</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Worst Witch</title>
    <desc>On her birthday, Indigo discovers the shocking truth that her mother has been searching for her for 30 years, while Miss Hardbroom reaches a heartbreaking decision.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbb7d6d74c14f3d973f26c1ae6835e561</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Best mates Riley and Maddie battle a boys' team, and pals Masai and Ernest swap the pitch for the kitchen. Michael Dawson is in Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb9ec97d8e3e1263bc1a76cc84cda911b</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Jamie Johnson</title>
    <desc>Drama series. Kingsmount are through to the cup final at St George's Park, the home of the England national team, and the pressure is immense.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p162f0c6ec7c83386570067056f502e81</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Duncan, Leshawna and Jude vie for corner pieces of Izzy's birthday cake. Who will get one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe2e1748a1a2ebd9e384f8c9c0e17c0dd</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When Owen gets cheated out of a much-wanted ice cream, the kids unite to right the wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0e0faa507faa293dac67782cacaa6f8</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Snowman is hired as Danger Mouse's new sidekick, leaving Penfold without a job.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb9a8b62eb1f051a7a86e10437f9214c</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>There's relief all around when Penfold's pilfering of Squawk's gadgets and clandestine late night trips to shady warehouses turns out to be preparation for his taking part in 'bot battles' - a fight club for homemade robots. Penfold hopes to enter his own creation, Geoff, into the competition but is sidelined by an overeager Danger Mouse and his own robot, the CRN 3000! When the CRN 3000 obliterates all challengers, DM's call for a worthy opponent is answered by Megahurtz. But Megahurtz may have a secret android army agenda..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pde29da8858858630df09e3d74b98aad8</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold are in a training simulation when one of DM's flying kicks damages the holodeck with catastrophic consequences. They wake to find they have been in a three-year dream, that they aren't secret agents and work in IT instead, and the Danger Agency has been a figment of their imaginations! Whilst Penfold and Squawk quickly settle into a life of menial office work, DM struggles to accept life as Dane G Mouse.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2be9862d6d9621fc75eda5af2c518c22</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the kids convince Mum and Dad to take part in a family-friendly TV game show, they unwittingly kick-start an over-the-top rivalry which threatens family peace.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3e34f81b247411a4beb10866bfd9dd4</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids visit an eco-camp to learn how to grow vegetables. Unfortunately, the Smith twins are also there and have no intention of pulling their weight.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b79e6f21331e9d0af4c6704b5c5c660</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Boy and Girl start receiving lavish gifts addressed to ?two great kids?, Mouse thinks it must be a mistake. He and Dog set out to investigate whether these presents are meant for someone else, but the other kids don't like that idea at all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p83183b454813d61ba000f321722fff50</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings use magic Chinese lanterns for sound and light shows.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc5e5b2b6e0498ea0f97679ba5f75b9a4</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find a mask that terrifies anyone who looks at it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1940c1b33ce8f0692bb0dbf611d37b6</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings crack the codex system of a mysterious box and are sucked into it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e5fff82fda3d97623ba81a31c11afdb</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes wake up on Snow Day morning, there isn?t a snowflake in sight! The heroes must quest to free the Snow Dragon and save Snow Day for all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70e545bcacb2d124e1fd8b0469e27b2a</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Mr Friendlyface?s hat has been stolen by a Big Ole Worm, and the heroes must quest to get it back. As they trail the worm through the Prickly Desert, Trevor accidentally spikes himself all over on a cactus. But all is not lost ? now that he is covered in sharp spikes, Trevor realises that he has a unique superpower, and when the time comes to confront the Big Ole Worm, it?s Spiky Trevor to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d893098488de351f2861251077cc5bc</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The forest has run out of bath sponges and is becoming very stinky. Their latest order never arrived, and so the heroes must quest under the sea to Merhaven to collect them. However, Hoofius, whose singing stinks worse than his armpits, decides to enter the annual Merhaven Song Contest and accidentally causes a simple quest to collect bath sponges to turn into something much more perilous.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ed5d646aa33c0f016a4f842cc22d80c</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Salam City goes dark when the power goes out, but Mansour finds a clever solution.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf9fc7e52810177a3801b603b4cf0b803</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Adventures of Mansour: Age of AI</title>
    <desc>Mansour and friends have a surprising and confusing encounter with a very different Blink.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d071457a6abec7f0701d8494f703c07</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>Caleb is desperate to put his relationship with Priya back together, while the campers tear apart the largest objects they can find.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc85496d685398077382f30da5229846</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>A prehistoric sponge is unfrozen and causes chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0dc730653145e151cb5ab24672b98545</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:45PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>A flock of clams descend on Bikini Bottom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdfca11fd35d063c2f9ff48721d046a1e</image>
    <start>06:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm, where Shaun's flock live a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. Shaun's hijinks with the rotary clothes line end up making the Farmer's washing filthy - so the race is on to get it clean again before he finds out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96869896002a4ac9f3819da319113c89</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Second of two parts. Danger Mouse faces his toughest challenge ever as a mysterious super-villain releases all the villains from Arkwright and plots the end of our hero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe62c1a98a6a993b1b609fda59528d5d</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The class dig up a mysterious time capsule which sets them off on a race to find hidden treasure before Walter or a greed-crazed Paul the Potato can find it first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p659edd59775ca7523bb64a0d16d30e47</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>K-Jam is moving into the neighbourhood and staying with the family for a while. However, Girl gets insecure and thinks that her awesome best friend is trying to take her place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbace25267391c527963e66f359240ab</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8b1e781d86b3c267ed2e2cbf279449d2</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Something wicca this way comes when Witchy is released early, trading a bottle in the archive room for a new broom with a view and leaving Pierce disenchanted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5badf274218ccc4f3bcba74374228182</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Patrick leads a stranger around Bikini Bottom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p19b3d890a68b01014ae82a46077e0608</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds an electrode that controls a robot, and the Lemmings plot to take it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14a442001db4c31977f8ed627d7ed027</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover tai chi movements that generate balls of energy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b9957284a15c047dd703c3b45dbab9b</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug faces a young singer who has turned into Frightningale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb14af49296eee598f737636d2b900d91</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Bro's in Control stars Adam B, Callum B and Joe Tasker go head-to-head against the Blue Peter presenters in three bonkers battles... with an unexpected prank! Shini goes behind the scenes at Heathrow Airport to discover the epic jobs and secret areas you never usually get to see.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ad36727ce459667469b317a4d815882</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>It's the start of a new school year, and the school is buzzing as boarders find out who they are sharing a dorm with and day pupils reunite at the lockers. No time is wasted on day one as the students go head-to-head for roles in the new show: Anything Goes. And this year could be life-changing for dancer Jakob as he starts his preparations for one of the world?s most prestigious international ballet competitions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe43e8702039ee3f0a37066f6e5bc0013</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:50AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Cooking Buddies</title>
    <desc>Buddy and Conker get a call from Sienna, a footballer who needs Buddy?s help. Her grandparents? wedding anniversary is coming up and she wants to cook something to surprise them. Buddy knows that making pizzas from scratch is bound to score well with everyone, so they make their own dough and tomato sauce, and choose their own toppings to make personalised pizzas (with faces!) that everyone will love. This time, Conker also has a playmate as Sienna brings her little pug, Bella with her. Conker tries to impress Bella with his jokes as they both cheer Buddy and Sienna on! Taking a break from their ?Keepy Uppy Pizzas?, Sienna drills Buddy on the football pitch, challenging his fitness by racing him with parachutes on their backs, dribbling to test his control of the ball and learning to do rainbow flicks, before going into the ultimate penalty shootout. Join Buddy, Conker, Sienna and Bella in this fun and tasty episode of Cooking Buddies that scores big. You can get all of Buddy?s recipes, and LOADS more, at bbc.co.uk\/food.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f434b14b3b46f480cbd0e8a48981672</image>
    <start>09:50AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>So Awkward</title>
    <desc>Lily gets a part-time job waitressing at Mugshotsz Caf?, determined to prove to straight-talking owner Lou that teenagers make good workers. However, her mission goes wrong when Jas gets a job at the caf? too. Jas is messy and thoughtless, which upends Lily?s need for perfection, yet Lou thinks Jas is brilliant. Meanwhile, Sid has been invited to audition for a performing arts college. Rob is upset that Sid may leave Cranmede, and Mr Malone is annoyed that his free guitar lessons will end. Torn between going to the audition or not, Sid turns to Jas for advice. Ollie has a girlfriend, Kat, which Martha finds nauseating. She is unnerved that Kat attends Cranmede, has persuaded Ollie to set up a tech company with her, and worse still, has taken Martha?s seat in the caf?, forcing her to sit away from the power socket.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbacb82dc335880b8f053135da87a7b36</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>The leisure centre is hosting a roller disco later that afternoon and Joy tells Danny and Mick if they want to be at the disco they need to finish every job on her list first. Danny spots a way to get some skating practice in and finish the jobs in double quick time ? by doing all their work on wheels! Unfortunately, when a runaway Danny crashes through the disco it looks like the whole thing might be off. Can Mick save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52e4ee264a5d8048836ac7900ce9cffb</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>The centre needs to be decorated for a wedding later today, but Danny?s more interested in his new invention ? which unfortunately blows through every toilet roll in the centre. When Mick distracts him mid-order, he accidentally requests 10,000 toilet rolls instead of 100 by express delivery, and they arrive in a whole mountain of boxes. Fearing Joy?s reaction, the boys decide to hide the loo rolls.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3ecc6e1702eeac871d1350e3e6a88646</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum is a Little Bro in control! His Big Bro Adam is going up against best mate Joe to see who will win a series of funny, gungy and gross challenges, and who?ll take on a forfeit from the Wheel of Doom. Callum isn?t taking any nonsense, so they have to work hard to impress him! The National Art Gallery has called: they need replicas making ASAP! It?s a job for Big Bro and Big Joe... using flour and gunge, natch. But whose art will be fit for a gallery, and whose will fail? Little Bro Callum decides the winner in this epic art showdown. Not all is lost, as the loser gets a chance to redeem themselves in the No Hands Challenge. Who can set up a Date Night using only their pockets, their wits and a giant shark with a violin? Sound extra? Callum?s challenges definitely are in this hilarious, gross and gungy contest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0773f124bfcc55203ef81a9817b791c7</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Giant is pranked by Nitro when he appears as a guest of honour at a fake school award ceremony! The other Gladiators have sneaky fun backstage at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe24d7c7ee4f1aef3442ee32cdd611f0c</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve and the team embark on a truly incredible adventure across the vast island of Madagascar. Many of the creatures they meet cannot be found anywhere else in the world. From gremlin-like aye-ayes to Madagascar's most ferocious carnivore, Steve has some unique encounters as he searches for contenders for the Deadly 60.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb6612f6d349b2d1396babb7ec2820694</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors celebrate as the NHS turns 75. They award Ouch Hero medals in the hospital, hear Ouchers? big NHS stories and travel through time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8c1733ea13c7085a5e0a93025673013a</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>In a special musical episode of the award-winning Horrible Histories, host Rattus Rattus chooses his favourite songs from the fourth series to entertain his young nephew.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9833b9ef0b1aaba4c381c12f8668a232</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Big Brain has a chemical catastrophe, Sir Isaac Newton rides a coaster again, with shocking results, Loofah is after a murderer, and Dr Henry VIII on call.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peee6d9a3675c97b17d21716f58b7d6ed</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Man Ray rents Squidward's house.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p110a8b96185ebf2ed896d5b6702bd462</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Mr Krabs makes Larry the Lobster temporary manager.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd0e22dd97fb97622e2e8e8094bbc594c</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob is afraid to leave the Krusty Krab roof.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3abb572d932ffb348185a0d80de3f6bd</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Having transformed himself into a teenager to help expose a nest of vampires at school, Helsing displays no class when he joins Daisy's bullies instead.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe95e5a989ec6fe9443e3864f2352f0a5</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Defending the house on Halloween, Charlie is in for a fright when Pierce invites the neighbourhood (and at least one monster) over for a costume party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p68c8d66eaa392128e8f3a1074c76a006</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>While riding their scooters at the park, the bickering kids meet the Smiths. A brother and sister who don't seem to argue like our gang does - in fact, the two Smiths are super-supportive of each other! When they start pushing the other kids around, Boy, Girl, Dog, Cat, Mouse and Cheese challenge the Smiths to a race around the park! But our heroes have one problem - Cat doesn't know how to ride a scooter! The kids take turns teaching her and, when race day comes, Cat will really need to kick it into high gear if she wants to help the family beat those smug Smiths.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fd76bdc48953edfd54c15e16338e394</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:45PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse buys a video game that is supposed to teach the family teamwork. When they end up bickering as they play, Mouse creates a robot that turns off the game if they argue. However, a robot malfunction places the whole family in danger. To survive they will have to finish the video game without arguing - unless they can think of a way to make bickering help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5254962cb1e76d16d6aef47dd42d2b0b</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>With Boy's new help-for-hire business booming, he overworks his unpaid employee, Dog, without realizing. Dog is too loyal to say no, but he's miserable, especially when his next job is walking some mean cats. Girl sets out to teach Dog a lesson about standing up for himself, pretending to lose the cats to make Dog realize he should have said no to Boy, which will teach him to do just that in the future! But when the cats really go missing, they frantically set out to find them before Boy's business is ruined.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd34a23b7cb8266ab6bf47342b3519166</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Noah tries to rescue the chocolates Owen forgot outside before something else steals them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe990410924ceb1db2243b7a84a432d8e</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Courtney must go all day without correcting her friends, regardless of what they do wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe12d009fb4b08949cdf975f6bbb47a8</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>A walkie-talkie hidden inside a chili dog causes Harold to worry an alien has arrived.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd55181ac1b0277a6a03b77b9b2b7602a</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A container full of Yummy? What a dream for Grizzy and the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa0fb4c14616b7fac90132c14ceaa7f84</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>After the Yeti's house is destroyed, the Lemmings are quick to point the finger at Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p08d177e86e46cf42f4ecb3cb64daa9c2</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Jun does a Tarot reading and interprets its meaning to be that the riders will disband.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p921f51c780aea1bc664cf581d5e5b551</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Brodie discovers something huge about Chelsey?s past that threatens her relationship with her twin, Keira. Meanwhile, Frankie sets out to prove he is the true Chaos Master of the DG.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1aaf6800fccc18d51819344646971c72</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Addie?s council event hangs in the balance when a grumpy Miriam refuses to reveal her secret. Meanwhile, Iona holds band auditions and finds a surprising lead singer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56849dd6eddeabf135280a0c5d23a971</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>It's the start of a new school year, and the school is buzzing as boarders find out who they are sharing a dorm with and day pupils reunite at the lockers. No time is wasted on day one as the students go head-to-head for roles in the new show: Anything Goes. And this year could be life-changing for dancer Jakob as he starts his preparations for one of the world?s most prestigious international ballet competitions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe43e8702039ee3f0a37066f6e5bc0013</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Meet the Tottenham Hotspur academy players. Lia Lewis picks her Three of the Best, and Dominic Solanke takes on 11-year-old Konan in Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p88eec7f914b4c5e2f11d416e2a1eaf76</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>Julia gets between Caleb and Priya during the most painful memory game of all time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d656e5bd2675f07c2ceecdd81f59549</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Plankton's pet amoeba Spot has puppies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3aec6731d44095522f9d9a86d66803dd</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Mr Krabs is too scared to get his physical.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc83b687ea889f4f6d02736b5f0be2494</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>While falling, Grizzy performs a series of acrobatics that amazes the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p723cb1057326be4e83853b78617595a0</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Animated adventures with the mischievous young sheep and his flock. Shaun and Bitzer discover that a visitor to the farm is not as cute and adorable as she seems.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p113da15aa6ff745d88153ce098d4d1c0</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold accompany Professor Squawkencluck to the Brainiac Symposium - the annual science convention, where King Kong Brunels's latest misfiring invention, the Cow Trainer, reminds his fellow boffins exactly why he is the laughing stock of the scientist community. When King Kong Brunel suggests that the Professor's success is all due to her privileged life as Danger Agency lab technician with scientist parents, an irked Squawk uses Brunel's Cow Trainer to swap bodies with him in order to show that she could be just as successful in his shoes. However, she soon finds that life as King Kong Brunel is as dispiriting as he makes out, as she is laughed out of the symposium when masquerading as her simian adversary. Elsewhere, an opportunistic King Kong Brunel finds himself revelling at playing Squawk, as finds he himself inside her lab having hitched a lift back to HQ with an unwitting Danger Mouse and Penfold. On discovering the truth, Danger Mouse and Penfold have the body- swapper turned on them, as KKB escapes back to the convention with his newly acquired Squawk-shaped credibility, and a new invention so poorly put together that it could end the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10d782c873c5cb440e14211052a06036</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Hoofius plays his grandfaun?s old magical panpipes, his friends do exactly what he asks them to do - perfect for leading a quest... or so he thinks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbada50b36a9303ac56775c369e7c2be0</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids want to impress Gramps by completing the Gauntlet of Greatness carnival attraction that he did when he was their age. However, Dog and Girl just can't seem to beat it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db98e87d457a49378a84e78a275e08d</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf0a915ab271c1c9c1e1b2a33188e7991</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings invent a whole bunch of bouncing games with spongy jelly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe74f0b84aee020f2055f16fd17fbfae0</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings happen upon a bracelet that increases the strength of its wearer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf006c51e34db491fb6b6a7f5babd196</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>The long-lost episode of Mermaid Man is finally showing on TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbf9a7e2afdc7aa6d3136c4226bae6879</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Villain Miss Information is using graphs to spread falsehoods about Odd Squad, which is leading to the public not trusting them. Can Captain O get the public back on side.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81bd195210835185fd3d564b62fdc1a6</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>When an ex-chores boy reappears wearing Helsing?s invisibility jacket, the gang is tasked with destroying it. But can Pierce resist the temptation to be bad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb3ce24ec5d9349cd2520f3d380cbd25</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>A special visit from the mayor means that his chains need putting away safely, while he goes for a swim. As head of security, Mick locks them in Joy?s safe, but due to his forgetfulness, Danny and Mick now need to work out another way to retrieve them before the mayor returns.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67d3bf33fe7afe0b424f8e1914b79a2f</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Numbers to 100, finding one more and one less, signs and symbols.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8497519bb2385402291d2ce16bce6065</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Could you build a slide to the other side of the world? You would need to start in space, use the slippiest slide ever and make sure you have enough supplies before you go down it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c93e4b0e1fc4adb5f1d0842be1d0abe</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Out of This World</title>
    <desc>In this episode, Dr Maggie tells the story of the Space Race, what it was, the key missions involved and how the USA, competing against and then collaborating with the Soviet Union, got us to where we are today in space. Dr Maggie?s guest is Tim Peake, the first British astronaut to live on board ISS, who tells us how astronauts from different countries successfully work together in space. Dr Maggie also answers your space questions and unveils her top five 'firsts in space'. Buckle up, it?s time to go Out Of this World.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ae90359fda623e4c4cca90584ac5fec</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>The girls get creative as Daisy and her friends give the common room a colourful makeover. Eva and Evie enter the school photography competition, with some top tips from wildlife presenter Megan McCubbin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p284c6a12a13bdaf11b948cf74d39429b</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs get festival-ready as they craft carnival headwear, artist Lakwena Maciver makes a grey rooftop pop with paint, and Abi Clarke draws a pirouetting otter in a tutu.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0953a9c9704625e78726ab7d76ad8ed3</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The One Zoo Three zoo celebrates the opening of some amazing new animal habitats with a new den for the sun bears - but will the jaguars feature pad be a bit hit or miss.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82c799404a8b398ad1720b5d28fab278</image>
    <start>10:20AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Archie is ten years old and as well as planting, growing and harvesting vegetables, he loves looking after his chickens. Archie sells his home grown veg and eggs locally and uses the profits to buy food for his local food bank. He's taken his enterprise as far as he can and desperately needs a farm den so he can increase his productivity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56791e20903f1fb7af1af660dda2480a</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius: Monster Builds</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom go supersized in this massive movers spectacular in which they trace the origins of the genius ideas that have made shifting heavy weights a whole lot easier. In their element, the boys head to a scrapyard to find out how hydraulic grabbers work, get up close to one of the weirdest-looking aircraft ever built and get to grips, literally, with the world's largest hydraulic hand.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f2118c4c2ca8416715ca1a3003f20f5</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories returns for a special about King John and Magna Carta, starring Ben Miller. John annoys the barons and agrees Magna Carta at Runnymede after a banging rap battle. Meanwhile, across the world, we meet the formidable Genghis Khan in Mongolia and catch up with the crafty Saladin during the Crusades. With, of course, our host Rattus to guide the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p704659bf05f3ee09e78f5adba8ddd40d</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It's staff charity cabaret night at the Pottsfield Leisure Centre and special guest and ventriloquist Paul Zerdin is performing. When his sidekick Sam goes missing. Danny and Mick have to step up to perform their own ventriloquist act.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7994c29c48222559183f36600d7e659f</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Danny needs a cake for his parents? wedding, and fast! The band deliver a cake, but Mac?s size-shifting machine causes chaos, and they have an angry wedding organiser to contend with.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1cbb1d1ebd8080b7915706128afa381</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Bionic ends up dressed as a rabbit when Nitro pranks him at a fake photoshoot, and the rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes as they prank the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf7d7f9299d05e5c92784905daf4991d</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated deep sea adventure series. Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. When an underwater tremor separates the Gup-X and its crew, Barnacles seeks guidance from a mysterious sea turtle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f9f6d55e7dfb1bfbda6c8a0a55e82dd</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad and Cosima both think they're the best at pranking. Their prank war quickly spirals out of control, until Big Lizard finally reveals Proxima's real pranking champion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea0f60cf71247ea3d276941d6971e477</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>If being zapped with a mind-controlling Mindzooka ray by a couple of D-list villains wasn't bad enough, Danger Mouse's shame goes viral thanks to a series of embarrassing videos. Determined to stop the release of the most incriminating video of all, Danger Mouse turns to the villain behind the mind-control tech - the incarcerated Crumhorn! Crumhorn offers an anti-mind control device, but it comes with a catch - he has to be temporarily released back to Crumcorp Towers to retrieve it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p402f93b5d6cb5e8e2fc05b79645fff74</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes set out on a quest to find out who is draining colour from the forest and muster all their positivity to save it from greyness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3d4f995b8c3040f9e2b17fe57dfa29f</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When a parrot steals a fisherman?s lucky captain's hat, the Ninjas search for a replacement on a cruise ship, only for Konpeki and Aka to get distracted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e8f614bd723264869f90ef1bf1f4b24</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve dives with 100 grey nurse sharks - aka ragged-tooth sharks - a wobbegong and a gigantic whale shark, and he joins a mission in Indonesia to save sharks from over-fishing with eco-tourism.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdcc05d21452d9faf35f104aaea0c088f</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>In a bid to prove that girls are just as good at football as boys, Felicity and June disguise Clarissa. Meanwhile, Darrell and Susan help Mr Murray with his chamber investigation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd011de15557cf8f3fdef27c8afd96390</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. Shaun finds the farmer's old record player on the dump and organises a rave in the barn, but trouble looms when the naughty pigs gatecrash the party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d85e8a5e8a7604eacfba23dddab4e8d</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s time for Gnasher?s annual bath, but the stinky hound will do anything to avoid the tub. Dennis and Gnasher go head to head in a town-wide game of cat and mouse ? or rather, tripe hound and wheelie bathtub.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cd3695300ecc962061ac4a3338675c2</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The forest has run out of bath sponges and is becoming very stinky. Their latest order never arrived, and so the heroes must quest under the sea to Merhaven to collect them. However, Hoofius, whose singing stinks worse than his armpits, decides to enter the annual Merhaven Song Contest and accidentally causes a simple quest to collect bath sponges to turn into something much more perilous.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ed5d646aa33c0f016a4f842cc22d80c</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After breaking their games console, the kids decide to sell Boy's homemade cookies to raise money for a new one. All is well until they get some unexpected competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/ped62b0d7cfc54d8c982819332e593aa3</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Susie and Dog set aside their differences to partner up for a figure-skating competition. All is well until they realise that someone is sabotaging them and their chances of winning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42f9e79e93d36b6515c3a875959500de</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The jelly cake battle takes on epic dimensions into a 'heroic fantasy' world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7540cfc28a15de2ef3fc5c8015f20b14</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob invents a new persona.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p15a3e516d535e143ed23b99e8ae441e0</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>The others try to cheer Rory up after he is punished and sent to the office.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6853721e6e0a07518571c0a31c3f1c4d</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>With a spike in oddness in the UK, Department of Help agent Ozzie suggests they send for help from the best agent in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2daff7b5a508d12e0255a7449c918759</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Charlie uses Helsing?s time remote to bring a heavily muscled future version of himself back to the present to change his life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf77616ab1a39e80807a661849b4d161a</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>A walkie-talkie hidden inside a chili dog causes Harold to worry an alien has arrived.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd55181ac1b0277a6a03b77b9b2b7602a</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko, Roy and Dot jump into action when the Explorers stage an attack on Naranja Academy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe6a25376dd9d029398b4d31755dde01c</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>With Christmas around the corner, the juniors give a festive performance at the local town fair. Meanwhile, it's time for Encore's end-of-term performance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc3462f0723775ab4ee62e020a81d77a7</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Gwen is shocked into drastic action when her father refuses to sign her application to finishing school. Meanwhile, Darrell and Felicity fall out during the North Tower Spelling Bee.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d81b1dd5f4376b5dc9a2f540ed83af0</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio. James and Riley struggle with their duet. Michelle demands an answer from Eldon - why is he avoiding her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe139849510e43a951abbc6f52b345676</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings end up lost after misplacing their jar of Yummy in a labyrinth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6adf7709b4293ae1023ab4a70b88ad6</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
