<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas battle a hungry space blob as they try to fulfill an order for a flag for astronaut Lewis Weaklegs to plant on the moon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa72aa11d357947a4eb9393e0f89a1c2e</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve is underwater in Indonesia with funny-looking frogfish, a stargazer, flamboyant cuttlefish, a mimic octopus and a Bobbit worm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p05d0ffe9c9db73525c7c9d7a55013bde</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>After stealing from Matron?s safe, Jo and Connie are too afraid to own up and go on the run. Fred attempts to help them escape, but it?s not long before Darrell catches up.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p24166c67de4f6cfb9a8d76ae2e0370ff</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>This time on Shark Bites, Steve Backshall meets one of the ocean's greatest sharks. The oceanic whitetip is an adventurer of the abyss. Steve and his crew track down this nautical nomad in the Pacific Ocean off the coast of Hawaii. In the empty ocean, they are constantly on the move searching for food, relying on some vital features - their fins. Back in Steve's Shark Lab, he reveals how the shark uses its different fins for perfect power and sensitive steering.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7f05e9050815d3dc812a2b05206bdb71</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Intrigued by a horror film on television, Timmy wanders into the farmhouse late one night. Shaun's rescue mission convinces the Farmer that the place is haunted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69270eb66e8c141c109ea661f900dd4b</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Convinced that Mrs Creecher is secretly a master of Blamjitsu, JJ persuades the gang to help trick her into revealing her blam credentials.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p631f5a239e4e0ec4323d1cb7272bc565</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes have found the Wishing Trident, which will help them on their quest to prevent the summoning of the legendary two-headed dragon, Iceburn. The problem is, Blossom has used one wish by mistake, and Herbert has accidentally used a second one. Now the heroes are left to defeat the dragon using only one wish, a never-ending ice cream cone (with sprinkles) and a giant spicy sausage hat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf940465ee4740a280d4541c1e5c9723d</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After accidentally destroying Ms Rodriguez's flowers, Girl enlists her siblings to help her cover up the accident.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4615ee002e64bd6c224b1b27c9e288ca</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>It's time for the First Day of Summer Festival, and Cheese is ready to perform for the whole town. However, she is so excited that she refuses to listen to warnings about an imminent heatwave.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e34d62f8fd44838aa3d1c6a0cc6dc1e</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings plot to remove the bear from the castle and prevent him from returning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p19d0bfe8e3ed2a98dca54b9d08058172</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Plankton hasn't tried to steal the formula in a while..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb2a92a68099badb07c32c3850e4f31f8</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>While Atticus's parents are away, his Ya-Ya makes disgusting lunches for him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fe16f5c005c04a154841223577386f4</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When things start turning into delicious puddings, Ozzie and Orli are taken on a tour of the town, which leads them to... a tour of the town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0dcddf159a14a8e76cddf5dfe85d2fd3</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Que?s beloved pet Snorp is undergoing some wild changes, and she is not sure she is going to like what comes out the other side.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p368f7fd9b21b56c3e30d27ff4848f78c</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Leshawna creates a paint-balloon fight to decide who she will take to an amusement park.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd7c0c7f590fb463746b3ee96bdc467cb</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Back on the Brave Olivine, Liko, Roy and Dot receive an unexpected challenge to battle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc610269f8f8b3a6cfce6acc923f40f3</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>Dancer Jakob has trained so hard to earn a place at one of the world?s most prestigious international ballet competitions - but will his hard work be worth it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p91658bc56dc21f5ae8079241584b8ec9</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>After a prank goes wrong, Max must prove himself to his family by leading the Hawx U14s to victory against Foxborough ? by any means necessary.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc2b38b54ba8602d9fa90f2f484a3343e</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>As the studio grows in popularity it must make space for new members of J-Troupe. Michelle and Amanda promote the studio at their school while the others mentor J-Troupe. Daniel gives Kate an ultimatum.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8974061e1d2c1e1b710b0b00a8282ebe</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall meets the most ferocious shark of all. The great white shark is one of the greatest hunters on the planet, and Steve looks at what it is that makes them such perfect predators. He dives with them in the open ocean, revealing clever camouflage, and heads into his shark lab to take a closer look at their terrific teeth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9e37c6c60a7579827f1d1690c50dd33b</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>22 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Set on a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. It is a scorching hot day and the flock are desperate to cool down in the sheep dip, but there is one thing in their way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99247af3bb54dbfb5b21c8add5c3b739</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Jeopardy Mouse are on a mission in space - will they work together as a team? In the midst of an interstellar team-up, a bickering Danger Mouse and Jeopardy Mouse crash-land on a desolate planet. While Penfold, Squawkencluck and King Kong Brunel search for a way to bring the pair back to Earth, the stubborn pair split up in their new surroundings. DM and Jeopardy Mouse are brought back together when they're captured by a horde of Fly People - the planet isn't deserted after all! The Fly People's hatred of DM is explained when our hero is reunited with Lionel the huge World Wide Spider, who he accidentally sent to the planet of the flies. Lionel's fondness for snacking on the local population has landed him a place on the menu - he's going to be fed to the terrifying pit-dwelling 'Beast', and now DM and Jeopardy are going to be eaten too! Will DM and JM finally resolve to cooperate to get out of this perilous position.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6d72d4eed999a80d4b929f9cf71a337</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Much to Trevor?s irritation, a rare phoenix woodpecker takes a liking to him - so he demands an immediate quest to return the bird to its real home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd460f05ee8f6efe98ada93b746aa74d</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Everyone is excited for the annual camping trip with Gramps, but when Cheese wins an invitation to a big movie premiere, she lies and says she has to stay home for charity work.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa9f68c8c20c4d3ca7eb8e7eaaa3c57ec</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p441ff792fce0cfefb18d6870b9c5fb0c</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings meet fairies, one of which breathes life into their bagpipes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52ca24e90332e5cc7495b2699e4a3e40</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds a magic shepherd's crook, which he uses to direct the sheep according to his desires.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p26bd434e9877c2bf24c794f7b28b75cf</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>A gang of kids steal the Krusty Krab's grill.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p01e67e2c4bbe079242398b7907e24bb9</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Orli has rescued a clam which needs to be returned to its home in the 60th dimension via a portal on the 60th floor. However, to get there, she must negotiate HQ?s odd lift network.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11c6ba8b45b8289f8bd5234f041ac147</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:40AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Charlie is cool with Que possessing him, especially when he has a book report due! But what happens when she refuses to get out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc1f59d0445d6c0ea79a16b631e0d18ba</image>
    <start>08:40AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It is the Webbthorpe's summer fete, and Danny and Mick want to take the cash prize by winning the biggest pumpkin competition. All they need now is try and grow the biggest pumpkin ever, whatever way possible - but will their cheating ways be successful.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p95beb47a004cf724c4e358876ee751cc</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 9-11 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about negative numbers and adding and subtracting.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8cbce02485a3c8b3c2beb1097d8fb56a</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Bugs might be annoying, but we would soon regret it if we got rid of them - all our favourite foods would disappear, and there would be dung everywhere.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p532a0dbc87e381353d1a16b1b7ba941a</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Out of This World</title>
    <desc>In this episode, Dr Maggie reveals the game changers of space missions and spacecraft, from the space shuttle to the Hubble Space Telescope, that have transformed our lives on Earth and beyond. Dr Maggie?s star guest is Nasa astronaut Kathy Sullivan, who is a game changer herself. She flew in the space shuttle three times, delivered Hubble into orbit and was the first American woman to walk in space! Dr Maggie also counts down the Top 5 Most Expensive Missions and all your space questions are answered in Ask Maggie. Buckle up, it?s time to go Out of This World.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b0b18cdbf99d1277bb1a522f910d51d</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Since being diagnosed with scoliosis and undergoing spinal surgery, Emily hasn?t been able to follow her passion for dance. However, with the help of best friend Lottie and a special visitor, that is all about to change.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p239155d5e1604c3544690ff6df2dfe2e</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs craft cardboard games consoles you can actually play, Julian Beever warps reality with a pavement pork pie, and Tilly Lockey draws a shimmering mermaid.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12cc636ed9e0b0dcaabe47f036b4ec55</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:20AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The brothers celebrate some of the zoo?s strongest swimmers. Can Cam tempt the jaguars into their new pool? And who will win the tapir food raft challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p16346c1c6677039f3fb76f27fc1c261c</image>
    <start>10:20AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Nine-year-old Campbell loves cycling and uses rollers to train at home, but there isn't much room and he has to move the sofa to put the rollers down. His mum and dad are getting fed up of the oil he gets everywhere. Campbell needs a cycling den where he can cycle all over the world without getting oil on his parents' sofa.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe116654b61b01cde9a60ddbf604e520b</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius: Monster Builds</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom are under attack in this high-octane tour through defensive engineering. The boys delve into the work of three geniuses whose ideas have given us impregnable castles and reinforced concrete bunkers and may one day protect planet Earth from asteroid attack! To top things off, they head to the seaside for a mega-sized game of smash the sandcastle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa86d12e1c48a60d2d7ae59645c321e6b</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A special episode about William the Conqueror, starring Kevin Eldon. We meet young William, Duke of Normandy, as he quarrels with Harold Godwinson about who should be king of England, before bashing the English and taking the crown at the famous Battle of Hastings in 1066! Meanwhile, across the world, we discover Chinese technology light years ahead of the dunderheaded Normans and Saxons in England, and meet one of the world's first scientists in Egypt. With, of course, our host Rattus to guide the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p63d9c6a5eb1a107c683cee66aa0b8f03</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>April Fool?s day at the leisure centre can only mean one thing - more pranks than normal! Sharon tries to ban them, but there is a mystery pranker whose identity not even Danny knows. Meanwhile, Mick has his own idea of what an April fool is.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81690ef994195308e5212654f9e03359</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>The Odd Socks go back in time to help the young Maid Marian rescue treasure from the wicked Sheriff of Nottingham.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6d7be6b7038862730825899086258ec</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Diamond prank Comet at a fake Christmas calendar photoshoot. The other Gladiators have sneaky fun pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5cd8bf081d5ab1bc368bae668e80dd2d</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. Whether it's a perilous voyage to the bottom of the sea or the piratey pursuit of a giant squid, the Octonauts leap into action. The Octonauts are exploring Antarctica when Shellington discovers strange microscopic creatures living under the ice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p242d7c633b4f9fd6586900df211d6a72</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Rex is missing, but Dad, Cosima and Big Lizard need him to save them from a giant slug.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd05492cf93c8626bd0f248b5750c1ac2</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse inherits the ancient but sprightly MK3 car after the beloved MK4 gets jammed-up. But Penfold is suspicious when the MK3 is determined to have DM all to himself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paafdc13fd551ca2258f2e20f604f4d55</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse arrives in ancient Greece and befriends Zeus who grants him godly powers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pccc67fffbc56a07a3ea6d76b511f35c9</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>To avoid Herbert?s surprise visits via his tunnels in the Big Birch, the other heroes take any quest and must deal with an angry plant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1712e7d54bc565d7f40c59dd3788f999</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>The Ninjas battle a hungry space blob as they try to fulfill an order for a flag for astronaut Lewis Weaklegs to plant on the moon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa72aa11d357947a4eb9393e0f89a1c2e</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve is underwater in Indonesia with funny-looking frogfish, a stargazer, flamboyant cuttlefish, a mimic octopus and a Bobbit worm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p05d0ffe9c9db73525c7c9d7a55013bde</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>After stealing from Matron?s safe, Jo and Connie are too afraid to own up and go on the run. Fred attempts to help them escape, but it?s not long before Darrell catches up.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p24166c67de4f6cfb9a8d76ae2e0370ff</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>This time on Shark Bites, Steve Backshall meets one of the ocean's greatest sharks. The oceanic whitetip is an adventurer of the abyss. Steve and his crew track down this nautical nomad in the Pacific Ocean off the coast of Hawaii. In the empty ocean, they are constantly on the move searching for food, relying on some vital features - their fins. Back in Steve's Shark Lab, he reveals how the shark uses its different fins for perfect power and sensitive steering.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7f05e9050815d3dc812a2b05206bdb71</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Intrigued by a horror film on television, Timmy wanders into the farmhouse late one night. Shaun's rescue mission convinces the Farmer that the place is haunted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69270eb66e8c141c109ea661f900dd4b</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Convinced that Mrs Creecher is secretly a master of Blamjitsu, JJ persuades the gang to help trick her into revealing her blam credentials.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p631f5a239e4e0ec4323d1cb7272bc565</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes have found the Wishing Trident, which will help them on their quest to prevent the summoning of the legendary two-headed dragon, Iceburn. The problem is, Blossom has used one wish by mistake, and Herbert has accidentally used a second one. Now the heroes are left to defeat the dragon using only one wish, a never-ending ice cream cone (with sprinkles) and a giant spicy sausage hat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf940465ee4740a280d4541c1e5c9723d</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After accidentally destroying Ms Rodriguez's flowers, Girl enlists her siblings to help her cover up the accident.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4615ee002e64bd6c224b1b27c9e288ca</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>It's time for the First Day of Summer Festival, and Cheese is ready to perform for the whole town. However, she is so excited that she refuses to listen to warnings about an imminent heatwave.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e34d62f8fd44838aa3d1c6a0cc6dc1e</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings plot to remove the bear from the castle and prevent him from returning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p19d0bfe8e3ed2a98dca54b9d08058172</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Plankton hasn't tried to steal the formula in a while..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb2a92a68099badb07c32c3850e4f31f8</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>While Atticus's parents are away, his Ya-Ya makes disgusting lunches for him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fe16f5c005c04a154841223577386f4</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When things start turning into delicious puddings, Ozzie and Orli are taken on a tour of the town, which leads them to... a tour of the town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0dcddf159a14a8e76cddf5dfe85d2fd3</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Que?s beloved pet Snorp is undergoing some wild changes, and she is not sure she is going to like what comes out the other side.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p368f7fd9b21b56c3e30d27ff4848f78c</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Leshawna creates a paint-balloon fight to decide who she will take to an amusement park.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd7c0c7f590fb463746b3ee96bdc467cb</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Back on the Brave Olivine, Liko, Roy and Dot receive an unexpected challenge to battle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc610269f8f8b3a6cfce6acc923f40f3</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>Dancer Jakob has trained so hard to earn a place at one of the world?s most prestigious international ballet competitions - but will his hard work be worth it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p91658bc56dc21f5ae8079241584b8ec9</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>After a prank goes wrong, Max must prove himself to his family by leading the Hawx U14s to victory against Foxborough ? by any means necessary.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc2b38b54ba8602d9fa90f2f484a3343e</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>As the studio grows in popularity it must make space for new members of J-Troupe. Michelle and Amanda promote the studio at their school while the others mentor J-Troupe. Daniel gives Kate an ultimatum.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8974061e1d2c1e1b710b0b00a8282ebe</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall meets the most ferocious shark of all. The great white shark is one of the greatest hunters on the planet, and Steve looks at what it is that makes them such perfect predators. He dives with them in the open ocean, revealing clever camouflage, and heads into his shark lab to take a closer look at their terrific teeth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9e37c6c60a7579827f1d1690c50dd33b</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>23 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's cartoon adventures with the mischievous young sheep and his flock. The sheep's field is in a mess, and the farmer tells Bitzer to clean it up - but he makes the mistake of getting Shaun and friends to help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5286e7bd502dbe6fd8406b22d2104b1</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The baron's true love threatens to bring Danger Mouse to his knees.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfcaae47453a9f3c1541b759fb60634cb</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes and the Council of Happiness swap jobs, and when the council fail in their quest, the whole forest is at risk of being flooded by Stinkystuff.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a544a2a926fb3c68c7a21626bc95543</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse's latest experiment goes horribly wrong when he swaps brains with a house fly! With his sibling?s help, Mouse frantically tries reversing the wacky situation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc9a62ab07918a2510fd95a0b876404e</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p02f3a029e0c079d7c8dc98269b2b5d3c</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The jelly cake battle takes on epic dimensions into a 'heroic fantasy' world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7540cfc28a15de2ef3fc5c8015f20b14</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings befriend a sheep.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3bdcab42cc0853f2c7b501f9fc8e0bd1</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob helps out the Krusty Krab's night shift.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf53131582ffc8ddedb3702f5028e2a6f</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Opie leads her first public tour through HQ, but when Orwell discovers one member of the tour group is a villain, they must work out who it is before it?s too late.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d059ee6a76702046cbe248518e43706</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Que volunteers Helsing?s house for a sleepover with the popular girls at school - but how long can she keep her weirdness in check.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1a7879d623be5e2f595020aa18fb2b43</image>
    <start>08:40AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Joy orders Danny and Mick to clean all the windows outside the leisure centre. At first it is a fun job, but soon they realise that they need to bring in some bigger machinery to reach the higher windows. But do they know how to use it, and what could possibly go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf162016179badd07ed82d3165fcf0b51</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Capital letters, sentence punctuation, sentence types.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4f2536e1da89ae7745f8862bab2af951</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>From cloning to 3D printing, what if we could actually make copies of ourselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd716e61199a65feee2ad3a5b14863caf</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Out of This World</title>
    <desc>Dr Maggie explores living in space with star guest astronaut Jessica Meir, who spent 205 days on the International Space Station. Dr Maggie also answers your space questions in Ask Maggie and announces her top five list of how long people have spent in space. Buckle up, it?s time to go Out Of This World.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80c21c1b7c497619210db038722877e2</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Twins Lily and Rosie are battling with stage fright as they are asked to perform in the choir at the big school concert. Meanwhile, Crystal discovers a new passion when she joins the school cross-stitch club.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p55dd9ffa2c3c89887a3299125a0435ca</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs get messy paint-marbling their furniture, Nathan Wyburn paints Bukayo Saka on toast, and Horrible Histories? Martin Brown draws a Georgian lady and a Viking warrior.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcd1de3425d61ba6f03e3053e4ac80ac0</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:20AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The One Zoo Three animals are due some check-ups. Is Ta?iri the leopard losing his eyesight? And what's the best way to take the entire meerkat mob to the vets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa96e696842f90edbb25ebcbee5f11473</image>
    <start>10:20AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>St Hugh of Lincoln Primary School is in Manchester, many of their pupils have specific needs and would benefit from a space of their own. But the school has no extra space! To solve this they had the clever idea of using an old double-decker bus, but that was as far as they got. That?s where The Dengineers come in! With our top team and expert designer, we are the perfect people to convert the bus and give the deserving pupils their much-needed breakout space.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e057cb7848e9f13d2a077e5f9c81181</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius: Monster Builds</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom turn their attention to the incredible world of monster bridges, tracing the genius ideas that have taken us from ancient Roman arches to elegant cable-stayed suspension spans, to a future where we may see bridges 3D-printed by robots. In their challenge, the boys join the Royal Engineers for an army bridge-build race... complete with a severe dressing-down for the loser.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p58e5843c1d8e04e546c17d9a8bfffa92</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A special episode about Mary, Queen of Scots, starring Jessica Ransom. It follows the young Mary as she stumbles from being a young girl in Scotland to queen in France, back to queen in Scotland and finally to Elizabeth I's public enemy number one - with a bit of Queenian Rhapsody thrown in for good measure! Meanwhile, across the world, we meet silver-nosed Danish scientist Tycho Brahe, and Mr H gives us his unique take on the epic Battle of Lepanto in another History's Craziest Fools. With, of course, our host Rattus to guide the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc706a39e32ea0fa0d1c369902a517c5b</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It is the annual sports day competition at Pottsfield and this time around it's Danny v Lance. They compete in a selection of events, including the classic sport of who can put on the most clothes and who can pop the balloon fastest with their bum.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p04aeb7dbdd9bbc1f4e4e2a50d738cdff</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Rio has lost his air guitar and his confidence. The band travel through space to take him home to Planet Rock to see the Godfather of Rock, who will help him get them back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a24d8d454ad4b5f337d26d47e518be1</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Bionic prank Athena as a massive broccoli at a fake healthy eating film shoot. Meanwhile, the other Gladiators are up to mischief behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0478823e97e8046f6ca16e39a89023b6</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>The Octonauts roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. When the Octopod breaks down, Tweak and the crew search for a missing part aboard an abandoned prototype of the ship, not realising something lives there.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p082230a0fc9ae0dc894f38345f79100c</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When Dad's Lizard Translator malfunctions, Cosima is carried away by a giant beetle! Cosima and Big Lizard realise they don't need to speak the same language to be best friends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3cf532313614dbb34458c3f5f17ecaa</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse is left gadgetless when an unappreciated Squawk leaves the Danger Agency to work for tech genius Elon Muskrat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p30bdd1caee31eaf2db44d36613261332</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Penfold takes a trip inside Danger Mouse's body to save him from a deadly aversion to his own heroism.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ce6cb7f273c50dec13b586f423e47c3</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes quest on Spookyween to stop whatever is menacing the pumpkin patch and find that a headless skeleton is using pumpkins as a head.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70db7b045f1cd6782fd25e272db5691e</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When an exhausted mother orders a replacement for her daughter's lost cuddly toy, the Ninjas must travel to a seaside fairground and stand up to some delinquent dolphins.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3b5020e9a073546a256fef3123b5f68</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall is in Zambia to witness ten million fruit bats undertake the world?s largest aerial migration. However, these bats are a buffet for Africa?s top three eagles.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc0e2b17c8078c9a920a9c5eda425236c</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>With her mum working 12-hour shifts, Sienna has to spend most of her time at her nana's house, but the space is a bit boring and not really a great place to hang out. Add in Sienna's love of spying, and it seems that what Sienna really needs is a new bedroom which can double up as a spy den, with lots of techy gadgets inside her 'top secret' lair.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p79cb8526417b78b8dbb3ae8db63177ad</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Shaun comes across some newly hatched chicks who think he is their mum. He is determined to get rid of them, but how.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56d4d38a872d8e76290e5e8a055759dc</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Doctor Pfooflepfeffer covets the world-beating power of Gnasher?s indestructible teeth and will stop at nothing to get her hands on one of those doggy dental marvels.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59953623a390b0bb5924ff89d145ecab</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom draws the short cheese straw and, rather than join her friends on a picnic, she has to take a magic wand to the recycling centre. Faced with a long queue and a rumbly tummy, Blossom decides that life is too short for recycling - with disastrous consequences. The heroes must skip their picnic and go on a quest to save the forest from the magical mess Blossom has gotten them into.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38db6a019d90d683a5c507a27c6477df</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Noticing that Boy has been distant lately, Dog asks Cheese for advice. However, the advice she gives pushes Boy and Dog further apart.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e103ac1a184b73e1fe97420453b8d71</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Lady Burlington needs her official portrait painted, the siblings convince her that Dog is the artist for the job. What starts as a fun art project soon becomes a nightmare.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc4709d6b4aca75c58eb47770c6d2b2bf</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Using a ring that lets their astral bodies travel, the Lemmings decide to haunt Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3d4c3cf119692497d318da30bb58dfed</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Plankton goes to jail, and the secret formula is taken as evidence.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p921d051f6d4af7b6c46166e71b98b85a</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Tamara refuses to share the monkey bars, and Melanie won?t get off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1035983e831fbad3707bd8643fcb7f4b</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Odd Squad UK is celebrating its jubilee, but the party can?t get started until Orli locates the missing Ozzi, who has a bad case of the Saturdays.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0cc0452f982d60aa0d1416a766bc13f0</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Charlie is jealous when Pierce is put into a group with Malcolm, so he uses a magical tape player to turn goodie-goodie Malcom into a baddie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p49b6fed7f0564f91f4c96b2b37723bd1</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen struggles with the idea that he is about to lose his BFF Noah to a gifted military school.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9071f37e1942b65e7987bb64753f9acb</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Roy and Crocalor accidentally switch places while exploring a festival in Kitakami.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81f2a223a60d16fe5b399233394f87f5</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>Valentine?s Day is celebrated across the school in some unique ways. Year 7 make cards, Year 10 have a ?Galentines? gift exchange, and Harry sweeps girlfriend Dyli off her feet in a special dance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94f00de02cc799834b3034a715a79066</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>With morale at rock bottom, Coach Byrne takes his Hawx players into the wilderness. Back at the academy, the U12s undergo an unusual detention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd901b1a8b443d4c12bb1ac3c629c5c3d</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Riley struggles to move on from James while still working on their duet. Emily and Hunter get to know each other better when they get locked in the costume closet together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p129481b4863b41fdd71934fab78055c5</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall meets the most colossal shark in our seas. Measuring up to a record 18 metres, the whale shark is not only the largest shark, but the largest fish in the world. Steve dives with this gargantuan shark off the coast of Mozambique in Africa and reveals their somewhat surprising diet, before heading into his shark lab to get under their skin and reveal how they manage to filter their food from the water.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0cf2a6c3c89b13509338fd4c0b9595a3</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. When a strange spacecraft crash-lands on the farm, Shaun and company help its little green occupant get airborne again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p989a716e484e5625b53240388772f72b</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse makes short work of Burt Badboy and his newly acquired band of fanatical feline followers, the group's leader Mandy and her cult of cats immediately trade in their colourful mohican hairstyles for eyepatches and become Danger Mouse worshippers. At first Danger Mouse is having too much fun to take notice of Penfold's warnings about his new-found cult status, but even he is forced to act when the cats follow his example a little too literally and live life a little too dangerously. Danger Mouse's attempt to disown the cats goes down like a lead balloon, and they use mouse-fu skills and a superpowered amulet stolen from Tutenkamoo to show their idol the error of his ways. Danger Mouse battles the frenzied feline onslaught and saves HQ from becoming a giant scratching post. However, this only reaffirms the idea that he is the chosen one in the minds of Mandy and the cult of cats. Danger Mouse realises that the only solution is to find a new obsession for the cats.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cecc13bc26e14071dc1ed1bb687eebf</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are made to clean the Cave of Mirrors as punishment for frolicking before a quest is complete, and they accidentally release the Party Harpy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf80b921c507ca0e99023f7222f1a27bf</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy is afraid of being honest in case he hurts other people's feelings and finds himself doing things he doesn?t like just to keep others happy. Mouse and Cheese encourage him to be totally honest, only to find that Boy?s total honesty can be rather blunt. Can the gang rein him in before Boy alienates the entire town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p266389173e1520b4e65cb4c48680fe55</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa4c85487e2f2de6aad9fe3946b35050c</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings plot to remove the bear from the castle and prevent him from returning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p19d0bfe8e3ed2a98dca54b9d08058172</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Using a ring that lets their astral bodies travel, the Lemmings decide to haunt Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3d4c3cf119692497d318da30bb58dfed</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob visits Bubbletown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p17dc6e37464314ae66d1036906a35a2c</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When the exclusive Club 37 opens up in HQ, Orli and Ozzie set out to crack 37 cases so they can enter it. But with more fun clubs opening, will the agents? club obsession get the better of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe464d88f764c10fa67e3614ac3c1a289</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:40AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>The gang are cleaning Helsing?s swamp-like pool. Pierce is scared to get his new watch wet until he meets a mysterious fish monster named Finn.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80503b9fe16dfa7ebc31cfc572f13a6a</image>
    <start>08:40AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Through an accident at the leisure centre, Danny and Mick discover what they think is a treasure map. The hunt is on to follow the golden route, but they end up digging their way into trouble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbcc5bb5439043091d2c289d54b249b44</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 7-9 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Apostrophes for contraction, apostrophes for possession, using commas in a list.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p09950f92004696f479209743d9ea23a8</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Imagine if we had a thermostat that could turn the world temperature down - could we fix global warming??But be careful, a few degrees too far could cause an ice age.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1930619574c1e72bdd429122903b847a</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Out of This World</title>
    <desc>In this episode, Dr Maggie reveals that no matter how much you plan, prepare and practise for space travel, things can sometimes go wrong. Dr Maggie?s star guest is Professor David Southwood CBE, who was responsible for getting the European Space Agency?s Beagle 2 Lander onto Mars. However, it didn?t go to plan ? so what did he learn when things went wrong? And Dr Maggie answers viewers? space questions and counts down the top five greatest achievements that you won?t have heard of! Buckle up, it?s time to go Out Of This World.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p64ad579219f7a96bb1a2641760225d43</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>The girls reconnect with family for a revealing new history project, and Teni throws herself into a self-defence class after homesickness hits. Meanwhile, some of the boarders are treated to a surprise visit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef4903877e12e9ac5e3a70a9df38659e</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:05AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>DIY Deadly with Steve Backshall</title>
    <desc>In this unprecedented time of lockdown there has never been a better time to learn about the wildlife around us, and Deadly 60 fans have been sending in their videos, photos and questions for Steve Backshall to answer. In this episode, Steve focuses on our parks and gardens. This green space may look pristine, but for wildlife it?s savannah, jungle and mountains all rolled in to one. And judging by CBBC?s most observant viewers, its packed full of deadly animals! Steve unravels the mystery of some blue eggs in a nest, explains how a spider uses camouflage and trickery to lure in its prey, and tells about a worm that isn?t a worm... it?s a lizard! In a DIY demo, Steve then shows us how to keep hedgehogs warm and toasty during winter by building a hibernation house. But that?s not all. The audience gets their chance to ?beat Backshall? in a 60-second quickfire round. The question is, how many can Steve get right before his time is up? We also learn that fox cubs are endearing alarm clocks, and why you wouldn?t want to wander around an Australian garden without a grown-up.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4985504f05584abd2513378339cf9e65</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:20AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The brothers meet the zoo's youngest animals as Cam helps give two snow leopard cubs a health check. And it?s goodbye to Tashi the red panda as he begins a new adventure.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p615b8101c7072c63e4cdc5b7b10111ed</image>
    <start>10:20AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>The presenters look back at all the amazing dens the team have built throughout the series and reminisce about the great kids, the tense surprises and the big reveals.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a497a0dae279a7665143824d0b416ed</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius: Monster Builds</title>
    <desc>Absolute Genius presenters Dick and Dom sample all the fun of the fair in this thrill ride through the engineering genius of roller coasters and water slides. As well as learning how coasters somehow stay on the track when upside down, the boys don their swim shorts and bravely research the science behind the world's fastest water slides. Then they put their theories to the test with an epic slide challenge which attempts to topple a record owned by a certain Usain Bolt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa1291eccbb0794b162ffe9f4713c79aa</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A special episode about the great French leader Napoleon Bonaparte, starring Jim Howick. We follow Napoleon as he rises from humble beginnings to be the emperor of France, bashing most of Europe along the way and ultimately meeting his Waterloo at, well, Waterloo! Meanwhile, across the world, we meet the Indian traveller who brought shampoo to the world. With, of course, our host Rattus to guide the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6cefa66047c43e5b0a3501410e16db7c</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Sharon's boss, Mrs Harris, has come to the leisure centre to make sure that things are running smoothly. She thinks she can run it better herself and so fires a distraught Sharon. However, it is not as easy as it looks, and Danny and Mick make sure Mrs Harris' boss, Dame Frost, fires her and brings Sharon back to get things back under control.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc48c42de1ac92aebec5fbb26b4b82158</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Whiff says he needs help so Mac invents Robo Whiff ? a super efficient robot roadie. Things soon start to go wrong, however, as Whiff?s pushy robotic twin starts to take over the band.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa36b9e262eca9bf4e78ff33c7cbae2ea</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Phantom is pranked by Nitro and Steel when he believes he?s in a new Gladiators video game, and the other Gladiators have fun pranking the audience behind the scenes at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p236851b7e42258c7058fe0b17e13f20f</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>As newborn baby sea turtles make their way to the ocean, the Octonauts must steer them clear of a giant wave and hungry predators.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4d5b45cbeff5607eb1c91fbb76dfd161</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad gets trapped in the shower when D.O.R.I.S. decides to visit the sea. Can Big Lizard and Cosima stop her before she does herself permanent damage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0d1d9aac82bd92a8d9088f22af3f5cb2</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The danger agents are at Squawk's super-secret Wild West testing facility, home to a society of Penbots, robots who have a rather familiar face. Squawk is sure she has improved upon Penfold and made the perfect robotic sidekick for Danger Mouse, Tenfold. But Tenfold malfunctions and transforms into the ruthless Meanfold, determined to destroy anyone who is not quite perfect.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe9b5368e847ec4ab98ee821a340abf34</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold are celebrating another noisy victory, gleefully ringing Big Ben's bell, when an over-excited Penfold falls, pushing the clock hand forward, causing the sun to go down prematurely. Unbeknownst to them a mysterious figure watches on from nearby, noting the clock's incredible time-controlling powers. When DM realises that the day is being stolen and replaced with a silent night, he enlists the help of expert colleagues - the night shift! With Danger Moth and Danger Mole in tow, the team track the quiet culprit. But a noisy Danger Mouse might just be outwitted by this stealthy saboteur.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa64acadbfbc20de92cb92d011b03aaf8</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle feels she is being taken for granted by the other heroes, so she joins the Fairy Squad when they arrive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa88b9a6c763d7c35c89b5f246f002e9f</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>Desperate to prove he is still needed, Mega Powerful Man asks the Ninjas to find him a worthy villain to battle against.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p616e4c01756f32c11215949abe04f2ce</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall is in Sydney, Australia, searching for the world?s most venomous spider, the fastest striking snake and an ocean dragon that is a camouflaged assassin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pec34855b0901151f667aee5f74516c32</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>In this episode, we meet nine-year-old twin sisters Kiki and Queenie. We also follow U11 boys Teddy and Miles in their biggest tournament of the year.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p32db01aaffdf41be1b2b695848d338ff</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Set on a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. The Farmer decides it is time to give the flock a shearing. But when they see his first attempt, Shaun and the others plan their escape.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd7961b6ed2796ee4e8ca3c55e30d789f</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>In an attempt to deprive Gnasher of the food that fuels his active gnashy ways, Walter takes over Butch Butcher?s sausage-making business. His careless manufacturing produces a monster fatberg under Beanotown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb5164c803a844f8f80c3bae6cf0a997d</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>It?s been ages since their last quest, and the heroes are losing their edge, so Mr Friendlyface invents a strange and terrible monster that he says is stomping through the forest causing havoc, and sends the heroes on a fake quest to get rid of it. Friendlyface soon comes to regret his trickery when, with the heroes out of the way, the goblins decide to take over the forest for their jam jamboree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd73f5a342e51bd6aa4e1226b5b388fb</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The town has always revered the Smith twins' great-great-grandpa as a local hero. However, when the gang exposes him as a fraud, they need to find a way to cheer the twins up.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pad41075364923fdfbae55ade4bf74338</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Girl, Cheese and Dog start a babysitting business, but their first client is a real handful! If they want to please him, they might just need to take Boy's advice.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p72f1944bc02f139f094ac17ac13220a7</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find magic books that make their story content appear in real life when opened.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p01c270a57a4691a1423701fd684d5433</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Sandy builds a ship in a bottle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2b40fdad01bebe446e68ec986ca7f4f1</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Mrs Gonsha rescues a boy from the playground equipment and gets stuck herself.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4f6074069870f0233d739c421e23d5c2</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Ozzie is torn between helping his replacement, Opie, on her first day manning the Odd Squad Department of Help desk, and an important mission with Orli and Onom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f5d4ee2f0a077b41ef6c23d2798bc0d</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Que becomes an unexpected viral hit when she is filmed scaring some teens. Enjoying the spotlight, will she risk exposure for fame and fortune.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb7116d2745dabe591fc59327a90e720d</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Eleven-year-old Karis Musongole, who played young Elphaba in Wicked, flies into the studio for some Halloween fun and to show how to make creepy (but tasty!) witches? fingers. We reveal how you can get the Elphaba look at home, and don?t miss our latest spooky Book Club read.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27a3c43fb2adcefa28dd5ba44d70c2df</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings end up lost after misplacing their jar of Yummy in a labyrinth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6adf7709b4293ae1023ab4a70b88ad6</image>
    <start>05:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>It?s opening night for the sold-out senior show! After weeks of rehearsals and complicated set builds, tickets are sold out - but will the set hold up and the cast be ready in time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p46ff2d7160a131a5fcb1b178d6499eb5</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>Jess and her bouncy border collie Mickey, and Will and his speedy cockapoo Honey are getting ready for an adventure.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p446da48b3ff8d2061e48c593dd6af5b7</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Michelle finds out about the dance battle, and Hunter gets a chance at the nationals solo spot. Phoebe challenges select A-Troupers and J-Troupers to create a song and a dance in 24 hours.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p83af228ce585f83b5c474d1f76f66665</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall meets the most sinister shark in our seas. The ragged tooth shark has a mouth that's overflowing with terrifying teeth. But why does it need such gnarly gnashers? Steve heads out on a dive after dark to see these fearsome fangs for himself, before revealing their sinister secret in his shark lab.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ff2226cfdb7e138bed614be556ea724</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:30AM</finish>
    <date>25 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>04:30AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When a chicken ends up inside Shaun?s pillowcase, Shaun tries to get it back, only for the chicken to end up in the farmhouse and the Farmer to think he is being haunted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e44be1b3896db0978260dd7ae72a737</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:10AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Colonel K spins a terrifying tale about the Headless Postman - an ancient and alarmingly scary apparition. When the haunting figure of the postman suddenly appears, petrified panic reigns supreme amongst the Danger Agents, until Squawkencluck reveals herself as the postman in disguise and that the whole scenario has been a company-mandated bravery test. By remaining characteristically unfazed throughout, Danger Mouse fails the exam, which puts his job at risk, as in Squawk's words 'being truly brave means being afraid of something and still taking it on'. The gang try to scare DM, but he's fearless... until he discovers that the Headless Postman lives.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9eb97117d9ccb8820c2cba0e8c6555c3</image>
    <start>06:10AM</start>
    <finish>06:20AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>There's a werewolf-type creature on the prowl and suspicion falls on Gnasher. Dennis has to prove his best pal's innocence as the full moon shines down on Beanotown..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7bd095aa830e7aad546c21dc4103e322</image>
    <start>06:20AM</start>
    <finish>06:35AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Cheese tells Boy he has been the victim of a weredog staredown, he becomes convinced he will turn into a weredog too.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6cc7f43074fc2f3ea13127028d4a1f88</image>
    <start>06:35AM</start>
    <finish>06:45AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc9aa8b83acfa6b9fc3e07f31cb2e25fa</image>
    <start>06:45AM</start>
    <finish>06:55AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Charlie's efforts to scare Helsing backfire when the gang summon powerful, interdimensional fear monsters that threaten to destroy the world. Could this be the end of the strange chores.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p47847240e5b1aeb2db2524f4caf01fba</image>
    <start>06:55AM</start>
    <finish>07:05AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Monster Loving Maniacs</title>
    <desc>Ernest is excited, and Edith and Bo want to stay in.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7d2dda2082996d9bf20e649a57be42b6</image>
    <start>07:05AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>The Halloween school play causes anxiety among all the friends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p328a1ad93b44fbcea6344aae497851a6</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:40AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Can the bros survive Britain?s most haunted castle as they navigate spooky rooms, in an attempt to avoid the tricks and collect the treats? As if that wasn?t scary enough, they also have to face four terrifying Gladiators - Dynamite, Viper, Diamond and Apollo! Callum also invites Adam and Joe to apply for a place at his Witch School, but which witch will win the challenge and which bro will be forced to face an eight-legged fear as a forfeit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8a749b803f4d83ff2870f3e86b201865</image>
    <start>07:40AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Saturday Mash-Up! Live</title>
    <desc>Joe, Shereen, Stanley and Kia throw a Halloween party with Philip Green and the stars of Jamie Johnson FC.?Kristen Wiig plays truth or dare, while Stanley visits a haunted hotel.?Get ready for a huge Joe v Shereen challenge, and there?s two episodes of SpongeBob Squarepants. Saturday Mash-Up is totally live? so anything can happen.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3eddd6dca8170cf61bd875884d86caa9</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Eleven-year-old Karis Musongole, who played young Elphaba in Wicked, flies into the studio for some Halloween fun and to show how to make creepy (but tasty!) witches? fingers. We reveal how you can get the Elphaba look at home, and don?t miss our latest spooky Book Club read.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27a3c43fb2adcefa28dd5ba44d70c2df</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:55AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs go full monster-mode as they make spooky costumes, David Shrigley builds a giant praying mantis, and comedian Katherine Ryan draws a cute cat with big eyes and serious sass.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62f1b53b7b5ee67bf6a33909def92bd6</image>
    <start>10:55AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>It?s time to get messy with Splatoon! Guided by pro-gamer Yammy, the teams face off in an ink-filled showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27987bbc67e39e72b95f53ed0527afce</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The agents throw a surprise party for Ms O.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd06d0252d4a42cd589c7972d7010d53d</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:45AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When the alarm system at headquarters is triggered, Olive, Otto, Ms O and Oscar must avoid a series of booby traps in order to shut it off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ee744fcaa99bdb41275089482d89fd1</image>
    <start>11:45AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Spooky Files</title>
    <desc>The Spooky Crew investigate a series of disappearances at camp, while Robina starts to notice their secretive behaviour.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd101c8deab1f5efc42dc31a905ec39f3</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pickle Storm</title>
    <desc>At the school table sale, Lystra decides to sell her old shields, Hendrick rides a bicycle, and Pickle wants to buy something amazing.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pba61de38fa21b28c9cb925a5ed96f653</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Worst Witch</title>
    <desc>When Mistress Nightshade makes a surprise visit, Enid is left in a terrible dilemma - complete her studies at Cackle?s or join the family magic show? Will Mildred?s great debate challenge help her make up her mind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14b47428fd14b81408a7ab1d41d958ad</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Under-12s Carter and Alex jet off to Portugal for a huge tournament, Riley and Maddie take on Crystal Palace in the cup, and under-10 Julian takes on Spurs legend Sandro in The Maradona 7.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9bd4c1c8d0cdb04ce1b403a60d35924d</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Christina fights for the right to play football again, while rivals Hawx United and Foxborough start sharing an academy - what could possibly go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf6194e5e50af06f0d92f759b4a5bff78</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Beth sets out to get rid of all their old toys, hoping Chef will buy the new toy she wants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65f80c82e11fb083e3d726fe80ab11f0</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's film star status is threatened by a toilet uprising. An epic battle on the streets of Tokyo between Danger Mouse and Dr Loocifer! Oh, wait - it's just a scene being filmed for Danger Mouse: The Movie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa699c08bac85f3f5f4670350bfb26834</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse faces the Queen of Weevils in a fearful Halloween special.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ff6788cafa5778e2972fb67508deb9d</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>In the run-up to the school play, spooky goings-on around the school make the gang wonder if the mythical Bash Street Bogeyman might be real, and still stalking the corridors.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc8f6d7fdd6a4ac9a55694d8f3fff2bd1</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes quest on Spookyween to stop whatever is menacing the pumpkin patch and find that a headless skeleton is using pumpkins as a head.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p70db7b045f1cd6782fd25e272db5691e</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Defending the house on Halloween, Charlie is in for a fright when Pierce invites the neighbourhood (and at least one monster) over for a costume party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p68c8d66eaa392128e8f3a1074c76a006</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>When a chicken ends up inside Shaun?s pillowcase, Shaun tries to get it back, only for the chicken to end up in the farmhouse and the Farmer to think he is being haunted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e44be1b3896db0978260dd7ae72a737</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Set on a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock leads a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog, Bitzer, but Shaun's insatiable curiosity often leads him into the unlikeliest adventures. One dark and stormy night the flock are unable to sleep. Shaun investigates a series of sinister events only to discover who is really scaring the sheep.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d8c7f69eeb45f18c396237da7a16dc6</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Intrigued by a horror film on television, Timmy wanders into the farmhouse late one night. Shaun's rescue mission convinces the Farmer that the place is haunted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69270eb66e8c141c109ea661f900dd4b</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Arthur</title>
    <desc>This Halloween is the spookiest ever for Arthur and friends. While trick-or-treating, Francine meets an old woman with a mysterious past, while Binky finds himself at Mr Ratburn?s house. Muffy and Bailey decide to cut through a dark, rainy cemetery. And as for Arthur, Buster and Ladonna, their treehouse sleepover seems to be haunted... by a little sister and brother.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p18ba78da024d6f32f043b52dfbb07140</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Arthur</title>
    <desc>This Halloween is the spookiest ever for Arthur and friends. While trick-or-treating, Francine meets an old woman with a mysterious past, while Binky finds himself at Mr Ratburn?s house. Muffy and Bailey decide to cut through a dark, rainy cemetery. And as for Arthur, Buster and Ladonna, their tree house sleepover seems to be haunted... by a little sister and brother.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p15f139b64df3522b2ac50da0a9ae80dc</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:40PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A Lemming finds a mysterious mask that endows him with the power of telekinesis.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peecc469e064293cb3826d2ecd69c6307</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy unwittingly brings to life some medieval armour.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f1e5b7a6310872f1132ccb2ba2d6f94</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Using a ring that lets their astral bodies travel, the Lemmings decide to haunt Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3d4c3cf119692497d318da30bb58dfed</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings decide to free a spirit and send it to Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb25a4b3039a20295b074ea055e10f7d9</image>
    <start>05:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Monsters vs Aliens: Mutant Pumpkins from Outer Space</title>
    <desc>Animated short film. Susan Murphy and the monsters are now working with the US government as special ops. So when an alien presence is detected in Susan's hometown of Modesto, California, right before Halloween, the team is dispatched to investigate.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1be52ca94fd54a2d9dc56439583514c6</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>It's Halloween, and the Flying Dutchman is going to make sure everyone is scared.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6ecb8383b3c6788ad5213f11259d90e4</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:30AM</finish>
    <date>26 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation featuring the adventures of Shaun and his flock. Shaun and the other sheep give the Farmer's tractor a quick makeover when it won't start.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb2cfa134e0273b4af9708b721653bb3f</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Playtime is over as Danger Mouse battles an army of vengeful soft toys. Pink Dawn's henchman teddy bear Snuggles is on an angry rampage. He is zapping cuddly toys, bringing them to life as rage-filled criminals. He will annihilate anyone who refuses to be his friend. Danger Mouse spots the source of Snuggles's power - Pink Dawn's tiara! When Penfold's beloved teddy, Bernard, rejects his owner to join Snuggles's new gang, Danger Mouse and the distraught Penfold rush to confront Dawn. They are shocked to discover that Dawn has ditched pink in favour of a superpowered goth darkness. Can DM reunite Dawn and Snuggles and put a stop to this rampage? Will Bernard ever return to the ever-loving Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9dfcc413a353c078b8d6f7e592c273fa</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis recruits Grizzly Griller to help make school sports day more extreme, but as he and JJ get competitive against each other, who is sabotaging both their chances of winning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59a7ef36f278f1b30593801e12d27fc2</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>To prove she can be selfless, Cheese begins granting wishes. However, when a rival shows up to do the same, Cheese loses sight of her goal as she tries to remain number one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99a5c24d810a52fe55d6ef82c9add8ce</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c3928cd1c56a24f8babcf7b2204e187</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>The gang is in a sticky situation when Pierce's homemade slime swallows the whole town, leaving them trapped in the local shop and up to their necks in trouble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f803149da01dc04cc1f5c3b46c0041b</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Monster Loving Maniacs</title>
    <desc>Arthur believes real monsters are at play at Gruselbrook Funpark's ghost ride attraction.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p93d639c4172b7c47e3b227137f6750ea</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:15AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Monster Loving Maniacs</title>
    <desc>Dracula is coming for Arthur, and the Van Altens prepare to face one angry vampire.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p11a3e030c25034b8b5bff4646162c68c</image>
    <start>08:15AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Monster Loving Maniacs</title>
    <desc>The heroes desperately try to avoid a confrontation with the invincible Dracula.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe71a787ba2b9c8b09838adac71d03c9b</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:40AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Prepare to be petrified, as Adam and Joe have to escape Callum?s Halloween House! Which bro will be crowned the Halloween champion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf7345764bf565dc1a6d35d2d7887a6f2</image>
    <start>08:40AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Eleven-year-old Karis Musongole, who played young Elphaba in Wicked, flies into the studio for some Halloween fun and to show how to make creepy (but tasty!) witches? fingers. We reveal how you can get the Elphaba look at home, and don?t miss our latest spooky Book Club read.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27a3c43fb2adcefa28dd5ba44d70c2df</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>With Halloween approaching, the Year 7s have been told about the school ghost and set off to hunt for it. Meanwhile, the Anything Goes cast try not to get too spooked by the thought of opening night for their show, and Encore - the most senior dancers at the school - warm up for their next big show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb23418f094c47204647f6ce302d72560</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:50AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Cooking Buddies</title>
    <desc>Buddy and Conker are joined by Taye, a young street artist who wants to make a surprise birthday meal for his dad, who loves crispy chicken. Together, they make the crispiest, most delicious fried chicken, served up with homemade slaw, potato wedges and corn on the cob in what must be the best birthday present ever! In return for Buddy?s help, Taye shares some of his artistic skills and shows him how to create his very own bubble-writing signature. Join Buddy, Conker and Taye as they create a work of art both on paper and on a plate with a great homemade takeaway! You can get all of Buddy?s recipes, and loads more, at bbc.co.uk\/food.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p43577acb2448ba2aba73e7b0ad25f64f</image>
    <start>09:50AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>So Awkward</title>
    <desc>It?s Humanitarian Week and the pupils have to commit to acts of charity and kindness in order to receive Community Spirit Awards. Ollie and Martha get competitive, signing up to teach digital to the over-sixties. But winning an award is going to be harder than Martha and Ollie think: Martha's pupil Mazel knows absolutely nothing about tech, and Ollie?s ex-punk student Jonny is anti-technology. At the charity sumo wrestling bake-off event, Lily threatens to shred her teddy bear to force Jas to admit she is the secret shopper. When Jas overhears Lily discuss the teddy-shredding trap with Rob, Jas ups the ante by threatening to shred her teddy, too. Only at the very last moment do they admit the truth to one another, saving both the teddies and the friendship.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe9d933b30e2cce4caf107df9a58a482f</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Danny is convinced it's Joy?s birthday and ropes Mick and Naomi into his plan to create a surprise party. Mick?s in charge of decorations, Naomi?s in charge of the cake, Danny?s in charge of making sure Joy doesn?t suspect a thing. What can go wrong? Everything ? it?s Danny and Mick! Soon it?s time to spring the surprise ? will Joy be thrilled, annoyed or simply confused? Hint: It?s all three.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p647309c04520ff895b7fddfab73af85d</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Naomi has asked for a raise, Joy?s advised her to take some time off to think about it, which is why Danny and Mick are in charge of the cafe. They?ve just about got the hang of it when a new automated smoothie maker arrives. The machine is supposed to make life easier, but that?s not how Danny and Mick see it. Soon smoothies are flying, and everyone is left with egg on their face. And strawberry. And a bit of banana?.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b4c9cf8f021ccd65862af8d996b9857</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum is a Little Bro in control! He?s pitting his Big Bro Adam against best mate Joe to see who will win a series of funny, gungy and gross challenges and who will land an awful forfeit from the Wheel of Doom in this epic competition. Callum's the Little Bro, but he?s in control, so Adam and Joe had better impress him! When Joe and Adam press play on a mysterious voice note, they know it?ll be a long but extra 24 hours. Little Bro Callum is challenging them to let him control their day. With tasks like bathing in cold mud, snacking on edible insects and wearing their pants on their head, nothing's normal in this high-key contest to be the best. After Callum?s decided on a winner, it?s onto the next funny challenge: will they choose to save their crab friend or their stuff? And why is a giant shark distracting them?</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc79e0414b499bd676d87a6f418b89161</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Apollo with fake influencer Aubry Devonne Keep, causing a big splash! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82fea0673a28a4c34c10d3bc5eb06fcf</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve is in Uganda, getting up close and personal with some of our closest relatives - the primates. He meets gorillas in the mountains and squabbling baboons on the savannah. He even has a dawn encounter with chimps in the forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f238ce530b35ccf75af7c1517b672e2</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Could farts power a rocket? If you ask a question like that to Dr Chris and Dr Xand, you know they will want to investigate ? and if they can, they will blast off an actual rocket too! We welcome Gladiator Dynamite to Team Ouch! Her job is to referee Dr Dan and Dr Raph as they pit their bodies against each other in Dan vs Raph: Body Battles. Today, it?s a muscle they are testing: the triceps. Will it be Dr Dan or Dr Raph who ends up in the ice bath as a loser?s forfeit? One thing is for sure, Dynamite?s decision is final! Doctors Chris, Xand and Ronx are Ouch and About giving answers to kids? medical questions, with Margot asking why people have asthma. In Australia, the Flying Doctors fly Jack and his mum to hospital in New South Wales for a check-up following Jack's bone marrow transplant. Back in the emergency department in the UK, Logan has hurt his knee after tripping and landing on a log, and Harshali has a pink bead stuck up her nose! Ouch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94a8d6fd6580fb7b64d941699a3b2c35</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories favourite Death, of 'Stupid Deaths' fame, presents his very own show crammed full of spooky highlights. We join him at home and get a good look around as he reveals his creepiest moments - a Tudor family show us the extent of their ghostly superstitions and the Vikings demonstrate how to become truly terrifying to your enemies. Death himself is joined by some rather creepy friends to sing about his favourite scary things.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcbeb89fe77c342b9d74dc4b9d4fb9085</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Dr Big Brain has an electrical short circuit, Marie Curie is wowed by a rocket man, some of the great women of science are celebrated, and 200 monks get electrocuted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21daa97d981587de14f8ff3ad8bddf40</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>A new secret formula has disastrous results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7138f69a1361ba835321ad9eea6b2a23</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Mr Krabs and Plankton take boating school classes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0e38c6a2d56e911ee73f2a02f3740747</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Mr Krabs gets in trouble for littering.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd5889480b90deea1f79d64a220c51d2</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Helsing tasks the gang with finding a magical genie lamp, thinking that they won't give it a polish. Now, Charlie is famous, Pierce is a CEO and Que has legs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p91ee48925752b847214b40962f3ce830</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>The gang find Helsing's monster phone book and prank call Frank, the world?s scariest monster. The gang must prepare the house when a furious Frank seeks his revenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf82a4655b1e582d10ff2733ea238236</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse wants the other kids to stop being lazy and achieve some goals - in the form of breaking world records. With Mouse's relentless coaching, the family soon gets carried away. Can Mouse get things back to normal before anyone gets hurt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p952612adea8a4c9c25efe350e0b666cf</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When one of Mouse?s inventions accidentally sticks Cat?s discarded fur to Boy?s face, his new 'beard' suddenly makes him the most popular kid in school! Seeing her chance to stop her enemy Lila Bird from becoming class president, Girl convinces Boy to run for president too. It looks like Boy might win, until another accident causes Cat?s whole body to get stuck to his face. Can he win the election with such a strange new beard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p914a4dbe62695432e7ae7da249569069</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The Girls and the Boys compete to get to the top of Bear Mountain, using very different styles of camping. But when the legendary bear appears, they have to team up to survive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb67492964d5542c23a8c00dc0f1fb470</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When Courtney refuses to share her valuable rare toy, friends join forces to question her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e518a8dee62348a4c879f5a681603a2</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Leshawna creates a paint-balloon fight to decide who she will take to an amusement park.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd7c0c7f590fb463746b3ee96bdc467cb</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen struggles with the idea that he is about to lose his BFF Noah to a gifted military school.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9071f37e1942b65e7987bb64753f9acb</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy decides to adopt a coconut.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa46da99ab8403e36a8d474b0b8fb95b6</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy pretends to have a twisted ankle so that the Lemmings have to take care of him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe6b0094f479dde28e14b93fc8b4a9ca9</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings set up a mini-fair, but Grizzy steals the Lemmings' tickets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p37fc83ff5409cc94ecc3a582cef047e2</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>With the dragon riders disbanded, Eugene attempts to start his own dragon club.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8492884e34bc23e0558ef5df55b30fd2</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Maisie is determined to win a place at a fashion school, but it won?t be easy. At the DG, Shanice has a bad hair day, and Vinny is struggling with his homework.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p332b04217c6c69ac4e9b881e356fc9f6</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>The Founders? Day dance takes Juniper back to 1944. Addie feels on top of the world, but a well-meaning mistake threatens to undo all her good work.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59f40b6cf0832b72deb80aefbf44ceaf</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>There is a buzz around the school as the Anything Goes cast list is finally revealed. Will Lucas get the part of Moonface, a role usually reserved for the older years? Best friends Uma and Anna are both hoping for the lead, but will they be happy with their parts? Meanwhile, singer Max has been busy writing new songs over the summer, and his dreams of life as a pop star are ever closer as he releases new music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p30e66f289f8ed538419999a240859642</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Best mates Riley and Maddie battle a boys' team, and pals Masai and Ernest swap the pitch for the kitchen. Michael Dawson is in Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb9ec97d8e3e1263bc1a76cc84cda911b</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>Release the hounds! Campers are hunted by a pack of fearsome attack dogs... and one pug.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6b6bb0170f1530fcddc459da67e91a0a</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Plankton poses as a wish-granting genie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe0475aead4a39a8890da63d1ec55b26f</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:45PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Heat-loving hippies move into Mr Krabs' soup vat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69a33c4df7c05a5a8d1f49d00087621d</image>
    <start>06:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Another adventure with the mischievous young sheep and his flock. The Farmer decides to get a robotic sheepdog, but it turns out to be even stricter than Bitzer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9e15148a77af1005bd9f4c43f27cbc8a</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold receive a crash course in the customs of America's oldest holiday when they cover for Jeopardy Mouse as she takes time off for Thanksgiving. After barely escaping from the war zone of a Black Friday sale, they find themselves back at Jeopardy's apartment. DM prepares to tuck into the plentiful Thanksgiving spread when Hissteria and Ham Hands rise out of the dishes. They announce their newly formed coalition and joint plans to vanquish America. DM sticks to his stand-in duties and refuses Jeopardy's help as he and Penfold follow Hissteria and Ham Hands' trail. They find the villainous pair hijacking the Thanksgiving Day parade - launching a gas attack from the air that will turn everything in sight to stuffing. With holiday-saving solutions at a premium, Penfold convinces a reluctant DM to call Jeopardy for help. Jeopardy assures DM that doing things with friends is what Thanksgiving is all about as they set about taking Ham Hands and Hissteria down. They distract them long enough to cut them loose along with the rest of the gas-filled balloons.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5362698311ba343ffe4571fba7fb7bc3</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes set out on a quest to find out who is draining colour from the forest and muster all their positivity to save it from greyness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3d4f995b8c3040f9e2b17fe57dfa29f</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Much to the kids' horror, Gramps starts spending a lot of time with mean Miss Molly! The gang do whatever it takes to keep the two apart.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc164d1eb50b7b3d1b3041fdb1b4540e9</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf67d0f376e0516e66eac525e23095592</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find magic books that make their story content appear in real life when opened.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p01c270a57a4691a1423701fd684d5433</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a card that enables them to teleport a magic closet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa08b154dad94ed665954fc65a2a2e098</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Sandy invites Karen and Mrs Puff out for a night on the town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p981dbd008d7b392bb732da721fc82486</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Pumpkins mysteriously disappear one after another, leaving nothing but a trail of slime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6abffca1412150e0b8a491be688483e</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>The others try to cheer Rory up after he is punished and sent to the office.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6853721e6e0a07518571c0a31c3f1c4d</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Charlie uses Helsing?s time remote to bring a heavily muscled future version of himself back to the present to change his life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf77616ab1a39e80807a661849b4d161a</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Winx Club - The Magic Is Back</title>
    <desc>Following a scary encounter with a magic creature on her 16th birthday, Bloom discovers that she has magical powers. She is rescued by two fairies from Alfea School for Fairies and Witches.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa392635580aa64d93ddb96931017eac9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Stormy Weather - aka Aurore Bor?ale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p46e354ffdf97b682b4acb0e2971f158e</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Marinette?s class is headed to New York, the city of superheroes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5d5e0f2bc8193376ae4309e49cdce04</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:45AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>A prehistoric sponge is unfrozen and causes chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0dc730653145e151cb5ab24672b98545</image>
    <start>10:45AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>A flock of clams descend on Bikini Bottom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdfca11fd35d063c2f9ff48721d046a1e</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced madcap, stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The potato racers are driving each other round the bend, the DIY doughnuts attempt to fix the bathroom, the cavemen mushrooms come face to face with some big, hairy mammoth pots, fearless Pete Parsnip takes on a ferocious foe, and Slippery Nana takes on a pizza-cutting unicycle in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc75a0813855bf2fc00f9eb5e7b778651</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall tracks cheetahs across Zambia by motorbike, witnessing epic hunting and the challenges faced by this endangered predator.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fceb6dcae8bced48912e9f9f2bd0e93</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>It's the start of a new school year, and the school is buzzing as boarders find out who they are sharing a dorm with and day pupils reunite at the lockers. No time is wasted on day one as the students go head-to-head for roles in the new show: Anything Goes. And this year could be life-changing for dancer Jakob as he starts his preparations for one of the world?s most prestigious international ballet competitions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe43e8702039ee3f0a37066f6e5bc0013</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Meet the Tottenham Hotspur academy players. Lia Lewis picks her Three of the Best, and Dominic Solanke takes on 11-year-old Konan in Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p88eec7f914b4c5e2f11d416e2a1eaf76</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Christina fights for the right to play football again, while rivals Hawx United and Foxborough start sharing an academy - what could possibly go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf6194e5e50af06f0d92f759b4a5bff78</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Gwen is shocked into drastic action when her father refuses to sign her application to finishing school. Meanwhile, Darrell and Felicity fall out during the North Tower Spelling Bee.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4a52cdf5ec5bb3d79b323bd471e8f1fe</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>From taking man to the moon to figuring out how to get rid of a poo in a submarine, Mark Labbett joins Rattus for a look at some of history?s most brilliant brainboxes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6ef2832f3f770d4773416091121d176b</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall is in Brazil searching for the world?s most elusive cat: the jaguar. He sees them swimming, meets mothers and cubs, and even witnesses one jaguar hunting a caiman.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12fe4d899fb5e401c27fe914c8c9d9be</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Gwen is delighted when Ron suggests they go for a walk together, but it quickly derails when Gwen is left to babysit. Meanwhile, Felicity discovers her love for running.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7d3c9e562e9dea488214233094681b9b</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy discovers a special lamp that can compact organic elements.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a53737e98d0f3674c4501f7700dd884</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Set on a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. Shaun finds a camera which some ramblers have dropped and sets about taking snapshots of the flock. Bitzer is soon on the trail of the missing camera.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbfdf487e61bc85086eaec74349686a06</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>With Paul on vacation, Pieface falls under the influence of a fiery chilli pepper and unexpectedly turns rogue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6a5852bb24bcb8b318f0993738dc0f68</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Dog finds out he has fleas! But when he befriends them, he must hide them from his family to prevent them from getting zapped.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p06176b1ed385e0a4f53417001f70afba</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>To celebrate Christmas, Mum and Dad suggest that the siblings make each other gifts.?When Dog is assigned to give a gift to Cheese, she sneaks to find out what the gift is.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p281f32aaafd23ca825b0cb1dffad639a</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a card that enables them to teleport a magic closet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa08b154dad94ed665954fc65a2a2e098</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>The long-lost episode of Mermaid Man is finally showing on TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbf9a7e2afdc7aa6d3136c4226bae6879</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Debra-Jo is taken to the lost and found box after losing her glasses.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p784dfde268da77c3868768f3c0bdfddb</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When Ozzie catches bad-luck-itis, Orli and Osgood must go on a magical quest to find the ingredients for the antidote before his increasing bad luck blows apart HQ.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5b2efcc04a1283fa7cbc827922fc7c8c</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Charlie takes a three-headed monster dog to school for pet day, but his unwillingness to enforce the rules sees it grow bigger and more dangerous.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3687765f0e813b952b6bc8df96e4492a</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen and Beth decide they must defend the ants that Courtney and Leshawna want to harm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31b289722eba2b0fc5112c5ea20ab77f</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Life is back to normal for Roy and friends, until wild Pok?mon begin to act strangely..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p05aca3c75a07c7eb775df1c9398ee116</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>Elliot faces a tough tap audition, the cast list is out for the underwater show, and Kanon heads back to the Dumping Ground set for more filming.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5e49ee8290b5d4eb1336fdfa1ab27486</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Gwen plots for movie star and Miss Grayling?s estranged cousin Lily Vernon to visit the school. Lily has her own secrets. Meanwhile, Nancy plans a prank to stop eating carrots.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p06cec2ea3d8a72058211819558c62bcc</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio. Michelle holds a scholarship fundraiser for young dancers, while the elite competition gets a step up. Amanda misses a band practice and feels bad about lying to her new friends. West and Giselle get caught up in a talent war.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p901b8dc25e90cc01ffaa0f518f9cdcf4</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings are victims of inexplicable thefts.[(96057)] </desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9da5aa1da675153d73ce99c93b198990</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
