<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Eleven-year-old Cammy is one of six siblings. You'd think that would be reason enough for him to deserve his own space, but Cammy also has Sensory Processing Disorder. Sometimes the bustle of his busy family home is too much for him, and when he gets agitated he knows it's too much for his siblings. He thinks they need a break from him as much as he needs a break from them. Cammy's SPD means he can be oversensitive to certain sounds, smells, textures and flavours. He needs a place where he can be on his own, in calm and quiet to let his senses relax.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p794fe1fca1edf7b7d206c02ead9fd7ea</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius Super Tech with Dick &amp; Dom</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom meet man's future best friend - robots! The boys reveal three geniuses whose ideas have changed the world of robotics and they come face to face with one of the world's largest humanoid robots. They also create their very own destructive robot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf68188727ae3fce3e6bde29444f2a771</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories returns for a special about King John and Magna Carta, starring Ben Miller. John annoys the barons and agrees Magna Carta at Runnymede after a banging rap battle. Meanwhile, across the world, we meet the formidable Genghis Khan in Mongolia and catch up with the crafty Saladin during the Crusades. With, of course, our host Rattus to guide the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p704659bf05f3ee09e78f5adba8ddd40d</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It's a big day at Pottsfield Leisure Centre - there is a new boss in town. Sharon Granger means business and wants to create an advert to bring in more customers and make her mark. She tasks Danny and Mick to make an advert showing the best bits of the leisure centre... what could possibly go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7bb2d3421a49fd3a99f24a2c68077b06</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Odd Sock Elliott needs to get his lost football back from next door?s garden, so Andy and the Band fly into action and meet the scariest neighbour in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9874971bfba58cf9892240203aa76e42</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Apollo prank Dynamite, turning her into a singing banana! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99a45e9399b5fa5991e3b3eb060bfd42</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated deep sea adventure series. Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. While rescuing river creatures after a storm, the Octonauts find a strange egg and come under attack by stinging platypuses.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35471c6d77b1a0cdf5daf0d16325235d</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When Big Lizard and Cosima get covered in nectar, they become unwilling house guests to some overfriendly beetles. Will Dunk come to their rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p524c511b14f3f403c4ed79db32c143e3</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron and Penfold are stranded on a desert island. In the skies above, there is a race to snatch Brunel's All Encompassing Remote Control.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa7b8e966b5c6c306f3a119bdf3118798</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Colonel K disappears on a free holiday, Danger Mouse pulls rank and assumes the mantle of caretaker colonel. However, the role is much less exciting than he anticipated, as world-saving missions make way for endless paperwork. Meanwhile, K's freebie spa retreat happens to be a diversion tactic in Greenback's latest plot to take over the world, with the baron banking on the Danger Agency falling apart without its figurehead and the world descending into disarray.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paef6868cdecdac98504d06f4fc8a956a</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When tasked with the simple quest of building a flat-packed wardrobe, the heroes fail to read the instructions and are whirled into a wonky world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb7deb542b557edde37b8d10af30afbd6</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A Viking Captain summons the Ninjas to find him a steady beat to get his oarsmen moving in time and outrun his rival, Captain Bullyson.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc098a56c9c36f47530d4c941bded98ca</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>It?s the inter-school tournament, and the Vipers might just win. Jessica is determined to spoil everything, and Aoife must use all her detective powers to keep the team together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p146b239f847b5c78963ab9a0c9716863</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Keedie is in burnout after the drama at school. Can Addie help her and find out what happened in Miss Murphy?s office all those years ago. Can Frank and Nina find a lost tortoise.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfea14b2888bc092ce5a7755d6f852e37</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer, but Shaun's insatiable curiosity often leads him into the unlikeliest adventures. A cabbage from a passing truck bounces into the field, and Shaun decides to use it as a football, but the pigs are out to spoil the sheep's game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p80680a81b918e259f7cb575922293686</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Rubi gets a place in a Summer School for Super Smart Kids, which turns out to be one of Walter's tricks so he can learn the secrets of her new invention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p87c783d97968f1517f2ea593080b21bd</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>To avoid Herbert?s surprise visits via his tunnels in the Big Birch, the other heroes take any quest and must deal with an angry plant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1712e7d54bc565d7f40c59dd3788f999</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Boy and Tuck offer to build a clubhouse for Cat and Charlotte, but the two boys have a hard time letting go of their wonderful creation, driving the two girls up the wall.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe57d1a3dab33749509621e5f543584cc</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Girl and K-Jam find Gherkin crying because nobody likes him, he confesses to them that he wants to change and become nicer. After asking the girls to help teach him how to be nice, the girls reluctantly agree and recruit Girl's siblings to help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p44bce5edfd027032c6de54de2dfbed40</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>In the midst of a heatwave, Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over the fridge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa972752e707eb996f7a33d53ae54e9e5</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob and Patrick help Bubble Bass move.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f960595dc2e224cb0527ef746e5aead</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Tamara accuses Melanie of not washing her hands and 'germblocks' her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6856dade9461c07807c6eed288b3a46</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Three villains team up with Bonnie Blaster and her high-powered, oddness-causing gadget.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7cd5c36956c5e871d89db42c64be2346</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Trapped in Helsing?s study with a shapeshifter that can look like anyone, Charlie begins to suspect one of his friends is not what they seem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ee85fc4e5b8555572f4fedec5945634</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen has his superball confiscated, so the gang set off to retrieve it from Chef?s office.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p73436548f2765fadaa07495786f981bd</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Dot shines when dysfunction is on the menu for Kingambit and a struggling cafe.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfcbb083d3a324479121d54dd6ed21e30</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Winx Club - The Magic Is Back</title>
    <desc>The Winx plan a day of adventure in Magixia, but Griselda's restrictions and an incomplete project keep them grounded... until Robin helps them sneak away.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7ade826bf0f43ef15acff860c1cd3f09</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Fury prank Cyclone, who thinks she is filming an animal-themed exercise video dressed as a turtle. The other Gladiators have fun pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14568fca763cea3c2d50d63ef4e99370</image>
    <start>05:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Mac?s latest invention, an AI assistant named Felicity, makes everyone?s lives easier. However, as the band take advantage, Felicity takes matters into her own hands.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p93230023027bf937bd3ad75002395c13</image>
    <start>06:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. The Next Step must face Seeds in the semi-finals of the regionals. The pressure gets to Emily, and when Eldon steps in to help, Emily misinterprets his pep talk.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa67bb3439d6c17dd94cd64d7ca95209f</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our Black History Heroes</title>
    <desc>Mason explains why Jamaican champion sprinter Usain Bolt is his black history hero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p067ed327d55a7227f23f221b58a40b29</image>
    <start>06:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
