<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Can the students pull off a big surprise party for school receptionist Kendall? That?s just one of their challenges as Our School ?pays it forward? with plenty of acts of kindness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c3ec7d03bcefe30448f75f4600d64f3</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs get festival-ready as they craft carnival headwear, artist Lakwena Maciver makes a grey rooftop pop with paint, and Abi Clarke draws a pirouetting otter in a tutu.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0953a9c9704625e78726ab7d76ad8ed3</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The brothers check out their resident dinosaur descendants! Will the black hornbills' new love hut work its magic? And will penguin chick Marli brave her first dip.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p751b6ded65ccd308a894c43d9d6c9df5</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>The presenters look back at all the amazing dens they have built throughout the series and reminisce about the great kids, the tense surprises and the big reveals.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9635d23a1a0dd1903684878172c628b2</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius with Dick and Dom</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom reveal the genius of Alexander Fleming, the man who discovered penicillin. Inspired by Fleming's discovery, they come up with their own genius idea, which involves an attempt to turn billions of germs into priceless works of art.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p309d30b8d42b09979b89d379f9ab2a99</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors put the acoustic reflex to the test with an enormous balloon, and a serious case of snotting awaits the loser of today?s Ouchology.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe0a0c0d282469d6dbaebbfb4a6fdecb3</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Naomi is stressing out about running her first kids party at the leisure centre, and Danny and Mick aren?t helping ? especially after they accidently make Walter Whizz the party entertainer 'magically vanish'. With a host of kids desperate for a pirate party, there is only one thing for it - boys and girls, please welcome Captain Danny the Pirate Magician and his lovely assistant Mick.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p039e96ccd2f99e45a568f04870487377</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>It?s time for the interschool sports day! However, Moxy?s hyper-competitiveness starts to overshadow the events on the field, causing the Odd Socks to make a stand.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b91003b8bac40331972a43ba9ad0bd2</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum is a Little Bro in control! His Big Bro Adam?s going head-to-head against best mate Joe in some funny, gungy and gross challenges: who?ll take the win, and who?ll take on a forfeit from the Wheel Of Doom? Callum isn?t taking any nonsense so they have to work hard to impress him! When animal costumes turn up at their door, Joe and Adam know another messy, wild challenge from Little Bro Callum?s about to begin. Can Adam?s dung beetle take on Joe?s kangaroo and win? Will Joe?s bumblebee emerge victorious against Adam?s spider? Both want to swipe the win and avoid a forfeit from Wheel of Doom, but only one top dog can claw their way to success. Who will it be.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6caeca3d2547c557ab1850e1e3cbef4b</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>Tracker spots some northern bald ibises migrating in the wrong direction.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8c8d2d3a1c4e087fee1f99c9575db24c</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad has left Cosima in charge for the day. It seems like an excellent opportunity to have a massive party! What could possibly go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p98357575927603ff0a5021307d4a4d30</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. In trying to prove he does not believe in magic, Danger Mouse accidentally unleashes an evil magical queen into the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd4935d86a65a4e2a8c44fe8bd4ffa0d5</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Jeopardy Mouse wins the Agent of the Month competition, Danger Mouse and Penfold are forced to travel to New York for a lesson and to take on the criminal organisation known as Hydrant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9bea4a009f4a743a746eef2582c505df</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang produce a hand-drawn comic which is a surprise hit all round Beanotown. Envious of their success, Walter embarks on a mission of cartoon-drawing sabotage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5a49050e52f6494391bec7f241f68794</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Deep in the caverns below Beanotown town hall, a mysterious species of over-sized hamsters may or may not exist, so may or may not be at risk of being hunted down and turned into fluffy slippers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbd0702cc5afebf8a17005c88036a955a</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Hoofius has decided not to quest. Not because he would rather be doing a puzzle or playing his panpipes (though that is rather enjoyable), but because this will be his 1,000th quest and will be added to the Scroll of Honour for all to see for eternity. His friends reluctantly quest without him, but when they don?t return, Hoofius soon comes to regret staying behind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6721a1465173d7050ebe831f36cb4589</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Trevor is extremely proud of being the clever one in the gang and thinks that his smart mouth is his superpower. However, his friends feel that sometimes his jokes go too far - and they are right to be concerned! When Mr Friendlyface sends the heroes on a quest to prevent Toothgrinder the Ogre from messing up the village green, it?s Trevor?s smart mouth that puts all the heroes in danger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbc10a55045431109408268b6cc99aaf5</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Tasked with letting go of items that might be holding them back, Lily struggles to shred Matt Furnish?s love letters, and Claire can?t sell her beloved merch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7c8c057f5b92b690440da8b3d67e808a</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Addie and Audrey?s friendship blossoms as they go door-to-door to spread the word about Juniper?s witches. Maggie starts a secret rebellion, putting her at odds with Elinor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fe90bee762eed019908d0b716da7059</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Dennis and the gang think they have caused Ralf to lose his job, they're determined to make his last day at Bash Street School totally blam by setting up the greatest prank Ralf's ever known.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3d939c9462f01933b550eae67571eb8</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When a witch struggles to master her new wand, Twinkle decides to have a go, only to make her friends vanish. She must now go on a solo quest to find them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f70c51f662eb1e9f7b58d6b81511ec0</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>K-Jam is moving into the neighbourhood and staying with the family for a while. However, Girl gets insecure and thinks that her awesome best friend is trying to take her place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbace25267391c527963e66f359240ab</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a container filled with metal survival food flasks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0287b9b09672b2fe39abe8f7f107f3fa</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings attempt to take back a chocolate egg from a group of penguins.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb634cea656ce1728d93bd2b352b1369c</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Squidward sends SpongeBob and Patrick on a scavenger hunt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p33ba18c96af3fb5afa9ccad939dcb794</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Debra-Jo is taken to the lost and found box after losing her glasses.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p784dfde268da77c3868768f3c0bdfddb</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When villain mastermind William Ocean plans to cover the entire world in water, the Mobile Unit heads to his underwater lair.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc43a0e2897d8c63f5cbf52ac222e33e8</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Dot creates a plan for her Tera training aptitude test against Iono - but will it work.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p29d0f0fcb80808c46ffd306e4bb9cedd</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Winx Club - The Magic Is Back</title>
    <desc>Bloom learns from Faragonda that she possesses the powerful Dragon Flame, but she fears the dangers it might bring. Meanwhile, Stella is excited about a blind date with the mysterious Prince Luke.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa0384c3ad2f0f31e632ffb83f5e5ee53</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Can under-15s defender Sol lead his team to victory in The Floodlit Cup? Can Konan bounce back with a little help from family? Spurs legend Jenna Schillaci takes on Eloise and Holly in Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe54318761874ad558e22c95105f153b7</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Abby discovers dinosaur footprints on the Isle of Skye.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p853cbe1dff81eab4047ae8da30fcbb70</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Bound for their world tour, the Odd Socks detour to Moxy?s old school to wish an old teacher farewell. However, seeing the school in dire straits, the Odd Socks agree to help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p41734c8c3da718be74178e786f718043</image>
    <start>06:05PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>With Women?s Rugby World Cup fever riding high, one rising star has her eyes set on the top. Talented, fearless, and utterly dedicated, 14-year-old Ava is used to pushing herself hard -but this summer, something unexpected shifts. Her coach asks her to help with a younger girls? team who are at risk of dropping out, and Ava starts to see how much rugby can give beyond winning. Along the way, she meets her Red Roses heroes, watches them play in the World Cup opener, and pushes herself to the limit at her first England trials. What begins as a summer about chasing her own dream soon becomes a powerful journey of connection, confidence, and discovery. As Ava helps inspire others to stay in the game, she realises what rugby truly gives you - and why lifting others can matter as much as any trophy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2214aa91919ba69dcc25426ec51123c8</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>23 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Shaun comes across some newly hatched chicks who think he is their mum. He is determined to get rid of them, but how.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56d4d38a872d8e76290e5e8a055759dc</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse is responsible for Professor Squawkencluck losing her job his clumsy attempts to get her back help the Baron steal half the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3bb8928291651f97c9f27761acb6a515</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Gnasher becomes the star of an action movie, playing Grizzly's on-screen sidekick. But filming keeps him and Dennis apart, leaving Dennis feeling lonely. Could Dennis and Gnasher really become Grizzly and Gnasher.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf69b7bfa9708ece3ec2df8941e20525f</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Lady Burlington's precious jewels are stolen, the kids believe that Cat was the unwitting thief and didn't know that she was stealing. They try to put things right by returning the valuables and teaching Cat the error of her ways. However, with Lady Burlington?s security guard searching for the burglar, the kids find their task way trickier than anticipated.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf59c8d2dec2daca258b148dd3d1f8a36</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p66969daa0f99e33d82e5a573ecd56e26</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy tries to catch a fish despite the Lemmings kitesurfing and the presence of a shark.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3efc618f6e8e450995739fce85facb20</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings search for a treasure to get food from a Yummy vending machine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdb531860e4f8bc74791e6847b3f6060c</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Patrick thinks he's an old man.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5453b45a0769636dd6bffdc50852e51e</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Little O has been asked to record a new training video for kids interested in becoming Odd Squad Agents. However, a Sandbeast is on the loose and causing oddness all over town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc84a2d4cd3b3481b97279f3595596cd9</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve dives with 100 grey nurse sharks - aka ragged-tooth sharks - a wobbegong and a gigantic whale shark, and he joins a mission in Indonesia to save sharks from over-fishing with eco-tourism.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdcc05d21452d9faf35f104aaea0c088f</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 9-11 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn how to multiply by 10, 100, and 1000 and separate larger numbers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbfdf9aeb5c05ee3f4b4da994b6f7e33e</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Get ready for incredible experiments and mind-bending puzzles to impress your friends with Wow That?s Amazing. Owain and Tilly are here to explore epic science tricks to try at home and showcase brand new technology innovations from around the world! In this episode, find out how to make totally trashy music, discover we all grow and shrink in a day, learn that a volcano can erupt in your kitchen, and order a burger? from a robot.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe0d513e868178bc756bd1e7250185026</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Can energetic Year 7 Ibby focus on his task of being a classroom assistant for a day? And Year 8 have a challenge of their own - to entertain the residents of a nearby care home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p474b76ba9dd919e5b6ed70c3a8d77276</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs bowl into space with DIY alien skittles, Emma Stothard weaves a wicker dog, and Kiell Smith-Bynoe draws a ghost so spooked, it?s nearly see-through.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe84a9fb444c89c3b7b8033f116add9f6</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The brothers check out who the alpha animals are at the zoo. What will the lions make of the brothers? homemade zebras? And how will Jet the lanner falcon?s new tail feathers fare.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe5815f68679c6a3337c0a9e643f96215</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>The presenters look back at some of the amazing dens from series one and two, seeing how they have been enjoyed and finding out how they changed the lives of the young Dengineers. Lauren revisits the survival, art, Hollywood cinema and DJ dens.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p06e90393814f26d710735c04befcb2a7</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius with Dick and Dom</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom reveal the genius of Italian inventor Guglielmo Marconi, the man behind wireless communication. Inspired by Marconi, Dick and Dom come up with their own genius idea, which involves Dick taking to the skies in a hang-glider for an extreme radio broadcast.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p23bfe5720beb818f89fef3ca97720e01</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors reveal how the human brain creates maps to prevent getting lost.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbfd2b611a77bd2909d004bbba7d36529</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It?s the annual five-a-side challenge match against the rival leisure centre, and team captain Lance knows exactly what position to play Danny and Mick in: the laundry room, well away from anywhere they can do anything that will cost them the game. However, a tiny accident with the kit leads to a mass walk-out from the team, and it?s up to Danny, Mick, and three other dummies to take to the field for the beautiful game and become leisure centre legends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb83948b7c649d96366bc478be2bf34c4</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Mac?s latest invention, an AI assistant named Felicity, makes everyone?s lives easier. However, as the band take advantage, Felicity takes matters into her own hands.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p93230023027bf937bd3ad75002395c13</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>It?s Bro?s Sports Day, and Adam and Joe break out the clubs for a mini-golf challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7d7b5023c89dcc6c5a491409ea2007c1</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated deep sea adventure series. Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. Kwazii and Dashi become entangled in a strange deep sea creature, a siphonophore, and when a geyser blasts it towards the surface, the Octonauts must stop its ascent before it bursts.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf68cb89c310b4fe234e0393bc292b6cd</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>When it unexpectedly snows, Cosima decides it must be Christmas! Rex disrupts her festive preparations, but it doesn't stop the family having a perfect 'Proximas'.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa8fc139e5b9503360fe4922cf761c7d3</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Penfold's addiction to social media helps the Baron turn all of Danger Mouse's secrets against him in a plot to deflate the planet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6f7ce120fee94baea61d80208ee3e590</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The Princess is back and erases all weekdays so she can play at the weekend forever. Danger Mouse must ruin everyone's lives by fixing the problem.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51b2ee65ff2e3f266a9013ffa3688df9</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Miss Mistry and Mrs Creecher clash over the best way to teach Class 3C about butterflies. The gang just want to get through the lesson so they can get out of school in time for a Grizzly Griller Wildlife Event.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f724fc607801733f58ba35ac017e5a6</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When Olive surprises herself and everyone around her by actually becoming a good cook, Dr Pfooflepfeffer tries to cash in by turning the school canteen into an exclusive and super-expensive dining experience.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdee355ef68772da8fcf20dd134fad956</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are questing to find out who is behind a string of cake thefts, and go into detective mode. After questioning the baker, they decide to stage a stakeout at the bakery. However, when they spy cakes apparently walking off by themselves, they realise that there is more to this mystery than meets the eye - and a quest to find some missing cakes soon turns into a quest to save the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5645751379a5d59cdd33d1d6bc3124d3</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert receives a bottle of Goldenbeard to make his beard longer, stronger and more golden than ever ? and the results are dramatic! Everyone is talking about Herbert Goldenbeard, the great hero and quester, and Herbert is loving the attention. However, when he is kidnapped by the goblins and needs his friends to rescue him, Herbert soon realises that they are much more important than any golden beard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p86555ecedfb25de25cc47ca98336e9a0</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Animal lover and social media superstar Kyle Thomas wants to prove that creepy crawlies can be cute, and Joel is challenged to wear thousands of bees on his face. Meanwhile, Shini meets one of the UK?s cutest birds, and Henry gets a bath.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paed749e84c79e1b0af7bbe48e1cfdd57</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>A trip to the big city leads to a shocking discovery about Maggie?s disappearance, and Nina and Keedie build a shaky truce while party shopping.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb6421909aa03af91feccab45bb170d8c</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis recruits Grizzly Griller to help make school sports day more extreme, but as he and JJ get competitive against each other, who is sabotaging both their chances of winning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59a7ef36f278f1b30593801e12d27fc2</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes find treasure as they bid to save Merhaven from an angry seaweed. Blossom is delighted with her bath bomb treasure, but rather than use it, she insists on bringing it along on the watery quest to save it for a special occasion. But as the angry seaweed nears Merhaven, Blossom realises she must finally sacrifice her treasure to save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4cabd4631ea30373511762999c2b1fe4</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When the kids think that Mom may be pregnant, they set out to prove they will be great babysitters. Along the way, they learn that it's much harder to do it alone than it is together.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb5bb5a7b40090762af8e629842f8f3e8</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings transform the ice field into an open-air discotheque.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f06f9cbceff3fdffb587982bedc67b7</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings come up with a ride worthy of a county fair in the living room.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc5ca0446f5b7a01f0879450c3aac0187</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>No-one else can see SpongeBob's new giant, fluffy hamster friend.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1127fcb8121280c85cc9b9bae3a1ad2d</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Rory forgets his lunch and goes to the milk bar but keeps it secret from Mrs Gonsha.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa2e5d44326098b1a993a545713f04e94</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Dream Weaver is turning Little O?s dreams into nightmares. Now that she isn?t getting much sleep, cases are piling up.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5843ca9fbd5cd95df2c361c176448128</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko keeps getting distracted by Hatenna and Terapagos, and Floragato isn?t happy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52233d61e7c818e33e104ab3f1c62293</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Winx Club - The Magic Is Back</title>
    <desc>When Vexius launches a devastating attack on Red Fountain, Winx and Specialists must unite to protect the school. Meanwhile, Bloom uncovers a shocking connection between Vexius and her Dragon Flame.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf77c216983dbcba49c78f522d41b26fc</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Can Charlie return to goalscoring after injury? And will Ace or Julian come out on top? Martha Thomas takes on under-11 Harry in a fiercely fought Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4001519207c28582f14615e77df38b69</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Apollo prank Dynamite, turning her into a singing banana! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99a45e9399b5fa5991e3b3eb060bfd42</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:15PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy is determined to make the Odd Socks into ?proper? teachers, but the band?s unique methods lead to chaos. Can they turn it around before the school day ends.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8112d8a5b097c024da3a23604243c06c</image>
    <start>06:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. Riley tries to make amends with her sister, but it doesn't go exactly as planned. Eldon struggles with the feelings he has for both Michelle and Emily.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p03bb486c2a4c3e2c3e18364c14d663b5</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Set on a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. The Farmer decides it is time to give the flock a shearing. But when they see his first attempt, Shaun and the others plan their escape.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd7961b6ed2796ee4e8ca3c55e30d789f</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold must travel to the Twystyverse to stop the evil tyrant Baron Silas von Penfold from taking over both versions of the Earth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96bd7bb99d9e77929da195732a4166fb</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis needs to pull off a magnificent stunt to save the skate park from closure, so Gran gives him the skateboard of the legendary Kendo 360 to help. When the special board goes missing at the worst possible moment, Dennis needs to dig deep and realise that it's the skater and not the board that's important.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p54738b714536b205261da7b9c907d809</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids are asked to watch their neighbour's pet hamster and are given strict instructions not to let it out of its cage. However, Mouse doesn't believe any animal should live in a cage.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p28f3c819160e656641eaee19a23624e6</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ea81f0e5ff7b0216221cecc26300601</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Retrieving data. Wait a few seconds and try to cut or copy again.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5182ecf611fd5ff1885769a76c91b757</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy notices that the Lemmings have laid hands on a pirate cannon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf7d718e20f9db9f57661911a80b230c3</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob and Patrick exchange tiny living versions of themselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdaaa0c4f05e10cfcd5bad7aa815ae717</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Little O has been asked to record a new training video for kids interested in becoming Odd Squad Agents. However, a Sandbeast is on the loose, causing oddness all over town and making things difficult.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35890290f3f330578f3929990adfcb3c</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve is underwater in Indonesia with funny-looking frogfish, a stargazer, flamboyant cuttlefish, a mimic octopus and a Bobbit worm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p05d0ffe9c9db73525c7c9d7a55013bde</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn how to use subordinating conjunctions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc00193ae136a4870756158b89a1d24e9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Get ready for incredible experiments and mind-bending puzzles to impress your friends with Wow That?s Amazing. Owain and Tilly are here to explore epic science tricks to try at home and showcase brand new technology innovations from around the world! In this episode, discover a weird way to puzzle your pupils, reveal the fizzy secrets of sand, find out that static electricity can be attractive and learn to bust some earthquake dance moves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p149161a86c186417f1b6bc6adea33717</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>Year 8 Tom is looking for someone to join his band and perform in front of the school. Who will pass the audition? CBBC boy band The Wonderland make a surprise visit to help out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc6f0ebdad7a879424677c791a1ec1561</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs craft cardboard games consoles you can actually play, Julian Beever warps reality with a pavement pork pie, and Tilly Lockey draws a shimmering mermaid.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12cc636ed9e0b0dcaabe47f036b4ec55</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The boys welcome some new arrivals to the zoo. Mimo the Pygmy Marmoset emerges from its nest box for the first time and two penguin chicks hatch. Meanwhile, it?s Tilly the red panda?s birthday, and to celebrate, the brothers decide to hold a cake-off. It?s a tradition at the zoo that when a new animal in born, all the animals get presents. Finally, we catch up with the boys in Rwanda as they meet wildlife heroes fighting to save the planet?s largest primates - the mountain gorilla.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p120bbe7f3af27ea48621bd070c1e29c5</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>The presenters look back at some of our amazing dens from series 1 and 2, seeing how they have been enjoyed and finding out how they changed the lives of the young Dengineers. Lauren revisits the train, magical library, community and plane dens.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd48971ffa97eb1d602e9f37f2e1d279c</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>BBC Live Lessons</title>
    <desc>A series of 30-minute presenter-led educational programmes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peccf79fcc1db6414be4efc5476d241e9</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The hunt is on for grossest thing ever seen on Operation Ouch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13c5142daca6e04150509a7f11d1594e</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Joy wants to check up on Danny and Mick, so has called in a mystery undercover customer to keep them on their toes. The boys think they can beat this test by working out who the undercover customer is - but there are a lot of needy customers in the centre today, and it could be anybody. So, one by one, Danny and Mick set out to narrow down the list of suspects in their own chaotic way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p22cf52be221d321ea3b86f7d951215f2</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Hopeful of getting more students to join, Andy leads an open day to show off the school at its best. However, disaster strikes after a mix-up with Andy?s plan for the band.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdcb3ae4ecb4566607fdb548a3f056e91</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>It?s Mum?s birthday, but Adam and Joe have forgotten to sort her surprise party! Who can decorate the house and bake her a cake in this birthday blackout bonanza.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pce2cf20f8b5fff85d77c8470b7e98176</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated deep sea adventure series. Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. The Octonauts venture into a dangerous red-hot lava tube to rescue a teeny-tiny water bear who doesn't seem to mind the heat at all.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p51a1a08808ca88acfd726d9e768aa10a</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Ammon gets spooked by a tiny insect, but overcomes her fear to rescue Cosima and Big Lizard from the rapids.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8716df18f87dcc163f737012ee52ca4c</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>When Danger Mouse is responsible for Professor Squawkencluck losing her job his clumsy attempts to get her back help the Baron steal half the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3bb8928291651f97c9f27761acb6a515</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Our dynamic duo take on a shoddy army of knock-offs when alien Quark's latest money-making scheme is to create cheap copies of Danger Mouse and Penfold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc3534acab020f64bb5ca220b64ae15c1</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Professor von Screwtop gets mistaken for the new kid in school and joins Class 3C for the day. Rubi is so embarrassed at her dad?s antics that she resorts to pranking to get him into trouble and out of the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p060c373a4ae75d174dc60fc03089f42e</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>JJ applies for an elite sporting school. However, not realising it's miles away from Beanotown, he needs to do badly in the sporting assessment to get out of it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p25f8c727ad716ff6332cb203cd3afeab</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom is terrible at keeping secrets, and Trevor can?t help but point that out. To prove him wrong, Blossom refuses to reveal the secret hiding place for her piece of the Amulet of Protection, even though the heroes need it to stop Balthazar casting a weather spell on the forest. With a rain of crabs heading their way, the heroes must quickly persuade Blossom to reveal her secret.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96c570335130856ee7aaba63648a0da2</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The Gnome Crystal Mine has ground to a halt, leaving the forest with no crystals, no power supply and melting ice lollies! The heroes are tasked with a quest to find out what has happened and to fix it. It turns out that a slimy beast named Smarg has made the mine her home. But with Hoofius?s fear of gunk getting the better of him, evicting the slippery Smarg is not going to be easy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p858de20cb9333a64f647c54c77975ddd</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>When Miss Marmaduke?s love of sushi leads to firing all the teachers, Lily, Claire, Jin and Mr Malone join forces with the kids to get their jobs back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0b9515de0bf5e11b5e51007faabc9d74</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Addie is determined to make Nina and Keedie?s party the best ever, but the plan falls apart when Emily blags a ticket. Meanwhile, a party in the 16th century puts Maggie in danger.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d09ee7dbe24b8bab9f38e6465015d2c</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Power-hungry tiny alien Empress Miasma takes control of Gnasher from the inside and uses him in her attempts to take over planet Earth. But when Miasma breaks out of Gnasher into Beanotown for real and Walter helps her grow in size, mayhem really takes hold.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf248fb354599260a283147e9ab8857c1</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:25PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes go on a quest to get Hoofius?s Toby Jug back from the depths of the Riddling Ruins and are faced with a series of puzzles and traps to solve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67fad6fb2cc188991a416f8965659da7</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>To prove she can be selfless, Cheese begins granting wishes. However, when a rival shows up to do the same, Cheese loses sight of her goal as she tries to remain number one.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p99a5c24d810a52fe55d6ef82c9add8ce</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings perform acrobatic high jumps, competing for the winning prize.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbceb34cff7926fc79529e5fea7f726cf</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A penguin decides to help Grizzy catch piles of fish, and the pair strike up a friendship.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p782529c432d87dbd62b376749b3264f4</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Patrick wants to be a horse.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfc50fe65e0fbc3383dc2ac35e4d268cb</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Debra-Jo and Tamara stop speaking to each other, and Melanie must pick a side.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8cebd879ef7546627439bc928d80a9b1</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>With Jimmy Jam?s Scrambler Machine scrambling Odd Squad communication, the villains plan to unleash oddness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf97649b294dc6a672513c4c89ad71a6b</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>When Roy needs help, Wattrel gets a chance to show its trainer just how much it has grown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1a3b9e50994bdb7b5a52b73cdcd5d55f</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Winx Club - The Magic Is Back</title>
    <desc>With Vexius?s dark power growing, Alfea prepares for a looming battle, but Bloom?s sudden disappearance raises alarm. Meanwhile, Bloom learns a shocking truth about her past and her family.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7d9bb8619ef686f3b89d20638d9e069f</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Do Rio and Etta have what it takes to be accepted into the Football Academy? Can captain Sol and new signing Phoenix beat Fulham in the cup? Destiny Udogie takes on George and Ace in Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p206b4cf0cac44be673b9aa6395357ef9</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro and Phantom prank Fire at a kids' birthday party! The rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3eb6afc7027c8bfed2f443d8a7e7d70e</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:15PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Pushed out of his comfort zone, Blu must tackle his inability to dance in order to put on a show and impress a celebrity judge. The whole school is counting on him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p44b1570c05248dbb219bc90913aa1ef5</image>
    <start>06:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. Giselle wants to make her mark in A-Troupe by doing a dangerous lift, but Daniel isn't so sure it is a good idea. Michelle thinks it's exactly what they need to get them to regionals and wants to help them, against Kate and Chris's wishes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paedc725e065c6152c9989e1e70056bd8</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>25 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
