<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc181cd80735ffb3a2df17f8becbb137e</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a crab that can open coconuts with a snip of its claw.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd852285adcf3efc4195388236c228122</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A helicopter takes off from the beach, leaving behind installations for a TV game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4170a715769540ec9092bd83b32da0fd</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob and Patrick help Bubble Bass move.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f960595dc2e224cb0527ef746e5aead</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Globetrotting villain Stu Venir is turning monuments into keychains! Agents must uncover a pattern to predict where he will strike next.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5a8c8e6bcfcf82a3d99f9f5878d0704</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall is in Brazil searching for the world?s most elusive cat: the jaguar. He sees them swimming, meets mothers and cubs, and even witnesses one jaguar hunting a caiman.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12fe4d899fb5e401c27fe914c8c9d9be</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about counting in halves and quarters, and doubling and halving numbers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa05c54ca475359c69660ad480e837b8a</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Owain and Tilly find out how to make super-weird goo, discover a quick fix for a bad case of bed hair, try a puzzling way to fool thirsty friends, and explore future space travel.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96a8262135d5f3523e561167bc4f873b</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>It?s Bonfire Night and Year 7 Ta?Kya wants to overcome her fear of fireworks. Can a science lesson help? And the school launches a club to give students their first taste of cricket.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p694388911899efc3cbc3606b19cabde4</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ricky Wilson's Art Jam</title>
    <desc>Sports presenter, travel documentary maker and former Paralympian Ade Adepitan visits the Art Jam studio to show Ricky three items that mean the world to him - his precious London 2012 medal moulds, a special family photo from the day they left Nigeria for the UK and a one-of-a-kind brightly coloured hoody. While chatting to Ricky, Ade shares amazing stories about his childhood, falling in love with basketball, winning medals as a Paralympian and his passion for travelling the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcdfdc7caea8e8e3d59c5fcc1a93f2620</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The One Zoo Three brothers create a winter wonderland at the zoo, with special festive treats for the Amur tigers. Meanwhile, Tim and Tam the Tapirs tuck into a winter vegetable challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7b7e2a7c1562f1cef670346c4cc7689d</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Ocean, nine, from Brentwood has had a tough time. His younger brother Sky died two years ago and he needs a place to escape to when things get too much for him. He also has a new baby sister which he's excited about but his house has become pretty noisy! Ocean loves marble runs because they're like rollercoasters and one day he'd like to be a rollercoaster designer. He wants a marble run den where he can get away from it all and work towards his dream.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1cdcdc5b3d5a535b8636ae230cca3c3d</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius with Dick and Dom</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom reveal the genius of Charles Darwin and explore the theory of evolution. Inspired by Darwin's genius ideas, they come up with their own genius idea when they take the plunge and go face to face with one of the most perfectly evolved predators on the planet - a terrifying shark.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p83632f555b5c18907018d9e31353de27</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Identical twins Dr Chris and Dr Xand van Tulleken experiment and explore their way through the fascinating world of medicine and biology. Chris and Xand will let the viewer in to their exclusive world of medicine and explain the awesome things our bodies can do. The doctors experiment on their muscles to show how they work. Dr Chris meets some wriggly maggots that are helping to heal a sore foot, and Dr Xand goes on call with an emergency ambulance team. Meanwhile, over in accident and emergency, one patient has some grit in his head after a fall in the playground and another has injured his neck after performing a karate kick.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p740d99449bb67f0c5621ccc607d407c8</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Joy has a Valentine?s Day date and has ordered the boys to turn the caf? into a romantic restaurant. Just as they are finishing up Clive arrives - he also has a date and wants some top tips. Danny and Mick are happy to help until they find out Clive?s date is with Joy! It?s bad enough having her as a boss, the boys don?t want to start calling her mummy too! Can they break the happy couple up before the date is over.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdafa4a9e989df2d40776349470f2c257</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy?s sister Ruby wants to meet her hero, superstar vlogger Fay Moss, so Andy and the Band risk missing their next gig by racing off to help out. Staging a fake fashion photoshoot by posing as flashy designers, they attempt to bag some time with Fay by distracting her security guard! Cousin Mac?s new auto-tuner invention is put to good use, but after an epic diva tantrum, will Fay live up to all of Ruby expectations.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fd9ca307fd295ae771597804d126e27</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Celebs Viggo Venn and Phil Green come to the aid of Adam and Joe as they try to prove to Callum who is the most talented. With impressions and dad dancing, what?s not to like.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p957c5bfbca86c719e8a1a2eb81ec77ee</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated deep sea adventure series. Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. When a sardine swallows the key to a treasure chest, a humpback whale helps Kwazii track it down.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3eaf03545ac852155a351f47d0f3797</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Big Lizard wants to have a go with Dad's new drone, but first he has to prove that he can go a whole day without breaking something precious. Good luck, Big Lizard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p850b309749660e2b38b39d00c45b2933</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse must battle Quark again, but this time in the weirdest and most dangerous of places: Penfold's dreams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef370659f818656714ea292bc7ca5e2e</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron steals DM's confidence and gives it to his shy daughter, Delilah Von Greenback, creating a dangerous criminal mastermind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5df627a084f7c486593e10df1725c85c</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis leads the gang on the baffling trail of a mysterious Beanotown secret society.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbe40fbbd57946697982b8c481f8009a4</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Walter and Dennis go head to head in a sponsored silence. Being quiet doesn?t come naturally to either of them, as they struggle to make it through a chaotic school day and keep schtumm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f774701f77fb51f6357283a8b30f9ef</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The blossom has gone missing. No, not Blossom the unicorn, the blossom on the trees! The heroes are sent on a quest deep into the heart of the forest, where legend has it you can see a face watching you from the trees. Twinkle doesn?t believe in legends, but when help comes from nowhere as they try and stop the scoundrel that is stealing the blossom, she is forced to reconsider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2f8d2357ef662dfdfa8453de1222ecd1</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are relieved that the loud, threatening voice they can hear actually belongs to a small slug named Zorgoth, who is armed with a megaphone. However, when Zorgoth uses his Orb of Compression to shrink the heroes down to the size of ants, their relief evaporates. They must now embark on a long and dangerous quest, through their picnic items and beyond, to warn the Council before Zorgoth shrinks the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe50df153eaba594e89a65c54ae953f0c</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>The chance of a trophy has Aoife focused on a win. However, Charlotte is distracted, and Aoife has to ?mute the cute? if Charlotte is going to get back on her game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94f9fd034f66efa4b9eb4790a62d3096</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Addie?s fundraising campaign disrupts a beloved village event, and Maggie?s attempts to get help end in disaster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27e109732967cd8e2202bc1b959e71ff</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang train Bertie in the art of standing up to people so he can rebel against Walter's bossiness - but they train him too well and he becomes a dangerous rebel without a clue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ee81567708d80e99b9f35e4a420add2</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Much to Trevor?s irritation, a rare phoenix woodpecker takes a liking to him - so he demands an immediate quest to return the bird to its real home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd460f05ee8f6efe98ada93b746aa74d</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Girl gets the chance to put together the school fair, her friends and family jump at the chance to help - until she gets advice from a hardened businesswoman.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4cd9a8aad5a8972f434d9ccaeb212454</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A Lemming finds a mysterious mask that endows him with the power of telekinesis.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peecc469e064293cb3826d2ecd69c6307</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy chases after the Lemmings and the jar of Yummy in their remote-controlled car.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p92aff3c434c1be5d19dc5f8fd5c7244c</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob doesn't need a licence to operate a self-driving car.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9c4826b562f0a562124128ccc6c32e52</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Tamara sprains her ankle and can?t do the beep test, so she decides to coach Debra-Jo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbeece33f0ad0f9256f37364a6d66065</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>With The Big O in space, the Xs are checking Agents? licenses for fighting oddness. Orla and Oswald must get their creature handling licenses, and fast.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf237663a38f9fcb4e07c97b0cffde0d3</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Friede visits his former workplace to look for clues about the mystery behind Terapagos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c3dda388bac2abac98c77251721d451</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Winx Club - The Magic Is Back</title>
    <desc>Following a scary encounter with a magic creature on her 16th birthday, Bloom discovers that she has magical powers. She is rescued by two fairies from Alfea School for Fairies and Witches.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa392635580aa64d93ddb96931017eac9</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Mia and Lucy face their biggest game of the season, and buds Masai and Ernest get competitive. Spurs legend Sandro takes on Jayden in Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p63635eb94acbd201ba1c631551fc90cc</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>The story of a 12-year-old boy waiting for a heart donor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p180a95149418c0f1a499e7ebf31fadae</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Gladiators? stars Apollo and Electro surprise children in a Salford school when they lead a PE lesson with a difference.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfcd4e5a3bdf2843cec4b8f9fe7289d76</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. Chloe's financial problems finally boil over and she is forced to leave A-Troupe. Michelle and Emily decide to be co-captains and work together to not only choreograph a new routine but also get Chloe back in the group.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b21f3b07f6556fa35c2ceb7213b4edc</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
