<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>Julia gets between Caleb and Priya during the most painful memory game of all time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d656e5bd2675f07c2ceecdd81f59549</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Plankton's pet amoeba Spot has puppies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3aec6731d44095522f9d9a86d66803dd</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Mr Krabs is too scared to get his physical.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc83b687ea889f4f6d02736b5f0be2494</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>While falling, Grizzy performs a series of acrobatics that amazes the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p723cb1057326be4e83853b78617595a0</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Animated adventures with the mischievous young sheep and his flock. Shaun and Bitzer discover that a visitor to the farm is not as cute and adorable as she seems.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p113da15aa6ff745d88153ce098d4d1c0</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold accompany Professor Squawkencluck to the Brainiac Symposium - the annual science convention, where King Kong Brunels's latest misfiring invention, the Cow Trainer, reminds his fellow boffins exactly why he is the laughing stock of the scientist community. When King Kong Brunel suggests that the Professor's success is all due to her privileged life as Danger Agency lab technician with scientist parents, an irked Squawk uses Brunel's Cow Trainer to swap bodies with him in order to show that she could be just as successful in his shoes. However, she soon finds that life as King Kong Brunel is as dispiriting as he makes out, as she is laughed out of the symposium when masquerading as her simian adversary. Elsewhere, an opportunistic King Kong Brunel finds himself revelling at playing Squawk, as finds he himself inside her lab having hitched a lift back to HQ with an unwitting Danger Mouse and Penfold. On discovering the truth, Danger Mouse and Penfold have the body- swapper turned on them, as KKB escapes back to the convention with his newly acquired Squawk-shaped credibility, and a new invention so poorly put together that it could end the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10d782c873c5cb440e14211052a06036</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Hoofius plays his grandfaun?s old magical panpipes, his friends do exactly what he asks them to do - perfect for leading a quest... or so he thinks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbada50b36a9303ac56775c369e7c2be0</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids want to impress Gramps by completing the Gauntlet of Greatness carnival attraction that he did when he was their age. However, Dog and Girl just can't seem to beat it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db98e87d457a49378a84e78a275e08d</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf0a915ab271c1c9c1e1b2a33188e7991</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings invent a whole bunch of bouncing games with spongy jelly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe74f0b84aee020f2055f16fd17fbfae0</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings happen upon a bracelet that increases the strength of its wearer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf006c51e34db491fb6b6a7f5babd196</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>The long-lost episode of Mermaid Man is finally showing on TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbf9a7e2afdc7aa6d3136c4226bae6879</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Villain Miss Information is using graphs to spread falsehoods about Odd Squad, which is leading to the public not trusting them. Can Captain O get the public back on side.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81bd195210835185fd3d564b62fdc1a6</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>When an ex-chores boy reappears wearing Helsing?s invisibility jacket, the gang is tasked with destroying it. But can Pierce resist the temptation to be bad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb3ce24ec5d9349cd2520f3d380cbd25</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>A special visit from the mayor means that his chains need putting away safely, while he goes for a swim. As head of security, Mick locks them in Joy?s safe, but due to his forgetfulness, Danny and Mick now need to work out another way to retrieve them before the mayor returns.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67d3bf33fe7afe0b424f8e1914b79a2f</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Numbers to 100, finding one more and one less, signs and symbols.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8497519bb2385402291d2ce16bce6065</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Could you build a slide to the other side of the world? You would need to start in space, use the slippiest slide ever and make sure you have enough supplies before you go down it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c93e4b0e1fc4adb5f1d0842be1d0abe</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Out of This World</title>
    <desc>In this episode, Dr Maggie tells the story of the Space Race, what it was, the key missions involved and how the USA, competing against and then collaborating with the Soviet Union, got us to where we are today in space. Dr Maggie?s guest is Tim Peake, the first British astronaut to live on board ISS, who tells us how astronauts from different countries successfully work together in space. Dr Maggie also answers your space questions and unveils her top five 'firsts in space'. Buckle up, it?s time to go Out Of this World.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ae90359fda623e4c4cca90584ac5fec</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>The girls get creative as Daisy and her friends give the common room a colourful makeover. Eva and Evie enter the school photography competition, with some top tips from wildlife presenter Megan McCubbin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p284c6a12a13bdaf11b948cf74d39429b</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs get festival-ready as they craft carnival headwear, artist Lakwena Maciver makes a grey rooftop pop with paint, and Abi Clarke draws a pirouetting otter in a tutu.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0953a9c9704625e78726ab7d76ad8ed3</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The One Zoo Three zoo celebrates the opening of some amazing new animal habitats with a new den for the sun bears - but will the jaguars feature pad be a bit hit or miss.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82c799404a8b398ad1720b5d28fab278</image>
    <start>10:20AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Archie is ten years old and as well as planting, growing and harvesting vegetables, he loves looking after his chickens. Archie sells his home grown veg and eggs locally and uses the profits to buy food for his local food bank. He's taken his enterprise as far as he can and desperately needs a farm den so he can increase his productivity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56791e20903f1fb7af1af660dda2480a</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius: Monster Builds</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom go supersized in this massive movers spectacular in which they trace the origins of the genius ideas that have made shifting heavy weights a whole lot easier. In their element, the boys head to a scrapyard to find out how hydraulic grabbers work, get up close to one of the weirdest-looking aircraft ever built and get to grips, literally, with the world's largest hydraulic hand.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f2118c4c2ca8416715ca1a3003f20f5</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories returns for a special about King John and Magna Carta, starring Ben Miller. John annoys the barons and agrees Magna Carta at Runnymede after a banging rap battle. Meanwhile, across the world, we meet the formidable Genghis Khan in Mongolia and catch up with the crafty Saladin during the Crusades. With, of course, our host Rattus to guide the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p704659bf05f3ee09e78f5adba8ddd40d</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It's staff charity cabaret night at the Pottsfield Leisure Centre and special guest and ventriloquist Paul Zerdin is performing. When his sidekick Sam goes missing. Danny and Mick have to step up to perform their own ventriloquist act.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7994c29c48222559183f36600d7e659f</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Danny needs a cake for his parents? wedding, and fast! The band deliver a cake, but Mac?s size-shifting machine causes chaos, and they have an angry wedding organiser to contend with.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1cbb1d1ebd8080b7915706128afa381</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Bionic ends up dressed as a rabbit when Nitro pranks him at a fake photoshoot, and the rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes as they prank the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf7d7f9299d05e5c92784905daf4991d</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated deep sea adventure series. Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. When an underwater tremor separates the Gup-X and its crew, Barnacles seeks guidance from a mysterious sea turtle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f9f6d55e7dfb1bfbda6c8a0a55e82dd</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad and Cosima both think they're the best at pranking. Their prank war quickly spirals out of control, until Big Lizard finally reveals Proxima's real pranking champion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea0f60cf71247ea3d276941d6971e477</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>If being zapped with a mind-controlling Mindzooka ray by a couple of D-list villains wasn't bad enough, Danger Mouse's shame goes viral thanks to a series of embarrassing videos. Determined to stop the release of the most incriminating video of all, Danger Mouse turns to the villain behind the mind-control tech - the incarcerated Crumhorn! Crumhorn offers an anti-mind control device, but it comes with a catch - he has to be temporarily released back to Crumcorp Towers to retrieve it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p402f93b5d6cb5e8e2fc05b79645fff74</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes set out on a quest to find out who is draining colour from the forest and muster all their positivity to save it from greyness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3d4f995b8c3040f9e2b17fe57dfa29f</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When a parrot steals a fisherman?s lucky captain's hat, the Ninjas search for a replacement on a cruise ship, only for Konpeki and Aka to get distracted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e8f614bd723264869f90ef1bf1f4b24</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve dives with 100 grey nurse sharks - aka ragged-tooth sharks - a wobbegong and a gigantic whale shark, and he joins a mission in Indonesia to save sharks from over-fishing with eco-tourism.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdcc05d21452d9faf35f104aaea0c088f</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>In a bid to prove that girls are just as good at football as boys, Felicity and June disguise Clarissa. Meanwhile, Darrell and Susan help Mr Murray with his chamber investigation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd011de15557cf8f3fdef27c8afd96390</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. Shaun finds the farmer's old record player on the dump and organises a rave in the barn, but trouble looms when the naughty pigs gatecrash the party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d85e8a5e8a7604eacfba23dddab4e8d</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s time for Gnasher?s annual bath, but the stinky hound will do anything to avoid the tub. Dennis and Gnasher go head to head in a town-wide game of cat and mouse ? or rather, tripe hound and wheelie bathtub.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cd3695300ecc962061ac4a3338675c2</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The forest has run out of bath sponges and is becoming very stinky. Their latest order never arrived, and so the heroes must quest under the sea to Merhaven to collect them. However, Hoofius, whose singing stinks worse than his armpits, decides to enter the annual Merhaven Song Contest and accidentally causes a simple quest to collect bath sponges to turn into something much more perilous.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ed5d646aa33c0f016a4f842cc22d80c</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After breaking their games console, the kids decide to sell Boy's homemade cookies to raise money for a new one. All is well until they get some unexpected competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/ped62b0d7cfc54d8c982819332e593aa3</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Susie and Dog set aside their differences to partner up for a figure-skating competition. All is well until they realise that someone is sabotaging them and their chances of winning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42f9e79e93d36b6515c3a875959500de</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The jelly cake battle takes on epic dimensions into a 'heroic fantasy' world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7540cfc28a15de2ef3fc5c8015f20b14</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob invents a new persona.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p15a3e516d535e143ed23b99e8ae441e0</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>The others try to cheer Rory up after he is punished and sent to the office.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6853721e6e0a07518571c0a31c3f1c4d</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>With a spike in oddness in the UK, Department of Help agent Ozzie suggests they send for help from the best agent in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2daff7b5a508d12e0255a7449c918759</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Charlie uses Helsing?s time remote to bring a heavily muscled future version of himself back to the present to change his life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf77616ab1a39e80807a661849b4d161a</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>A walkie-talkie hidden inside a chili dog causes Harold to worry an alien has arrived.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd55181ac1b0277a6a03b77b9b2b7602a</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko, Roy and Dot jump into action when the Explorers stage an attack on Naranja Academy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe6a25376dd9d029398b4d31755dde01c</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>With Christmas around the corner, the juniors give a festive performance at the local town fair. Meanwhile, it's time for Encore's end-of-term performance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc3462f0723775ab4ee62e020a81d77a7</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Gwen is shocked into drastic action when her father refuses to sign her application to finishing school. Meanwhile, Darrell and Felicity fall out during the North Tower Spelling Bee.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d81b1dd5f4376b5dc9a2f540ed83af0</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio. James and Riley struggle with their duet. Michelle demands an answer from Eldon - why is he avoiding her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe139849510e43a951abbc6f52b345676</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings end up lost after misplacing their jar of Yummy in a labyrinth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6adf7709b4293ae1023ab4a70b88ad6</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
