<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>With Halloween approaching, the Year 7s have been told about the school ghost and set off to hunt for it. Meanwhile, the Anything Goes cast try not to get too spooked by the thought of opening night for their show, and Encore - the most senior dancers at the school - warm up for their next big show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb23418f094c47204647f6ce302d72560</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:50AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Cooking Buddies</title>
    <desc>Buddy and Conker are joined by Taye, a young street artist who wants to make a surprise birthday meal for his dad, who loves crispy chicken. Together, they make the crispiest, most delicious fried chicken, served up with homemade slaw, potato wedges and corn on the cob in what must be the best birthday present ever! In return for Buddy?s help, Taye shares some of his artistic skills and shows him how to create his very own bubble-writing signature. Join Buddy, Conker and Taye as they create a work of art both on paper and on a plate with a great homemade takeaway! You can get all of Buddy?s recipes, and loads more, at bbc.co.uk\/food.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p43577acb2448ba2aba73e7b0ad25f64f</image>
    <start>09:50AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>So Awkward</title>
    <desc>It?s Humanitarian Week and the pupils have to commit to acts of charity and kindness in order to receive Community Spirit Awards. Ollie and Martha get competitive, signing up to teach digital to the over-sixties. But winning an award is going to be harder than Martha and Ollie think: Martha's pupil Mazel knows absolutely nothing about tech, and Ollie?s ex-punk student Jonny is anti-technology. At the charity sumo wrestling bake-off event, Lily threatens to shred her teddy bear to force Jas to admit she is the secret shopper. When Jas overhears Lily discuss the teddy-shredding trap with Rob, Jas ups the ante by threatening to shred her teddy, too. Only at the very last moment do they admit the truth to one another, saving both the teddies and the friendship.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe9d933b30e2cce4caf107df9a58a482f</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Danny is convinced it's Joy?s birthday and ropes Mick and Naomi into his plan to create a surprise party. Mick?s in charge of decorations, Naomi?s in charge of the cake, Danny?s in charge of making sure Joy doesn?t suspect a thing. What can go wrong? Everything ? it?s Danny and Mick! Soon it?s time to spring the surprise ? will Joy be thrilled, annoyed or simply confused? Hint: It?s all three.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p647309c04520ff895b7fddfab73af85d</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Naomi has asked for a raise, Joy?s advised her to take some time off to think about it, which is why Danny and Mick are in charge of the cafe. They?ve just about got the hang of it when a new automated smoothie maker arrives. The machine is supposed to make life easier, but that?s not how Danny and Mick see it. Soon smoothies are flying, and everyone is left with egg on their face. And strawberry. And a bit of banana?.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b4c9cf8f021ccd65862af8d996b9857</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum is a Little Bro in control! He?s pitting his Big Bro Adam against best mate Joe to see who will win a series of funny, gungy and gross challenges and who will land an awful forfeit from the Wheel of Doom in this epic competition. Callum's the Little Bro, but he?s in control, so Adam and Joe had better impress him! When Joe and Adam press play on a mysterious voice note, they know it?ll be a long but extra 24 hours. Little Bro Callum is challenging them to let him control their day. With tasks like bathing in cold mud, snacking on edible insects and wearing their pants on their head, nothing's normal in this high-key contest to be the best. After Callum?s decided on a winner, it?s onto the next funny challenge: will they choose to save their crab friend or their stuff? And why is a giant shark distracting them?</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc79e0414b499bd676d87a6f418b89161</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Apollo with fake influencer Aubry Devonne Keep, causing a big splash! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes and pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82fea0673a28a4c34c10d3bc5eb06fcf</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve is in Uganda, getting up close and personal with some of our closest relatives - the primates. He meets gorillas in the mountains and squabbling baboons on the savannah. He even has a dawn encounter with chimps in the forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f238ce530b35ccf75af7c1517b672e2</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Could farts power a rocket? If you ask a question like that to Dr Chris and Dr Xand, you know they will want to investigate ? and if they can, they will blast off an actual rocket too! We welcome Gladiator Dynamite to Team Ouch! Her job is to referee Dr Dan and Dr Raph as they pit their bodies against each other in Dan vs Raph: Body Battles. Today, it?s a muscle they are testing: the triceps. Will it be Dr Dan or Dr Raph who ends up in the ice bath as a loser?s forfeit? One thing is for sure, Dynamite?s decision is final! Doctors Chris, Xand and Ronx are Ouch and About giving answers to kids? medical questions, with Margot asking why people have asthma. In Australia, the Flying Doctors fly Jack and his mum to hospital in New South Wales for a check-up following Jack's bone marrow transplant. Back in the emergency department in the UK, Logan has hurt his knee after tripping and landing on a log, and Harshali has a pink bead stuck up her nose! Ouch.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94a8d6fd6580fb7b64d941699a3b2c35</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories favourite Death, of 'Stupid Deaths' fame, presents his very own show crammed full of spooky highlights. We join him at home and get a good look around as he reveals his creepiest moments - a Tudor family show us the extent of their ghostly superstitions and the Vikings demonstrate how to become truly terrifying to your enemies. Death himself is joined by some rather creepy friends to sing about his favourite scary things.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcbeb89fe77c342b9d74dc4b9d4fb9085</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Dr Big Brain has an electrical short circuit, Marie Curie is wowed by a rocket man, some of the great women of science are celebrated, and 200 monks get electrocuted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p21daa97d981587de14f8ff3ad8bddf40</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>A new secret formula has disastrous results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7138f69a1361ba835321ad9eea6b2a23</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Mr Krabs and Plankton take boating school classes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0e38c6a2d56e911ee73f2a02f3740747</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Mr Krabs gets in trouble for littering.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd5889480b90deea1f79d64a220c51d2</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Helsing tasks the gang with finding a magical genie lamp, thinking that they won't give it a polish. Now, Charlie is famous, Pierce is a CEO and Que has legs.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p91ee48925752b847214b40962f3ce830</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>The gang find Helsing's monster phone book and prank call Frank, the world?s scariest monster. The gang must prepare the house when a furious Frank seeks his revenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdf82a4655b1e582d10ff2733ea238236</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse wants the other kids to stop being lazy and achieve some goals - in the form of breaking world records. With Mouse's relentless coaching, the family soon gets carried away. Can Mouse get things back to normal before anyone gets hurt.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p952612adea8a4c9c25efe350e0b666cf</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:40PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When one of Mouse?s inventions accidentally sticks Cat?s discarded fur to Boy?s face, his new 'beard' suddenly makes him the most popular kid in school! Seeing her chance to stop her enemy Lila Bird from becoming class president, Girl convinces Boy to run for president too. It looks like Boy might win, until another accident causes Cat?s whole body to get stuck to his face. Can he win the election with such a strange new beard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p914a4dbe62695432e7ae7da249569069</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The Girls and the Boys compete to get to the top of Bear Mountain, using very different styles of camping. But when the legendary bear appears, they have to team up to survive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb67492964d5542c23a8c00dc0f1fb470</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When Courtney refuses to share her valuable rare toy, friends join forces to question her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e518a8dee62348a4c879f5a681603a2</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Leshawna creates a paint-balloon fight to decide who she will take to an amusement park.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd7c0c7f590fb463746b3ee96bdc467cb</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen struggles with the idea that he is about to lose his BFF Noah to a gifted military school.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9071f37e1942b65e7987bb64753f9acb</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy decides to adopt a coconut.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa46da99ab8403e36a8d474b0b8fb95b6</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy pretends to have a twisted ankle so that the Lemmings have to take care of him.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe6b0094f479dde28e14b93fc8b4a9ca9</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings set up a mini-fair, but Grizzy steals the Lemmings' tickets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p37fc83ff5409cc94ecc3a582cef047e2</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>With the dragon riders disbanded, Eugene attempts to start his own dragon club.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8492884e34bc23e0558ef5df55b30fd2</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Maisie is determined to win a place at a fashion school, but it won?t be easy. At the DG, Shanice has a bad hair day, and Vinny is struggling with his homework.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p332b04217c6c69ac4e9b881e356fc9f6</image>
    <start>04:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>The Founders? Day dance takes Juniper back to 1944. Addie feels on top of the world, but a well-meaning mistake threatens to undo all her good work.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p59f40b6cf0832b72deb80aefbf44ceaf</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>There is a buzz around the school as the Anything Goes cast list is finally revealed. Will Lucas get the part of Moonface, a role usually reserved for the older years? Best friends Uma and Anna are both hoping for the lead, but will they be happy with their parts? Meanwhile, singer Max has been busy writing new songs over the summer, and his dreams of life as a pop star are ever closer as he releases new music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p30e66f289f8ed538419999a240859642</image>
    <start>05:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Best mates Riley and Maddie battle a boys' team, and pals Masai and Ernest swap the pitch for the kitchen. Michael Dawson is in Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb9ec97d8e3e1263bc1a76cc84cda911b</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:10PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>Release the hounds! Campers are hunted by a pack of fearsome attack dogs... and one pug.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6b6bb0170f1530fcddc459da67e91a0a</image>
    <start>06:10PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Plankton poses as a wish-granting genie.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe0475aead4a39a8890da63d1ec55b26f</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:45PM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Heat-loving hippies move into Mr Krabs' soup vat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69a33c4df7c05a5a8d1f49d00087621d</image>
    <start>06:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>27 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Another adventure with the mischievous young sheep and his flock. The Farmer decides to get a robotic sheepdog, but it turns out to be even stricter than Bitzer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9e15148a77af1005bd9f4c43f27cbc8a</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold receive a crash course in the customs of America's oldest holiday when they cover for Jeopardy Mouse as she takes time off for Thanksgiving. After barely escaping from the war zone of a Black Friday sale, they find themselves back at Jeopardy's apartment. DM prepares to tuck into the plentiful Thanksgiving spread when Hissteria and Ham Hands rise out of the dishes. They announce their newly formed coalition and joint plans to vanquish America. DM sticks to his stand-in duties and refuses Jeopardy's help as he and Penfold follow Hissteria and Ham Hands' trail. They find the villainous pair hijacking the Thanksgiving Day parade - launching a gas attack from the air that will turn everything in sight to stuffing. With holiday-saving solutions at a premium, Penfold convinces a reluctant DM to call Jeopardy for help. Jeopardy assures DM that doing things with friends is what Thanksgiving is all about as they set about taking Ham Hands and Hissteria down. They distract them long enough to cut them loose along with the rest of the gas-filled balloons.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5362698311ba343ffe4571fba7fb7bc3</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes set out on a quest to find out who is draining colour from the forest and muster all their positivity to save it from greyness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3d4f995b8c3040f9e2b17fe57dfa29f</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Much to the kids' horror, Gramps starts spending a lot of time with mean Miss Molly! The gang do whatever it takes to keep the two apart.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc164d1eb50b7b3d1b3041fdb1b4540e9</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf67d0f376e0516e66eac525e23095592</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings find magic books that make their story content appear in real life when opened.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p01c270a57a4691a1423701fd684d5433</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a card that enables them to teleport a magic closet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa08b154dad94ed665954fc65a2a2e098</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Sandy invites Karen and Mrs Puff out for a night on the town.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p981dbd008d7b392bb732da721fc82486</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Pumpkins mysteriously disappear one after another, leaving nothing but a trail of slime.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6abffca1412150e0b8a491be688483e</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>The others try to cheer Rory up after he is punished and sent to the office.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6853721e6e0a07518571c0a31c3f1c4d</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Charlie uses Helsing?s time remote to bring a heavily muscled future version of himself back to the present to change his life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf77616ab1a39e80807a661849b4d161a</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Winx Club - The Magic Is Back</title>
    <desc>Following a scary encounter with a magic creature on her 16th birthday, Bloom discovers that she has magical powers. She is rescued by two fairies from Alfea School for Fairies and Witches.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa392635580aa64d93ddb96931017eac9</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug and Cat Noir face Stormy Weather - aka Aurore Bor?ale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p46e354ffdf97b682b4acb0e2971f158e</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:45AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Marinette?s class is headed to New York, the city of superheroes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5d5e0f2bc8193376ae4309e49cdce04</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:45AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>A prehistoric sponge is unfrozen and causes chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0dc730653145e151cb5ab24672b98545</image>
    <start>10:45AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>A flock of clams descend on Bikini Bottom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdfca11fd35d063c2f9ff48721d046a1e</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:15AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced madcap, stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The potato racers are driving each other round the bend, the DIY doughnuts attempt to fix the bathroom, the cavemen mushrooms come face to face with some big, hairy mammoth pots, fearless Pete Parsnip takes on a ferocious foe, and Slippery Nana takes on a pizza-cutting unicycle in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc75a0813855bf2fc00f9eb5e7b778651</image>
    <start>11:15AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall tracks cheetahs across Zambia by motorbike, witnessing epic hunting and the challenges faced by this endangered predator.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fceb6dcae8bced48912e9f9f2bd0e93</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:50AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>It's the start of a new school year, and the school is buzzing as boarders find out who they are sharing a dorm with and day pupils reunite at the lockers. No time is wasted on day one as the students go head-to-head for roles in the new show: Anything Goes. And this year could be life-changing for dancer Jakob as he starts his preparations for one of the world?s most prestigious international ballet competitions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe43e8702039ee3f0a37066f6e5bc0013</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Meet the Tottenham Hotspur academy players. Lia Lewis picks her Three of the Best, and Dominic Solanke takes on 11-year-old Konan in Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p88eec7f914b4c5e2f11d416e2a1eaf76</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Jamie Johnson FC</title>
    <desc>Christina fights for the right to play football again, while rivals Hawx United and Foxborough start sharing an academy - what could possibly go wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf6194e5e50af06f0d92f759b4a5bff78</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Gwen is shocked into drastic action when her father refuses to sign her application to finishing school. Meanwhile, Darrell and Felicity fall out during the North Tower Spelling Bee.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4a52cdf5ec5bb3d79b323bd471e8f1fe</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>From taking man to the moon to figuring out how to get rid of a poo in a submarine, Mark Labbett joins Rattus for a look at some of history?s most brilliant brainboxes.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6ef2832f3f770d4773416091121d176b</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall is in Brazil searching for the world?s most elusive cat: the jaguar. He sees them swimming, meets mothers and cubs, and even witnesses one jaguar hunting a caiman.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12fe4d899fb5e401c27fe914c8c9d9be</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Gwen is delighted when Ron suggests they go for a walk together, but it quickly derails when Gwen is left to babysit. Meanwhile, Felicity discovers her love for running.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7d3c9e562e9dea488214233094681b9b</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy discovers a special lamp that can compact organic elements.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2a53737e98d0f3674c4501f7700dd884</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Set on a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. Shaun finds a camera which some ramblers have dropped and sets about taking snapshots of the flock. Bitzer is soon on the trail of the missing camera.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbfdf487e61bc85086eaec74349686a06</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>With Paul on vacation, Pieface falls under the influence of a fiery chilli pepper and unexpectedly turns rogue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6a5852bb24bcb8b318f0993738dc0f68</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Dog finds out he has fleas! But when he befriends them, he must hide them from his family to prevent them from getting zapped.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p06176b1ed385e0a4f53417001f70afba</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>To celebrate Christmas, Mum and Dad suggest that the siblings make each other gifts.?When Dog is assigned to give a gift to Cheese, she sneaks to find out what the gift is.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p281f32aaafd23ca825b0cb1dffad639a</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover a card that enables them to teleport a magic closet.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa08b154dad94ed665954fc65a2a2e098</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>The long-lost episode of Mermaid Man is finally showing on TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbf9a7e2afdc7aa6d3136c4226bae6879</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Debra-Jo is taken to the lost and found box after losing her glasses.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p784dfde268da77c3868768f3c0bdfddb</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When Ozzie catches bad-luck-itis, Orli and Osgood must go on a magical quest to find the ingredients for the antidote before his increasing bad luck blows apart HQ.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5b2efcc04a1283fa7cbc827922fc7c8c</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Charlie takes a three-headed monster dog to school for pet day, but his unwillingness to enforce the rules sees it grow bigger and more dangerous.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3687765f0e813b952b6bc8df96e4492a</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Owen and Beth decide they must defend the ants that Courtney and Leshawna want to harm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p31b289722eba2b0fc5112c5ea20ab77f</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Life is back to normal for Roy and friends, until wild Pok?mon begin to act strangely..</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p05aca3c75a07c7eb775df1c9398ee116</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>Elliot faces a tough tap audition, the cast list is out for the underwater show, and Kanon heads back to the Dumping Ground set for more filming.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5e49ee8290b5d4eb1336fdfa1ab27486</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Gwen plots for movie star and Miss Grayling?s estranged cousin Lily Vernon to visit the school. Lily has her own secrets. Meanwhile, Nancy plans a prank to stop eating carrots.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p06cec2ea3d8a72058211819558c62bcc</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio. Michelle holds a scholarship fundraiser for young dancers, while the elite competition gets a step up. Amanda misses a band practice and feels bad about lying to her new friends. West and Giselle get caught up in a talent war.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p901b8dc25e90cc01ffaa0f518f9cdcf4</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings are victims of inexplicable thefts.[(96057)] </desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9da5aa1da675153d73ce99c93b198990</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>28 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
