<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>When Seattle Mr O accidentally turns himself into a creature, the Mobile Unit is called in to help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc6d44b0a576d9c48ce8cb33817fc1005</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Law and order has a new face as the gang investigate who is responsible for a series of mysterious slimings in the neighbourhood - they are gonna crack this case wide open.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc58aa39feb97377485fec7559bdc35aa</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:45AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Salesman Mr Smallman wants to sell his new robot Bot-Bot to the leisure centre to make their lives easier. He leaves it for a day so they can trial it, but Danny breaks it within minutes. However, he has a bright idea and convinces Mick to become Bot-Bot and fool Sharon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p53ec60c247653a0fd3c29e0d1eefe5e7</image>
    <start>08:45AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about sharing by halving, sharing equally and grouping equally.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pae85e2f5830747efc2ccec7d4120ff0a</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Get ready for incredible experiments and mind-bending puzzles to impress your friends. Owain and Tilly are here to explore epic science tricks to try at home and showcase new technology innovations from around the world! In this episode, we discover the bubbly science behind burping, meet the robot taking the art world by storm, find out how a playing card can defy gravity and learn how to juggle using a hairdryer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbcbd3d57fb2db017a366707f3621458b</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>It?s a new term for everyone at Our School. There is an exciting ?human sat-nav? challenge for year 7, plus a quiz on how much all the students know about their teachers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p074e397600c0f87671b0bf1f1cfeca90</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:55AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs make a bug jungle, Chris Howarth makes sand art waves, and Rob Biddulph shows how to draw a furry monster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p37672a63f7ec87e89f34fc36ae95bc34</image>
    <start>09:55AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The One Zoo Three brothers are on a mission to compose a zoo musical using the sounds of the animals. Lar gibbons Shany and Raff swing into action and audition to be the perfect percussionists, while a health check with Bombura the loud kookaburra sees him in with a shout for lead vocals. Even playful jaguar cub Inka proves she can add a cracking big crunch to the mix! Meanwhile, Aaron reveals some facts about Darwin the hornbill?s hidden talents, Tyler takes on a breathtaking challenge with an anaconda, and the brothers recall their conservation travels to Uganda to see how rangers are helping protect the African elephant population.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf2b66fd8b8419d8db89805dc886542a2</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Community on Solid Ground is a youth centre in Whalley Range. Before they took over the building the area didn't offer much for the youngsters living there and antisocial behaviour was very common. That has dropped by 73 per cent since Community on Solid Ground came along, the kids can hang out, play sports and have a place to go that means they aren't hanging around the streets. Sadly the facilities are very tired, and they don't have areas they can play their beloved sport on. The Dengineers are going to transform their outside space into a sports arena worthy of the Olympics... well, nearly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2332b63ee2ff35164e4f2cb6797427ce</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius with Dick and Dom</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom reveal the genius of Archimedes, the ancient Greek mathematician and expert engineer. Inspired by Archimedes, they come up with their own genius idea when they bring one his most brilliant inventions to life, with some explosive results.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p68e55d515695718d5246be6f98988b5e</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors put the strength of human hair to the test and find out what makes different colours and types of hair.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p77a1f4ca12613eb52f1ea3a8ed1f630f</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall meets a superspeedy shark. Reaching speeds of 50kph, the mako is the fastest shark in the sea. With fast-swimming prey like tuna and mackerel, mako sharks need to move quickly. But how do they reach such meteoric speeds? Steve first snorkels with these lightning-quick sharks off the coast of San Diego in California, before getting under their skin in his shark lab to reveal their hidden speed secrets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1deea9923ad5b042ba1a7eef9bd746d</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Danny and Mick?s boss, Joy, has had her office redecorated and has asked the brothers to put everything back in her office. As always, Danny and Mick get distracted and don?t get the job done. Joy finds them messing about which causes Danny to accidentally spill a smoothie on her new wallpaper. Joy is unaware, so Danny and Mick need to secretly sort out the problem before she finds out! Danny and Mick don?t do anything easily and ending up in a lot of mess with a lot of wallpaper paste.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pffaebcd7a3adfde8a605c149a75d8c53</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>After Moxy?s drums go missing, Andy concludes it was their rival band, Sandy and the Same Socks! Getting paranoid, a chase ensues as Andy accuses them of stealing everything.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb25b473cf84269836f676090139fbcec</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum is a Little Bro in control! He?s made a series of funny, gungy and gross challenges for his Big Bro Adam and best mate Joe to see who?s the best and who loses, having to take on a forfeit from the Wheel of Doom. When a slime baby shows up at their front door, Adam and Joe suddenly take on daddy duties. But how do you comfort a slime baby, teach it to speak or take it for a walk without spilling the slime? And once that?s over, Callum challenges them to become life-sized toys and hunt around their house for epic accessories. Who?ll race back to their toy box first, Adam or Joe? These daddy-os are about to find out in this head-to-head epic battle to determine who?s the CEO and who?s taking a spin on the Wheel of Doom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf309fbf017e2b95f5612f22d43948e02</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts: Above &amp; Beyond</title>
    <desc>A lyrebird confounds the Octonauts with its ability to mimic any sound it hears.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd9ec98781dde513afc9be5dba18a3d7d</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>A triple solar eclipse is about to happen! Cosima and Big Lizard race down the volcano and hitch a lift on a dragonfly so that they can get vital equipment to Dad in the nick of time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3620d0f17b180290a41ba17a09aedaf8</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse must fight his own urge to be awesome to stop the world turning into a gigantic intergalactic tourist attraction. Attempting to prove his theory that what the world always needs is a hero, Danger Mouse fights off what appears to be an alien invasion of Earth - but his inflated ego soon becomes the real intergalactic threat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d43d2ca6490ff7c844b2a28644f5408</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. When the Baron rearranges the countries of the world, Danger Mouse reluctantly joins forces with his American counterpart Jeopardy Mouse and takes New Zealand for a spin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p360a767bfafedebd93220d5ac0d52736</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The after-school art club is under threat of imminent demolition. In trying to save the club, the gang end up on the trail of the mysterious undercover urban artist known only as Pranksy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p361a97fdcd2b35beabb23cae8c4b65d6</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Convinced that Mrs Creecher is secretly a master of Blamjitsu, JJ persuades the gang to help trick her into revealing her blam credentials.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p631f5a239e4e0ec4323d1cb7272bc565</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>To avoid Herbert?s surprise visits via his tunnels in the Big Birch, the other heroes take any quest and must deal with an angry plant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1712e7d54bc565d7f40c59dd3788f999</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When tasked with the simple quest of building a flat-packed wardrobe, the heroes fail to read the instructions and are whirled into a wonky world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb7deb542b557edde37b8d10af30afbd6</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>So Awkward Academy</title>
    <desc>Can underdog Cranmede take on the mighty reigning champions Gorsforth at the Interschool Country Dance Championships? And can Tam overcome her dance demons in time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1485a447b6247106aa11cbbdb4498d5d</image>
    <start>02:15PM</start>
    <finish>02:45PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Game on Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Guided by pro-gamer Slogo, the teams serve up an epic game of Switch Sports Tennis. Who will ace it and bag a place in the finals.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf20e40909fa38f94a3e9a1c2e51fb269</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Tom and the Riders try to save Icaris when it is revealed to be in danger from a monstrous dragon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f90cf43a2d0b19473e8eebdbd47c29d</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When poor Gnasher is laid up wearing the 'collar of shame', Dennis takes Rasher to school instead, disguised as an exchange student. Walter takes a shine to this new girl and, totally embarrassed to find that the object of his affections is Rasher the pig, plots his revenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p83bacc981bca1b92db0933dc6138164c</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A school girl orders a wish-granting vase so she doesn't have to go to school, but the Ninjas must face a series of tests set by the vase's guardian in order to get it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6b01e1206010854040758ec2d81ae7d</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When the heroes quest to stop Balthazar from turning forest folk into household objects, Herbert realises that he can defeat the wizard?s spell by using the magic tricks he has practiced. Blossom is particularly intrigued by Herbert the Peculiar?s tricks, not to mention his stage name, so when Herbert himself is transformed into a table lamp, it?s Blossom the Very Impressive to the rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p02b5755668bd5974ec3f672d77162daf</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. It is a peaceful night at the farm, until Shaun starts to walk in his sleep and the flock cannot resist their natural instinct to follow.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p012e6a9e43043401ef147d944e67d24a</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy snares a swordfish, but the Lemmings lure it out to sea. The cabin starts to slide.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0968970dcc0d4cd006f82ccdcaade21d</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Cheese is disappointed by the role she was cast in for her favourite soap opera, she takes matters into her own hands to get a bigger role.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p77202f615499606034c7279b65f4a4b7</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Heat-loving hippies move into Mr Krabs' soup vat.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p69a33c4df7c05a5a8d1f49d00087621d</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit faces a series of odd challenges that only Orla knows how to stop.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p60e9d42389818974756ac19dc607b6e7</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>The Mobile Unit must teach the agents in the Odd Squad Arctic office how to solve a case for themselves.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65046a9a28d0a2c87f916d20fe70a281</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Learn how the heroes became Ladybug and Cat Noir.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p13756d1dd4ab40bb9be92476adfabee1</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Winx Club - The Magic Is Back</title>
    <desc>Following a scary encounter with a magic creature on her 16th birthday, Bloom discovers that she has magical powers. She is rescued by two fairies from Alfea School for Fairies and Witches.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa392635580aa64d93ddb96931017eac9</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall tracks cheetahs across Zambia by motorbike, witnessing epic hunting and the challenges faced by this endangered predator.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3fceb6dcae8bced48912e9f9f2bd0e93</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Michelle learns the truth about Chloe's financial situation. The dancers compete for the solo spot in the regionals routine.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e60930dc8faa32cbbf2b58fcc616d88</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall meets the most sinister shark in our seas. The ragged tooth shark has a mouth that's overflowing with terrifying teeth. But why does it need such gnarly gnashers? Steve heads out on a dive after dark to see these fearsome fangs for himself, before revealing their sinister secret in his shark lab.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ff2226cfdb7e138bed614be556ea724</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
