<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>With his crew in tow, Steve is on a mission to find all the animals that most Africans spend as much time as possible avoiding. Steve braves the big waves of the Durban coast to get up close and personal with a pack of 30 hungry blacktip sharks, getting a bit too close for comfort. After swimming in shark-infested waters, Steve abseils down to a nest of killer bees with a painful outcome. An eerily close encounter with a ragged tooth shark is followed by getting airborne with the awesome black eagle. Unlike Rourke the eagle, Steve comes down to earth with a bump.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pda3c1522e19d8e3abc2e54e24992b3e6</image>
    <start>11:50AM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Dr Xand has broken the rules and snuck a marble run into the lab, but will Dr Chris notice in today?s blood pressure experiment?! And there is a life-saving mission in Australia.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p760226d4653c0c40cc883fde88dc707b</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Emperor Nero visits the victims of the Great Fire of Rome, some Crusaders attend a training course on how to fight weird monsters, and we meet the man with the best (and worst) job in Tudor England.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0197e8fa0ee5cafa8d9f1673e7483f40</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Fred Sirieix stars in Scientific First Dates, Marie Curie reacts to space, and the dinosaurs get an unwelcome musical meteor visitor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd2a33358dcb8b4090c89b64ab78a468a</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Diamond when the guest on a live TV show can?t stop pumping! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes, pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p124aa384cfc9de9b57a6c0777805b147</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>In the distant future, the social outcast Derek Mullard watches a video of the world being destroyed by history's biggest villain - Danger Mouse! To make matters worse, Danger Mouse is Derek's ancient ancestor and the reason he's forbidden from marrying his beautiful paramour, Pennyfold. Meanwhile, in the present day, Danger Mouse is in the midst of foiling Quark's latest plot, which involves auctioning off the nice bits of the world and compact crushing the rest. A time-travelling Derek arrives on the scene to confront Danger Mouse and prevent the world's destruction, correcting the course of history in the process.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p65fea07e21b46cf4819aacca1edb7291</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>After reports of unexplained unruliness at the UN, Danger Mouse and Penfold arrive to scenes of quarrelling diplomats, whose messages of peace and goodwill have been turned into playground insults by the sabotaged translation system. Danger Mouse spots the culprit, Crumhorn, lurking in the shadows and goes after him but is stopped in his tracks by Ian, for whom the UN's security is apparently no match.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p991bca59a6726dbedd59a764f5d09fdc</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>On seeing his adopted goldfish get busted for stealing top-secret documents, Penfold bewails the fact he has never had a pet of his own to love and cherish. He gets his wish when Danger Mouse and Squawk discover the Baron's plans to brainwash the world's pets into becoming his personal army of slaves, and they hand him the responsibility of babysitting the Baron's own pet Nero, having craftily swapped him with a robotic impersonator as a means of getting to the Baron's mind control device - the Pet Whistle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pda092f5371bdaf387f43f04cace63c4b</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis is desperate to prevent Pieface from failing Mrs Creecher's maths test. He persuades the gang to use Professor Von Screwtop's mind-swapping device. But in a disastrous turn of events, Screwtop is on the loose with the brain of Paul the potato and Pieface is left with a potato with the brain of Screwtop to help get him through the test.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc07a4c98f6086963197d9b148493fe6a</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:45PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>When the gang go on an adventure in search of the Beanotown Yeti, Walter follows with plans of his own for the rare beast, and Dennis and his chums must come to its rescue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf5af966c8ed18cc139dfae028f192e9d</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>After Dennis persuades Pieface that Paul is an undercover superhero, Gnasher, JJ and Rubi go along with the story and help Dennis to 'prove' it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc8c9fa7b93940d75583a1afdfc0dfe3b</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Blossom draws the short cheese straw and, rather than join her friends on a picnic, she has to take a magic wand to the recycling centre. Faced with a long queue and a rumbly tummy, Blossom decides that life is too short for recycling - with disastrous consequences. The heroes must skip their picnic and go on a quest to save the forest from the magical mess Blossom has gotten them into.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p38db6a019d90d683a5c507a27c6477df</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>It?s been ages since their last quest, and the heroes are losing their edge, so Mr Friendlyface invents a strange and terrible monster that he says is stomping through the forest causing havoc, and sends the heroes on a fake quest to get rid of it. Friendlyface soon comes to regret his trickery when, with the heroes out of the way, the goblins decide to take over the forest for their jam jamboree.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdd73f5a342e51bd6aa4e1226b5b388fb</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>During their quest to stop Balthazar the Fabulous from sucking every last sunbeam out of the sky, the heroes realise there is something wrong with Hoofius, who keeps tripping up and has totally lost his confidence. Herbert explains that Hoofius has lost his mojo! To help their friend and complete the quest, the heroes take Hoofius up Mojo Mountain to help him get his mojo back.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p35139f8d551193defc2163be2972f380</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings get a magical Mayan disc that transforms them into mutants.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc3746559cf8b3e9331661a0997ea62a8</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight for the last jar of Yummy with magic Mayan bracelets.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3350d31a4a867d7f6c51ff44d720bdd</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>While playing in Mayan Temple, the Lemmings set off a cosmic phenomenon.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pca3bcced1a9c602c5d934b4cffd1db83</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy decides to teach the Lemmings how to behave in his presence.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p913be4806ad3e2c1689fd5eb48cd770b</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced, madcap stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The potato racers are crashing around the kitchen, the cavemen mushrooms' plan is foiled, and Stunt Tomato attempts an exciting escapology trick. Dr Rhu-barb is under attack from his arch-enemy, who is trying to 'extermi-grate' him, and a piece of toast impresses the judges with fire-juggling tricks at the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p79e2649337afce7930ccc80cfcccd42c</image>
    <start>04:15PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Phil threatens to shut down D?Angelo?s new dragon hospital and ban dragons from Icaris.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p197fcf1e4105851d58d47e7897bb38ad</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Jimi is shocked when he bumps into his brother and is forced to make an important decision about his future at the DG. The gang think Ben is sick, very sick, and not in a good way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8d6ca1b3f021d30e25f26f23cb7bfdc9</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Audrey organises a Shark Day for Addie as a way to break her big news. However, Jenna?s crush, Emily?s guilt and a break-in at the shop threaten to derail Audrey?s plans.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p343b3df99928fbf1761c1148b1bb2a74</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. In order to heal Eldon's broken spirit, Emily agrees to go on a date with him. Riley overhears Emily talking about kicking Michelle out of the studio and decides to take action.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf5ac76b851c65e2aab439c9120df0dca</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. Eldon struggles to choose between Emily and Michelle as his partner for his duet performance. Meanwhile, West and Stephanie are at odds on how to proceed with their duet, leaving West wanting to quit altogether.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p04808ce7876b8c91c18ff4bcda0224b8</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:20PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Who will race to the finish line first in a tough head-to-head race on adaptive mountain bikes?! Will it be Abby or Joel?</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p682a8c1a318bd7d4ff702f3c22499c0f</image>
    <start>06:20PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Science goes too far in Fartenheimer, music goes too far in Heads, Shoulders, Knees, Toes and All the other Bones in the Body, and there's a Swiftian take on the water cycle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa83dcfd68984c53c5bff2b5550e247f5</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation featuring the adventures of Shaun the Sheep. Bitzer falls in love with a dog from the local camp site.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p01b4dd61a314181bb6798b7be0707500</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse goes undercover as the fifth member of Quark's mega-popular boy band, discovering his inner performer and a musical plot to destroy the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p77a97761345f53edbf51556bc28c35eb</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Rubi gets a place in a Summer School for Super Smart Kids, which turns out to be one of Walter's tricks so he can learn the secrets of her new invention.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p87c783d97968f1517f2ea593080b21bd</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>In this second part of the flashback story of Mum and Dad?s wedding, the kids realize how unhappy they were apart, but they can't see how to fix things. Then a bird-based emergency sees both groups of kids leap into action to work together and save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4e535fd2fee7b3b090c7ca871cc213c7</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc181cd80735ffb3a2df17f8becbb137e</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a crab that can open coconuts with a snip of its claw.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd852285adcf3efc4195388236c228122</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A helicopter takes off from the beach, leaving behind installations for a TV game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4170a715769540ec9092bd83b32da0fd</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob and Patrick help Bubble Bass move.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5f960595dc2e224cb0527ef746e5aead</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Globetrotting villain Stu Venir is turning monuments into keychains! Agents must uncover a pattern to predict where he will strike next.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd5a8c8e6bcfcf82a3d99f9f5878d0704</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall is in Brazil searching for the world?s most elusive cat: the jaguar. He sees them swimming, meets mothers and cubs, and even witnesses one jaguar hunting a caiman.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p12fe4d899fb5e401c27fe914c8c9d9be</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Learn about counting in halves and quarters, and doubling and halving numbers.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa05c54ca475359c69660ad480e837b8a</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Owain and Tilly find out how to make super-weird goo, discover a quick fix for a bad case of bed hair, try a puzzling way to fool thirsty friends, and explore future space travel.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96a8262135d5f3523e561167bc4f873b</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>It?s Bonfire Night and Year 7 Ta?Kya wants to overcome her fear of fireworks. Can a science lesson help? And the school launches a club to give students their first taste of cricket.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p694388911899efc3cbc3606b19cabde4</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ricky Wilson's Art Jam</title>
    <desc>Sports presenter, travel documentary maker and former Paralympian Ade Adepitan visits the Art Jam studio to show Ricky three items that mean the world to him - his precious London 2012 medal moulds, a special family photo from the day they left Nigeria for the UK and a one-of-a-kind brightly coloured hoody. While chatting to Ricky, Ade shares amazing stories about his childhood, falling in love with basketball, winning medals as a Paralympian and his passion for travelling the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pcdfdc7caea8e8e3d59c5fcc1a93f2620</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The One Zoo Three brothers create a winter wonderland at the zoo, with special festive treats for the Amur tigers. Meanwhile, Tim and Tam the Tapirs tuck into a winter vegetable challenge.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7b7e2a7c1562f1cef670346c4cc7689d</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Ocean, nine, from Brentwood has had a tough time. His younger brother Sky died two years ago and he needs a place to escape to when things get too much for him. He also has a new baby sister which he's excited about but his house has become pretty noisy! Ocean loves marble runs because they're like rollercoasters and one day he'd like to be a rollercoaster designer. He wants a marble run den where he can get away from it all and work towards his dream.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1cdcdc5b3d5a535b8636ae230cca3c3d</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius with Dick and Dom</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom reveal the genius of Charles Darwin and explore the theory of evolution. Inspired by Darwin's genius ideas, they come up with their own genius idea when they take the plunge and go face to face with one of the most perfectly evolved predators on the planet - a terrifying shark.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p83632f555b5c18907018d9e31353de27</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>Identical twins Dr Chris and Dr Xand van Tulleken experiment and explore their way through the fascinating world of medicine and biology. Chris and Xand will let the viewer in to their exclusive world of medicine and explain the awesome things our bodies can do. The doctors experiment on their muscles to show how they work. Dr Chris meets some wriggly maggots that are helping to heal a sore foot, and Dr Xand goes on call with an emergency ambulance team. Meanwhile, over in accident and emergency, one patient has some grit in his head after a fall in the playground and another has injured his neck after performing a karate kick.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p740d99449bb67f0c5621ccc607d407c8</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>Joy has a Valentine?s Day date and has ordered the boys to turn the caf? into a romantic restaurant. Just as they are finishing up Clive arrives - he also has a date and wants some top tips. Danny and Mick are happy to help until they find out Clive?s date is with Joy! It?s bad enough having her as a boss, the boys don?t want to start calling her mummy too! Can they break the happy couple up before the date is over.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdafa4a9e989df2d40776349470f2c257</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Andy?s sister Ruby wants to meet her hero, superstar vlogger Fay Moss, so Andy and the Band risk missing their next gig by racing off to help out. Staging a fake fashion photoshoot by posing as flashy designers, they attempt to bag some time with Fay by distracting her security guard! Cousin Mac?s new auto-tuner invention is put to good use, but after an epic diva tantrum, will Fay live up to all of Ruby expectations.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fd9ca307fd295ae771597804d126e27</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Celebs Viggo Venn and Phil Green come to the aid of Adam and Joe as they try to prove to Callum who is the most talented. With impressions and dad dancing, what?s not to like.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p957c5bfbca86c719e8a1a2eb81ec77ee</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:50PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated deep sea adventure series. Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. When a sardine swallows the key to a treasure chest, a humpback whale helps Kwazii track it down.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe3eaf03545ac852155a351f47d0f3797</image>
    <start>12:50PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Big Lizard wants to have a go with Dad's new drone, but first he has to prove that he can go a whole day without breaking something precious. Good luck, Big Lizard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p850b309749660e2b38b39d00c45b2933</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Danger Mouse must battle Quark again, but this time in the weirdest and most dangerous of places: Penfold's dreams.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pef370659f818656714ea292bc7ca5e2e</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:20PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. The Baron steals DM's confidence and gives it to his shy daughter, Delilah Von Greenback, creating a dangerous criminal mastermind.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5df627a084f7c486593e10df1725c85c</image>
    <start>01:20PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis leads the gang on the baffling trail of a mysterious Beanotown secret society.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbe40fbbd57946697982b8c481f8009a4</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Walter and Dennis go head to head in a sponsored silence. Being quiet doesn?t come naturally to either of them, as they struggle to make it through a chaotic school day and keep schtumm.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f774701f77fb51f6357283a8b30f9ef</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The blossom has gone missing. No, not Blossom the unicorn, the blossom on the trees! The heroes are sent on a quest deep into the heart of the forest, where legend has it you can see a face watching you from the trees. Twinkle doesn?t believe in legends, but when help comes from nowhere as they try and stop the scoundrel that is stealing the blossom, she is forced to reconsider.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2f8d2357ef662dfdfa8453de1222ecd1</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes are relieved that the loud, threatening voice they can hear actually belongs to a small slug named Zorgoth, who is armed with a megaphone. However, when Zorgoth uses his Orb of Compression to shrink the heroes down to the size of ants, their relief evaporates. They must now embark on a long and dangerous quest, through their picnic items and beyond, to warn the Council before Zorgoth shrinks the entire forest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe50df153eaba594e89a65c54ae953f0c</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:25PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>High Hoops</title>
    <desc>The chance of a trophy has Aoife focused on a win. However, Charlotte is distracted, and Aoife has to ?mute the cute? if Charlotte is going to get back on her game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p94f9fd034f66efa4b9eb4790a62d3096</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>02:50PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Addie?s fundraising campaign disrupts a beloved village event, and Maggie?s attempts to get help end in disaster.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p27e109732967cd8e2202bc1b959e71ff</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:15PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>Dennis and the gang train Bertie in the art of standing up to people so he can rebel against Walter's bossiness - but they train him too well and he becomes a dangerous rebel without a clue.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ee81567708d80e99b9f35e4a420add2</image>
    <start>03:15PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Much to Trevor?s irritation, a rare phoenix woodpecker takes a liking to him - so he demands an immediate quest to return the bird to its real home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfd460f05ee8f6efe98ada93b746aa74d</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>When Girl gets the chance to put together the school fair, her friends and family jump at the chance to help - until she gets advice from a hardened businesswoman.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4cd9a8aad5a8972f434d9ccaeb212454</image>
    <start>03:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A Lemming finds a mysterious mask that endows him with the power of telekinesis.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peecc469e064293cb3826d2ecd69c6307</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy chases after the Lemmings and the jar of Yummy in their remote-controlled car.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p92aff3c434c1be5d19dc5f8fd5c7244c</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob doesn't need a licence to operate a self-driving car.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9c4826b562f0a562124128ccc6c32e52</image>
    <start>04:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Tamara sprains her ankle and can?t do the beep test, so she decides to coach Debra-Jo.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbeece33f0ad0f9256f37364a6d66065</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>With The Big O in space, the Xs are checking Agents? licenses for fighting oddness. Orla and Oswald must get their creature handling licenses, and fast.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf237663a38f9fcb4e07c97b0cffde0d3</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Friede visits his former workplace to look for clues about the mystery behind Terapagos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c3dda388bac2abac98c77251721d451</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Winx Club - The Magic Is Back</title>
    <desc>Following a scary encounter with a magic creature on her 16th birthday, Bloom discovers that she has magical powers. She is rescued by two fairies from Alfea School for Fairies and Witches.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa392635580aa64d93ddb96931017eac9</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Mia and Lucy face their biggest game of the season, and buds Masai and Ernest get competitive. Spurs legend Sandro takes on Jayden in Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p63635eb94acbd201ba1c631551fc90cc</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>The story of a 12-year-old boy waiting for a heart donor.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p180a95149418c0f1a499e7ebf31fadae</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Gladiators? stars Apollo and Electro surprise children in a Salford school when they lead a PE lesson with a difference.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfcd4e5a3bdf2843cec4b8f9fe7289d76</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>A reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio as they attempt to win the regional dance championships. Chloe's financial problems finally boil over and she is forced to leave A-Troupe. Michelle and Emily decide to be co-captains and work together to not only choreograph a new routine but also get Chloe back in the group.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b21f3b07f6556fa35c2ceb7213b4edc</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>30 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
