<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pacac24743c494eb3b848635637544aad</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings take part in a safari photo competition on an animal reserve.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p939bb07d2cf38d91a8625be934e44b2f</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings are trapped in a ball, and an ostrich sits on it, mistaking it for an egg.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd360edab947bab57be77ecad7762ad6c</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob introduces Patrick to books.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0fb652d78b3aac1848edf4db5a38cde8</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Odd Squad UK is celebrating its jubilee, but the party can?t get started until Orli locates the missing Ozzi, who has a bad case of the Saturdays.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0cc0452f982d60aa0d1416a766bc13f0</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:40AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Stressed about a big talk at school, Pierce finds a way to protect himself from his fears - by wearing Que?s gigantic robot battle suit.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p04867c9554a2fb39849cfe36faeee53b</image>
    <start>08:40AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It?s holiday time for Danny and Mick, but Joy has not approved their time off, and so they are not going anywhere! However, Mick's brilliant idea of bringing a caravan to work gets the boys in the holiday mood - but is there enough room for both of them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd6fe085c61da069134cdb67209f58ad8</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 9-11 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>12- and 24-hour clocks, reading timetables, and counting up time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1be68914e1b51dbdfb294793df9b7161</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Wow That's Amazing</title>
    <desc>Owain and Tilly discover how to turn bad beats into good vibrations, learn some top tricks guaranteed to give you goosebumps, and we meet Sammy, the spectacular, swimming squid.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7e7cb0d3c96dc8149d532965e510e75e</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:35AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>With trips abroad on hold, the staff decide to bring a holiday into school - Spanish style.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p786949be6dc09ac1552acfab71cc1363</image>
    <start>09:35AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs go full monster-mode as they make spooky costumes, David Shrigley builds a giant praying mantis, and comedian Katherine Ryan draws a cute cat with big eyes and serious sass.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p62f1b53b7b5ee67bf6a33909def92bd6</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>On an extremely hot day at the zoo, the white-cheeked gibbons enjoy a puzzling picnic, Spike the bearded dragon visits the vet, and there is a warm welcome set for Kyra the sun bear.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p58b75e5c348ed8580bf91d2851f97e87</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Cara, 9, has a form of dwarfism called achondroplasia and finds it difficult to get things appropriate for her height and age. Cara has a sweet tooth and loves to make and eat sweets. She also loves keeping fit and dancing. Cara needs a Sweetie Den where everything is the right height for her and she can disco dance to her heart's desire.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p72d7224bc06f20b166942f90ef689c07</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius Super Tech with Dick &amp; Dom</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom put the eight finalists of the Absolute Tech Genius contest through their paces to crown one of them the ultimate absolute tech genius. Judging these finalists through a variety of challenges will be industry experts, including Jon Bentley from the Gadget Show, Clive Beale from Raspberry Pi, Lucy Hedges, the tech editor of the Metro, and our very own CBBC channel controller - Cheryl Taylor. The three finalists who make it through to the later stages of the contest will be flying out to America to attend CES in Las Vegas and Apple HQ in Silicon Valley to meet the ultimate tech genius - Sir Jonathan Ive.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p77a941e477a8029a97eda9fb9b3335cb</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>A special episode of the historical sketch show about the great Egyptian queen Cleopatra, starring Kathryn Drysdale. We meet Cleo as she clashes with her brother, seizes power and hooks up with great Roman leaders Julius Caesar and Mark Antony. Meanwhile, across the world, we catch up with the thoughts of famous Chinese philosopher Confucius and encounter the less glamorous side of life in Rome. With, of course, our host Rattus to guide the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7ff5c32df6de7b10e4b1cad79cb235e2</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It's Wild West Wednesday at the Leisure Centre, there?s a bucking bronco and Naomi is making her spicy chilli for the occasion. Sharon is interviewing for a lifeguard job at the leisure centre. There's only one candidate and he is also a familiar face, which only leads to confusion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p729d64a120ee251d8030ee814e941041</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Odd Sock Mary has a valuable vase that she would like protecting, so cousin Mac invents a super security alarm - but there is a notorious art thief on the prowl.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0a7f7f3039cc9a0a0adda5bca2a06e39</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Nitro pranks Diamond when the guest on a live TV show can?t stop pumping! The other Gladiators have fun behind the scenes, pranking the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p124aa384cfc9de9b57a6c0777805b147</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated deep sea adventure series. Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. A sea sponge that houses other sea creatures in its pores suffers from a mysterious illness, and Peso must figure out the cause.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf71db7100abaf4526af2d41b336ce2b9</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad gets a severe case of Proximan hiccups. Big Lizard and Cosima do their best to help, but their attempt to scare Dad goes wrong when a real 'monster' turns up.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5ddd5626eeb3a49f1e8f652d03cfb731</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>The last thing DM would normally want to do is play a boring board game, but when one arrives in the post, it releases knockout gas and he's surprised to wake up in the town of Greenback. Jeopardy Mouse, Hazard Mouse and Danger Cash have also been snatched and are equally clueless why until a dragon attacks the group and a net drops from the sky at an opportune moment. Our guys realise they have been shrunk to chess-piece size by Ian the Danger Fan and are now pawns in his real-life board game.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p89d3a3ac086dc94904568d6e0040f283</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:25PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse's addiction to challenges threatens the world. Quark tricks Danger Mouse into transporting a ticking time bomb back to Earth. This device threatens to turn the entire world into gold within hours. Quark's face print is the key to deactivating the bomb, and while dragging the extra-mouthed extraterrestrial across space wouldn't usually pose much of a problem to DM, Quark aims to see his plan through by exploiting his captor's recently diagnosed 'Compulsive Challenge Disorder'. With the HQ in sight and minutes to spare, DM's 'CCD' takes hold at the worst possible moment, and he abandons the mission in order to battle an army of bounty hunters. Can DM come to his senses and channel his affliction into saving his friends and stop the planet from turning into a huge gold bauble.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3a0eba2335e392bf6d0c015b6b6474e7</image>
    <start>01:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Herbert is starting to feel his age and secretly drinks from the Fountain of Youth. However, his desire to be young puts the whole quest in jeopardy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ecebebc10b6dd928dcf3e72f8f98353</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>A frantic bride needs a romantic ice sculpture to appease her nervous groom, so the Ninjas travel to the north pole to deliver a wedding day she will never forget.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4244299fed08c9f23c9ffa18cc4ee1d7</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Harry Hill joins us in the studio to set the presenters some silly (but hilarious) challenges! Meanwhile, Joel swaps his Blue Peter Badge for a bow tie as he trains to be a butler at one of the world?s most luxurious five-star hotels.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf6ae1340cb89da232f9fcb0b17d7dad1</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>June takes drastic action to support Clarissa when a demanding Gwen pushes monitor duties too far - but will her radical plan pay off.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8b6e7dbcf62e4ac88051b2ef34927aac</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>OOglies</title>
    <desc>The OOglies slip, slide and splat all over the place. This fast-paced madcap, stop-motion animation uncovers the mischief everyday household objects get up to when no-one is looking. The potato racers are driving each other round the bend, the DIY doughnuts attempt to fix the bathroom, the cavemen mushrooms come face to face with some big, hairy mammoth pots, fearless Pete Parsnip takes on a ferocious foe, and Slippery Nana takes on a pizza-cutting unicycle in the talent show.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc75a0813855bf2fc00f9eb5e7b778651</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation. Set on a remote rural farm, Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. But Shaun's insatiable curiosity often leads him into the unlikeliest adventures. A pesky goat is tethered in the sheep's field, and threatens to eat all their grass.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14a3da180a2a70e76d1dbb99bb1662bd</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The gang get lost in the woods and stumble into the Land of Lost Things, where Gnasher gets dognapped by a Gnashersaurus rex which has lost its beloved egg. To save Gnasher they have to rely on Pieface logic to reunite the G-rex with its egg before Walter makes a record-breaking giant omelette with it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe14e0937e8213c0c362c0b4d2017acf4</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>Twinkle uses her excellent pocket beast card skills when on a quest to rescue the missing Council of Happiness from Grackle the Giant.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1c52df7e45b3a76f78f6ac5a5d573bb1</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Dog and Cat enjoy a collar-free lifestyle, until an animal-control officer thinks they are strays! Together, they must escape the only place worse than the vet - the pound.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p66b1230c6754e619942b53f531c1c413</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After Mouse underestimates Cat, she figures out how to make his time machine work. After getting stranded in prehistoric times, they have to figure out how to get back home.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6acd0d4f1e391e9107c90e276ca84339</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy unwittingly brings to life some medieval armour.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f1e5b7a6310872f1132ccb2ba2d6f94</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>The Krusty Krab runs out of mustard.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3204906fd1aefd440566cfe4bd2add8f</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>Rory announces that he wants to be prime minister.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb163234d404d4df5d2595a5bfa16f83b</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Orla thought she was the only ancient Agent left. However, when a distress call comes through, it becomes clear that she was wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd39f72e6540a95c86bb3e4e8236c5f9a</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Pierce watches a scary video and panics, eating too much mind-wipe gum and losing everything! It?s up to Que and Charlie to refresh his memory.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc24efd164f9337c7f405d79a7213a30b</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>When Owen gets cheated out of a much-wanted ice cream, the kids unite to right the wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb0e0faa507faa293dac67782cacaa6f8</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko and her Pok?mon face gym leader Grusha in battle on top of snowy Glaseado Mountain.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c83dc575ecb03c9763621068eea47db</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>There is a buzz around the school as the Anything Goes cast list is finally revealed. Will Lucas get the part of Moonface, a role usually reserved for the older years? Best friends Uma and Anna are both hoping for the lead, but will they be happy with their parts? Meanwhile, singer Max has been busy writing new songs over the summer, and his dreams of life as a pop star are ever closer as he releases new music.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p807240146244f7a364f98d645374483a</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>My Life</title>
    <desc>Eleven-year-old Australian Taj is a guitar prodigy. He has only been playing the guitar for four years, but has shared the stage with some of the biggest names in world music and played in front of tens of thousands of people at some of the most iconic venues in the world. However, his world turns upside down when lockdown hits, and he makes a big decision.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p45b8cd2c75ed0f9264d1b8fc8fe51a71</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Hunter challenges Eldon to a secret dance battle, with Michelle as the prize. Kate asks James to dance a duet with Beth when her partner drops out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9328cdd3e3c71043d6e7bd127a931a2e</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Get to know Hacker T Dog as he gives an access-all-areas tour of his hometown of Wigan.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2500c5c93798a92fe51991412e75ffa3</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>15 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
