<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>A prehistoric sponge is unfrozen and causes chaos.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0dc730653145e151cb5ab24672b98545</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:45PM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>A flock of clams descend on Bikini Bottom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdfca11fd35d063c2f9ff48721d046a1e</image>
    <start>06:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>19 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm, where Shaun's flock live a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. Shaun's hijinks with the rotary clothes line end up making the Farmer's washing filthy - so the race is on to get it clean again before he finds out.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p96869896002a4ac9f3819da319113c89</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Animated series. Second of two parts. Danger Mouse faces his toughest challenge ever as a mysterious super-villain releases all the villains from Arkwright and plots the end of our hero.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe62c1a98a6a993b1b609fda59528d5d</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>The class dig up a mysterious time capsule which sets them off on a race to find hidden treasure before Walter or a greed-crazed Paul the Potato can find it first.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p659edd59775ca7523bb64a0d16d30e47</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>K-Jam is moving into the neighbourhood and staying with the family for a while. However, Girl gets insecure and thinks that her awesome best friend is trying to take her place.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfbace25267391c527963e66f359240ab</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8b1e781d86b3c267ed2e2cbf279449d2</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Something wicca this way comes when Witchy is released early, trading a bottle in the archive room for a new broom with a view and leaving Pierce disenchanted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5badf274218ccc4f3bcba74374228182</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:05AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Patrick leads a stranger around Bikini Bottom.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p19b3d890a68b01014ae82a46077e0608</image>
    <start>08:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy finds an electrode that controls a robot, and the Lemmings plot to take it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p14a442001db4c31977f8ed627d7ed027</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings discover tai chi movements that generate balls of energy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4b9957284a15c047dd703c3b45dbab9b</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Miraculous: Tales of Ladybug &amp; Cat Noir</title>
    <desc>Ladybug faces a young singer who has turned into Frightningale.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb14af49296eee598f737636d2b900d91</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Blue Peter</title>
    <desc>Bro's in Control stars Adam B, Callum B and Joe Tasker go head-to-head against the Blue Peter presenters in three bonkers battles... with an unexpected prank! Shini goes behind the scenes at Heathrow Airport to discover the epic jobs and secret areas you never usually get to see.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ad36727ce459667469b317a4d815882</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>It's the start of a new school year, and the school is buzzing as boarders find out who they are sharing a dorm with and day pupils reunite at the lockers. No time is wasted on day one as the students go head-to-head for roles in the new show: Anything Goes. And this year could be life-changing for dancer Jakob as he starts his preparations for one of the world?s most prestigious international ballet competitions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe43e8702039ee3f0a37066f6e5bc0013</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:50AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Cooking Buddies</title>
    <desc>Buddy and Conker get a call from Sienna, a footballer who needs Buddy?s help. Her grandparents? wedding anniversary is coming up and she wants to cook something to surprise them. Buddy knows that making pizzas from scratch is bound to score well with everyone, so they make their own dough and tomato sauce, and choose their own toppings to make personalised pizzas (with faces!) that everyone will love. This time, Conker also has a playmate as Sienna brings her little pug, Bella with her. Conker tries to impress Bella with his jokes as they both cheer Buddy and Sienna on! Taking a break from their ?Keepy Uppy Pizzas?, Sienna drills Buddy on the football pitch, challenging his fitness by racing him with parachutes on their backs, dribbling to test his control of the ball and learning to do rainbow flicks, before going into the ultimate penalty shootout. Join Buddy, Conker, Sienna and Bella in this fun and tasty episode of Cooking Buddies that scores big. You can get all of Buddy?s recipes, and LOADS more, at bbc.co.uk\/food.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9f434b14b3b46f480cbd0e8a48981672</image>
    <start>09:50AM</start>
    <finish>10:10AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>So Awkward</title>
    <desc>Lily gets a part-time job waitressing at Mugshotsz Caf?, determined to prove to straight-talking owner Lou that teenagers make good workers. However, her mission goes wrong when Jas gets a job at the caf? too. Jas is messy and thoughtless, which upends Lily?s need for perfection, yet Lou thinks Jas is brilliant. Meanwhile, Sid has been invited to audition for a performing arts college. Rob is upset that Sid may leave Cranmede, and Mr Malone is annoyed that his free guitar lessons will end. Torn between going to the audition or not, Sid turns to Jas for advice. Ollie has a girlfriend, Kat, which Martha finds nauseating. She is unnerved that Kat attends Cranmede, has persuaded Ollie to set up a tech company with her, and worse still, has taken Martha?s seat in the caf?, forcing her to sit away from the power socket.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbacb82dc335880b8f053135da87a7b36</image>
    <start>10:10AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>The leisure centre is hosting a roller disco later that afternoon and Joy tells Danny and Mick if they want to be at the disco they need to finish every job on her list first. Danny spots a way to get some skating practice in and finish the jobs in double quick time ? by doing all their work on wheels! Unfortunately, when a runaway Danny crashes through the disco it looks like the whole thing might be off. Can Mick save the day.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p52e4ee264a5d8048836ac7900ce9cffb</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>The centre needs to be decorated for a wedding later today, but Danny?s more interested in his new invention ? which unfortunately blows through every toilet roll in the centre. When Mick distracts him mid-order, he accidentally requests 10,000 toilet rolls instead of 100 by express delivery, and they arrive in a whole mountain of boxes. Fearing Joy?s reaction, the boys decide to hide the loo rolls.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3ecc6e1702eeac871d1350e3e6a88646</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bro's in Control</title>
    <desc>Callum is a Little Bro in control! His Big Bro Adam is going up against best mate Joe to see who will win a series of funny, gungy and gross challenges, and who?ll take on a forfeit from the Wheel of Doom. Callum isn?t taking any nonsense, so they have to work hard to impress him! The National Art Gallery has called: they need replicas making ASAP! It?s a job for Big Bro and Big Joe... using flour and gunge, natch. But whose art will be fit for a gallery, and whose will fail? Little Bro Callum decides the winner in this epic art showdown. Not all is lost, as the loser gets a chance to redeem themselves in the No Hands Challenge. Who can set up a Date Night using only their pockets, their wits and a giant shark with a violin? Sound extra? Callum?s challenges definitely are in this hilarious, gross and gungy contest.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0773f124bfcc55203ef81a9817b791c7</image>
    <start>11:05AM</start>
    <finish>11:20AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Giant is pranked by Nitro when he appears as a guest of honour at a fake school award ceremony! The other Gladiators have sneaky fun backstage at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe24d7c7ee4f1aef3442ee32cdd611f0c</image>
    <start>11:20AM</start>
    <finish>11:35AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve and the team embark on a truly incredible adventure across the vast island of Madagascar. Many of the creatures they meet cannot be found anywhere else in the world. From gremlin-like aye-ayes to Madagascar's most ferocious carnivore, Steve has some unique encounters as he searches for contenders for the Deadly 60.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb6612f6d349b2d1396babb7ec2820694</image>
    <start>11:35AM</start>
    <finish>12:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors celebrate as the NHS turns 75. They award Ouch Hero medals in the hospital, hear Ouchers? big NHS stories and travel through time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8c1733ea13c7085a5e0a93025673013a</image>
    <start>12:05PM</start>
    <finish>12:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>In a special musical episode of the award-winning Horrible Histories, host Rattus Rattus chooses his favourite songs from the fourth series to entertain his young nephew.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9833b9ef0b1aaba4c381c12f8668a232</image>
    <start>12:35PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Science</title>
    <desc>Big Brain has a chemical catastrophe, Sir Isaac Newton rides a coaster again, with shocking results, Loofah is after a murderer, and Dr Henry VIII on call.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peee6d9a3675c97b17d21716f58b7d6ed</image>
    <start>01:05PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Man Ray rents Squidward's house.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p110a8b96185ebf2ed896d5b6702bd462</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:45PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Mr Krabs makes Larry the Lobster temporary manager.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd0e22dd97fb97622e2e8e8094bbc594c</image>
    <start>01:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob is afraid to leave the Krusty Krab roof.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3abb572d932ffb348185a0d80de3f6bd</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Having transformed himself into a teenager to help expose a nest of vampires at school, Helsing displays no class when he joins Daisy's bullies instead.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe95e5a989ec6fe9443e3864f2352f0a5</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:20PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Defending the house on Halloween, Charlie is in for a fright when Pierce invites the neighbourhood (and at least one monster) over for a costume party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p68c8d66eaa392128e8f3a1074c76a006</image>
    <start>02:20PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>While riding their scooters at the park, the bickering kids meet the Smiths. A brother and sister who don't seem to argue like our gang does - in fact, the two Smiths are super-supportive of each other! When they start pushing the other kids around, Boy, Girl, Dog, Cat, Mouse and Cheese challenge the Smiths to a race around the park! But our heroes have one problem - Cat doesn't know how to ride a scooter! The kids take turns teaching her and, when race day comes, Cat will really need to kick it into high gear if she wants to help the family beat those smug Smiths.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9fd76bdc48953edfd54c15e16338e394</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:45PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Mouse buys a video game that is supposed to teach the family teamwork. When they end up bickering as they play, Mouse creates a robot that turns off the game if they argue. However, a robot malfunction places the whole family in danger. To survive they will have to finish the video game without arguing - unless they can think of a way to make bickering help.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5254962cb1e76d16d6aef47dd42d2b0b</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>With Boy's new help-for-hire business booming, he overworks his unpaid employee, Dog, without realizing. Dog is too loyal to say no, but he's miserable, especially when his next job is walking some mean cats. Girl sets out to teach Dog a lesson about standing up for himself, pretending to lose the cats to make Dog realize he should have said no to Boy, which will teach him to do just that in the future! But when the cats really go missing, they frantically set out to find them before Boy's business is ruined.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd34a23b7cb8266ab6bf47342b3519166</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Noah tries to rescue the chocolates Owen forgot outside before something else steals them.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe990410924ceb1db2243b7a84a432d8e</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>Courtney must go all day without correcting her friends, regardless of what they do wrong.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pfe12d009fb4b08949cdf975f6bbb47a8</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>A walkie-talkie hidden inside a chili dog causes Harold to worry an alien has arrived.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd55181ac1b0277a6a03b77b9b2b7602a</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>A container full of Yummy? What a dream for Grizzy and the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa0fb4c14616b7fac90132c14ceaa7f84</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>After the Yeti's house is destroyed, the Lemmings are quick to point the finger at Grizzy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p08d177e86e46cf42f4ecb3cb64daa9c2</image>
    <start>03:50PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dragons: The Nine Realms</title>
    <desc>Jun does a Tarot reading and interprets its meaning to be that the riders will disband.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p921f51c780aea1bc664cf581d5e5b551</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dumping Ground</title>
    <desc>Brodie discovers something huge about Chelsey?s past that threatens her relationship with her twin, Keira. Meanwhile, Frankie sets out to prove he is the true Chaos Master of the DG.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1aaf6800fccc18d51819344646971c72</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>A Kind of Spark</title>
    <desc>Addie?s council event hangs in the balance when a grumpy Miriam refuses to reveal her secret. Meanwhile, Iona holds band auditions and finds a surprising lead singer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56849dd6eddeabf135280a0c5d23a971</image>
    <start>04:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:15PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>It's the start of a new school year, and the school is buzzing as boarders find out who they are sharing a dorm with and day pupils reunite at the lockers. No time is wasted on day one as the students go head-to-head for roles in the new show: Anything Goes. And this year could be life-changing for dancer Jakob as he starts his preparations for one of the world?s most prestigious international ballet competitions.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe43e8702039ee3f0a37066f6e5bc0013</image>
    <start>05:15PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Football Academy</title>
    <desc>Meet the Tottenham Hotspur academy players. Lia Lewis picks her Three of the Best, and Dominic Solanke takes on 11-year-old Konan in Skill Showdown.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p88eec7f914b4c5e2f11d416e2a1eaf76</image>
    <start>05:40PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Drama</title>
    <desc>Julia gets between Caleb and Priya during the most painful memory game of all time.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p5d656e5bd2675f07c2ceecdd81f59549</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Plankton's pet amoeba Spot has puppies.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3aec6731d44095522f9d9a86d66803dd</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:35PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>Mr Krabs is too scared to get his physical.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc83b687ea889f4f6d02736b5f0be2494</image>
    <start>06:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>While falling, Grizzy performs a series of acrobatics that amazes the Lemmings.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p723cb1057326be4e83853b78617595a0</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>20 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>This is CBBC!</title>
    <desc>Tune every day from 7.00am.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pac6f5338cb209460533f978542c5195a</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Animated adventures with the mischievous young sheep and his flock. Shaun and Bitzer discover that a visitor to the farm is not as cute and adorable as she seems.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p113da15aa6ff745d88153ce098d4d1c0</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>Danger Mouse and Penfold accompany Professor Squawkencluck to the Brainiac Symposium - the annual science convention, where King Kong Brunels's latest misfiring invention, the Cow Trainer, reminds his fellow boffins exactly why he is the laughing stock of the scientist community. When King Kong Brunel suggests that the Professor's success is all due to her privileged life as Danger Agency lab technician with scientist parents, an irked Squawk uses Brunel's Cow Trainer to swap bodies with him in order to show that she could be just as successful in his shoes. However, she soon finds that life as King Kong Brunel is as dispiriting as he makes out, as she is laughed out of the symposium when masquerading as her simian adversary. Elsewhere, an opportunistic King Kong Brunel finds himself revelling at playing Squawk, as finds he himself inside her lab having hitched a lift back to HQ with an unwitting Danger Mouse and Penfold. On discovering the truth, Danger Mouse and Penfold have the body- swapper turned on them, as KKB escapes back to the convention with his newly acquired Squawk-shaped credibility, and a new invention so poorly put together that it could end the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p10d782c873c5cb440e14211052a06036</image>
    <start>07:10AM</start>
    <finish>07:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>When Hoofius plays his grandfaun?s old magical panpipes, his friends do exactly what he asks them to do - perfect for leading a quest... or so he thinks.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbada50b36a9303ac56775c369e7c2be0</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>07:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>The kids want to impress Gramps by completing the Gauntlet of Greatness carnival attraction that he did when he was their age. However, Dog and Girl just can't seem to beat it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6db98e87d457a49378a84e78a275e08d</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>07:45AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Newsround</title>
    <desc>Topical news magazine for children.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf0a915ab271c1c9c1e1b2a33188e7991</image>
    <start>07:45AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings invent a whole bunch of bouncing games with spongy jelly.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe74f0b84aee020f2055f16fd17fbfae0</image>
    <start>07:55AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The Lemmings happen upon a bracelet that increases the strength of its wearer.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf006c51e34db491fb6b6a7f5babd196</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>The long-lost episode of Mermaid Man is finally showing on TV.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pbf9a7e2afdc7aa6d3136c4226bae6879</image>
    <start>08:10AM</start>
    <finish>08:25AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>Villain Miss Information is using graphs to spread falsehoods about Odd Squad, which is leading to the public not trusting them. Can Captain O get the public back on side.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p81bd195210835185fd3d564b62fdc1a6</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:35AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>When an ex-chores boy reappears wearing Helsing?s invisibility jacket, the gang is tasked with destroying it. But can Pierce resist the temptation to be bad.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/peb3ce24ec5d9349cd2520f3d380cbd25</image>
    <start>08:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>A special visit from the mayor means that his chains need putting away safely, while he goes for a swim. As head of security, Mick locks them in Joy?s safe, but due to his forgetfulness, Danny and Mick now need to work out another way to retrieve them before the mayor returns.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p67d3bf33fe7afe0b424f8e1914b79a2f</image>
    <start>08:50AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Bitesize Daily: 5-7 Year Olds</title>
    <desc>Numbers to 100, finding one more and one less, signs and symbols.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8497519bb2385402291d2ce16bce6065</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Hey You What If?</title>
    <desc>Could you build a slide to the other side of the world? You would need to start in space, use the slippiest slide ever and make sure you have enough supplies before you go down it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0c93e4b0e1fc4adb5f1d0842be1d0abe</image>
    <start>09:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Out of This World</title>
    <desc>In this episode, Dr Maggie tells the story of the Space Race, what it was, the key missions involved and how the USA, competing against and then collaborating with the Soviet Union, got us to where we are today in space. Dr Maggie?s guest is Tim Peake, the first British astronaut to live on board ISS, who tells us how astronauts from different countries successfully work together in space. Dr Maggie also answers your space questions and unveils her top five 'firsts in space'. Buckle up, it?s time to go Out Of this World.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p4ae90359fda623e4c4cca90584ac5fec</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:40AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Our School</title>
    <desc>The girls get creative as Daisy and her friends give the common room a colourful makeover. Eva and Evie enter the school photography competition, with some top tips from wildlife presenter Megan McCubbin.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p284c6a12a13bdaf11b948cf74d39429b</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Go Get Arty</title>
    <desc>The Kwapongs get festival-ready as they craft carnival headwear, artist Lakwena Maciver makes a grey rooftop pop with paint, and Abi Clarke draws a pirouetting otter in a tutu.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0953a9c9704625e78726ab7d76ad8ed3</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:20AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>One Zoo Three</title>
    <desc>The One Zoo Three zoo celebrates the opening of some amazing new animal habitats with a new den for the sun bears - but will the jaguars feature pad be a bit hit or miss.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p82c799404a8b398ad1720b5d28fab278</image>
    <start>10:20AM</start>
    <finish>10:40AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Dengineers</title>
    <desc>Archie is ten years old and as well as planting, growing and harvesting vegetables, he loves looking after his chickens. Archie sells his home grown veg and eggs locally and uses the profits to buy food for his local food bank. He's taken his enterprise as far as he can and desperately needs a farm den so he can increase his productivity.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p56791e20903f1fb7af1af660dda2480a</image>
    <start>10:40AM</start>
    <finish>11:10AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Absolute Genius: Monster Builds</title>
    <desc>Dick and Dom go supersized in this massive movers spectacular in which they trace the origins of the genius ideas that have made shifting heavy weights a whole lot easier. In their element, the boys head to a scrapyard to find out how hydraulic grabbers work, get up close to one of the weirdest-looking aircraft ever built and get to grips, literally, with the world's largest hydraulic hand.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p0f2118c4c2ca8416715ca1a3003f20f5</image>
    <start>11:10AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Horrible Histories</title>
    <desc>Horrible Histories returns for a special about King John and Magna Carta, starring Ben Miller. John annoys the barons and agrees Magna Carta at Runnymede after a banging rap battle. Meanwhile, across the world, we meet the formidable Genghis Khan in Mongolia and catch up with the crafty Saladin during the Crusades. With, of course, our host Rattus to guide the way.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p704659bf05f3ee09e78f5adba8ddd40d</image>
    <start>11:40AM</start>
    <finish>12:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danny and Mick</title>
    <desc>It's staff charity cabaret night at the Pottsfield Leisure Centre and special guest and ventriloquist Paul Zerdin is performing. When his sidekick Sam goes missing. Danny and Mick have to step up to perform their own ventriloquist act.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7994c29c48222559183f36600d7e659f</image>
    <start>12:15PM</start>
    <finish>12:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Andy and the Band</title>
    <desc>Danny needs a cake for his parents? wedding, and fast! The band deliver a cake, but Mac?s size-shifting machine causes chaos, and they have an angry wedding organiser to contend with.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe1cbb1d1ebd8080b7915706128afa381</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>12:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Gladiators: Epic Pranks</title>
    <desc>Bionic ends up dressed as a rabbit when Nitro pranks him at a fake photoshoot, and the rest of the Gladiators have fun behind the scenes as they prank the audience at Sheffield Arena.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/paf7d7f9299d05e5c92784905daf4991d</image>
    <start>12:40PM</start>
    <finish>12:55PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Octonauts</title>
    <desc>Animated deep sea adventure series. Captain Barnacles and his intrepid band of explorers roam the oceans in search of adventure and fun. When an underwater tremor separates the Gup-X and its crew, Barnacles seeks guidance from a mysterious sea turtle.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p3f9f6d55e7dfb1bfbda6c8a0a55e82dd</image>
    <start>12:55PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Big Lizard</title>
    <desc>Dad and Cosima both think they're the best at pranking. Their prank war quickly spirals out of control, until Big Lizard finally reveals Proxima's real pranking champion.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pea0f60cf71247ea3d276941d6971e477</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>01:15PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Danger Mouse</title>
    <desc>If being zapped with a mind-controlling Mindzooka ray by a couple of D-list villains wasn't bad enough, Danger Mouse's shame goes viral thanks to a series of embarrassing videos. Determined to stop the release of the most incriminating video of all, Danger Mouse turns to the villain behind the mind-control tech - the incarcerated Crumhorn! Crumhorn offers an anti-mind control device, but it comes with a catch - he has to be temporarily released back to Crumcorp Towers to retrieve it.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p402f93b5d6cb5e8e2fc05b79645fff74</image>
    <start>01:15PM</start>
    <finish>01:40PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The heroes set out on a quest to find out who is draining colour from the forest and muster all their positivity to save it from greyness.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pb3d4f995b8c3040f9e2b17fe57dfa29f</image>
    <start>01:40PM</start>
    <finish>01:55PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Ninja Express</title>
    <desc>When a parrot steals a fisherman?s lucky captain's hat, the Ninjas search for a replacement on a cruise ship, only for Konpeki and Aka to get distracted.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1e8f614bd723264869f90ef1bf1f4b24</image>
    <start>01:55PM</start>
    <finish>02:05PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Steve dives with 100 grey nurse sharks - aka ragged-tooth sharks - a wobbegong and a gigantic whale shark, and he joins a mission in Indonesia to save sharks from over-fishing with eco-tourism.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pdcc05d21452d9faf35f104aaea0c088f</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>In a bid to prove that girls are just as good at football as boys, Felicity and June disguise Clarissa. Meanwhile, Darrell and Susan help Mr Murray with his chamber investigation.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd011de15557cf8f3fdef27c8afd96390</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shaun the Sheep</title>
    <desc>Children's animation set on a remote rural farm. Shaun's flock lives a peaceful life under the watchful eye of their sheepdog Bitzer. Shaun finds the farmer's old record player on the dump and organises a rave in the barn, but trouble looms when the naughty pigs gatecrash the party.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2d85e8a5e8a7604eacfba23dddab4e8d</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Dennis &amp; Gnasher Unleashed!</title>
    <desc>It?s time for Gnasher?s annual bath, but the stinky hound will do anything to avoid the tub. Dennis and Gnasher go head to head in a town-wide game of cat and mouse ? or rather, tripe hound and wheelie bathtub.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9cd3695300ecc962061ac4a3338675c2</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:20PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Super Happy Magic Forest</title>
    <desc>The forest has run out of bath sponges and is becoming very stinky. Their latest order never arrived, and so the heroes must quest under the sea to Merhaven to collect them. However, Hoofius, whose singing stinks worse than his armpits, decides to enter the annual Merhaven Song Contest and accidentally causes a simple quest to collect bath sponges to turn into something much more perilous.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p8ed5d646aa33c0f016a4f842cc22d80c</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>After breaking their games console, the kids decide to sell Boy's homemade cookies to raise money for a new one. All is well until they get some unexpected competition.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/ped62b0d7cfc54d8c982819332e593aa3</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Boy Girl Dog Cat Mouse Cheese</title>
    <desc>Susie and Dog set aside their differences to partner up for a figure-skating competition. All is well until they realise that someone is sabotaging them and their chances of winning.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p42f9e79e93d36b6515c3a875959500de</image>
    <start>03:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>The jelly cake battle takes on epic dimensions into a 'heroic fantasy' world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p7540cfc28a15de2ef3fc5c8015f20b14</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>SpongeBob SquarePants</title>
    <desc>SpongeBob invents a new persona.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p15a3e516d535e143ed23b99e8ae441e0</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:20PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Little Lunch</title>
    <desc>The others try to cheer Rory up after he is punished and sent to the office.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p6853721e6e0a07518571c0a31c3f1c4d</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>04:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Odd Squad</title>
    <desc>With a spike in oddness in the UK, Department of Help agent Ozzie suggests they send for help from the best agent in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p2daff7b5a508d12e0255a7449c918759</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:45PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Strange Chores</title>
    <desc>Charlie uses Helsing?s time remote to bring a heavily muscled future version of himself back to the present to change his life.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pf77616ab1a39e80807a661849b4d161a</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Total Dramarama</title>
    <desc>A walkie-talkie hidden inside a chili dog causes Harold to worry an alien has arrived.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pd55181ac1b0277a6a03b77b9b2b7602a</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:10PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Pok?mon Horizons</title>
    <desc>Liko, Roy and Dot jump into action when the Explorers stage an attack on Naranja Academy.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe6a25376dd9d029398b4d31755dde01c</image>
    <start>05:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Stage Stars</title>
    <desc>With Christmas around the corner, the juniors give a festive performance at the local town fair. Meanwhile, it's time for Encore's end-of-term performance.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pc3462f0723775ab4ee62e020a81d77a7</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Gwen is shocked into drastic action when her father refuses to sign her application to finishing school. Meanwhile, Darrell and Felicity fall out during the North Tower Spelling Bee.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p9d81b1dd5f4376b5dc9a2f540ed83af0</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:25PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>The Next Step</title>
    <desc>Reality-style drama following the lives of a group of dancers at the Next Step Dance Studio. James and Riley struggle with their duet. Michelle demands an answer from Eldon - why is he avoiding her.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pe139849510e43a951abbc6f52b345676</image>
    <start>06:25PM</start>
    <finish>06:50PM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Grizzy and the Lemmings</title>
    <desc>Grizzy and the Lemmings end up lost after misplacing their jar of Yummy in a labyrinth.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/pa6adf7709b4293ae1023ab4a70b88ad6</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
