<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <id>ABC.au</id>
    <title>Ask the Doctor</title>
    <desc>Is growing old and frail inevitable? Sandro discovers how to stay younger for longer, Shalin shows fun ways to stave off dementia, and Caroline breaks down menopause myths by throwing an unusual party.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/75/95/47/759547_p14186106_b_h9_al_360.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <id>ABC.au</id>
    <title>The Art Of...</title>
    <desc>Join Namila as she meets mavericks making change around the world. Featuring Grammy Award winner Angelique Kidjo, singer-songwriter Kutcha Edwards, drag queen fashionista Bimini and educator Joris Lechene.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/77/66/78/776678_p27457223_b_h9_ab_360.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:59PM</finish>
    <date>07 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <id>ABC.au</id>
    <title>Gardening Australia</title>
    <desc>Jerry meets a staghorn and elkhorn fern collector, Jane shows how to grow fruits in small spaces, Costa visits an urban farm training deaf and hard-of-hearing students and Sophie tours a spectacular dryland garden.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/74/79/14/747914_p11986162_b_h9_ae_360.jpg</image>
    <start>06:59PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <id>ABC.au</id>
    <title>Insiders</title>
    <desc>David Speers and the panel discuss the week in federal politics including defence spending, climate policy, Iran, Gaza and Ukraine, the housing crisis, productivity, economic reform and national security.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/70/37/49/703749_p945802_b_h3_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC AU</name>
    <id>ABC.au</id>
    <title>News Breakfast</title>
    <desc>As the day begins get the facts you need to stay informed. Bridget Brennan and James Glenday present the latest news, overnight developments and top stories, joined by Catherine Murphy with sport and Nate Byrne with weather.</desc>
    <image>https://s3-ap-southeast-2.amazonaws.com/nine-tvmg-images-prod/80/01/59/800159_p553013_b_h9_ad_360.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
