<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>The Litany Of The Blessed Virgin Mary</title>
    <desc>Join the Franciscan Missionaries of the Eternal Word as they recite this beautiful prayer in honor of the Blessed Virgin Mary from the Shrine of the Most Blessed Sacrament in Hanceville, Alabama. (11 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:49AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>The Oldest Gospel In The World</title>
    <desc>The fascinating story of the Hanna Papyrus, an artifact 18 centuries old containing the text of two Gospels. Learn the mysteries of its discovery, its history through the ages and the steps being taken to preserve it. (60 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Priesthood Of Jesus Christ</title>
    <desc>Fr. Miller briefly discusses the aspects of the priesthood which will be discussed in future episodes. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Father Spitzer?s Universe</title>
    <desc>Fr. Spitzer answers viewer questions on a wide range of subjects, including: Reason, Faith, Suffering, Virtue, and the Existence of God. (60 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>&lt;span Class=&quot; Theme Emphasis&quot;&gt;new!&lt;/span&gt; Women Of Grace</title>
    <desc>Fr. Thomas Petri shares his call to religious life, subsequent ordination, and what he considers to be the most important rungs in our spiritual ladder to union with God. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Where God Weeps</title>
    <desc>In a country with approximately 830 different languages, Christians in Papua New Guinea face unique challenges adapting to rapid social developments in the modern information age. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Stones And Pearls: The Rosary In The Holy Land</title>
    <desc>The second luminous mystery unfolds at the wedding feast of Cana. By turning water into wine, Jesus shows he?ll offer his own blood on the cross and in the Eucharist, and will become the Eternal Bridegroom of his people. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Saints And Heroes</title>
    <desc>The life of St. Francis of Assisi from care-free youth to his conversion and radical embracement of poverty for the love of God. Animated. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Massterpiece Donut Shop</title>
    <desc>When the Donut Shop kids accidentally skip an important part of their play about the Mass, Fr. Joe saves the day by stepping in to explain the final steps of Mass so that everyone leaves ready to share the Faith with the world. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Mother Angelica Live Classics</title>
    <desc>Mother talks about Pentecost and how the Holy Spirit dwells within us. (60 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Champions Of Faith</title>
    <desc>Featuring Major League Baseball?s biggest stars, discover the intersection of sports and Faith with those whose careers have been strengthened and magnified by their Faith in God. (70 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Pier Giorgio Frassati Get To Know Him</title>
    <desc>A brief introduction to Blessed Pier Giorgio Frassati: a young, joyful man, whose devotion and charity towards the poor caused Pope Francis to encourage young people to look up to him as an example of holiness. (20 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
