<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Stones And Pearls: The Rosary In The Holy Land</title>
    <desc>The second luminous mystery unfolds at the wedding feast of Cana. By turning water into wine, Jesus shows he?ll offer his own blood on the cross and in the Eucharist, and will become the Eternal Bridegroom of his people. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Saints And Heroes</title>
    <desc>The life of St. Francis of Assisi from care-free youth to his conversion and radical embracement of poverty for the love of God. Animated. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Massterpiece Donut Shop</title>
    <desc>When the Donut Shop kids accidentally skip an important part of their play about the Mass, Fr. Joe saves the day by stepping in to explain the final steps of Mass so that everyone leaves ready to share the Faith with the world. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Mother Angelica Live Classics</title>
    <desc>Mother talks about Pentecost and how the Holy Spirit dwells within us. (60 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Champions Of Faith</title>
    <desc>Featuring Major League Baseball?s biggest stars, discover the intersection of sports and Faith with those whose careers have been strengthened and magnified by their Faith in God. (70 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Pier Giorgio Frassati Get To Know Him</title>
    <desc>A brief introduction to Blessed Pier Giorgio Frassati: a young, joyful man, whose devotion and charity towards the poor caused Pope Francis to encourage young people to look up to him as an example of holiness. (20 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:10PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
