<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>The Litany Of The Divine Child Jesus</title>
    <desc>Join the Franciscan Missionaries of the Eternal Word as they recite the litany of the Divine Child Jesus from the Shrine of the Most Blessed Sacrament in Hanceville, Alabama. (12 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:48AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>&lt;span Class=&quot; Theme Emphasis&quot;&gt;new!&lt;/span&gt; Scripture And Tradition With Fr. Mitch Pacwa</title>
    <desc>Fr. Mitch examines (Proto) Isaiah, chapters 21 and 22, the visions of catastrophe they describe, and the meanings behind these visions. (60 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Grandparents</title>
    <desc>Fr. James explores how a grandparent?s faith can be a powerful influence on their grandchildren, especially in circumstances where they don?t live in practicing households. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Journey Home</title>
    <desc>Mother Seraphina Marie, FDM, talks about her reversion to the Catholic Faith. Hosted by Marcus Grodi. (60 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Women Of Grace</title>
    <desc>The consecration to Our Lady profoundly shaped the spiritual life and pontificate of St. John Paul II. Monsignor Arthur Calkins shares his unique insight on its history, from the early days of the Church to the present. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>&lt;span Class=&quot; Theme Emphasis&quot;&gt;new!&lt;/span&gt; First Papal Audience With Pope Leo Xiv</title>
    <desc>Live from the Vatican, Pope Leo XIV delivers his weekly address to the faithful in what will be his first public address as Pope since his election. (75 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:15AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Gospel Glimpses</title>
    <desc>Unlike scholars who often contradict each other, the best explainers of Scripture are the saints. Today, discover why we must pay attention to them, because they?re dauntless in their faith and truly love the church. (15 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:15AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>&lt;span Class=&quot; Theme Emphasis&quot;&gt;new!&lt;/span&gt; Living Divine Mercy</title>
    <desc>Fr. Chris Alar, M.I.C. helps viewers get a better understanding of the Divine Mercy message, and shares powerful, real life examples of people who live Divine Mercy in their every day lives. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Get A Life In Christ</title>
    <desc>Fr, Benedict is developing the theme over several episodes of the gift of the virtues being powers afforded us from God.  This episode is devoted to his discussion of &quot;Whatever Happened to Virtue?&quot;  It is no longer politically correct to be virtuous and, of course, Fr. Benedict takes exception to that position. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Chaplet Of Divine Mercy</title>
    <desc>From the chapel of the National Shrine of the Divine Mercy in Stockbridge, Massachusetts. (20 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Reflections With Fr. Leo Clifford</title>
    <desc>Father Leo Clifford develops the idea that our deepest yearnings are put there by God due to His great love for us.  He wants us to learn to love Him as much as He love us, impossible though that may be. (10 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:50AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Vaticano</title>
    <desc>We reflect on our new Pope?s challenges. Discover the Church's role during World War II. Hear from Cardinal Czerny on the Conclave. Explore the Caravaggio exhibition. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Jeanne Jugan: Yesterday And Today</title>
    <desc>A look at the life and ministry of the Little Sisters of the Poor, founded by Jeanne Jugan with a special mission of hospitality, particularly towards the elderly. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>The Roamin? Catholic</title>
    <desc>As Rob prepares and attempts to leave for back to back trips, he and Pete realize the meaning of being a good host and a good houseguest, just as Mary was to her cousin Elizabeth. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
