<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>The Holy Land Rosary</title>
    <desc>Fr. Mitch Pacwa leads the Glorious Mysteries of the Rosary from the actual holy sites and shrines where they took place, bringing the Gospels to life and offering a deeper understanding of the Rosary meditations. (18 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30AM</start>
    <finish>04:48AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>The Litany Of Saint Joseph</title>
    <desc>Join the Franciscan Missionaries of the Eternal Word as they recite this inspirational litany asking for the prayers of Saint Joseph from the Shrine of the Most Blessed Sacrament in Hanceville, Alabama. (12 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:48AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>My Lourdes Faith Journey</title>
    <desc>Brian Weber lost his only son in a car crash before getting deployed to Afghanistan. He shares how an encounter with Our Lady of Lourdes in the Grotto changed his life and brought light into the darkness of suffering. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Life Is Worth Living</title>
    <desc>Archbishop Sheen explains how to make humanity more loveable and points to three stages of love. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Catholicism On Campus: The Students</title>
    <desc>Msgr. Stuart Swetland and guests talk with the students of Mount Saint Mary's about the Eucharistic power of the Mass. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Ewtn News In Depth</title>
    <desc>EWTN?s weekly one-hour discussion of current events in the Church, politics, and culture, from a Catholic perspective. Covering the underreported stories and clarifying the Church's position on key teachings, with a focus on the laity's needs and concerns. Hosted by Catherine Hadro. (60 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>&lt;span Class=&quot; Theme Emphasis&quot;&gt;new!&lt;/span&gt; Called To Communion With Dr. David Anders</title>
    <desc>Dr. Anders answers caller questions about biblical history as literal or figurative, the presence of apostles at the Last Supper, and a marriage convalidation works in the Church. (60 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>&lt;span Class=&quot; Theme Emphasis&quot;&gt;new!&lt;/span&gt; Solemnity Of The Feast Of Sts. Peter And Paul</title>
    <desc>From St. Peter?s Basilica (Altar of the Chair), and presided over by the Holy Father on the Solemnity of Saints Peter and Paul. Holy Mass and blessing of the Pallia for the new Metropolitan Archbishops. (105 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:15AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Catholic Center At Nyu: An Icon Of The New Evangelization</title>
    <desc>A documentary on the Dominican-run center at New York University, which provides the spiritual and intellectual formation of 18,000 Catholic students. (15 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:15AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Six Paths To The Priesthood</title>
    <desc>Learn about the different ways Jesus Christ drew each man to the priesthood in this deeply personal account of six Dominican friars ordained by Bishop Robert Barron, who reflects upon his own experiences as well. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Angelus With Pope Leo Xiv</title>
    <desc>On the Solemnity of the Most Holy Trinity, Pope Leo XIV recites the Angelus in St Peter?s Square, invoking the Blessed Mother and uniting in prayer with many throughout the world. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>&lt;span Class=&quot; Theme Emphasis&quot;&gt;new!&lt;/span&gt; Ewtn Bookmark</title>
    <desc>Financial specialist David Bahnsen explains how we discover meaning and purpose in work, and why a successful life is rooted in productivity and cultivation of God?s created world. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>The Spirit Of Catholic Leadership</title>
    <desc>How to integrate Christian love into your leadership lives; putting principle and the common good before personal interests. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>29 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
