<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Where God Weeps</title>
    <desc>Nigeria is a multiparty democracy that has become Africa?s economic and demographic powerhouse. But the country also has a terrorism problem that has grown bigger and more complex. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>St. Thomas More: A Hero For Our Times</title>
    <desc>Dr. Gerard Wegemer of the University of Dallas discusses the life and heroic virtues of St. Thomas More, who gave his life defending the Faith during the reign of Henry VIII. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Saints And Heroes</title>
    <desc>Nicholas was still a young boy when he discovered the love of Jesus and the gift of giving that changed the world. Based on historical facts and traditions this film is worth watching with family and friends. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Massterpiece Donut Shop</title>
    <desc>Join Duncan and The Donut Repair Club is singing along with original songs about the Mass featured on Massterpiece Donut Shoppe. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>Mother Angelica Live Classics</title>
    <desc>Mother discuss's the Trinity and its meaning. (60 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <title>A Wolf In Sheep?s Clothing</title>
    <desc>An expos? of the lies and deception spun by 60's radical, Saul Alinsky. His political tactics and theories espoused social justice, but carried an agenda that threatened core beliefs of Christianity and the Church. (90 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>21 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
