<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <id>AandE.ca</id>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A look at some of the wildest courtroom moments; a judge takes a bullet and fires back; a defendant tries to charm his way out of jail; a woman provides testimony to send her boyfriend to prison for life.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <id>AandE.ca</id>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>The courtroom erupts into chaos during a hearing for a murder case; the judge chastises a defendant for making horrible decisions; a prosecutor strongly disagrees with what he feels is an unreasonable sentence from the judge.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <id>AandE.ca</id>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A judge loses his job when his temper gets the best of him; a standard security check gets physical; a father gains national attention through an unforgettable act of forgiveness.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <id>AandE.ca</id>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>An actor tells the judge that make-up is to blame for his failed alcohol test; a man charged with assault is not happy with his lawyer; the family of a fatal highway accident victim is not happy when the judge sentences the driver to probation.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28131919_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <id>AandE.ca</id>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A quiet Michigan courtroom erupts into an all-out melee; a pro-pot defendant lights up right in front of a judge; a tension-filled husband and wife murder trial ends with a shocking verdict.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <id>AandE.ca</id>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A teen impersonating a cop takes the law into his own hands; family members of a murdered woman seek revenge in the courtroom; a high-speed chase ends with a heated court appearance.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <id>AandE.ca</id>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>Family members of defendants and victims erupt in a Florida courthouse; a murderer has a shocking courtroom outburst; an adoption brings a judge to tears.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <id>AandE.ca</id>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A family attempts revenge on a killer; a wanted felon stops at nothing to evade police; a drunken driver pays a steep price for her shocking courtroom behavior.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <id>AandE.ca</id>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>An exchange of bullets at a suburban home ends with a dramatic courtroom exchange; a surprise performance by a man accused of attempted murder fails to impress the judge; hunger strikes, outrageous claims and shocking behavior in court from a killer; and more.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>17 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <id>AandE.ca</id>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A brawl breaks out between supporters of both the victim and the defendant at a sentencing hearing; a man refuses to cooperate at his plea hearing; a 56-year-old defendant asks his mother to explain why he can't pay his court costs and fines.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28131919_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>18 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>A&amp;E CA</name>
    <id>AandE.ca</id>
    <title>Court Cam</title>
    <desc>A look at some of the wildest courtroom moments; a Massachusetts courtroom erupts in a storm of fists and f-bombs; a judge pays the price for her outrageous behavior; a doctor appears for a hearing via Zoom during surgery.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p17612551_b_h8_aw.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>18 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
