<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC One NL</name>
    <id>BBCOne.nl</id>
    <title>Stranded on Honeymoon Island</title>
    <desc>A mysterious crate sweeps ashore to help the honeymooners get better acquainted. Tensions spill over at the first Couples' Cove, before Davina delivers a dilemma that could change one pair's fate forever.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p31003400_e_h10_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:10AM</start>
    <finish>01:10AM</finish>
    <date>10 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Parliament UK</name>
    <id>BBCParliament.uk</id>
    <title>House of Lords</title>
    <desc>Business in the House of Lords on Tuesday 9 September.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:45AM</start>
    <finish>01:45AM</finish>
    <date>10 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>BBC Two NL</name>
    <id>BBCTwo.nl</id>
    <title>Clemency</title>
    <desc>Bernadine Williams is a prison warden who, over the years, has been drifting away from her husband while dutifully carrying out executions in a maximum security prison. When she strikes up a unique bond with death-row inmate Anthony Woods, a layer of emotional skin is peeled back, forcing Bernadine to confront the complex-and often contradictory-relationship between good intentions, unrequited desires, and what it means to be sanctioned to kill.</desc>
    <image>https://staticqbr-nl-prod.prod.cdn.dmdsdp.com/image-service/ImagesEPG/EventImages/p16875318_bd_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:45AM</finish>
    <date>10 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Band Sports BR</name>
    <id>BandSports.br</id>
    <title>Encontro de Craques</title>
    <desc></desc>
    <image>https://cdn.mitvstatic.com/programs/br_sports-talk-encontro-de-craques_l_m.jpg</image>
    <start>12:15AM</start>
    <finish>01:15AM</finish>
    <date>10 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>CBBC UK</name>
    <id>CBBC.uk</id>
    <title>Shark Bites</title>
    <desc>Steve Backshall meets the most sinister shark in our seas. The ragged tooth shark has a mouth that's overflowing with terrifying teeth. But why does it need such gnarly gnashers? Steve heads out on a dive after dark to see these fearsome fangs for himself, before revealing their sinister secret in his shark lab.</desc>
    <image>https://img.freeviewplay.tv/p1ff2226cfdb7e138bed614be556ea724</image>
    <start>06:50PM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>09 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>TV 5 Monde F-Be-Ch Fr</name>
    <id>TV5Monde.fr</id>
    <title>Bellefond</title>
    <desc>Mathilde Duprieur, propri?taire du Cocoon, un restaurant de plage, est accus?e du meurtre de Lionel, son mari. Elle fait appel ? Bellefond qui d?couvre que le commandant Philippe Vasquez, un ami de longue date, est en charge de l'affaire.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p24486627_b_h10_ac.jpg</image>
    <start>12:27AM</start>
    <finish>02:02AM</finish>
    <date>10 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>