<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Interrogations by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>A mother is in trouble when a furniture removal crew makes a horrific discovery in her freezer.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28173912_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>Woman laughs at police and strikes a few yoga poses after they arrest her.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>Police arrests a woman for alleged assault; she reportedly bites, kicks and spits at officers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A man caught urinating in public gets into a lengthy scuffle with police; car thief claims a crack addict let him borrow a car; police obtain vague details from bar patrons involved in a fight; a couple seeks help.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A criminal lectures officers on how the law works; a mother chastises her daughter after she is caught with drugs; a suicidal man claims to be just looking for attention; a father takes the fall for his son's drugs.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police intervene on a chase between a car thief and the owner of the stolen vehicle; a manic pot grower goes in circles with police until he collapses; police investigate an assault on a homeless man.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police detain a robbery suspect responsible for holding a woman at gunpoint; a car chase suspect hits a dead end; a shaved down key proves a car thief's guilt; police caution a drug suspect on her lifestyle choices.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Ecstasy dealers get a bad deal from undercover officers; a DUI suspect fails several field sobriety tests; police mediate a dispute between a couple over a dent in a wall; police arrest a man stalking his ex-wife and kids.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A car chase suspect rides his tires down to the metal; an intoxicated mother is taken away from her newborn; a woman files false kidnapping charges on her boyfriend; police see through the holes of a young man's story.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police perform an undercover sting on a woman plotting to make a hit on her husband.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A drug suspect has part of his ear torn off by a K-9; a woman accepts her newly arrested boyfriend's marriage proposal; police break up a meth production; a worried wife wants to know if her husband is cooking meth.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A hit and run suspect complains to officers; a woman accuses her boyfriend of turning her house into a drug den; a house burglar is caught trying to steal copper wire from an abandoned home; a prostitute is arrested.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police question two men idling in their cars; a car thief is arrested for an elaborate ploy involving erotic photography to steal a woman's car; a mother brings her child to a drug exchange at a raided crack house.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Officers drive over a spike strip meant for their chase suspects; border patrol tracks an illegal alien into San Diego; a transgender is arrested for a stabbing; a supposed car thief's credibility is dismissed.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A drug suspect denies ownership of both his pants and his drugs; police bust a prostitute for the seventh time,;an ex-convict's parole goes up in smoke when he is caught with drug paraphernalia; a bar patron is arrested.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>An bicyclist tries to outrun police but hits a dead end; a prostitute on the strip claims to be going to dinner at 2 a.m.; a meth addict rambles to police about how he's being chased; two drug suspects get arrested.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A car thief runs the course with officers in a flatbed truck; a mother and daughter spar over a man they've both dated; a father gets a busted jaw for bullying his son.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police arrest three smash and grab suspects; a drug dealer's sob story touches police; a suspect is arrested for using his pain pill prescription to make a few extra bucks; police catch a drug suspect.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A drunk driver takes officers for a spin; a sting operation sniffs out several drug dealers; a chase suspect thanks an officer for not shooting him; police reason with an abuse suspect to come down from the roof.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A team of officers struggle to restrain a wild suspect; an officer nearly shoots a driver over a pellet gun; police thwart burglars' attempts to steal a projector; two road rage suspects are arrested.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police launch a search for a robbery suspect; a driver begs his passengers to take the rap for his drug charges; a driver is arrested for nearly running over her friend; several women get their stories mixed up.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police apprehend a robbery suspect twice; a prostitute begs her mom to take her to rehab as she is arrested; a female assault victim picks a fight with officers; two female neighbors quarrel over a slashed tire.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Officers search a car laced with cocaine and money; a homeless man is found residing in a house, hording the deceased owner's rare jewelry; a prostitute explains her stolen truck was exchanged for services rendered.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>An armed drug dealer flees from police; police track prostitutes stealing from men; a couple is arrested for public sex; a car thief has plenty of surprises for officers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A prostitute puts up a vicious fight with officers; a kid with a mohawk turns out to not be such a tough guy; after drugs are found in her car, a naked woman has a meltdown defending her innocence; four men are arrested.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A car thief claims he could not have stolen his car because he has the keys; a group of men &quot;throwing dice&quot;; two brothers sparring over unemployment; an intoxicated woman.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A reckless driver explains that the sheriff still has his license; a driver uses his passenger to hide drugs; a couple tries to steal a cop car; a traffic stop.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A drug suspect who claims to have been unaware she was fighting police; a hitchhiker tries to hide what is in her pants; a man hiding in his neighbor's marijuana filled backyard; a car thief and a crossdresser.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A chase suspect worth 1.5 million gives police a run for their money; a driver's fingerprints turn up two identities; a drunk driver is unaware her vehicle is missing a tire; a juvenile is arrested for assaulting a prostitute.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A chase suspect tries to play dead after crashing through a gas station; two suspects scramble to dispose of their drugs before police catch them; an inebriated driver is worn out by his drug and female problems.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Officers go undercover to catch an ecstasy dealer; people are questioned after allegedly getting run over by a car; a driver is pulled over and tries to destroy evidence.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>12:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>An officer breaks up a street fight; a jaywalker flees when police try to identify him; a parked cars occupants are arrested for prostitution.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Officers serve a warrant for unpaid child support; a woman is arrested for domestic violence; drugs and a firearm are discovered during a traffic stop.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>01:30AM</start>
    <finish>02:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A suspect tries to evade police on foot; an officer issues a citation for an illegal U-turn; police find drug related materials in a vehicle.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police find suspects threatening victims at gunpoint; a man pulled over has a suspended license; suspects crash their car after evading police.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>02:30AM</start>
    <finish>03:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police chase a man who runs a red light; police try to capture a twelve foot python; a registered sex offender is arrested.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>03:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A drunken driver crashes into a ditch; police investigate a hit and run; a driver throws a suspicious object out his window.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>03:30AM</start>
    <finish>04:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police escort a bar patron out; officers convene on a suspect on a motorcycle; a woman finds her missing dog with new owners; a parolee is arrested.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00AM</start>
    <finish>04:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A crowd gathers to see a man attack his ex-wife; a man tries to hide drugs in his mouth; a suspect assaults police officers.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>04:30AM</start>
    <finish>05:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Officers break up a fight outside of a nightclub; a domestic disturbance between two brothers is investigated; a car accident is investigated that may be the result of drunken driving; police find marijuana in a car.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00AM</start>
    <finish>05:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Officers chase a stolen vehicle; police arrest a woman in a parking lot after discovering a warrant for her arrest; young boys throw rocks off of an overpass.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>05:30AM</start>
    <finish>06:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Deputies confront a man suspected of shooting a gun in his yard; an officer follows a stolen vehicle to capture a suspect; police handle a domestic disturbance at a restaurant.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>06:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A suspect tries to evade police; an officer questions a man suspected of burglarizing vehicles; two women get into a fight over a vehicle title; officers pursue a man in a stolen car.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>06:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A suspect runs into a tree while being questioned; undercover officers bust up a drug transaction; a driver loses control of his vehicle while fleeing police.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Cops come to arrest and man for drug possession but he takes off running; cops stop to check up on a car sitting on the side of the road.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police arrest a woman for stealing the vehicle she's driving; a man shoots a bicyclist; officers bust up a drug deal.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A suspect flees a traffic stop; police respond to a domestic disturbance call; officers use force to stop a vehicle.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>Police arrest a man for prostitution and narcotics; a man is suspected of domestic violence; a man walking down a street with a shotgun is arrested.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A suspect leads police on a car chase; officers respond to a neighborhood feud; officers arrest men who are hiding weapons and drugs in their home; a women is arrested for drug possession.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A man out of jail on bond is arrested for drug possession; a young man gets disorderly conduct after waving around a BB gun; a man is arrested for DUI.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>Cops Reloaded</title>
    <desc>A man tries to flee police on foot; a woman hits a motorcycle and gets a DUI; a man is arrested for vehicle theft and grand larceny.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p11953512_b_h8_aa.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>Police discovers a family that has been executed after a teenager confesses to the murder.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>A Florida woman is arrested after taking off from a traffic stop and abandoning her car.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>Grandma shoots intruder while handcuffed to chair during robbery.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>Florida mom kidnaps daughter, leading police on a high-speed chase.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>Man realizes he stole a police bait car.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>New Mexico police arrest a lone criminal, reminiscent of Clyde.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>Deputies respond to a call in a store after staff catches a woman peeling and swapping price tags of several items.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>Sheriffs son learns why hes not untouchable.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>Ohio woman tased after allegedly ramming cop cars.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>Police struggle with a drunk man on a scooter in a Walmart.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>08:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>A Florida mother is arrested after allegedly attempting to sell her baby for $500.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>10:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>A drunk Karen unleashes a full-blown racist rant during a disturbing incident at the Holiday Inn.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>Police arrest a mom after allegedly leaving her four-year-old son home alone while she gets cosmetic surgery.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>12:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Law &amp; Crime US</name>
    <title>BodyCam by Law&amp;Crime</title>
    <desc>A drunken cowboy is apprehended by police twice in one week.</desc>
    <image>http://dshm.tmsimg.com/assets/p28078876_b_h8_ab.jpg</image>
    <start>12:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>09 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
