<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <id>EWTNAfricaAsia.za</id>
    <title>&lt;span Class=&quot; Theme Emphasis&quot;&gt;new!&lt;/span&gt; Ewtn Pro Life Weekly</title>
    <desc>EWTN Pro-Life Weekly is a half-hour news and commentary program that covers life issues including abortion, assisted suicide, in vitro fertilization, highlighting the mercy of a culture of life, from a Catholic perspective. This program features interviews, analysis, and actionable steps for viewers to defend the dignity of every human person from conception to natural death. Hosted by Abigail Galv?n. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:30AM</finish>
    <date>31 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <id>EWTNAfricaAsia.za</id>
    <title>Ewtn Great Britain On Location</title>
    <desc>Fr. Armand de Malleray explains his mission to strengthen Catholic identity and bring Catholic families closer to the faith. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <id>EWTNAfricaAsia.za</id>
    <title>In Concert: Religions United In Music</title>
    <desc>The Jerusalem Symphony Orchestra performs to honor the 30th Anniversary of diplomatic relations between the Holy See and Israel, and the reconstruction of the Basilica of St. Paul. (70 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:10AM</finish>
    <date>31 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <id>EWTNAfricaAsia.za</id>
    <title>A Journey With Carlo</title>
    <desc>The impact of Blessed Carlo Acutis is felt in the lives of the young people who knew him well. Hear the first-hand accounts from friends and family who paint a poignant picture of this remarkable young man. (20 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:10AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>31 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <id>EWTNAfricaAsia.za</id>
    <title>Mission To Educate</title>
    <desc>A history of the Catholic education system in St. Louis, which earned the nickname the ?Rome of the West? after religious communities began flocking to the city to help teach. (60 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>31 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <id>EWTNAfricaAsia.za</id>
    <title>The Long Road Of Fr. Domenico From Cese To Turin</title>
    <desc>Paul Badde goes on-location throughout Italy to tell the life story of Fr. Domenico da Cese, a close friend of St. Padre Pio. (30 minutes).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>31 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>EWTN ZA</name>
    <id>EWTNAfricaAsia.za</id>
    <title>Global Divine Mercy Chaplet</title>
    <desc>Children from around the world pray the Chaplet of Divine Mercy. (30 minutes).[(96057)] </desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>31 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
