<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Battleship</title>
    <desc>A fleet of ships is forced to do battle with an armada of unknown origins in order to discover and thwart their destructive goals.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Into The Blue 2: The Reef</title>
    <desc>Scuba diver Sebastian and his aspiring treasure hunter girlfriend are hired by a jet-setting European couple to retrieve sunken treasure - but the Europeans are actually terrorists targeting Pearl Harbour. (Chris Carmack, Laura Vandervoort).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Stompem Ground 2022 - Pigram Brothers</title>
    <desc>The iconic Broome band, Pigram Brothers a selection on their finest tracks for the epic Stompem Ground event in 2022.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:50PM</start>
    <finish>03:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Rage Guest Programmer</title>
    <desc>Australia's longest running music TV show, rage is home to the biggest vault of music videos from a diverse range of artists, genres and eras. Guest programmers curate an all-night playlist of their all-time favourite clips.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/LR2505H.jpg</image>
    <start>02:51PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Rage</title>
    <desc>Australia's longest running music TV show, rage is home to the biggest vault of music videos from a diverse range of artists, genres and eras. We curate the best clips of all time to surprise and entertain you for hours.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/LR2510H.jpg</image>
    <start>02:56PM</start>
    <finish>03:58PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Roland Garros 2025 - French Open Tennis Late</title>
    <desc>Wide World of Sports presents Roland Garros 2025 brought to you live from Paris. Join our all-star team including Todd Woodbridge and Jelena Dokic for all the action live and free. Live play continues.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Originals</title>
    <desc>Old wounds are re-opened when Elijah and Marcel are forced into an uneasy alliance. Together, they meet with Alaric who has tracked down a crucial artifact that could help in their fight against The Hollow.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Indonesian News</title>
    <desc>News via satellite from TVRI Jakarta Indonesia, in Indonesian, no subtitles.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>48 Hours</title>
    <desc>After a young mother is murdered, her son unknowingly hangs the killer's photo on his wall. 48 Hours contributor Jim Axelrod reports.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The 355</title>
    <desc>When a top-secret weapon falls into mercenary hands, wild card CIA agent Mason \&quot;Mace\&quot; Brown will need to join forces with rival German agent Marie, former MI6 ally and cutting-edge computer specialist Khadijah and skilled Colombian psychologist Graciela on a lethal, breakneck mission to retrieve it.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Good Game Spawn Point</title>
    <desc>This week on GGSP, we investigate how many rubber chickens Detective Pikachu Returns deserves, plus Mollie &amp; Reggie from Gardening Australia Junior join the Spawn Squad, and Granny Gem gives some sage advice!</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/CH2263H.jpg</image>
    <start>03:29PM</start>
    <finish>03:53PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Keeping Up With The Kardashians</title>
    <desc>When Tristan realizes that Khloe is stressed about her living situation, he takes steps to make her feel more comfortable.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Yorkshire Vet</title>
    <desc>Julian heads over to see alpaca lover Jackie Barlow, because of a large lump.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>House Hunters</title>
    <desc>An airline pilot and his wife look to upsize into a home where they can host family and future grandchildren in Greer, South Carolina. She wants a classic-looking home no matter the cost, but he's worried she'll break the bank.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Home Shopping</title>
    <desc>Synopsis.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Pawn Stars</title>
    <desc>Saddle up with the Pawn Stars when a customer brings in a bible believed to have been carried by Pony Express riders.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Flying Wild Alaska</title>
    <desc>John Ponts fights turbulence and passengers on a flight; Jim and Ferno leave the pilots in charge of the terminal and Sarah's rescue flight turns into a battle for survival.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Rocket Power</title>
    <desc>The Rocket Power gang returns to Hawaii with Noelani and her mother for the wedding preparations. But the wedding date conflicts with the opening of the highly-anticipated Zero Gravity Zone skatepark.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Be My Guest With Ina Garten</title>
    <desc>Ina has long dreamt of meeting incredible award-winning actress Julianna Margulies who's coming to East Hampton for amazing conversation, epic cooking and a sprinkling of the unexpected.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:30PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Attica</title>
    <desc>Drawing on the experiences and recollections of those who were there, Stanley Nelson's documentary tells the story of the famous prison rebellion on its 50th anniversary. In the fall of 1971, tensions between inmates and guards at the Attica Correctional Facility are at an all-time high. On the morning of September 9, it all comes to a head when inmates erupt into one of the largest U.S. prison riots ever witnessed.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Honeymoon</title>
    <desc>A romantic comedy about an American GI with a three day pass who misses his fiancee in Mexico for their wedding.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Suspect</title>
    <desc>Bruised by his encounter with Nicola, Danny goes to The Crimson Orchid gentlemen's club to look for Maia, who Nicola has accused of corrupting Christina. Maia stonewalls his questions, but when he tells her Christina may have been murdered, her fa\u00e7ade of indifference cracks. Danny learns Christina was selling drugs.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Media Watch</title>
    <desc>It's the show everybody loves until they're on it. Sitting in the hot seat is new host Linton Besser, a four-time Walkley award-winning investigative reporter and former foreign correspondent.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/FA2435H.jpg</image>
    <start>03:37PM</start>
    <finish>03:59PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
