<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>War With Grandpa</title>
    <desc>Upset that he has to share the room he loves with his grandfather, Peter decides to declare war in an attempt to get it back. (Robert De Niro, Uma Thurman, Rob Riggle).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Racenight Live: Sha Tin</title>
    <desc>Hong Kong thoroughbred twilight racing from Sha Tin Hong Kong.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Charade</title>
    <desc>Romance and suspense ensue in Paris as a woman (Audrey Hepburn) is pursued by several men who are after the fortune her murdered husband stole. She seeks help from a charming stranger named Peter (Cary Grant) but gets embroiled in a world of lies when she discovers he may not be who he claims to be. Directed by Peter Stone.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>James Martin's French Adventure</title>
    <desc>James's journey though France leads him to the glamour of St. Tropez. He starts by exploring the fantastic seafood market, then cooks sole goujons with tartare sauce.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Wheeler Dealers</title>
    <desc>Mike becomes an owner of an Isetta bubble car. Part car, part motorbike, this icon may be great to drive, but it's not so fun to repair. Can Edd convince this little car to come back to life and make a profit?</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Dogs Behaving (very) Badly</title>
    <desc>A German Shepherd is a real diva and goes crazy at a traffic signal, a terrier bullies his owner's partner at every opportunity and a patterjack hates all housework items.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Million Dollar Listing: La</title>
    <desc>Josh Flagg pops the big question to his beau in true style. James and David take on a Beverly Hills home that's been on the market for over 800 days with no buyer in sight.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>SBS World News</title>
    <desc>Latest reports and analysis of major national and international news of the day from Australia's only world news service.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Sunday Night Jewellery With Suzie And Lee!</title>
    <desc>Join Suzie and Lee for Sunday Night Jewellery, where stunning designs and dazzling gems take centre stage. Discover exclusive pieces, expert insights, and timeless elegance in this sparkling showcase.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Abandoned Engineering</title>
    <desc>The honeymoon home of a future queen, crumbling ruins from an evil empire, and a once thriving industrial complex shattered by a ruthless ruler. Within these decaying structures are the echoes of history.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>ABC National News</title>
    <desc>There's never been a more important time for transparency and trust. ABC News brings you the day's top stories and latest news with more reporters to tell you what's going on and why it matters. Presented by Meredith Sheehan.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/NU2525H.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Great Lakes Wild</title>
    <desc>Great Lakes Wild takes you on an adventure with the majestic animals that live on the shores of the Great Lakes.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Lego Masters Grand Masters Of The Galaxy</title>
    <desc>10 teams from around the world compete in this season's replicate challenge, re-creating items from a Regional Chinese themed Restaurant, featuring this season's first elimination.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Vicar Of Dibley</title>
    <desc>Romance is in the air as Geraldine becomes Cupid, attempting to bring together the desperately shy Alice and the even more shy Hugo, and it's an operation that makes the Normandy Landings seem simple.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The 1% Club</title>
    <desc>The 1% Club is a game show like no other! Unlike most quizzes, they don't need to brush up on general knowledge to do well. All they need is logic and common sense. Hosted by comedian Jim Jefferies.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Urdu News</title>
    <desc>News via satellite from PTV Islamabad Pakistan, in Urdu, no subtitles.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <desc>Hawkeye flees to the front with an archenemy to avoid a 'surprise' birthday party.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>House Hunters International</title>
    <desc>A single mom decides that her teenage daughter is old enough to uproot from Jamaica to Merida, Mexico. She has big dreams of exploring a new culture and growing her travel vlog, but finding a place downtown that's in her budget may tough.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>AFL</title>
    <desc>The Blues take on the Bombers, live and free from the MCG. Bounce time: 7:20pm AEST.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>ABC News</title>
    <desc>News from where we live. ABC News NSW brings you the day's top stories, exclusive investigations and original reporting on the issues that matter to you. Presented by Jeremy Fernandez.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/NU2501H.jpg</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:32AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Hard Quiz</title>
    <desc>Tom Gleeson isn't afraid to keep asking questions until someone hoists a Big Brass Mug. His contestants tackle the Australian Constitution, venomous snakes, the Mitford Sisters, and the Marvel Cinematic Universe!</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:05AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Bluey</title>
    <desc>Dad thinks the kids have too many toys and suggests a chuck out. To save their beloved Mr Monkey jocks from getting the chop, Bluey and Bingo must prove he is special.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/CH1903Q031S00.jpg</image>
    <start>10:20AM</start>
    <finish>10:29AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
