<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Dw English News</title>
    <desc>News and analysis of the top international and European news and current affairs from Berlin, in English.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>A player is bludgeoned to death on the fairway at an exclusive local golf club. Barnaby and Jones uncover a world of intense snobbery, illicit gambling and a history of unreported assaults.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:52PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Rage</title>
    <desc>Australia's longest running music TV show, rage is home to the biggest vault of music videos from a diverse range of artists, genres and eras. We curate the best clips of all time to surprise and entertain you for hours.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/LR2508H.jpg</image>
    <start>05:07PM</start>
    <finish>06:40PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Goblin Works Garage</title>
    <desc>The team work on a motorsport legend, the Ford Escort Mk2 rally car. When Jimmy finds a rust-free South African import, they take this custom build sideways.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Botched</title>
    <desc>A Cartel Crew bombshell who can't keep fat in her booty seeks advice from Dr. Dubrow.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Elizabeth Grant Beauty Est. 1958</title>
    <desc>Transform your skincare routine with Elizabeth Grant Beauty, a trusted name since 1958. Rejuvenate even the most damaged skin and experience the transformation today.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Supernatural</title>
    <desc>The Winchesters hunt down Cupid on Valentine's Day.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:35PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Body Of Proof</title>
    <desc>In conclusion of the thrilling Season 3 premiere, Megan learns why a serial killer targeted war veterans and just how one of their prime suspects figures in the case. But the killer has kidnapped Megan\u2019s daughter and is making sure that, now that Megan has cracked the case, she cannot reveal the answers to her team or the police while Lacey\u2019s life hangs in the balance. Meanwhile, Kate comes under fire with District Attorney Dan Russell.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:45PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Nitv On The Road: Yabun</title>
    <desc>From our travelling music series, NITV showcases veterans and newcomers alike as they perform on the Yabun stage at Victoria Park, Sydney.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>World's Wildest Police Videos</title>
    <desc>Buckle up for another California chase! This episode features a determined pursuit targeting a high-profile drug dealer.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>No Demo Reno</title>
    <desc>A couple asks Jenn to revitalise their outdated family home which contains, among other challenges, the most unusual bathroom she's ever seen. Next, Jenn works with a family whose home has lots of space but no personality.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Mixed Garden</title>
    <desc>Home &amp; Garden Care Innovations - See How Our Range Of As Seen on TV Products Will Help To Take The Hassle Out Of Cleaning And Maintaining Your Garden, Your Outdoor Spaces, In And Around Your Home And Even Your Vehicles, Boats And More!</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Better Homes And Gardens</title>
    <desc>Joh and Karen visit the sustainable Daylesford Longhouse. Melissa helps spruce up your garden. Fast Ed cooks up some chilli caramel chicken wings.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:00PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The World</title>
    <desc>There's never been a more important time to stay in touch with what's happening in our world. Weeknights at 9pm AEST, Girish Sawlani presents the latest international news from correspondents and interviews with guests.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/NC2508V.jpg</image>
    <start>06:02PM</start>
    <finish>06:59PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Raceday Review - Sandown</title>
    <desc>A full recap of racing from Sandown - Wednesday 4th June 2025.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:45PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Kamp Koral: Spongebob's Under Years</title>
    <desc>When Kamp Koral's mascot competition heats up, SpongeBob and Patrick's friendship is tested like never before. / A prideful bet forces Squidward and Krabs to play through a dangerous golf course.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:15PM</start>
    <finish>06:40PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Malory Towers</title>
    <desc>Matron Shipley arrives back unexpectedly and is horrified to learn that there is an imposter in the San! It's not long before Darrell and Sally uncover the surprising truth about the mysterious Nurse Jane...</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW4123A013S00.jpg</image>
    <start>06:21PM</start>
    <finish>06:49PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
