<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Live: Swan Hill/edenhope/port Augusta</title>
    <desc>Victorian thoroughbred racing from Swan Hill Cup Day. Victorian racing from Edenhope. South Australian racing from Port Augusta.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Live: NRL Sunday Footy</title>
    <desc>Wide World of Sports presents Wests Tigers v Panthers, live from CommBank Stadium. Join our expert commentary team for all the action, analysis and post match interviews. Kick off at 4:05PM AEST.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Courage Mountain</title>
    <desc>Heidi is a teenager when she's sent off to an Italian boarding school at the outbreak of WWI. When the school falls to the Germans, she escapes her captors and flees through the war-torn countryside.    (Leslie Caron, Juliette Caton, Charlie Sheen).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:05AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Better Homes And Gardens</title>
    <desc>Joh catches up with award-winning chef Josh Niland. Dr Harry is meeting a member of the Riverina Light Horse troop. Melissa shows you a DIY water fountain that's as simple as one, two, three!</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Escape To The Country</title>
    <desc>Nicki Chapman helps a campervan loving couple with 400,000-pounds find a perfect rural property within range of the Peak District.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Attack On The Iron Coast</title>
    <desc>Lloyd Bridges plays a WWII commando who leads a group of soldiers on a suicide mission to destroy a Nazi naval stronghold on the French coast. (Andrew Keir, Sue Lloyd).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Going Places With Ernie Dingo</title>
    <desc>Guest host Aaron Fa'aoso takes a trip into the abundant Granite Belt where he conquers a mountain with a ranger, visits a family-owned apple orchard and catches up with music legend Kev Carmody.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Close Encounters Down Under</title>
    <desc>We travel to Queensland\u2019s tropical coast to hear first-hand encounters of flying saucers landing in lush banana plantations to UFO encounters in Queensland\u2019s sugar cane fields.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Landline</title>
    <desc>Hosted by award-winning journalist Pip Courtney, Landline is Australia's only national agricultural television program covering stories from Australia's rural and regional heartland.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/RF2404Q.jpg</image>
    <start>07:01AM</start>
    <finish>07:59AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Point</title>
    <desc>Pat Turner has had an illustrious career in the public service. Now in the wake of the 2025 Federal Election she speaks to Karla Grant about how she plans to keep on fighting for First Nations people.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:20AM</start>
    <finish>08:20AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Emperor's Club</title>
    <desc>William Hundert (Kevin Kline) is a passionate and principled Classics professor who finds his tightly-controlled world shaken and inexorably altered when a new student, Sedgewick Bell (Emile Hirsch), walks into his classroom. What begins as a fierce battle of wills gives way to a close student-teacher relationship, but results in a life lesson for Hundert that will still haunt him a quarter of a century later.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Maltese News</title>
    <desc>News from PBS Malta with the latest updates from the Maltese Islands and beyond. Streamed to SBS from Valletta, Malta, in Maltese, no subtitles.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Salvage Hunters</title>
    <desc>In Gloucestershire, Drew finds a huge horse's head with a dealer specialising in sculptures. And, in Somerset he spots a valuable Persian rug lining a chicken shed.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Escape To The Chateau</title>
    <desc>An astonishing part of the chateau is revealed for the first time. While Dick is keen to use the space for storage, Angel's vision is to create a celestial-inspired 'sky bar'.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Carla Oates The Beauty Chef</title>
    <desc>Watch Carla in the kitchen whipping up certified organic and naturally fermented superfood blends - a powerhouse of nutrients and healthy bacteria. Beauty begins in the belly for radiant skin.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Baking It</title>
    <desc>Maya Rudolph and Amy Poehler welcome new teams of home bakers to the cabin, starting things off with a bang by asking the bakers to recreate a cake that just exploded.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Judge Jerry</title>
    <desc>Ventriloquist Comedian April is suing Vegas Room Production Manager, George, for a performance fee her puppet May never received.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Jeopardy!</title>
    <desc>Ken Jennings hosts Jeopardy! Where the answers are revealed and the contestants must guess the appropriate questions.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:30AM</start>
    <finish>07:55AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Masters Of Taste With Gary Mehigan</title>
    <desc>Gary visits one of India's best restaurants, Indian Accent, and checks out their signature Chef\u2019s Tasting Menu. Later, he hangs out with the boys from AIB, and shows how to whip up a Salmon Slider. They return the favour by cooking Gary a very spicy omelette.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:35AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Mythbusters</title>
    <desc>Seth Rogen joins the MythBusters for two blockbusting stories from his film, The Green Hornet: Elevator Car Cut and Explosive Escape.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:39AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Walking With Dinosaurs</title>
    <desc>An orphaned baby Triceratops, must outwit a deadly T-Rex. Today, palaeontologists are uncovering her remains, allowing us to bring her story to life with stunning VFX.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW4459A001S00.jpg</image>
    <start>07:40AM</start>
    <finish>08:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Gardening Australia Junior</title>
    <desc>Hannah works with two brothers to create a garden that delights all of the senses. Alfie is vision impaired and loves being active and playing, so they create a garden of games he can enjoy with his brother, William.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/CH2323H020S00.jpg</image>
    <start>07:48AM</start>
    <finish>08:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
