<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Racenight Live: Sha Tin</title>
    <desc>Hong Kong thoroughbred twilight racing from Sha Tin Hong Kong.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Charade</title>
    <desc>Romance and suspense ensue in Paris as a woman (Audrey Hepburn) is pursued by several men who are after the fortune her murdered husband stole. She seeks help from a charming stranger named Peter (Cary Grant) but gets embroiled in a world of lies when she discovers he may not be who he claims to be. Directed by Peter Stone.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Lego Masters Grand Masters Of The Galaxy</title>
    <desc>10 teams from around the world compete in this season's replicate challenge, re-creating items from a Regional Chinese themed Restaurant, featuring this season's first elimination.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:40AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Vicar Of Dibley</title>
    <desc>Romance is in the air as Geraldine becomes Cupid, attempting to bring together the desperately shy Alice and the even more shy Hugo, and it's an operation that makes the Normandy Landings seem simple.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:50AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The 1% Club</title>
    <desc>The 1% Club is a game show like no other! Unlike most quizzes, they don't need to brush up on general knowledge to do well. All they need is logic and common sense. Hosted by comedian Jim Jefferies.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>AFL</title>
    <desc>The Blues take on the Bombers, live and free from the MCG. Bounce time: 7:20pm AEST.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>01:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Law &amp; Order: Criminal Intent</title>
    <desc>When a pharmaceutical executive is found cut in half in midtown, Detectives Goren and Eames discover a greater crime when they learn that the victim was part of a scheme to ship tainted blood medications to Thailand for huge profits - and the case takes a new spin with the sexual proclivity of one of the dead man's associates. The police probe deeper and pull the lid off a Pandora's box of craven corporate corruption in the competitive field of high-profit pharmaceuticals.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Our Medicine</title>
    <desc>Paramedics Richard and Wade care for a neighbour in Yarrabah, while Nathan prepares for a kidney transplant. Our Medicine reveals the vital role of First Nations-led care across Australia.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Korean News</title>
    <desc>News via satellite from YTN Seoul Korea, in Korean, no subtitles.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Insiders</title>
    <desc>Start your Sunday morning with the show the politicians rely on to find out what's going on. David Speers presents Australia's must-watch political program, joined by a panel of the best political analysts and commentators.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/NC2505C.jpg</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Ancient Aliens</title>
    <desc>Erich Von Daniken's book, Chariots of the Gods?, claims that aliens came to the Earth in the past. Half a century after the book was released, some believe that his claims could be proven correct.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>12:30PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Botched</title>
    <desc>Daniella Mendez wants an implant with male and female options.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>London: 2,000 Years Of History</title>
    <desc>Dan Jones, Suzannah Lipscomb, and Rob Bell conclude the series by examining London in the 20th century, including the creation of the world's first underground rail network. This documentary examines the impact of both World wars and a Spanish flu pandemic on the city, as well as the marketing campaign that tempted millions to relocate to London's vast suburbia.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:25AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Cook Clever Waste Less With Prue &amp; Rupy</title>
    <desc>Culinary legend and queen of leftovers Prue Leith teams up with food expert Dr Rupy Aujla to help British families tackle food waste and save money.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Elvis</title>
    <desc>The life of American music icon Elvis Presley, from his childhood to becoming a rock and movie star in the 1950s while maintaining a complex relationship with his manager, Colonel Tom Parker. (Austin Butler, Tom Hanks, Olivia DeJonge).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>M*A*S*H</title>
    <desc>Klinger grows desperate to return home when his effort to bring a touch of Toledo to the unit fails.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Home Town</title>
    <desc>Erin's friend and former bandmate is recently divorced and needs to make a new start in his old home. Ben and Erin transform his spartan bachelor pad into the moody, customized house he always dreamed of.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Charlie Bears Collectables</title>
    <desc>From Yorkshire to Cornwall. Charlie Bears are  handcrafted with love in the UK. Each bear has a unique personality and a huggable design. Discover your new furry affectionate friend from TVSN.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:30AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Piano</title>
    <desc>Our very special concert is here! Mentored by Harry Connick, Jr. and Andrea Lam, each of our fabulous five were selected because they represent the sheer power of the piano. (Final).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:32AM</start>
    <finish>11:33AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Abandoned Engineering</title>
    <desc>Explore the vestiges of ambitious wonderlands, bizarre technologies, relics of ancient societies, and the ruins of conflict and war.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>QI</title>
    <desc>Sandi Toksvig quarrels with Jason Manford, Aisling Bea, Anuvab Pal and Alan Davies.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW2109A003S00_460.jpg</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:05AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Moominvalley</title>
    <desc>Moomintroll wants to try to stand on his own two feet and moves into his own place with Snorkmaiden. But is Moomintroll ready to give up the care and comfort of Moominamma and Moominpappa?</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:38AM</start>
    <finish>11:01AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
