<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Mixed Garden</title>
    <desc>Home &amp; Garden Care Innovations - See How Our Range Of As Seen on TV Products Will Help To Take The Hassle Out Of Cleaning And Maintaining Your Garden, Your Outdoor Spaces, In And Around Your Home And Even Your Vehicles, Boats And More!</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Bondi Vet</title>
    <desc>Chris heads to Victoria in response to an SOS from a young volunteer at Safe Haven Horse rescue. 11-year-old Tash has fallen in love with a surrendered appaloosa gelding, Charlie. Tash is worried about a huge lump growing on Charlie\u2019s eye and she\u2019s hoping Chris can save her much loved Charlie.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>9News</title>
    <desc>Join 9News for the latest in news and events that affect you in your local city, as well as news from across Australia and the world.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>ABC News Hour</title>
    <desc>Stay in the know with Australia's trusted news source. From your neighbourhood, across the country and around the world, ABC News bring you the day's top stories and latest news, all verified. Presented by Joe O'Brien.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/NU2524H.jpg</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Seven News</title>
    <desc>Seven News live coverage of local, national and international news, plus sport, finance and weather updates. Go to 7NEWS.com.au today for more live updates.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>American Pickers</title>
    <desc>The Wolfe brothers tour a massive West Virginia homestead complete with an antique auto showroom. And in Texas, an ex-drag racer with a mountain of petroliana is in the mood to sell.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Nepali News</title>
    <desc>News via satellite from Nepal Television Kathmandu Nepal, in Nepali, no subtitles.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Oliver's Twist</title>
    <desc>After preparing a hearty breakfast of yoghurt, a chilli scrambled egg wrap and Bloody Mary, Jamie and his friends gather around the TV to cheer on England at the 2002 World Cup.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Nanny</title>
    <desc>Maxwell is offered to turn one of his failed plays into a movie, and tells Fran they might be moving to California. However Fran is afraid the news is going to devastate her mother.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Neighbours</title>
    <desc>Byron and Sadie's relationship hits rocky shores. Terese is forced into blindsiding Paul by making a strong decision. Wendy begins a secret search for answers.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Claire Hooper's House Of Games</title>
    <desc>Spending time in Claire Hooper's House of Games this week, we've got TV darling Myf Warhurst, cricketer Damien Fleming, and comedians Sammy J and Zoe Coombs Marr tackling some trivia to win the trophy, and maybe a dog bowl.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:59AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>House Hunters</title>
    <desc>A Massachusetts couple with a toddler searches for a larger house to grow their family. She's looking for a Victorian in the suburbs while he wants to stay closer to the city and find a more common Colonial.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Dr Ho's Motionciser</title>
    <desc>Dr Ho's MotionCiser - Passive Exercise Machine Combining Soothing Heat, Continuous Movement &amp; Relaxing Vibrating Massage To Help Relieve Muscle Tension &amp; Naturally Stimulate Healthy Circulation. 10 Speed &amp; 5 Heat Settings + Wireless Control.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Middle</title>
    <desc>The Hecks' plans to eat at an all-you-can-eat buffet are delayed when the new reverend calls them in after church for some impromptu counseling.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Waterworld Africa</title>
    <desc>Life in this swamp is prolific and water dictates the rhythm of new life. It is home to a wide variety of African wildlife.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:40AM</start>
    <finish>10:29AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Get On</title>
    <desc>Get On previews the feature meeting and provides all the punting information from Racing.com's leading form analysts. From the favourites to the outsiders and some you need to forget, Get On has all the good form talk.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:45AM</start>
    <finish>10:45AM</finish>
    <date>05 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
