<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Racenight Live: Happy Valley</title>
    <desc>Hong Kong thoroughbred racing from Happy Valley Hong Kong.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:30AM</start>
    <finish>04:15PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Gemporia Live</title>
    <desc>Watch live as the prices drop during our jewellery auctions offering beautiful gemstone jewellery set in precious gold and silver at incredible prices!\u00a0www.gemporia.com.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>rage Vault: 70s New York</title>
    <desc>rage dives into the Vault to play the best clips from the Big Apple during the 1970s, from Blondie, Talking Heads, Lou Reed, Patti Smith and more.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/LR2510H.jpg</image>
    <start>02:21PM</start>
    <finish>03:22PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Handmaid's Tale</title>
    <desc>Following a coup, America is a country still at war with itself and ruled by a repressive regime. Past pollution means only 1 per cent of women can bear children, and female criminals found to be potential mothers are put into an institution run by 'Aunt Lydia' to be indoctrinated. One such is Kate, who then seduces Fred, a higher-up in the security forces, to attempt to procreate. Fred's wife Serena, is jealous and vicious, and the State's grip seems to be tightening. But Kate still has her own mind, and is finding that some other people are prepared to resist.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:25PM</start>
    <finish>04:25PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Police Custody Usa</title>
    <desc>A quiet neighbourhood in Kansas City, Kansas is shaken by a double homicide in a local deli, but what lies behind these seemingly senseless murders and will the killer be brought to justice?</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Getaway Driver</title>
    <desc>A stunt driver, a drift instructor, and an exotic car salesman get the chance to live their ultimate driving fantasy - wheelmen in their very own high-speed car chase; the fantasy quickly turns into a nightmare for one getaway driver.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:30PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>First Dates UK</title>
    <desc>Silver-fox teacher Will likes to reminisce about the olden days in the gay scene when things were more illicit and the bars were filled with handsome male \&quot;visions.\&quot;.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:35PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Veronica Mars</title>
    <desc>During the day, Veronica negotiates high school like any average teenage girl. At night, she helps her father's struggling, new private investigator business.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:40PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Jake And The Fatman</title>
    <desc>A psychiatrist convicted of patient abuse goes crazy with revenge, messing with Neely's mind and trying to drive her to suicide.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:55PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Professional Nibbler</title>
    <desc>The Professional Nibbler is an Australian made cutting tool. Cut corrugated iron, mild steel and stainless steel. No sparks, no distortion! Attaches to any electric or battery drill in seconds. professionalnibbler.com.au.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Wall: The Chateau Murder</title>
    <desc>Celine recruits Alex to secretly continue the investigation. They discover what Philippin was developing in his lab. As they put all the pieces of the puzzle in place, they learn who stole the sculpture from Joanie.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Touching Evil</title>
    <desc>A brilliant detective survives a near fatal gunshot to the head and now focuses, along with his partner, on solving shocking, high profile crimes.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>House Hunters</title>
    <desc>A Virginia couple looks to purchase a home in Virginia, and their struggle to compromise is harder than most. With a recent diagnosis of high-functioning autism, he's hyper-focused on his wish list, which leads to frustration for her.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>03:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Rizzoli &amp; Isles</title>
    <desc>After an undercover cop working a narcotics-smuggling sting is shot dead, the killers next turn their sites on Boston homicide headquarters, leaving Jane, Maura and Frankie Jr. trapped in a fight for survival on their home turf.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:01PM</start>
    <finish>03:57PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Anh's Brush With Fame</title>
    <desc>Michelle Payne is a big name in Australian horse racing. She overcame family tragedy and life-threatening injuries to achieve her dream of becoming the first woman to win the Melbourne Cup. How will Anh portray her?</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>03:33PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Cultural Connections Immersion Festival</title>
    <desc>Concert series with live performances from Indigenous artists at the 1770 Cultural Connections Immersion Festival in central Queensland.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Late Show With Stephen Colbert</title>
    <desc>Join The Late Show host Stephen Colbert as he catches up with guest, former New Zealand Prime Minister, Jacinda Ardern, to engage in candid conversations. Plus, a performance by King Princess.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:05PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Find My Country House Australia</title>
    <desc>Catriona Rowntree helps couples find their perfect country house whether in the mountains, on a farm or even near the beach.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>03:40PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Corsage</title>
    <desc>Faced with a future of strict ceremonies and royal duties, Empress Elisabeth of Austria rebels against her public image and comes up with a plan to protect her legacy.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Indonesian News</title>
    <desc>News via satellite from TVRI Jakarta Indonesia, in Indonesian, no subtitles.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>04:05PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Good Game Spawn Point</title>
    <desc>This week on GGSP, it's a special episode dedicated to The Legend Of Zelda! We'll be taking a deep dive into the history of the series, and taking on a special Tears Of The Kingdom build challenge!</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/CH2263H.jpg</image>
    <start>03:16PM</start>
    <finish>03:41PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Rocket Power</title>
    <desc>Sam Dullard moves to Ocean Shores he becomes friends with the Rocket gang // Reggie is left in charge of the Stimpletons pool, but will Otto, Twister, Sam, and Raymundo ruin it for her?</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:20PM</start>
    <finish>03:50PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
