<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Touching Evil</title>
    <desc>A brilliant detective survives a near fatal gunshot to the head and now focuses, along with his partner, on solving shocking, high profile crimes.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Corsage</title>
    <desc>Faced with a future of strict ceremonies and royal duties, Empress Elisabeth of Austria rebels against her public image and comes up with a plan to protect her legacy.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:10PM</start>
    <finish>05:20PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Rage</title>
    <desc>Keep the party vibe going as the sun comes up with continuous music videos, from new releases to classics and the songs we've long forgotten.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/LR2501H022S00.jpg</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:06PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>One Day In The Life Of Piugattuk</title>
    <desc>When the white man known as Boss arrives at Piugattuk's hunting camp, what appears as a chance meeting soon opens up the prospect of momentous change.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Dw English News</title>
    <desc>News and analysis of the top international and European news and current affairs from Berlin, in English.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Long Lost Family</title>
    <desc>Carole who 50 years ago met her father, brother and sister for the first and last time has been searching for them since. Samantha grew up in a white family and has not seen her Jamaican father since she was five. (Final).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:20PM</start>
    <finish>05:06PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Custom Carolina</title>
    <desc>A client brings Tommy his '73 Chevy Vega for a nostalgic restoration. The team has to roll up their sleeves and uncover all the issues on this half-baked restomod.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Superfeast Health Supplements</title>
    <desc>Nature's Powerhouse for You. Unlock the ancient wisdom of herbs and mushrooms. SuperFeast delivers pure, potent blends for daily wellness. Boost immunity, fight stress, and feel your best.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Below Deck Mediterranean</title>
    <desc>The boat faces a catastrophic storm that exposes a major leak, putting the deck crew on high alert. Tensions rise as the stews voice their frustrations over a deckhand. As the storm intensifies, the i.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Supernatural</title>
    <desc>The angels go back in time to kill Sam before he was born.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:40PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Body Of Proof</title>
    <desc>Megan returns to work months after Peter\u2019s death, and she is surprised by a man from her past\u2014Tommy Sullivan, the new detective assigned to her case. Megan, along with Tommy and his rookie partner, Adam Schaeffer, must stop a serial killer whose victims are young war veterans. As she learns more about the crime, the stakes rise when she gets a call from the killer -- who is holding her teenage daughter, Lacey, hostage.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:45PM</start>
    <finish>05:45PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Midsomer Murders</title>
    <desc>A player is bludgeoned to death on the fairway at an exclusive local golf club. Barnaby and Jones uncover a world of intense snobbery, illicit gambling and a history of unreported assaults.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:55PM</start>
    <finish>06:52PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>DW News</title>
    <desc>The latest international news and the day's top stories from a European perspective. Our broadcast partner DW brings you live coverage from Berlin with updated reports and expert analysis on the big global issues and events.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW4264A.jpg</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:14PM</finish>
    <date>04 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
