<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Live: NRL Sunday Footy</title>
    <desc>Wide World of Sports presents Wests Tigers v Panthers, live from CommBank Stadium. Join our expert commentary team for all the action, analysis and post match interviews. Kick off at 4:05PM AEST.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Attack On The Iron Coast</title>
    <desc>Lloyd Bridges plays a WWII commando who leads a group of soldiers on a suicide mission to destroy a Nazi naval stronghold on the French coast. (Andrew Keir, Sue Lloyd).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Emperor's Club</title>
    <desc>William Hundert (Kevin Kline) is a passionate and principled Classics professor who finds his tightly-controlled world shaken and inexorably altered when a new student, Sedgewick Bell (Emile Hirsch), walks into his classroom. What begins as a fierce battle of wills gives way to a close student-teacher relationship, but results in a life lesson for Hundert that will still haunt him a quarter of a century later.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:25AM</start>
    <finish>09:25AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Escape To The Country</title>
    <desc>Jules Hudson is in South Wales with a couple who have a 350,000-pound budget to buy a 'forever' home in the country.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Bluey's Big Play</title>
    <desc>Bluey and Bingo pull out all the stops to try to get Dad off his phone in their first live stage show, brought to life by brilliant puppets and featuring brand new original music.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/CH2413H001S00.jpg</image>
    <start>08:12AM</start>
    <finish>08:57AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Stompem Ground 2022 - Pigram Brothers</title>
    <desc>The iconic Broome band, Pigram Brothers a selection on their finest tracks for the epic Stompem Ground event in 2022.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:20AM</start>
    <finish>09:20AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Pbs Washington Week With The Atlantic</title>
    <desc>PBS Washington Week with The Atlantic is the longest-running primetime news and public affairs program on television. The show features a group of journalists participating in a weekly roundtable discussion of major news events.  Moderated by Jeffrey Goldberg, Editor-in-Chief of The Atlantic.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:25AM</start>
    <finish>08:50AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Maestro Air Purifier</title>
    <desc>This air purifier utilises intelligent filtration technology to detect and eliminate airborne particles and contaminants, ensuring a constant supply of clean and fresh air. Its portable design allows you to place it anywhere in your home. W.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Punjabi News</title>
    <desc>News via satellite from PTC Chandigarh India, in Punjabi, no subtitles.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Flat Out Food</title>
    <desc>Eggplants thrive in areas with long growing seasons and plenty of sunlight, and Jenn sees firsthand how Floating Gardens uses hydroponics for their own eggplant crop.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Inside D-day Filmmakers On The Frontline</title>
    <desc>Experience the Battle of Normandy: Allied forces versus the Third Reich after D-Day. Photographers and cameramen captured 85 days of brutal conflict alongside soldiers. From Carentan and Cherbourg battles in June, Saint-Lo and Coutances' destruction in July, to Paris' jubilant liberation in August. Witness the pivotal three months that shaped history.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Million Dollar Listing: La</title>
    <desc>Josh Flagg whisks boyfriend Bobby off to Paris to propose. Josh Altman takes on a listing with an unpredictable homeowner.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Tanked</title>
    <desc>Former Guns N' Roses guitarist DJ Ashba shows up at ATM and asks Brett and Wayde to build him a creepy, skull-themed aquarium.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Sydney Weekender</title>
    <desc>All aboard for an adventure with Abbey as she takes a ride on Puffing Billy, Lizzy joins a truffle-hunting adventure in the Southern Tablelands, and Matt tucks into a royal feast at The Nags Head.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Counting Cars</title>
    <desc>Emotions run deep when Danny receives an astronomical offer for one of his prized cars. Kevin helps spot an epic flip that brings in a ton of cash.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>House Hunters</title>
    <desc>An airline pilot and his wife look to upsize into a home where they can host family and future grandchildren in Greer, South Carolina. She wants a classic-looking home no matter the cost, but he's worried she'll break the bank.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>ABC News Regional</title>
    <desc>Take a closer look at what's making headlines in regional and rural Australia. ABC News reporters uncover the news and unique stories about what's really going on outside the big cities. Presented by Amy Culpitt.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/NC2518D.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>War With Grandpa</title>
    <desc>Upset that he has to share the room he loves with his grandfather, Peter decides to declare war in an attempt to get it back. (Robert De Niro, Uma Thurman, Rob Riggle).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>George Clarke's Old House New Home</title>
    <desc>In Stroud, George meets Phil and Leighla, who are transforming a Georgian farmhouse with an industrial-style extension. In Wootton Bassett, George helps a couple flip the lay-out of their Victorian terrace home.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:17AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Antiques Roadshow</title>
    <desc>Today's roadshow comes from glorious Sefton Park in Liverpool.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW3938A019S00.jpg</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:29AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Racenight Live: Sha Tin</title>
    <desc>Hong Kong thoroughbred twilight racing from Sha Tin Hong Kong.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Dr Harry's Animal Encounters</title>
    <desc>Doctor Harry has travelled far and wide for wild adventure, exotic animals, crazy chooks and domestic favourites. Elephants, flamingos, puppies, parrots, pet pigs, the perfect pooch and much more.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>08:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
