<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Rage Guest Programmer</title>
    <desc>Australia's longest running music TV show, rage is home to the biggest vault of music videos from a diverse range of artists, genres and eras. Guest programmers curate an all-night playlist of their all-time favourite clips.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/LR2505H.jpg</image>
    <start>02:51PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Roland Garros 2025 - French Open Tennis Late</title>
    <desc>Wide World of Sports presents Roland Garros 2025 brought to you live from Paris. Join our all-star team including Todd Woodbridge and Jelena Dokic for all the action live and free. Live play continues.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:00PM</start>
    <finish>06:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The 355</title>
    <desc>When a top-secret weapon falls into mercenary hands, wild card CIA agent Mason \&quot;Mace\&quot; Brown will need to join forces with rival German agent Marie, former MI6 ally and cutting-edge computer specialist Khadijah and skilled Colombian psychologist Graciela on a lethal, breakneck mission to retrieve it.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:25PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Attica</title>
    <desc>Drawing on the experiences and recollections of those who were there, Stanley Nelson's documentary tells the story of the famous prison rebellion on its 50th anniversary. In the fall of 1971, tensions between inmates and guards at the Attica Correctional Facility are at an all-time high. On the morning of September 9, it all comes to a head when inmates erupt into one of the largest U.S. prison riots ever witnessed.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:40PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Honeymoon</title>
    <desc>A romantic comedy about an American GI with a three day pass who misses his fiancee in Mexico for their wedding.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:35PM</start>
    <finish>04:55PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Rage Guest Programmer: Bliss N Eso</title>
    <desc>Join Aussie hip hop legends Bliss N Eso as they celebrate the release of their new record 'The Moon (The Light Side)' by guest hosting rage.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/LR2504H.jpg</image>
    <start>03:54PM</start>
    <finish>05:24PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Sing, Freetown</title>
    <desc>Two friends from one of the world's poorest countries, Sierra Leone, go on a journey to stage the most ambitious play in the nation's history. However, things do not all go to plan.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:55PM</start>
    <finish>05:35PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Building Alaska</title>
    <desc>Three new teams begin their projects and Matt and Amy quickly realize building in snow is more complicated than they planned. Mike and Dan mill lumber needed for their build, and professionals struggle to dig Jackie's foundation.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Originals</title>
    <desc>When The Hollow sends a terrifying message to Vincent, he must team with Hayley and Freya to embark on a desperate mission to stop the Hollow once and for all - even if it requires a heartbreaking sacrifice.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Repco Supercars Highlights</title>
    <desc>Catch all the highlights as the Supercars head to Western Australia for the 46th Perth Round.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>France 24 English News</title>
    <desc>International news and current affairs from Paris, offering a French perspective on world events via satellite in English.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>08:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>48 Hours</title>
    <desc>Four college students are found stabbed to death in their home. Police say the suspect had studied the criminal mind. 48 Hours correspondent Peter Van Sant reports.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:05PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Alaska: The Last Frontier</title>
    <desc>Eivin considers expanding the Kilchers' reach by becoming a bush pilot. Tela takes Alysse dipnetting and Jane's cousin Kate comes to visit from Texas.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Ainsley's Taste Of Malta</title>
    <desc>Heading to North Malta, Ainsley's adventure takes him to the Xemxija Heritage Trail, where he does some foraging. He visits an olive grove to learn how they revived the stock of indigenous olive trees.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:25PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Home Shopping</title>
    <desc>Synopsis.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Storage Wars</title>
    <desc>It's a regular father and son shootout in Victorville, as Ivy and Pops try to prove who among them is the most profitable. Brandi's secret weapon lands her more than she bargained for.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Great Australian Doorstep</title>
    <desc>Peter 'Spida' and Sheree Everitt explore amazing holiday destinations. All self drive holidays that anyone can do. Easy driving with a tonne of adventure.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Hey Arnold!</title>
    <desc>Grandpa enters his Packard in the classic car competition. It is admired by all until it is stolen. / Phoebe wins a perfect attendance award, but on stage, a microphone amplifies her accidental gas.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Shark Tank</title>
    <desc>As the show continues in Season 3, the critically acclaimed Shark Tank gives budding entrepreneurs the chance to make their dreams come true and possibly make a deal that will make them millionaires.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Landline</title>
    <desc>A tasty sampler of stories from the land - covering food, agriculture, crops, climate, business and innovation - as we meet the fascinating people who make our rural and regional communities unique. Presented by Pip Courtney.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/RA2501Q.jpg</image>
    <start>04:31PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Suspect</title>
    <desc>Danny goes to confront his old friend and former partner, Ryan. Initially, he doesn't mention the CCTV footage that proves Ryan was with Christina shortly before she died, but as Ryan becomes pricklier and more evasive in response to his questioning, it becomes too much for Danny and he reveals what he knows, prompting an extremely violent reaction.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:05PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Garden Gurus</title>
    <desc>This week we take you to the stunning Christmas Island to explore its unique hydroponic systems. Plus, Neville reveals the ultimate fertiliser packed with all the essential trace elements and nutrients to ensure your plants thrive.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:35PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Not Going Out</title>
    <desc>Lucy has an important speech to make at a conference and nobody to help her write it. Lee sees an opportunity to impress her and offers his services but at the expense of Tim, who also thinks he's the best man for the job.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:43PM</start>
    <finish>05:11PM</finish>
    <date>07 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
