<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Phil Spencer: Secret Agent</title>
    <desc>Phil goes to in south east London, meeting the owners of properties which seem stuck on the market, including a three bedroom semi-detached property and a larger than average property in a sought after cul de sac. (Final).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:18AM</start>
    <finish>10:06AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Adventures Of Paddington</title>
    <desc>Paddington, Jonathan and Judy are worried they've used up all of Lucky the dog's luck - how will they tell Sofia?</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW2512A018S00.jpg</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>09:41AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Hey Duggee</title>
    <desc>The sun is setting, and the squirrels are sitting on the sofa. Suddenly all the lights go out. Oh dear, there's been a power cut. Thanks goodness Duggee has got his torch, and he has torches for everyone.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW1224A022S00_460.jpg</image>
    <start>09:42AM</start>
    <finish>09:50AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Isadora Moon</title>
    <desc>Oscar the Ghost wants to play football with JJ but discovers it's harder than it looks when objects go straight through you.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:50AM</start>
    <finish>10:01AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Supertato</title>
    <desc>Supertato is out chasing a milkshake robot and leaves Broccoli in charge of Tato Tower. Evil Pea tries to take over the tower, but Broccoli puts on a great defence.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW3809A042S00.jpg</image>
    <start>10:01AM</start>
    <finish>10:08AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Hard Quiz</title>
    <desc>An unforgettable line-up on this week's Hard Quiz as Tom Gleeson grills expert contestants on the Siege of Tobruk, Shaun the Sheep, the Theory of Evolution, and - wait for it - the Ferguson TE-20 tractor...</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:06AM</start>
    <finish>10:35AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Rocket Club</title>
    <desc>When a solar flare disables all spacecraft throughout the solar system, Rocket Club and Calvin find themselves as improbable allies that must team up to harness the solar winds and restore power to their ships.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW4169A015S00.jpg</image>
    <start>10:08AM</start>
    <finish>10:20AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Bluey</title>
    <desc>When Muffin is told that she is special by her Dad, she interprets it as an excuse to do anything she wants, which means playing Bluey and Bingo's game of Library her way.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/CH1903Q038S00.jpg</image>
    <start>10:21AM</start>
    <finish>10:31AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Kids Baking Championship</title>
    <desc>Valerie Bertinelli and Duff Goldman ask the eight kid bakers to work in teams of two to build and decorate tasty, beautiful puff designs made of two different colours and flavours of cream puffs.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:31AM</start>
    <finish>11:12AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>QI</title>
    <desc>Sandi Toksvig tells you about tails (and tales) with Rob Beckett, Daliso Chaponda, Sarah Millican and Alan Davies.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW3533A.jpg</image>
    <start>10:35AM</start>
    <finish>11:06AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Celia Pacquola: I'm As Surprised As You Are</title>
    <desc>This is Celia's first new stand up hour since 2018 and a lot has happened in her life, including making a quiche for the first time and also a baby. Come and have a catch up with Celia. She's got a lot to tell you.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:07AM</start>
    <finish>12:13PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Chopped Junior</title>
    <desc>The junior chefs roll up their sleeves to deal with a large blue squash and make desserts with lollipops and green fruit. Food journalist Michelle Park, chef Chris Santos and singer Ruben Studdard take over the judging panel.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:13AM</start>
    <finish>11:55AM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Piano</title>
    <desc>Everyday pianists descend on the buzzing Sydney Metro station, and their talent, passion and purpose will stop the station in its tracks.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:55AM</start>
    <finish>12:53PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The IT Crowd</title>
    <desc>While on a date with Reynholm Industries' new receptionist, Roy somehow ends up with chocolate on his forehead. Unfortunately for Roy, his date thinks it looks like something else...</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZY8447A003S00_460.jpg</image>
    <start>12:13PM</start>
    <finish>12:37PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The IT Crowd</title>
    <desc>What is behind the mysterious red door in the IT department?</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZY8447A004S00_460.jpg</image>
    <start>12:38PM</start>
    <finish>01:02PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Fresh Off The Boat</title>
    <desc>The Huangs start to regret moving house as Eddie tries to find a way to stay close to the friends he has left behind, and Michael Bolton starts turning Cattleman's Ranch into a merchandising opportunity. (Final).</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:53PM</start>
    <finish>01:13PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The IT Crowd</title>
    <desc>Jen is mortified when she discovers that her latest date Bill Crouse, is in the habit of bragging to his mates about his sexual exploits.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZY8447A005S00_460.jpg</image>
    <start>01:02PM</start>
    <finish>01:28PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Fresh Off The Boat</title>
    <desc>Still homeless, the Huangs move in with Honey and Marvin, however Jessica's dreams come true when she gets a chance to compete on \&quot;Wheel of Fortune\&quot; with Honey. Eddie starts high school and is still on the outs with his pals.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:14PM</start>
    <finish>01:35PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Romano seizes control of the ER and offends nearly everyone. Luka begs Kerry to help him bring a dying Croatian child to Chicago for treatment. A cancer patient must choose between her own life and that of her unborn baby.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:29PM</start>
    <finish>02:14PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Dragon Ball Super</title>
    <desc>Vegeta prepares to face Frost, who has no intention of discontinuing his cheating. But with a single hit, Vegeta knocks Frost completely out of the ring for the win.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW1734A035S00.jpg</image>
    <start>01:36PM</start>
    <finish>01:59PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Pokemon: Diamond And Pearl</title>
    <desc>Our heroes discover a Buneary in the forest on the way to Jubilife City, and Dawn decides she just has to catch it!</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW4295A009S00.jpg</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:21PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Soundtrack To Our Teenage Zombie Apocalypse</title>
    <desc>Nick and Ella each decide to become solo artists but quickly realise that it's not so easy becoming a ground-breaking music act without the other person's skills.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:21PM</start>
    <finish>02:44PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!: Do Try This At Home</title>
    <desc>Dr Chris and Dr Xand are back in their kitchen lab! In this episode, the doctors put eye boogers under the microscope and show you how to make edible eye gunk!</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:45PM</start>
    <finish>02:59PM</finish>
    <date>31 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
