<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Operation Ouch!</title>
    <desc>The doctors reveal the incredible bit of body kit that keeps you balanced - your vestibular system, and find out what makes Team GB hockey star Shona McCallin superfast in today's 'Brilliant Bodies'.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:07AM</start>
    <finish>11:36AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Would I Lie To You?</title>
    <desc>Guests Joel Dommett, Sindhu Vee, Alex Horne and AJ Odudu join Rob Brydon, Lee Mack and David Mitchell. But are they telling the truth, or are they making it all up?</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:08AM</start>
    <finish>11:38AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>BTN Newsbreak</title>
    <desc>Find out what's going on in the world with a news bulletin designed for children, featuring stories that are relevant and easy to understand.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/NE2501S.jpg</image>
    <start>11:36AM</start>
    <finish>11:41AM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Unforgotten</title>
    <desc>Cassie and Sunny visit a priest who remembers Jimmy fondly, but unfortunately Father Robert Greaves is unable to identify 'Jo-Jo', the mysterious person who gave Jimmy the diary.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:38AM</start>
    <finish>12:23PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Abbott Elementary</title>
    <desc>Janine insists her second-grade class joins in on an eighth-grade egg drop activity.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:42AM</start>
    <finish>12:02PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Abbott Elementary</title>
    <desc>Janine is out sick for the day; Ava must step in herself to help out.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:02PM</start>
    <finish>12:24PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Unforgotten</title>
    <desc>Cassie and Sunny question Sir Phillip to find out exactly what his involvement was with a prominent East End crime family. Eric and Claire's anniversary party gets underway.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:24PM</start>
    <finish>01:12PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Doctor Who</title>
    <desc>As the Doctor makes his final journey to the shores of Lake Silencio in Utah, he knows only one thing can keep the universe safe - his own death. But has he reckoned without the love of a good woman? (Final).</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZX6017A006S00_460.jpg</image>
    <start>12:25PM</start>
    <finish>01:10PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Doctor Who: The Doctor, The Widow And The Wardrobe</title>
    <desc>On Christmas Eve 1941, the Doctor poses as a caretaker to give recently widowed Madge and her two children a truly magical Christmas, but things get out of hand when her son Cyril enters a snowy forest world full of dangers.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZX6457A001S00_460.jpg</image>
    <start>01:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:09PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Friday Night Dinner</title>
    <desc>Nobody is pleased when Grandma gets engaged to her nasty 85 year-old boyfriend Mr Morris. Elsewhere Jim goes collecting for charity while dressed in a dog costume complete with testicles.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:12PM</start>
    <finish>01:36PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Romano suffers a horrific life-threatening injury while the CDC probes a mysterious and deadly illness in the locked-down hospital. Meanwhile, newly-widowed Elizabeth returns to London as she ponders what to do with her life.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:37PM</start>
    <finish>02:22PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Merlin</title>
    <desc>A mysterious warrior arrives in Camelot, sending Arthur on a quest that could change his life forever.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW0066A008S00.jpg</image>
    <start>02:10PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Breeders</title>
    <desc>A chat with Darren and a chance encounter convince Ally she needs more friends, so she decides to reunite her antenatal class. Ally tells Luke and Ava this was a friendship group, but 17 years is a long time.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW4325A006S00.jpg</image>
    <start>02:22PM</start>
    <finish>02:45PM</finish>
    <date>14 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
