<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Partisan</title>
    <desc>Alexander, a boy who has been raised in a sequestered commune, finds that his increasing unwillingness to fall in line puts him on a collision course with Gregori, the society's charismatic and domineering leader.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:24PM</start>
    <finish>02:58PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>The Yorkshire Steam Railway: All Aboard</title>
    <desc>The summer heatwave brings record numbers of punters to the railway as it hits peak season.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:35PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>During the graveyard shift, Pratt treats a man who has lost the power of speech and a boy who has swallowed a quarter. Elsewhere, Abby has a frosty meeting with her ex-husband, while Elizabeth starts warming up to Dr. Dorset.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:50PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Nhk Japanese News</title>
    <desc>NHK's core news program wrapping up the days local and international events. News delivered via satellite from NHK Japan, in Japanese, no subtitles. Watch on SBS WorldWatch at 11pm everyday, also available on SBS OnDemand.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:35PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Into The Gobi Desert With Nick Knowles</title>
    <desc>Nick leaves the desert sands of the Gobi and the dramatic peaks of the West to travel to Mongolia's capital, Ulaanbaatar, the coldest capital in the world.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:05PM</start>
    <finish>02:55PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Merlin</title>
    <desc>The kingdom is on the brink of collapse, with Morgana poised to strike. As Lancelot races back to Camelot with the dying Merlin, Arthur must continue on his mission to vanquish the Dorocha without them.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:11PM</start>
    <finish>02:56PM</finish>
    <date>08 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
