<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Would I Lie To You?</title>
    <desc>Rob Brydon hosts with team captains David Mitchell and Lee Mack who lead celebrity guests Jack Whitehall, Rebecca Front, Nick Hewer and Miranda Hart.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:06AM</start>
    <finish>11:37AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>BTN Newsbreak</title>
    <desc>Find out what's going on in the world with a news bulletin designed for children, featuring stories that are relevant and easy to understand.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/NE2501S.jpg</image>
    <start>11:25AM</start>
    <finish>11:31AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Mythbusters: There's Your Problem!</title>
    <desc>Bunkered in the bunker and (hopefully) out of harm's way, the MythBusters spend this episode delving into the science of explosions.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:31AM</start>
    <finish>11:56AM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Inherent Vice</title>
    <desc>Marijuana-fuelled private investigator Larry \&quot;Doc\&quot; Sportello navigates a psychedelic world of surfers, stoners, hustlers, and cops in search of his ex-lover and her billionaire boyfriend who have mysteriously gone missing.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:38AM</start>
    <finish>02:02PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Robot Wars</title>
    <desc>Eight fighting robot teams battle it out to get past the initial group stage to progress into the mini-league of the head-to-heads. The two teams with the most points after the head-to-heads battle it out in the heat final.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:57AM</start>
    <finish>12:57PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Merlin</title>
    <desc>Merlin stumbles across a secret chamber and accidentally releases a Goblin. The mischievous creature possesses Gaius, leading the once-wise physician to develop a taste for gold, ale and magical jokes.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW0067A003S00.jpg</image>
    <start>12:57PM</start>
    <finish>01:41PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Officially Amazing</title>
    <desc>Extreme pogo jumping, synchronised dancing and mesmerising gymnastics feature in today's record attempts.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW4133A009S00.jpg</image>
    <start>01:41PM</start>
    <finish>02:10PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>In this unique episode, events leading up to Christmas are shown in reverse chronological order. Luka's speeding causes a crash on an icy road, while ER staff treat angry elves and a female hockey player with a head injury.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:02PM</start>
    <finish>02:46PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Deadly 60</title>
    <desc>Still in Canada Steve finds the biggest sea lion in the world; is on the trail of the smelliest animal on the planet, the skunk; then tries his hand at becoming a racoon; and tracks the powerful black bear.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:11PM</start>
    <finish>02:39PM</finish>
    <date>23 May 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
