<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Dance Life</title>
    <desc>Guest choreographers arrive at Brent Street to start preparing for grad and a run of relentless rehearsals that test the skill and strength of all.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:13PM</start>
    <finish>01:05PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Whose Line Is It Anyway?</title>
    <desc>Aisha Tyler hosts another episode of the legendary improv show with regulars Ryan Stiles and Colin Mochrie along with Jeff Davis and Brad Sherwood and star guest, beach volleyball Olympic champion, Misty May Treanor. (Final).</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW4255A016S00.jpg</image>
    <start>12:22PM</start>
    <finish>12:45PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Spooks</title>
    <desc>After 20 bombs go astray between Ireland and the UK and a family planning doctor is killed by a car bomb, Tom Quinn and his team realise they're after an extremely dangerous pro-life terrorist.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW4566A001S00.jpg</image>
    <start>12:45PM</start>
    <finish>01:37PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Secret Life Of The Kangaroo</title>
    <desc>This three part series features one species of kangaroo, the Eastern Greys, which populate the woodland, pasture and forests of the Eastern side of Australia.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:06PM</start>
    <finish>01:54PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>A patient accuses Pratt of inappropriate behaviour during a breast exam, while Neela studies strokes in a lab populated by brainy but bizarre graduate students, and Sam is confused by her ex's attempts to win her back.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:38PM</start>
    <finish>02:22PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Merlin</title>
    <desc>Morgana is now the head of a vast Southron army and a deadly net is closing around Camelot. After the sorceress strikes, everyone is forced to run for their lives including Arthur.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:54PM</start>
    <finish>02:38PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Not Going Out</title>
    <desc>During a skiing trip in Eastern Europe, Lee, Lucy and Daisy get stuck in a cable car with a heavily pregnant woman who speaks little English but definitely doesn't want to hang around.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:22PM</start>
    <finish>02:52PM</finish>
    <date>23 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
