<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Penn And Teller: Fool Us</title>
    <desc>Featured magicians include Hector Mancha, Adam Parisi, Ben Zabin and Robert Strong.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:39AM</start>
    <finish>12:20PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Hard Quiz Kids</title>
    <desc>Tom Gleeson is hanging on to the Big Brass Mug until one young expert can prove they deserve it with their knowledge of soccer legend Sam Kerr, babushka dolls, 80s Aussie rock bands, and The Lego Batman Movie!</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:41AM</start>
    <finish>12:11PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Dance Life</title>
    <desc>Who will shine when a dance convention gives the students the chance to learn from industry idols and offers a unique opportunity to be seen by professional choreographers in adynamic group routine.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:11PM</start>
    <finish>12:59PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Whose Line Is It Anyway?</title>
    <desc>Aisha Tyler hosts another tiptop episode of the legendary improv show featuring regulars Wayne Brady, Ryan Stiles and Colin Mochrie along with guest performer Jonathan Mangum and special guest, beatboxer Kaila Mullady.</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/ZW4255A015S00.jpg</image>
    <start>12:20PM</start>
    <finish>12:43PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Mythbusters</title>
    <desc>It's the MythBusters Volunteer Special as the guys tackle a myth about zombie weapons and a super story about how best to wait in line at the super-store, both of which require an army of human guinea pigs!</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:44PM</start>
    <finish>01:33PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Secret Life Of The Kangaroo</title>
    <desc>This three part series features one species of kangaroo, the Eastern Greys, which populate the woodland, pasture and forests of the Eastern side of Australia.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:47PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>ER</title>
    <desc>Medical students Abby and Neela gain a new perspective on emergency care, experiencing emotional highs and lows while caring for struggling infants as they serve a three-week rotation in the Neonatal Intensive Care Unit.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:34PM</start>
    <finish>02:19PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Merlin</title>
    <desc>Morgana joins forces with enigmatic wizard Alator to uncover a secret that could change the course of destiny. With allies on both sides of the castle walls, can anyone stop her before Merlin's greatest secret is revealed?</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:48PM</start>
    <finish>02:32PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Not Going Out</title>
    <desc>Jealousy rears its ugly head when Tim joins a band at work and Lucy falls for the lead guitarist - the enigmatic Stretch - who oozes too much charm for Lee's liking. Lee decides that if he can't beat 'em, he should join 'em.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:19PM</start>
    <finish>02:49PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>ABC Comedy AU</name>
    <title>Good Game Spawn Point</title>
    <desc>Harry, Gem, and Screen Goblin have a Pokemon play date but there's one problem: Gem has organised a hang out with old GGSP host Will instead! Could this mean the end of the gang?</desc>
    <image>https://www.abc.net.au/tv/common/images/publicity/CK2363H008S00.jpg</image>
    <start>02:32PM</start>
    <finish>02:52PM</finish>
    <date>16 June 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
