<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Hollywood News Feed</title>
    <desc>Arts, Debate, Newscast 2012 The entertainment industry shines equally with all its colors in Hollywood behind the scenes as it does on screen, with all the breaking scandals, gossip, relationships, and the making of award shows. Sarah Toce, Sarah Toce, David Freydt, Martin Saint Charles.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:30PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Hollywood On Set</title>
    <desc>Entertainment, Debate, People 2003 The host presents extensive footage and commentary from the making of major Hollywood productions, highlighting what makes a blockbuster and what elements determine its success, in addition to introspective interviews with actors and filmmakers. Angela Valley, Michelle Blenker, Michael Keaton, Oscar Isaac, Anya Taylor-Joy, Keri Russell, Jason Momoa, David Freydt, Paul Wynne, Paul Wynne, Anya Taylor Joy, Janett Hermosillo, Ann-Marie Lariccia, Martin Saint Charles, Reginald de Guillebon.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:30PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Emirates News</title>
    <desc>Finance, Newscast, Investigation Exciting and humane local news are given coverage, with a range of the latest breaking news and reports on business, entertainment, lifestyle, sports, weather, real estate, and more. Ramia Farrage, Graham Clews, Yunus Saif, Greg Fairlie.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Sisi</title>
    <desc>War, Drama, History 2021 When Duchess Elizabeth of Bavaria, Sisi, marries Emperor Franz of Austria, on the eve of a dreadful war, her life and the nation she becomes Empress of are forever reshaped. Dominique Devenport, Jannik Sch?mann, Marcus Grusser, Desiree Nosbusch, Jokubas Gutautas, Sven Bohse, Andreas Gutzeit, Robert Krause, D?sir?e Nosbusch, Jannik Schumann, Julia Stemberger.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Desperate Mrs. Seonju</title>
    <desc>Romance, Western, Drama, Family 2024 Pi Seon Ju, a dedicated interior designer, is married to Jeon Nam Jin, an ambitious architect, who insists on ending the marriage after he infatuated with Jin Sang A. Following their divorce, Pi Seon Ju resolves to rebuild her life from scratch. Shim Yi-yeong, Song Chang-ui, Choi Jeong-yun, Kang Woo Yeon, Derek Chouinard, Kim Heung Dong, Seo Jung.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>29 September 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
