<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Grand Designs</title>
    <desc>Culture, People, Design Presenter Kevin McCloud follows and meets some intelligent and creative individuals who can build their dream homes. They have large spaces and contemporary furnishings. Robert Gaukroger, Kevin McCloud, Jeremy Till, Tom Raffield, Danielle Raffield, Ned Williams, Kevin McCloud.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Emirates News</title>
    <desc>Finance, Newscast, Investigation Exciting and humane local news are given coverage, with a range of the latest breaking news and reports on business, entertainment, lifestyle, sports, weather, real estate, and more. Ramia Farrage, Graham Clews, Yunus Saif, Greg Fairlie.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>DXB Today</title>
    <desc>Cooking, Entertainment, Music, Arts, Fashion Presenters dive into the various facets of life in Dubai, reviewing reports from lifestyle and fashion trends to the latest news, where they also have exclusive interviews with celebrities.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Desperate Mrs. Seonju</title>
    <desc>Romance, Western, Drama, Family 2024 Pi Seon Ju, a dedicated interior designer, is married to Jeon Nam Jin, an ambitious architect, who insists on ending the marriage after he infatuated with Jin Sang A. Following their divorce, Pi Seon Ju resolves to rebuild her life from scratch. Shim Yi-yeong, Song Chang-ui, Choi Jeong-yun, Kang Woo Yeon, Derek Chouinard, Kim Heung Dong, Seo Jung.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
