<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>The War Below</title>
    <desc>War, Drama, History 2021 During WWI, Colonel Norton Griffiths devised a plan in which a group of miners were assigned to dig beneath the disputed area of no man's Land and lay bombs in an attempt to break the deadly stalemate at the Battle of Messines with the Germans. Tom Goodman-Hill, Sam Hazeldine, Kris Hitchen, Andrew Scarborough, Elliot James Langridge, J.P. Watts, J.P. Watts.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00AM</finish>
    <date>13 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Captain Phillips</title>
    <desc>Action, Biography, Crime, Thriller 2013 Somali pirates kidnap an American ship and hold Captain Richard Phillips and others as hostages. Phillips becomes a hero as he succeeded in rescuing himself and others. Barkhad Abdi, Tom Hanks, Barkhad Abdirahman, Catherine Keener , Michael Chernus, Paul Greengrass, Billy Ray, Catherine Keener.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:00AM</start>
    <finish>03:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Dubai Eye On Dubai One</title>
    <desc>Entertainment, Newscast, Magazine 2000 Brandy Scott, Richard Dean and Tom Urquhart present the latest headlines, followed by in-depth discussions on current affairs and interviews with the local and international figures most knowledgeable about them. Brandy Scott, Richard Dean, Tom Urquhart.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>03:00AM</start>
    <finish>07:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>The Tomorrow Man</title>
    <desc>People, Romance, Drama 2019 Ed spends his days bracing for an apocalypse that might never occur, and Ronnie fills her home with items she'll likely never put to use. In spite of their contrasting lifestyles, they're both ready to see if love can bloom between them. John Lithgow, Blythe Danner, Derek Cecil, Katie Aselton, Sophie Thatcher, Noble Jones, Noble Jones.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Hollywood News Feed</title>
    <desc>Arts, Debate, Newscast 2012 The entertainment industry shines equally with all its colors in Hollywood behind the scenes as it does on screen, with all the breaking scandals, gossip, relationships, and the making of award shows. Sarah Toce, Sarah Toce, David Freydt, Martin Saint Charles.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00AM</start>
    <finish>09:30AM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Hollywood On Set</title>
    <desc>Entertainment, Debate, People 2003 The host presents extensive footage and commentary from the making of major Hollywood productions, highlighting what makes a blockbuster and what elements determine its success, in addition to introspective interviews with actors and filmmakers. Angela Valley, Michelle Blenker, Michael Keaton, Oscar Isaac, Anya Taylor-Joy, Keri Russell, Jason Momoa, David Freydt, Paul Wynne, Paul Wynne, Anya Taylor Joy, Janett Hermosillo, Ann-Marie Lariccia, Martin Saint Charles, Reginald de Guillebon.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:30AM</start>
    <finish>10:00AM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Captain Phillips</title>
    <desc>Action, Biography, Crime, Thriller 2013 Somali pirates kidnap an American ship and hold Captain Richard Phillips and others as hostages. Phillips becomes a hero as he succeeded in rescuing himself and others. Barkhad Abdi, Tom Hanks, Barkhad Abdirahman, Catherine Keener , Michael Chernus, Paul Greengrass, Billy Ray, Catherine Keener.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>10:00AM</start>
    <finish>12:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>DXB Today</title>
    <desc>Cooking, Entertainment, Music, Arts, Fashion Presenters dive into the various facets of life in Dubai, reviewing reports from lifestyle and fashion trends to the latest news, where they also have exclusive interviews with celebrities.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>12:00PM</start>
    <finish>01:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Desperate Mrs. Seonju</title>
    <desc>Romance, Western, Drama, Family 2024 Pi Seon Ju, a dedicated interior designer, is married to Jeon Nam Jin, an ambitious architect, who insists on ending the marriage after he infatuated with Jin Sang A. Following their divorce, Pi Seon Ju resolves to rebuild her life from scratch. Shim Yi-yeong, Song Chang-ui, Choi Jeong-yun, Kang Woo Yeon, Derek Chouinard, Kim Heung Dong, Seo Jung.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>01:00PM</start>
    <finish>02:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Charming The Hearts Of Men</title>
    <desc>Romance, Drama, History 2021 Against the backdrop of discrimination against women in the early 1960s, Grace Jordan struggles to provide future generations of women with opportunities through her alliance with congress. Anna Friel, Kelsey Grammer, Starletta DuPois, Pauline Dyer, Aml Ameen, S.E. DeRose, S.E. DeRose.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>02:00PM</start>
    <finish>04:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Grand Designs</title>
    <desc>Culture, People, Design Presenter Kevin McCloud follows and meets some intelligent and creative individuals who can build their dream homes. They have large spaces and contemporary furnishings. Robert Gaukroger, Kevin McCloud, Jeremy Till, Tom Raffield, Danielle Raffield, Ned Williams, Kevin McCloud.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>04:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Emirates News</title>
    <desc>Finance, Newscast, Investigation Exciting and humane local news are given coverage, with a range of the latest breaking news and reports on business, entertainment, lifestyle, sports, weather, real estate, and more. Ramia Farrage, Graham Clews, Yunus Saif, Greg Fairlie.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:00PM</start>
    <finish>05:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>DXB Today</title>
    <desc>Cooking, Entertainment, Music, Arts, Fashion Presenters dive into the various facets of life in Dubai, reviewing reports from lifestyle and fashion trends to the latest news, where they also have exclusive interviews with celebrities.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>05:30PM</start>
    <finish>06:30PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Desperate Mrs. Seonju</title>
    <desc>Romance, Western, Drama, Family 2024 Pi Seon Ju, a dedicated interior designer, is married to Jeon Nam Jin, an ambitious architect, who insists on ending the marriage after he infatuated with Jin Sang A. Following their divorce, Pi Seon Ju resolves to rebuild her life from scratch. Shim Yi-yeong, Song Chang-ui, Choi Jeong-yun, Kang Woo Yeon, Derek Chouinard, Kim Heung Dong, Seo Jung.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>06:30PM</start>
    <finish>07:00PM</finish>
    <date>14 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
