<?xml version="1.0" ?>
<tv>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Boston Strangler</title>
    <desc>Thriller 2023 Reporter Loretta McLaughlin, determined to expose the Boston Strangler, teams up with Jean Cole to investigate the murders, facing both a sexist media landscape and corrupt police forces to uncover the killer's identity. Keira Knightley, Carrie Coon.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>07:00PM</start>
    <finish>09:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Cry Macho</title>
    <desc>Thriller 2021 An ex-rodeo star is requested to escort the son of his former boss to Mexico away from his troubled mother. On the road, both the man and the boy have to face their understanding of masculinity and redefine what it really means to be macho. Clint Eastwood, Dwight Yoakam, Daniel V. Graulau, Amber Lynn Ashley, Eduardo Minett, Ivan Hernandez, Fernanda Urrejola, Clint Eastwood, Nick Schenk, N. Richard Nash.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>09:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:00PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>Emirates News</title>
    <desc>Investigation Exciting and humane local news are given coverage, with a range of the latest breaking news and reports on business, entertainment, lifestyle, sports, weather, real estate, and more. Ramia Farrage, Graham Clews, Yunus Saif, Greg Fairlie.</desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:00PM</start>
    <finish>11:30PM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
  <channel>
    <name>Dubai One En AE</name>
    <id>DubaiOneEn.ae</id>
    <title>DXB Today</title>
    <desc>Fashion Presenters dive into the various facets of life in Dubai, reviewing reports from lifestyle and fashion trends to the latest news, where they also have exclusive interviews with celebrities.[(96057)] </desc>
    <image>https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/File:Image_not_available.png</image>
    <start>11:30PM</start>
    <finish>12:30AM</finish>
    <date>24 October 2025</date>
  </channel>
</tv>
